What's going on...?
E-Eri? What in the...
Wh-What happened?
Kouki-kun, I got you.
This is what's going on, Shizuku.
What do you mean...?
Hmm, you still don't get it?
I've always wanted Kouki-kun.
I did what I needed to do to get him.
If you're in love with Kouki, you should
have just confessed or something!
No, no, no. That won't do at all.
Kouki-kun is too kind,
he wouldn't make an exception.
Even surrounded by a trash heap of losers,
he's too nice,
he couldn't leave them alone.
In order to make him
truly mine and mine alone,
I needed to go out of
my way to take out the trash.
I'm so glad we landed in this world.
Taking out the trash
is really hard in Japan.
Obviously, I can't allow anyone
to go back to Japan.
Kouki-kun and I are going to live in
this world together, for ever and ever.
Eri.
The others don't seem right, is that...
Necromancy, of course!
They've been dead for a while now!
No way! Necromancy doesn't
let people talk and respond like that!
You can thank my job,
Necromancer, for that.
I modified regular necromancy so that some
memories and thought patterns remain,
allowing them to talk and stuff.
How...
My own special necromancy spell...
Let's call it "Spirit Binding."
I need to cast it right after death,
and I can only cast it on one
person at a time. What a bother.
Your deaths won't go to waste!
I'll put you all to good use!
Stop it, Eri! If you do that, I won't--
You won't ever forgive me?
I knew you'd say that,
since you're so kind.
I'll make sure to Spirit Bind
you properly so you'll be all mine!
You won't see anyone else.
You'll always just look at me.
You will only speak words that I want
to hear. My own Kouki-kun, just for me!
Oh, I'm losing my mind just imagining it!
Lies...
You're lying!
Eririn... Eri... You can't do this!
S-Stop...
--Stop!
--Stop it!
Reiichi!
Dammit! Nakamura! You!
Does it hurt? Are you sad?
Let me hear a pretty scream.
Try to resist, curse me in your pain!
You'll still be my little puppet!
A pathetic little toy!
Blessings to all deaths!
Ridicule to every sorry soul!
Spirit Binding!
One more puppet, done and done!
E-Eri, why...
Hey, Suzu. Thank you, for all you did
back in Japan and over here as well.
You were such a useful pawn when it
came to letting me be near Kouki-kun.
What?
It was so bothersome, how everyone
tried to go along with the idea that
Shizuku and Kaori were the only ones
who should be near Kouki-kun.
I had no powers back then,
so entrapping them and destroying
them would have taken too long.
So I really have to
thank you for being you, Suzu.
You were so obviously clueless, I could
do anything and let it come off as a joke.
N... No...
Being "Suzu Taniguchi's best friend"
was so useful. So, thank you.
Eri! How could you!
Are you angry?
Shizuku, your expression is great.
I've really truly despised you.
That's why you get to play a special role.
Role?
I wonder how Kaori
would react to being killed
by her best friend?
What?! You won't--
Did that hurt? Don't worry, I'm kind.
I'll end this torment right away.
Stop! Stop, please! Eri!
Goodbye, Shizuku. Pretending
to be your friend was truly revolting.
I'm sorry, Kaori...
What?!
Divine Shackles!
Shizuku-chan, hold on! I'll help you!
K-Kaori...
In this sacred realm, the mother
of all existence gives her blessing.
Gaze at the sky, those who desire.
See the light at the end of the darkness.
--You just can't stop getting
in my way, can you?
--That is the light of salvation.
Give prayer, show acceptance.
Everyone, what's going on?!
Please snap out of it! Eri, what is this?!
Shirasaki! Princess Liliana!
Are you all right?!
Hiyama-san?! Are you all right?
What a terrible injury!
No! Don't!
Kaori!
I did! I finally got her!
You prefer me over Nagumo,
don't you? Right, Kaori?
How dare you!
Divine Mother...
Smiling down from heaven...
Aetherflow.
I won't give up either,
Hajime-kun...
I won't let you!
You...
I will never forgive you!
Restrain him.
Stand back!
Heavenly Flash!
Tamai! Sonobe!
Tamai! Don't cut my hand off, okay?!
I wouldn't mess up like that!
Suzu! A barrier! Protect them!
What? Oh... I'm sorry.
She's in shock, it's only natural...
Dammit!
Stand your ground, Sakagami!
If we can't hold them back,
Tamai and the others won't either!
Get out of my way!
Kaori!
Heavenly Flash!
Eri! Hiyama!
N-No...
That's close enough, Kouki-kun.
Kouki, why are you swinging
that sword at me.
I never taught you to do that.
Meld-san, I...
Don't listen!
Meld-san... I'm sorry.
Help me, Kouki...
Wh-Wh-What is this? I can't...
Oh, it's finally working. That was
supposed to be a pretty strong poison.
If the prince wakes up
the princess with a kiss,
the princess putting
the prince to sleep with a kiss
sounds like a good plot too, right?
E-Eri, you...
Don't worry, it's not lethal!
I'll make sure to kill you
with my own hands.
Back then...
Just wait a while, okay? Kouki-kun!
Stop it, Eri!
--Does it hurt? Are you sad?
- Let me hear a pretty scream.
--Stop!
--Does it hurt? Are you sad?
Let me hear a pretty scream.
Try to resist, curse me in your pain!
--Stop!
You'll still be my little puppet!
--Eri!
--A pathetic little toy!
Blessings to all deaths!
Ridicule to every sorry soul!
What in the world is going on?
Tio, Sensei, please.
Yes, we will!
Sh-Shirasaki-san...
The wheels of heaven shall not yet turn.
--The vessel may be lost,
but this soul is trapped in this world.
--It's no use! She's already dead!
--The vessel may be lost,
but this soul is trapped in this world.
--It's no use! She's already dead!
--Then let us open a gate
to life in between worlds,
--Hey, if you promise
not to be hostile,
--Then let us open a gate
to life in between worlds,
--I can bring Kaori back to life using
my magic. How does that sound?
--ward off death,
and rebind the ties to this soul.
Wait. Wait, Nagumo.
Look at these people around us.
They look alive, don't they?
You can't do anything about the dead,
the least you could do
is keep them clean, right?
Plus, you'd be able to do
as you please with Kaori.
For that, you definitely need me--
Hah! You had your guard down!
Dammit... Kill him.
You too? That's too bad.
Please.
Got it.
--Everyone, get down!
--Oh no! Get down!
So?
You...
I don't care about your feelings or
your motivations or whatever else.
If that's all you've got, then just die.
Nagumo!
Shut up.
If it wasn't for you,
Kaori would be mine... You!
It's your fault!
Don't blame others.
You're the only one to blame for this.
You never take responsibility for
anything. You're a complete loser.
I'll kill you! No matter what!
See if you can survive.
No! Help me!
Master!
We were able to attach her spirit, but it
would take time to do anything further.
I'd like Yue's help if possible.
This won't last forever!
Surrender.
Don't you value the life of your comrades?
There are one hundred thousand
monsters outside the walls,
and a million more coming.
No matter how strong you are,
you can't continue fighting while
protecting everything, can you?
What...
When did I say I'm friends
with the kingdom or these others?
If you want to have a war,
go right on ahead.
Just stay out of my way. Otherwise,
I'll vaporize you all, like I just did.
Get out of my sight.
I will get my vengeance for this shame.
In the name of my god, I will destroy you!
Hajime, where's that ugly fool?
Hajime-san, where is that piece of trash?
Hajime?
What happened?
Nagumo-kun, Kaori... Kaori is...
What can I do...?
Shea, take care of Kaori.
Kaori-san.
Tio, guide Yue and the others.
Sensei, I need your help, too.
Understood. Everyone, let's get to
the top of the mountain. Follow me.
Ai-chan-sensei!
I'll take care of this!
Ai-chan-sensei, go help Kaori please!
Understood. Sonobe-san, please take care.
Yaegashi, hold it together.
Just believe in us and wait.
I promise, you'll see Kaori again.
Nagumo-kun...
If you stay like this, who would
clean up after my messes from now on?
I can trust you, right?
Next episode, "A New Journey."