Cool it, Shun! You're visibly
pushing way too hard!
How the hell am I supposed to do that?
After seeing the kind of
lap time Sawatari posted...
I'm so pumped with adrenaline,
it's hard to rein it in!
Seriously, ease up, Shun!
You're making a bunch of errors!
In the 9, Aiba's overexuberance causes lots of
minor errors as he swings his car about wildly,
and he sits fifth currently.
Sawatari's performance on the second day
keeps him in provisional pole for now.
Ogata Automotive Ltd.
After he set a new
record time for the course,
even the other higher-ranking racers
must be feeling the pressure.
MF Ghost
Inherited
Perception
Kyoko-senpai!
Ciao.
Yes! I'm so lucky
we're working the same shift!
What shifts you got, Ren-chan?
I'm doing today and tomorrow.
Mine's the first day,
today, and the final day.
That's a lot. Thanks for your hard work.
Ashinoko Skyline
So how's it going with that
one-sided crush of yours?
Oh, uh... I don't know if you'd call them dates
as such, but we've gone out a few times.
I see.
So he's probably someone
you're pretty close to.
What's he do, anyway?
I'm kinda not ready to say yet.
Sorry. But I promise I'll keep
you updated, Kyoko-senpai.
Sounds complicated.
Well, I'll be waiting.
Must be nice to be young.
Kyoko-san. Number Seven.
Please be on standby.
Right!
Ashinoko Skyline
Mama Mayuko.
Could you help me with something?
My employer at my part-time job
asked me to fill out some paperwork,
but I'm not sure what to do for it.
Sure. Let me take a look.
First, you'll want to write
your name and address here.
You probably can't write kanji,
so just use the English alphabet.
It's okay. I've already learned
my name and address.
No way. Westerners usually
have a lot of trouble with kanji.
Katagiri Kana
Kana-chan, are you... like Katherine?
Can you recall everything you see?
That was a mistake.
No, this isn't anything special.
I just practiced a lot, so...
You don't have to hide it from me.
Your mother and I were classmates
for four years at art school.
We were best friends and told
each other lots of private things.
I know pretty much everything about her.
Mama Mayuko...
My mum always used to say to me...
that I shouldn't show what I could do
around people who didn't know me.
It was totally normal to us,
but apparently quite unusual to others,
and that can sometimes
cause issues in relationships.
That's fair. If someone's unfamiliar with it,
I can see how they might react negatively.
But it's not an issue for me.
If anything, it just drives home
that you really are your mother's son.
The thing about your mother is, even in
a school filled with so many talented artists,
she still managed to stand out.
She had a natural brilliance as an artist.
But I didn't expect you to inherit it.
Seeing that kind of time
set on the second day
has kinda screwed with the
heads of everyone running later.
Well, I'm not gonna let
these younger guys beat me.
I won't be messed with!
And next up is the 16, the Lotus Exige.
It's the turn of Yashio Kakeru,
the older brother in the Yashi-Kita Gang.
Yesterday, we saw the 18, the Alfa Romeo 4C
driven by his sister, Kitahara Nozomi...
...post a good time that put her near the top.
Can the older sibling pull off
a similar feat? We watch with interest.
Number Seven's tuchus is the only thing
that can heal my broken heart now.
It's a damn work of art.
The cameraman today just doesn't get it.
A zoom won't do. Get right in there!
You need to get closer to
capture the real feel of it.
The first time I saw Katherine sketching,
I was honestly pretty shocked.
Most people usually look back and forth
between their subject and the canvas.
But that wasn't how Katherine did it.
She stared at the subject for a while...
then once her gaze switched to
her sketchbook, her eyes never left it.
She produced an incredible sketch
at a remarkable speed.
When I asked her how she did it,
she said she could accurately recall
everything she saw in her mind.
She said it had always been like that,
so it just seemed natural to her.
So I can see how people would be surprised.
Do you ever draw, Kana-chan?
My mum never really
encouraged me down that path.
I was the outdoorsy type,
playing soccer and racing karts,
and she always seemed happy
whenever I was playing a sport.
It's probably because she struggled
with her own health a lot.
I think she was really
concerned about mine.
I'm sure she was.
Well, if you ever feel like it, you're welcome
to come to the drawing class I teach.
I get the feeling you could
produce something remarkable.
Something tells me the senses you inherited
from Katherine weren't only meant for racing.
Katagiri Kanata
Yes, Mama Mayuko.
I'd love to learn how to draw one day.
I might be embarrassingly bad at it at first,
but one day, I'd like to draw
the landscapes of Kamakura.
If nothing else, I gotta beat Nozomi's time.
Can't maintain my brotherly pride otherwise.
Huh?
He's not doing great, is he?
All his checkpoint times
are slower than mine.
You're right. But I'd say
it's less Kakeru being slow
and more you being on fire
yesterday, Nozomi-chan.
Why not chew him out over comms?
That's not a good idea.
Unlike you, provoking him while
he's driving just seems to distract him.
Just let me say one thing to him, then.
Hand me the headset, Yamatani-kun.
Hey, wait, Nozomi-chan...
This is the booth.
At your current pace, bro,
you're two seconds behind me!
Over!
Say what?
That little...
Ah, she's done it now.
And the Yashi-Kita Gang's eagerly awaited
head-to-head ends in victory to the sister!
The next day, early rain grows
more persistent through the day,
Ashinoko Skyline
and the time trials are
immediately canceled.
Qualifying for MFG takes
place over an entire week,
so there are frequently delays
caused by changes in the weather.
This is allowed due to its nature as an internet
broadcast with no trackside spectators.
Hello, Ren.
Kanata?
What are you doing?
I'm on my way home from work.
That's not what I meant.
Why don't you have an umbrella?
No one uses umbrellas in England.
That's great and all, but this is Japan.
If you go out without an umbrella,
people are gonna think you're a weirdo.
I don't mind.
I like the rain.
W-Well, too bad. What if you get sick?
Thank you, Ren. You're so kind.
Kanata's face is so close to mine...
What were you thinking?
You're soaking wet, Kana-chan!
You need to learn to take an
umbrella when it's going to rain.
MF Ghost
MF Ghost.
And as the sun rises, we're looking at perfectly
dry conditions, so the time trials can resume.
Driving the 10, the Lexus
LC 500, is Emile Hänninen.
And in the 5, the Audi R8,
it's the highly acclaimed Sakamoto Yudai.
But Sawatari Koki's time is untouchable.
As the fourth day draws to a close,
the 4 car remains at the top.
Still, there's no telling how it'll end up,
because tomorrow,
the top three begin to appear.
First up on the fifth day of qualifying,
it's Akaba Kaito in the 2 car, the Ferrari!
There are monsters prowling in MFG.
It's devour or be devoured.
It's survival of the fittest.
Ogata-san, the red Ferrari is on its run.
What an expensive car. It's so cool.
I noticed the higher-ranked cars do
their runs first. Is there some kind of rule?
It's kind of a reward
for the top-ranked drivers.
Thank you.
Every time there's an accident on the course,
the time trials have to be delayed a while.
That means the further down the list you are,
the more your start time gets delayed.
So the sooner the run, the less chance you'll
be disrupted. And you can fine-tune your car.
Basically, being high up in the points means
you get a better, earlier slot to do you run.
I see. It's a well-thought-out system.
Qualifying at Lake Ashinoko
tends to get delayed a lot.
Yesterday was a total mess.
There were five accidents in the death zone.
It meant the final car ended up
being delayed by an hour and a half.
The death zone for this
course is seriously scary.
Be careful out there.
Yes, sir.
I've seen the demo run.
You really like those, huh?
They're delicious. Japan has
the best snacks in the world.
They're so refined,
I feel like I can eat them all day.
He's doing his run tomorrow.
How can he be so relaxed?
Doesn't he ever get nervous?
Ogata-san?
Y'know, I'm not the one behind the wheel,
but I'm still freaking out here.
My heart won't stop pounding.
Kanata, don't you feel pressure at all?
Not when it comes to racing, no.
After all, I've done it for longer than I can
remember, dating back to when I was small.
It'd be one thing if I was
in a championship fight,
but in this case, I'm a regular
challenger. I'm genuinely excited.
Akaba Kaito finishes in
provisional second place,
with Sawatari Koki still on top!
And next up is...
Driving the 8, the Porsche 911
Carrera GTS, it's Jackson Taylor.
Things have been weirdly tense
right from the start this season.
I can't afford to make any mistakes,
but playing it too safe would be even worse.
The second you start driving defensively,
you'll be blasted out of the Godly Fifteen.
That's how intense the
level of competition is now.
I've never gone into a time attack
feeling this amount of pressure before.
And Taylor in the 8 ends up
in a provisional fifth place!
There are two days of qualifying left!
Want some more coffee, Kana-chan?
I'm good. It's getting late,
so I'll head to my room now.
Thanks for the coffee.
I think I will, too.
I've got tomorrow off, so maybe
I'll do my extra lessons for Monday.
I don't want you two staying up too late.
Okay.
Right.
I'm impressed with Kanata-kun.
He's got an important qualifying run
tomorrow, but he's relaxed to the core.
Start Time
Car Number
Driver
Takehara Yuto
Hayami Takeru
Katagiri Kanata
Kikuchi Yuuki
I was trying to be considerate
by not bringing it up,
but it looks like I didn't need to worry.
I went over the setup,
so you should be good.
Thank you, Ogata-san.
Yo. I came to root for you.
Aiba-senpai!
I thought only associated personnel were
allowed in the paddock on the sixth day.
Big shots like me get by on recognition.
You'll wanna aim for provisional 12th
with all you've got, Kanata.
It'll be tough, but you need to
do that to qualify for the race.
The 86 has evolved quite a bit, so as long as
I don't make any mistakes, I've got a chance.
As usual, he's annoying calm.
Do you really understand
what's going on here, dude?
And day six's time attacks have begun!
Looks like Mami-san's on shift today.
She's got a dynamite body.
I'm gonna watch qualifying, too.
Can you explain anything
I don't understand, Daddy?
Sure, ask me anything.
If you're going to be an MFG Angel,
it's important you learn about the races.
I know.
This year's MFG visit to Lake Ashinoko
is proving to be a must-watch!
And the obvious spotlight falls on
the man with the most pole positions,
Ishigami Fujin in the 1 car!
But there's one other driver of note today...
Someone I bet the fans are
very familiar with by this point.
He qualified 15th last time out, despite
driving an underpowered Toyota 86 GT.
In the race, he shocked everyone
by clawing his way up to ninth.
On a relatively flat course like Ashinoko
with a lack of corners, how will he fare?
It's no surprise people call Katagiri
Kanata an unpredictable "miracle boy."
And so, the 86 arrives at the gate
with 15 seconds to go.
Over here, Katagiri-kun.
She winked and blew him a kiss?
Isn't that against the rules?
We're not supposed to show
favoritism to any particular driver.
I'm gonna tell the manager,
Uehara-san, about her.
Up goes the board.
Ten seconds to go.
Five. Four. Three. Two. One.
Ashinoko Skyline
And he shoots away like he's been launched!
Katagiri Kanata has begun
his Ashinoko GT run!
It starts with a steady uphill section.
Crap. My heart's gonna explode.
The main reason I wanted
to be in Kanata's booth
is because it gives me access to the
telemetry the regular audience doesn't see.
If I can find the secret
to his speed, I'll steal it!
He's coming up to the first checkpoint!
Where will he be on the leaderboard?
Let's take a look!
He's currently in 13th!
Katagiri Kanata is on the attack!
Wow.
So fast.
What's going on here? I thought
you said the engine wasn't touched.
The opening section's slightly uphill, too.
He already has the attention flag on him!
Lake Ashinoko is said to be
the toughest course in MFG,
and Katagiri Kanata's
technique is on blazing display!