Next up is a rookie
making his first appearance.
Car 86, driven by a
challenger from England.
Katagiri Kanata, 19 years old.
Kanata?
Are you kidding me? Is that really him?
What are you doing here, Kanata?
Is it me or did she just look
really surprised for a second?
Six. Five. Four.
Three. Two. One.
Kanata...
MF Ghost
The Shocking New
MFG Generation
And he's off!
An entirely AI-controlled drone gives chase,
beaming back the white-hot MFG footage
that fans around the world expect.
He hits the incline with
the pedal to the metal.
What kind of run will we see from
this challenger from England today?
Let's watch and find out!
I'm surprised.
I didn't expect him to enter under
his father's family name, Katagiri.
Maybe he's trying to send a message.
He might be reaching out to Ken-chan,
who he hopes is watching somewhere.
Telling him "Your son, Kanata,
is right here," without outright saying it.
He'd really go that far to reach out to the
father who abandoned him and his mother?
He's the only one who can
know how he really feels.
His mother's passed on, he's left the
country he lived in with his grandparents,
and he's come to a
foreign land all by himself.
Just thinking about how he might
be feeling makes my chest hurt.
It's so sad, I can't bear to watch.
It's Ogata. Am I coming through clearly?
Loud and clear, Ogata-san.
This is a long course.
Try to keep your focus. Over.
Roger.
I gotta say, Ogata...
Qualifying Run
Number 86? I'm surprised you
managed to get a two-digit number.
I didn't really think we'd get it
either when I put in for it,
but luckily for us, it wasn't being used.
Sector 1's looking rough so far.
Dunno how you expect him to compete
in a manual with an H-pattern shifter.
Paddle shifters with dual clutch is the
standard now. Anything else is a handicap.
Huh?
54th place? You gotta be kidding me.
Must be some kind of system error.
Happens all the time.
There's no way your busted
old 86 car could be so high up.
Hey! Less of the "busted," Shun.
That said, I agree it's probably an error.
Holy crap. It says he's up to 53rd.
It's not an error. Look at that!
The central computer's
stuck an attention flag on the 86.
No way. That's impossible.
Oh! What's this?
Car 86 has been marked
with an attention flag.
From memory, the only other driver
to manage that feat in his debut event
was Michael Beckenbauer last year.
The 19-year-old Katagiri Kanata is on a roll!
This doesn't make any sense. The top 100...
hell, the top 200 is full of cars with
more horsepower than Kanata's 86.
So how is he so high up on the timing charts?
I guess it means Kanata's cornering
is just that much faster.
It's not that simple, Ogata.
No, it can't be that. The grip-to-weight ratio
of MFG poses a real issue in that regard.
Shaving off a bit of time
in corners won't help much.
In Sector 1, sheer grunt is
the only way to get ahead.
You say that, but...
The thing about a uniform
grip-to-weight ratio is...
the heavier the car, the fatter its tires.
This means a mid-engine design and
four-wheel drive are disadvantages.
And sinking money into reducing weight
means thinner tires, which defeats the object.
There's no limit on engine power, but if
you go too hard, your tires won't hold up.
Even many of the top teams haven't
figured out the optimal balance yet.
Which is why European models
that are balanced and powerful
without needing to be modded
have come out on top so far.
But it's also why the rule gets mocked
and called the "rich man's regulation."
I'm not quite sure that's right.
There has to be another way.
I have to admit, this is
every bit as exciting as I'd hoped.
Grip-to-weight ratio being the only rule...
Who could've come up with an idea like that?
Probably MFG's executive organizer.
Some guy named Ryo Takahashi.
Despite how big MFG has gotten,
no one knows how old he is or where he's from.
And he never shows his face.
He's a real man of mystery.
I think he might be incredibly smart.
In Japanese, you'd call him
a "tensai." A genius.
Kanata said that?
The 86 car is nearly done with Sector 1.
He's moved up again and
is currently in 52nd place!
It's all downhill from this point.
That means more weight to the front,
so adjust your brake balance. Over.
The switch on panel three, right?
That's the one.
I'm getting a bit more used to the car now.
I'll try to pick up the pace.
Huh? Did you hear that?
So he's been taking it easy up to now?
Who the heck is this Kanata kid?
What's his past record like?
I don't really know. Someone
I trust made the introductions...
And when I met him,
he seemed like a good guy.
All I know for sure is he went to
a famous racing school in England.
Fantastic job, Ogata-san.
The balance of the car's underbody
is spot-on, brakes included.
With this baby...
I may even be able to do
what I came here for.
He's broken into the top 50!
Talk about rapid! He's blazing downhill!
It feels like we're witnessing
the birth of a superstar!
Katagiri Kanata, only 19 years of age!
Are you kidding me? Damn.
Get me Maebashi... No, put me through
to Ryosuke direct. It's an emergency!
It's me, Ryosuke.
Are you watching the race live?
No. I'm doing a pretty big procedure soon,
so I was prepping for that. What's going on?
He's actually here. Fujiwara's student.
But he entered under the name
Katagiri instead of Rivington.
I can't believe I missed him.
I see. Well, that's good news.
Keep your eyes on that driver, Fumihiro.
Well, the AI's already got
an attention flag on him, so...
He's got the potential to figure out
and overcome the rule I introduced...
as part of MFG's new generation.
Surgery time. Hanging up.
Curt as always.
And what's this stuff about
"figuring out" the rule, anyway?
You never mentioned that to me before.
Ryosuke!
Car 86 is climbing the leaderboard
at an unbelievable rate!
He's currently 44th.
Once past the large torii gate, the course
veers away from the shoreline and back uphill.
Car 86 has dropped down a place.
He's losing a bit of speed going uphill.
It seems the Toyota 86 GT has a displacement
disadvantage next to the competition.
Once the course passes the highest point
on the old Route 1, it enters Sector 3.
And it's no exaggeration
to say that the gains
made on this stretch are what racing
on Odawara Pikes Peak is all about!
Ogata-san, I'm gonna try
and pick up the pace a bit more.
That idiot. Gimme the headset, Ogata!
Ow, ow. What are you doing?
You're heading into Sector 3.
Quit screwing around!
Damn it, Kanata! Did you forget my advice?
If a rookie who doesn't know the course
attacks it too hard here, he might die! Over!
Don't worry, Aiba-senpai.
You see, this course...
A movie of it is playing in my head.
I need to focus now, so forgive me
for the radio silence. Over.
And so, he crosses into the steep downhill
section that sends you plunging 864 meters
like a meteor toward the finish line.
It'll be a challenge for
rookie Katagiri Kanata.
Will he taste glory or
bitter disappointment?
MF Ghost
MF Ghost.
That dumbass. I'm gonna
slug him when he gets back.
That's what happens when you
don't respect your senpai's advice.
I get that you've got
a great driving technique,
but a rich kid who
grew up driving on circuits
won't understand how scary
a natural downhill course can be.
The stuff they teach you in school is
always useless out in the real world.
Don't you get that, Kanata?
What's going on here?
Every time he goes through
a checkpoint, he gains places.
This is amazing.
I guess it should be expected from
a student of a legendary downhill racer.
The 86 is moving around like a go-kart.
It could spin out at any moment.
Hell, it's already halfway there.
Is he serious about driving on the edge
like this all the way to the finish?
Are you nuts, Kanata?
I think he might be serious about trying
to set a time that gets him into the race.
You mean, break into the Godly Fifteen?
There's no way. That's completely
impossible. I mean, he's in an 86.
It's not very likely,
but it's not impossible.
With that being the case, we'd be
better off not insisting that he brakes more.
It might even be safer to help him
maintain his crazy motivation.
I know more about
a driver's psychology than you.
How's this for a plan?
That can't be a good idea.
That's like telling him to go on the attack.
Don't worry about it. Have faith in Kanata.
That kid...
I dunno what it is, but his driving
is beyond what you can imagine.
I got the fifth best time, so I can tell.
There's something fundamentally
different about where he's at.
Come on, quick. Tell him, Ogata.
Ogata here. Just giving you
an update. No need to respond.
There's 26 cars ahead of you. Over!
Good job, Ogata-san.
That's just what I wanted to know.
The way he's shot up the leaderboard
since entering Sector 3 is dizzying.
Can this really be
a rookie in his first race?
This Katagiri Kanata kid is
displaying unimaginable potential!
And with a driving style that
has a whiff of danger about it,
he approaches Odawara Pikes
Peak's infamous death zone!
The commentator, Tanaka-san,
seems really hyped up.
There's a real buzz in the air.
Kanata's in the mountains of Hakone.
Oh, Kanata, you stupid idiot!
You never said anything about racing in MFG.
Hakone's mountains are filled with tigers
and leopards and crocodiles and bears.
There's fearsome beasts around
every corner. It's incredibly dangerous.
It's no place for a good-natured boy like you.
You're a stupid liar, Kanata.
You told me you came to
Japan to find your father.
Cast your eye on this. See how the whole area
around old Kawaki-en is shrouded in mist?
Ever since Mount Fuji's north side
erupted a few years ago,
depending on the wind, this area can
become choked with volcanic gases.
Year after year, this abandoned
hot springs district is beset by thick fog.
You might even say they're clouds
of death that wander a ghost town.
And there goes the 86 car.
Into the death zone!
Hey, hold on. Is it just me or
is the fog even thicker than usual?
Odawara Pikes Peak sees a lot of accidents,
and most of them happen around here.
Even veterans tend to
prefer to play it safe here.
He talks a big game about knowing
the course, and so far, he's proved it.
Visibility might be nil,
but he has a good idea how far apart the
corners are, and which direction they go in.
You can see it by the lines he's taking.
But a 2D map in your head
isn't gonna help here.
This isn't a circuit. A public road
has gaps in the asphalt and dips.
You could be braking and have
the Gs drop out from under you,
or hit a patch that sends you two meters
off-line in a corner. Plenty of spots like that.
Qualifying Run
Unless you know what you're dealing with and
how the car will react, you're bound to crash.
So how's Kanata pulling this off?
You see, this course...
A movie of it is playing in my head.
What did he mean by a movie?
Is he talking about the demo runs
on the official website?
But that's...
Odawara Pikes Peak is 40 kilometers long.
He can't possibly have memorized all of it.
I'm freaking out, Shun.
Kanata can't see a thing, and watching him
go into corners at these kind of speeds...
It's crazy scary. I can barely watch.
I'm so nervous,
I'm starting to feel nauseous.
Oh, man. I think I really might puke.
Get a grip, Ogata.
And do your job.
Ogata here.
You have 16 cars left. I repeat, 16 left.
Over!
The 86 car is nearly into
the points-paying positions!
He shows no signs of flinching in the face
of the danger presented by the death zone!
We're seeing an otherworldly performance
here from 19-year-old Katagiri Kanata!
He might actually bag some points.
I didn't think that was even possible.
Points
System
Position
Points
Making the top 30 where
the points are dished out
is the dream and ambition
of every MFG participant.
Even scoring a tenth of a point
comes with plenty of benefits.
You get your tires free, and they set you up
with a booth without you needing to ask.
But best of all is you get your
car number highlighted in gold.
It looks so sweet. Plus, it's a mark of pride
for racers who have scored points.
That's plenty for me.
I would never ask to make the Godly Fifteen.
Just don't do anything
crazy out there, Kanata.
You can total the car for all I care.
Just make it back in one piece,
and I'll welcome you back with a hug!
Hard on the brakes as the steep
downhill slope leads into a 90 left!
He blazes through the
Miyanoshita intersection in style!
Would you look at that?
The footage from Car 86's drone
clearly shows a total lack of visibility.
It's enough to give you chills.
Yet he's managed to slip past
eight cars in the death zone.
I'm at a loss here, folks.
I don't have the vocabulary to describe
what the 86 is accomplishing here!
That's 26th place!
That's 25th!
This is the kind of thing
that makes MFG a must-watch!
The arrival of this driver is going
to be the hot topic of this season!
And he's out of the death zone!
You can see the Ohiradai hairpin
up ahead of the 86 car, clear as day!
I'm getting flashbacks. For a second,
I saw that black-and-white Panda Trueno.
That's Fujiwara Takumi's
super high-speed four-wheel drift!
Ogata here! 9 cars left! Over!
Next time, Turn 03:
The Kamaboko Straight.