The 16, 18, and 86
ascend toward the toll plaza.
We're seeing real sparks fly
between these three cars.
And so, the race enters its second lap.
Will we see more upsets
from Katagiri Kanata?
Good luck, Kanata.
Katagiri Kanata
I don't want you to be famous, but...
I want your dream to come true.
Glorious!
She's got such a cute tush.
Yeah.
Oh, shoot!
I let my guard down.
Now that's done, let's hit
Number Seven with a question.
Who's your favorite driver?
U-Um, I only just joined the Angels,
so I don't really know the drivers yet.
Liar.
You know one of them real well.
This is a riot. Right, dear?
Please don't heckle your daughter.
I can't label someone
I don't know as my favorite.
So I want to spend my first year
working really hard as one of the Angels,
and learn about MFG.
I'm sorry, but that's
all I can say right now.
The end.
She's got a bit of a tsundere streak.
That was a fresh outlook from
the new recruit, Number Seven!
And so, all 14 cars still running
have now started their second lap.
This is where it really
heats up, Kogashiwa-san.
I'd say so, yeah. Most drivers try to
conserve their tires on the first lap.
Every year, the second lap of Odawara Pikes
Peak tends to be where the race shakes up.
We'll see these motorized monsters
unleash all of their power
as they try to battle their way
to the front of the pack!
MF Ghost
The Man
in the 4 Car
In eighth, Akaba in the 2 car
continues his assault on the field!
Next in his sights is Taylor in the 8!
It seems only a matter of time
before he overtakes him.
I have a hard time believing a 450 HP Carrera
GTS can keep a 650 HP Ferrari behind for long.
I've figured out something crucial.
Thanks to a sensor issue, I wasn't getting
the usual power out of my boost in qualifying.
But I was able to beat my best time
in Sector 3 in spite of that.
That's gotta be a clue to
figuring out the big MFG mystery.
Ain't that right, Ryo Takahashi?
And here he comes!
The 2 car overtakes Jackson Taylor in the 8!
He's good. I couldn't do a thing to stop him.
There are three drivers in MFG
I consider exceptional.
Beckenbauer is one.
He's a completely different animal.
Then, there's you, Akaba.
As for the third...
That'd be last year's fourth-placed driver,
who didn't even show up for this race.
Huh? Hey, Ko-kun.
Isn't that an MFG race on
the big screen over there?
It's gotta be a repeat
of an old one, right?
Nope, it's live footage.
Wait, what? Shouldn't you be racing in it?
Is it okay for you to be here, Ko-kun?
Of course it is.
After all, it's your birthday, Sana.
Huh? But if you don't race,
you won't earn any money.
You don't need to worry about that, Sana.
I came fourth last year. Do you even
know how much money I made?
Still, I can't help feeling
nervous all the time.
I mean, you're older, you're hot,
and you're a celebrity to boot.
I get anxious because even if you don't
approach girls, they come up to you.
No Fear of Blind Corners
The MFG Theme Song
Plus, the Angels are
all cuties with great bodies.
The angels are all old hags
compared to you, Sana.
Oh, c'mon.
I'm just a totally normal
high school student.
That's not true.
You're more than normal.
You're special, Sana.
I mean, you're 17, right?
Ah, 17.
How I love the sound of it.
That number that shakes
my soul to its very core.
There's only two things I love
with all my heart in this world.
The first is how I fall head
over heels for 17 year old girls.
And the other is how I feel when I'm behind
the steering wheel and pushing to the limit.
It's just so cool.
By comparison, the money doesn't matter.
I'll spend it all on a girl, then once
it's gone, I'll risk my life to earn more.
Let's go get you a birthday present, Sana.
Let's really live it up. Unlimited budget!
You're so awesome, Ko-kun.
You need to attack, Ishigami-san!
If you don't get him in Sector 1,
your chances of winning are—
I don't need you to tell me that.
Just shut up! You're distracting me!
I was so convinced this baby's
engine made it invincible.
Out of all the cars competing in MFG,
this is the only one that can reach
9000 RPM with a flat-six that has 500 HP.
And yet, it somehow feels
underpowered right now.
It's not enough.
It's still not enough to compete with him.
He's got no openings.
There's no angle of attack I can take!
There are several points in Sector 1 where
a car at full throttle can exceed 200 kph.
I bet some viewers are asking how our drones
that have a max speed of 180 kph can keep up.
Well, these flying drones
can turn faster than the cars,
so any losses on the straights
are clawed back in the corners.
This ain't good. It's looking kinda bad for me.
Come on, Lady Luck. I need your help.
For my beloved Number Seven!
Emergency
Escape
Ramp
This is Ogata. Do you read me, Kanata?
Loud and clear. Over.
You sure you're not going too fast?
I'm worried about your tires.
In qualifying, they were
about 80% worn after one lap.
If you go into the second lap with the same
approach, you'll run out of grip halfway.
It's not a problem, Ogata-san.
They drilled tire management
into us at the academy.
I know from experience how long I can go in
a stint—or rather, the distance I can drive...
before all the grip
from a set of tires is gone.
It's bad to burn through them too quickly,
but worse to have rubber left at the end.
I won't go all out until
the final downhill section.
I'm confident I can execute that task
better than anyone else here.
I believe I can present you with a higher-placed
finish than where I am right now, Ogata-san.
Over.
Crap, I'm getting goosebumps.
And I can't help but tear up after that speech.
Beckenbauer in the 12 isn't letting
Ishigami in the 1 car gain any ground on him.
His pristine white Porsche Cayman has
zoomed past the rest house in first place!
This is a real upheaval. It's hard to imagine
anyone getting past him at this point.
This young man known
as the Stuttgart Slayer
is aiming to obliterate
the two-time champ's prestige.
The 9 car is in third, and the 5 car is in fourth.
Otani in the 7 is on his own in fifth place.
And that brings us to the battle for sixth.
The 2 car is clinging to the rear of the 6!
Will we see Akaba Kaito make his move?
Is this it?
And the 2 car completes a successful
overtake on the 6 car! He's now in sixth!
Damn. Crawling all over me in a
tight section with that wide-ass car...
Aren't you being a little
too eager, Akaba Kaito?
Here come more of the pack.
It's Taylor in the 8, followed by Oishi in the 3.
Where's Akaba? Where'd Akaba Kaito get to?
He's 9 seconds up the road.
You've got two cars between you.
Settle down, Daigo. Stay calm
and focus on getting past the 8.
Damn it.
How the hell am I supposed to stay calm?
Our cars should be evenly matched,
so how'd he get so far ahead in Sector 1?
The Yashi-Kita Gang
are still formation flying.
And about six seconds back,
a red vehicle is climbing up.
Out of the 15 cars in this race,
the Toyota 86 GT is the most down on power.
And since this is the power section,
the cars ahead are pulling away.
This must be a difficult race for Katagiri.
That said, his car's weakness makes the
driver's performance stand out all the more.
Even next to Beckenbauer in the lead and Akaba
Kaito, who's climbing up through the field,
we're seeing a similar level
of driving skill from him.
And back in last place,
the 13 enters Sector 2.
The second half of the course from Mount Taikan
to the lakeside is in pretty rough shape.
It's bumpy enough to cause bad vibrations.
And the dust here is no joke.
Push too hard and you might lose control.
That should make
any driver a little hesitant.
So all I can ask is "How?"
How is he the only one
fiercely picking up speed?
MF Ghost.
MF Ghost
Beckenbauer's on the cusp
of breaking away in first place.
The 1 car is making no impression.
He's gradually being left behind!
But we're seeing some
activity in the group behind.
Despite driving smoothly before,
the pace of the 9 seems to be dropping off.
The gap he'd built up to the
5 car has almost evaporated.
We're seeing signs of
understeer from the 9 car.
I think his tires are worn thin.
Damn. My front tires wore down
faster than I expected.
I'm struggling to control this thing's
heavy body under braking now.
But my rear traction is fine.
These roads are narrow enough.
I won't let him pass me.
I'm not giving up that kiss from
Number Seven, you dumb son of a bitch.
Booth to Kaito. Do you read me?
The 9's slowed down quite a bit,
and he's trying to hold on for third.
Keep this pace up and
you'll be on him by the end!
Copy that. Though first, I've gotta
catch the AMG in front of me.
I can see his rear end
getting bigger and bigger.
And now, we switch cameras.
Here come the 16, the 18, and the 86.
These three have been
together all through the race.
You could call it the
"Yashi-Kita Gang vs. Katagiri Kanata,"
though that doesn't mean their
machines are on an equal footing.
It's more like the 86 car is clinging
to the cars in front for dear life.
I imagine it's frustrating for Yashio
and Kitahara to be chased like that.
They run and run, but he
sticks to them like a shadow.
Yashio Kakeru: 22 years old.
Kitahara Nozomi: 20.
And Katagiri Kanata: 19.
It's a clash between talented,
prideful young drivers!
But who will have the last laugh?
Stay focused, Nozomi.
We've gotta carefully make it
through every corner, one by one!
Even little mistakes add up
to tire degradation over time!
I know. But are you sure you're not a bit
too worried about who's behind us, Bro?
I'm not as soft as you think I am.
If you show enough restraint,
storing up even a single second
can turn into a huge advantage
when you least expect it.
That's just how racing works.
National Route 1 Apex
Kanagawa
Prefecture
The drivers near the highest point on Route 1
as they enter the second half of the final lap.
Everyone's tires are bound to be
steadily losing tread by this point.
Wh-What is it, Kyoko-senpai?
Oh, y'know. I was just
checking out how skinny you are.
Even as a girl, I felt tempted
to give your waist a touch.
I wouldn't say I'm especially thin. You have
a pretty slender waist, too, Kyoko-senpai.
Only 'cause I hold it in while I'm at work.
I'm cheating.
You were on some kind of
sports team, weren't you, Ren-chan?
I did track in middle school
and my first year of high school.
That explains it. I was thinking you had just
the right amount of muscle on those legs.
If you're a high school
second-year, then you're 17?
That's right.
Wow, 17, huh?
Nice. That makes you
the youngest Angel ever.
So, tell me, Ren-chan...
Do you have a boyfriend?
No, I don't.
I've never even gone out with a guy before.
Do you have a boyfriend, Kyoko-senpai?
You seem like you would.
Not right now, no.
There is someone I'm interested in, though.
But it's been all on my side for two years now.
That's a surprise.
I bet.
Despite how I may seem, I tend to be pretty
buttoned-down when it comes to men.
Here's Taylor in the 9 car and
Oishi in the 3 car fighting over eighth.
Get outta my way, damn it. There's no way
a Lambo sticks to a Porsche's ass for long.
The short straight just after the highest
point on Route 1 is where I'll make my move.
I'll show you what this
5.2-liter V10 engine can do!
The two he caught up to in the first half
of the lap are leaving him behind again.
This climb in the back half
of Sector 2 is pretty steep.
It really drives home how
a racing car needs power.
You can talk all you want about balance,
but horsepower is a major factor, too.
Kanata must feel even more frustrated out
there driving than I do sitting here watching.
I wish he had more power.
What we need is more power!
And the lead car passes
the highest point on Route 1.
This mid-engine Porsche continues to leave
the pack of motorized monsters in its wake.
And that's despite the
flat-four at its heart
being a 2.5-liter engine
with meager displacement.
But behind the steering wheel is the
brilliant driver, Michael Beckenbauer.
In second, it's Ishigami in the 1 car.
Looks like he's cruising and
measuring up the cars behind him.
Here's the group fighting for third.
With Aiba in the 9, and Sakamoto in the 5.
They're both 4WD vehicles, but the 5 is
handicapped by being a mid-engine car.
He's on the verge of catching, but not quite.
But Aiba's Nissan GTR is still picking up
speed out of those sharp exits!
How well can he defend his position?
It's impossible to look away!
Behind them is the battle for fifth.
Whoa! And the Ferrari takes off!
Akaba Kaito is looking fierce!
Now he's used to the racing,
he's showing his true might!
He jumps up into fifth!
A great example of how your placing
in qualifying doesn't matter at all!
Akaba-kun's really going for it.
It'd be hard to rein him in at this point.
It's only a matter of time before
he catches up with the group in third.
And here comes Yanagida
in the 6 car in seventh.
Behind them is the group fighting over
eighth, Taylor in the 8, and Oishi in the 3.
And it looks like the 3 car is going for it!
It's a risky exchange, and they're close
to making contact! Is he going to make it?
It looks like the 3 car
has left the 8 car behind!
Will he be able to close in
on the prancing pony badges?
The charging bull digs its hooves into
the ground in pursuit of its nemesis!
These two Italian models
that were quiet in the first half
are now out to shatter
the German power bloc!
And we're closing in on the
last section of the race.
As the tires wear away,
things will only get harsher.
A descent down the mountains of Hakone
that demands a driver's full focus.
A nightmarish 874 meter downhill!
And here he is, the man who made his name
in Sector 3, driving the bright red 86 GT!
Plunging down Hakone's mountains,
this young man is blessed by gravity
in a way that seems miraculous.
A new breed of driver,
imported from England...
Katagiri Kanata is making a move!
Let's go.
Next time, Turn 08: The Voice Callout.