Am I alive?
Or am I already dead?
It's too dark to see anything.
Looks like I'm not dead yet.
Where am I?
I fell pretty deep into
the Great Orcus Labyrinth...
I can't be so deep that
nobody's made it down here, right?
In any case, I better get
to the upper levels, fast.
Gotta find some stairs that lead upwards.
This level is huge...
Not like any of the other levels before.
A bunny? All the way down here?
I thought the monsters in
the deeper levels were tougher...
Crap! That bunny is crazy tough!
It found me!
It's eating it...
It was just prey for a predator.
Just like me!
My arm!
It ate my arm!
T-Transmute!
Transmute!
Transmute, Transmute, Transmute, Transmute!
Transmute, Transmute,
Transmute, Transmute, Transmute!
Get away, get away,
get away, get away, get away!
C-Crap, it won't stop bleeding...
I'm passing out...
My arm hurts...
That's... a Holy Crystal.
A mythological stone formed by
the crystallization of mana over milennia...
"The saturation of mana turns to liquid
and begins to flow from the stone.
That liquid is called Holy Water,
and it can heal any injury and dispel any curse."
I've been visiting the Royal Library to try
and glean information to help my classmates,
"Status: Hajime Nagumo"
"Skills: Transmute, Language Comprehension"
but it looks like if I can't fight,
then there's no way I'm gonna
get out of here or even survive.
I can't fight that thing!
It's way tougher than a Behemoth!
I should have never gone
into the Labyrinth...
Someone, help me!
Listen up! Everyone helps
each other in the Labyrinth.
No matter what, got it?
Got it!
I'll keep everyone safe!
Thanks, Amanogawa-kun.
Why're you bothering with a sword?
You're still totally useless.
Are you okay, Nagumo-kun?
Yeah.
You just have to work harder, Nagumo.
If I were you,
I'd be using every scrap of free time
to train and get a little bit stronger.
What's that? It's so shiny.
Is that...
That's a glanz crystal.
You don't see big ones like that all too often.
It's apparently a pretty popular
engagement ring stone.
It's beautiful!
Well, then, I'll go grab it!
Hey! Don't go off on your own!
We haven't even checked to see if it's safe!
It's a trap! Get back!
Get to those stairs, hurry!
Thanks, Shizuku!
Hurry, everyone!
Get a move on!
I'm not going to let you die here!
O God, grant thy beloved
children thy divine protection
from all wishing to cause them harm,
let the soil at our feet become divine
ground that keeps our enemies at bay!
Hallowed Ground!
Run, Kaori!
Transmute?
Nagumo-kun!
Run! Now's your chance!
You all right, kid?!
This won't hold for long, Captain Meld!
G-Get Shirasaki-san and yourself to safety!
Hurry!
I swear, we'll rescue you.
All right... Keep it up!
It's not gonna last!
Get out of there, kid! We'll cover you!
Ready, everyone?
Ready!
Run, kid! Hurry!
Got it!
Why? Why?
Why? Why?!
Just die already. Die!
I don't wanna die... Die!
No, I don't want to die... Die!
I don't want to die... Die!
I don't want to die!
Dammit! My left arm hurts so much!
It got bitten off, but it still hurts!
Whose fault is this?! Who's to blame?!
Who? Who did this?! Who, dammit?!
I swear, we'll rescue you.
Fire!
Second volley, fire!
Hang in there, Nagumo-kun!
Huh?
Why's it coming this way?!
I don't remember anyone
ever wanting to kill me.
But that was aimed directly
at me, to try and kill me.
Who the hell was it?!
It was him!
But why?
Guess it doesn't matter anymore...
Kid!
Run!
What?!
Did someone miss?!
Nagumo-kun!
Don't!
But Nagumo-kun's--!
No!
Shirasaki-san?
It's the middle of
the night, what's up?
I don't want you to go with us
to train in the
Great Orcus Labyrinth.
Please. I had a really horrible dream.
I think something's
going to happen to you...
Hold on a sec.
We were in a dark place,
and when I tried calling out to you,
you didn't respond...
I ran after you, but I couldn't catch up...
A-And then...
And then?
You disappeared...
Huh...
Well, then, would you protect me?
Huh?
My Synergist job is super commonplace
and not really well-suited to combat,
but you're a Priest, right, Shirasaki-san?
If I end up getting really hurt,
you can just use your powers to heal me.
Okay. I promise
I'll protect you, Nagumo-kun.
No!
Nobody's going to rescue me...
What should I do now?
Why do I have to suffer like this?
What did I do?
Why is this happening to me?!
I was brought here
in some crazy turn of events,
my classmates all betrayed me,
and the enemies are too damn powerful!
What do I want in this
hopeless pit of despair?
I want to survive and go home...
Everything between me
and home is my enemy!
That's right. If something's in my way,
if someone's forcing me to do crap...
...then I'll kill them!
I'm thirsty and hungry, too.
Dammit! I don't care
if I have to eat a monster.
I'll frickin' eat it!
Shut up! I'm pissed off
'cause I'm so damn hungry!
Shut up and let me eat you!
These tough monsters
are pretty damn resilient.
God, this is way grosser
than I'd imagined...
Wh-What the hell?!
It's like something's
eating me from the inside...!
I-It won't stop!
What the hell is happening to...
Shit, do you die
if you eat monster meat?
I'd be screwed without this Holy Water.
I'd have died when
the monster meat tore me apart.
For once, I don't feel any pain.
My body actually feels lighter.
What the hell happened to me?
Damn, I look like a demon.
Guess I should take
a look at my status plate.
Eating monster meat
made my level jump up, huh?
"Skills: Transmute (+Mineral Apprasial),
Mana Manipulation, Iron Stomach,
Lightning Field, Language Comprehension"
"Lightning Field, Language Comprehension"
And I've got new skills.
Mana Manipulation? Guess it means
just what it says, I can manipulate mana.
"Skills: Transmute (+Mineral Apprasial),
Mana Manipulation, Iron Stomach,
Lightning Field, Language Comprehension"
Damn, I don't even need to say the spell.
I must've gained these skills
by eating that monster meat.
Lightning Field?
That move, huh?
Hey, I did it.
The mana light's turning red.
I can't shoot it like that two-tailed wolf did,
but if I can manipulate
the voltage and amperage...
Smells like crap,
but it's better than eating it raw.
At any rate, I need some kind of weapon.
"Skills: Transmute (+Mineral Apprasial),
Mana Manipulation, Iron Stomach,
Lightning Field, Language Comprehension"
Whoa! I can know what
a rock is just by grabbing it.
I should be able to make
a weapon if I use it right...
"Taur Stone"
"A hard black rock. Hardness 8, Toughness 8.
Strong against force and heat but weak to cold.
Weakens when frozen. Add heat to bond."
Taur Stone. A hard black rock.
Hardness 8, Toughness 8.
Strong against force
and heat but weak to cold.
Weakens when frozen. Add heat to bond.
"Blast Rock"
"A flammable stone. Can explode when
pressure and heat is applied in a closed space."
Whoa!
Blast Rock, a flammable stone.
Can explode when pressure and
heat is applied in an enclosed space.
With enough volume and pressure,
produces explosions that rival
the highest tier of fire magic spells."
So it's basically gunpowder.
With enough volume and pressure,
produces explosions that rival
the highest tier of fire magic spells.
Now I've got bullets.
A six-shot revolver and bullets crafted
from extremely tough Taur Stone.
Each bullet was packed
with Blast Rock powder.
And if I accelerate them
with Lightning Field...
I'd better give him a good name...
I got it; I'll name it Donner.
This doesn't get any easier...
Let's check my status...
"Skills: Transmute (+Mineral Apprasial)
(+Precise Transmute) (+Mineral Probe),
Mana Manipulation, Iron Stomach,"
Good, the numbers went up.
Whenever I eat a monster I haven't
eaten before, my stats go up a lot.
"Lightning Field, Air Walk (+Aerodynamics)
(+Quick Step), Language Comprehension"
And these new skills will
probably help me find the exit.
"Quick Step"
Quick Step... That's how it teleported.
"Aerodynamics"
Aerodynamics...
That was when it pushed off the air.
Guess I should go repay a favor
to a favorite monster of mine.
Hey, long time no see.
Enjoy snacking on my arm?
That's the spirit. Time for a rematch!
I'm gonna kill you and eat you!
Quick Step!
That's right, I'm your enemy!
I'm not some sniveling prey
for you to hunt!
Aerodynamics!
Dammit!
I'm real proud of this creation.
Take a good look!
Ugh, tastes like crap.
But for some reason, it tastes
way better than anything else.
Lightning Field!
I'm going home...
I'm going to survive this and go home!
I don't care who stands in my way
or what they might be...
I'll kill them.
ARIFURETA: From Commonplace
to World's Strongest.