Guess eating him won't make
my level go up any higher.
"Skills: Transmute (+Mineral Appraisal) (+Precise
Transmute) (+Mineral Probe) (+Mineral Isolation)
(+Mineral Fusion), Mana Manipulation, Iron Stomach,"
If I can't find a way up,
"Lightning Field, Air Walk (+Aerodynamics)
(+Quick Step), Spirit Claw, Language Comprehension"
then I'm gonna have to keep going down.
I can use Transmute to move horizontally,
so I should be able to use it to move vertically.
They said this labyrinth had 100 levels,
but which level am I even on?!
Can't see a damn thing...
I know shining a light in the
dark's dangerous, but I have to...
Petrifaction?!
Dammit, you got me...
Now then,
what is it that you found on the
20th level of the Great Orcus Labyrinth?
Your highness,
we found a new kind of trap
that utilized a glanz crystal.
It instantly transported
us to the 65th level.
That's quite deep.
That is the deepest level ever reached,
and the lair of the Behemoth.
Our fight against the
Behemoth and Traum Soldiers was...
...regretfully, in vain.
Word that one of God's chosen heroes has
perished is spreading through the kingdom.
Say nothing more about
this matter. Understood?
Understood.
You are all in agreement, yes, Heroes?
Huh?!
The Behemoth! This is the 65th floor!
That's the furthest anyone's ever gotten...
Take the students and
attack the Traum Soldiers!
Yes, sir!
The rest of you, hold this beast back!
We'll help!
You fools!
Run! Now's your chance!
I swear, we'll rescue you.
All right... Keep it up!
It's not gonna last!
Get out of there, kid! We'll cover you!
Second volley, fire!
Why's it coming this way?!
Nagumo-kun!
Don't!
But Nagumo-kun's--!
Nagumo-kun!
Kaori!
Let go of me!
We have to save Nagumo-kun!
Kaori!
It's too late!
I promised... I promised to protect him!
Kaori!
Nagumo-kun!
You didn't have to do that!
Koki!
Thank you.
We can't lose any more of you.
Right.
C'mon, you can cut open a path for us.
Get us all out of here.
Right... I can.
Welcome to Tortus.
Let me formally welcome you great heroes
and your retainers to our kingdom.
According to Pope Ishtar,
there are three races
of creatures in this world:
humans, demons, and beastmen.
Humankind and demonkind have been
engaged in a bloody war for centuries...
But demons have learned to control monsters,
tipping the scales in their favor...
Humanity is now on the brink of destruction.
To prevent that, the god of creation
worshipped by the people of Tortus, Ehit,
summoned heroes with incredible
power to his kingdom--that's us.
The people of this kingdom are in danger.
We can't let them die!
I think we should fight to save them all!
A... Amanogawa-kun?!
I-I can't let you do that!
No, I cannot let you do that!
I have a duty as your
teacher to keep you all safe!
I'll fight, too.
I don't want you to have to fight alone.
Even if it wasn't my duty, I'd protect you!
You're all very dear to me!
Ryutaro...
I'll fight, too.
That's all we can do right now.
H-Hey, Amanogawa-kun,
are you listening to me?!
Shizuku!
U-Uh...
When your teacher is talking, you have
to listen and respond to her, understand?!
I-If Shizuka-chan is going
to fight, then I'll try, too!
Kaori!
Can't you understand how I feel?!
You can't! You simply can't!
Listen to your teacher!
We are going to have them send us
back to school as soon as possible!
Until that happens,
you are still my students, and...
Something's wrong.
No way it's that easy...
I-It's fine.
Nobody'll ever find out.
Nobody saw me do it...
Everything went perfectly. It's fine.
Hiyama-kun?
Yaegashi?!
What's up?
N-Nothing! What's up with you?
Just training.
Gotta keep up or I'll get rusty.
Why don't you do a bit of training yourself?
N-No, I'm fine.
Was Hiyama-kun always like that?
You know, he was always
picking fights with Nagumo-kun.
"Skills: Transmute, Language Comprehension"
Even when we came over here...
Does Hiyama-kun like Kaori...?
No, it couldn't be.
Kaori!
Thank goodness...
Shizuku-chan.
How are you feeling?
I'm okay. Just a little tired.
You've been asleep for five days,
no wonder you're tired.
That long? But why?
I remember we were
in the Labyrinth, and then--
Hey, you thirsty?
I can't remember.
Where's Nagumo-kun?
He's okay, right?
We saved him, didn't we?
Right?
No...
Don't... that can't be true!
Kaori!
Shizuku-chan, let go of me!
I have to go!
Nagumo-kun must be waiting for us!
He must be so sad, down there all alone!
I've got no idea how
far down this place goes.
I've gone down 50 levels since I fell.
Maybe the answer's
waiting behind those doors.
Just like Pandora's Box.
What hope lies beyond those doors?
I'm going home.
I'm surviving this and going home.
And if anything gets in my way,
I'll kill them.
Man, I'm stumped. I did a whole
lot of studying, but I never saw this.
Must mean it's pretty old.
Guess I'm just gonna
have to use Transmute...
Dammit!
Yeah, I should've expected that cliché.
Sorry, I see what's goin' on,
and I'm not gonna wait for the
both of you to come out to fight you!
Defensive magic, huh...
Sorry, but I already know its weakness!
His arm's in the damn way!
What's wrong? Come and get me!
Can't get too far from the door, huh?
Is what's behind it that much of a secret?
You got nowhere left to go!
Over here!
Now, what were you protecting here?
Shizuku-chan, I want to believe...
...that Nagumo-kun is still alive.
Kaori...
I know. It's more unlikely he'd be alive.
But we won't know for sure
until we check for ourselves.
I'm going to get stronger.
I'm going to get stronger
and see for myself!
Shizuku-chan...
Will you help me?
Sure. I'll be with you all the way.
Thanks!
No need to thank me. We're friends, right?
Mm-hmm.
Mana stones?
Guess the monsters
themselves were the keys.
I'll eat them later. For now...
Who's there?
Is that... a person?!
Sorry to bother you.
W-Wait! Please, help me!
No thanks.
Why?! I'll do anything!
Look, nobody in their
right mind would release someone
obviously sealed away
down here on purpose!
I'm busy!
No!
It's not my fault!
Please, wait, I...
I was betrayed!
Dammit.
You were betrayed, huh?
That doesn't explain why
you were sealed down here,
even if what you're saying is true.
Why'd the people who betrayed
you seal you up down here?
Hey, you listening?
If you don't feel like talking, I'm leaving.
I'm one of a long line of vampires
and extremely powerful, too...
I worked really hard to protect my people.
But one day, my ministers said
I was no longer needed...
My uncle said he was going to rule instead...
And I was fine with that.
Were you the royalty of some kingdom, then?
But they said I was too dangerous...
And they couldn't kill me,
so they sealed me down here...
What do you mean, they can't kill you?
I heal quickly.
When I get hurt, it heals right away.
Is that what you meant by powerful?
That, and I can manipulate mana...
I don't even need a circle.
Damn. Those are some
rule-breaking powers.
That'd make you immortal for sure.
Please help me.
The hell am I doing...
This thing really doesn't wanna go...
But I've got the power now!
Come on!
Want some?
You're warm.
Well, duh. I'm still alive.
What's your name?
Hajime. Hajime Nagumo.
Hajime...
Hajime, Hajime, Hajime...
What's yours?
Huh?
What's your name?
Give me one.
What? Give you one?
Did you forget yours or something?
I don't need that old one anymore!
I want whatever name
you give me, Hajime!
What do you mean, you don't need it...
M-Man, even if
I wanted to name you, I just...
How about "Yue"?
Yue?
Yeah. Where I come from,
it means "moon."
Moon?
When I first came into this room,
your blonde hair and red eyes
reminded me of the moon in the night sky.
How about it?
From this day on, I'm Yue...
Thank you!
N-No prob.
Hajime! Hajime!
"Good morning," "Good night,"
all those simple things
are so dreamlike and beloved to me
Because I finally met you
Everything is so special, thank you again
I didn't think I'd be lonely all by myself
That is, until you found me
I wasn't afraid of anything
That is, until I thought of a world without you
Can you believe it?
I miss you, I'm so fond of you
I love you, don't forget it
Shine bright like the first star in the night
and stay closer to me than anyone else
I'll never let you go
I'll never let go of that hand
Stay by my side and shine
ARIFURETA: From Commonplace
to World's Strongest