Hajime!
I let my guard down!
Guess it's here to make sure you don't escape...
Here.
Put this on.
Hajime, you perv.
Hold on tight, Yue!
Come at me!
You get in my way,
then I'm gonna kill and eat you!
Quick Step!
I've gotta do something
about that hard carapace...
What's up?
Huh?!
It can manipulate the earth around it...
Nice trick, but that's my specialty!
That was delicious.
Azure Blaze!
You okay?
High-level magic is tiring...
I know you're tired,
but could you do that one again?
I can, but it'll be little...
That's fine.
Do you remember where
I shot him with my Donner?
Mm-hmm.
When I give the signal, you hit him there!
Mm-kay!
Okay, let's go!
Yue!
Why?
Huh?
Why didn't you leave me behind and run?
I haven't fallen that far.
You were horribly betrayed,
then entrusted me with your safety.
What kind of man would I be if I left you?
If I remember right,
the vampires were eradicated in
a war that took place 300 years ago.
300 years ago...
Which means you must be over 300 years old.
That's rude.
Do all vampires live that long?
I'm special. Because I regenerate, I don't age.
Must be a special kind of magic
that makes you immortal.
Mm-hmm...
So, do you know where we are right now?
Or do you know of
any way up to the surface?
I don't...
But they say this labyrinth
was built by one of the Mavericks.
The Mavericks?
They were the messengers of deities that fought
against their gods during the Age of Gods.
There were people who went against the gods?
They say the Mavericks
tried to destroy the world,
but their plans fell apart, and they
escaped into what are their labyrinths.
Does that mean this
Great Orcus Labyrinth, too?
Mm-hmm, and it seems the Maverick
resided at the bottom of each labyrinth.
In the deepest depths of hell, huh?
If we go there,
we might find a way to the surface.
I get it.
It'd make sense that someone wielding divine
magic could just create a path to the surface.
"An ore with a high affinity to magic.
The more mana it absorbs,
the stronger it becomes."
Shtar Ore.
An ore with a high affinity to magic.
The more mana it absorbs,
the stronger it becomes.
Guess that's why it's so hard.
What're you making?
This is the railgun version
of a antimateriel rifle.
Rail...?
You saw my gun Donner, right?
That's a pretty powerful gun.
The bullets are special, too.
But I'm gonna use this perfect material
to make Donner pack more of a punch.
Okay, all done.
This one's named Schlagen.
Why are you down here, Hajime?
Huh?
Why can you manipulate mana directly?
Wha?!
How can you eat monsters?
Are you human? What happened to your arm?
H-Hold on a sec!
I'll explain everything in order, just hold on!
Okay, where should I even start...
One day, we were summoned
to this world by the god Ehit.
They said we were supposedly the
people to save humanity from demonkind.
However, my job was Synergist,
which wasn't well-suited for combat.
Everyone said I was totally useless in a fight.
We teamed up with the
Royal Guard to clear out the labyrinth.
In the middle of battling a Behemoth,
I was betrayed by one of my classmates,
and before I knew it,
I was down here in the depths.
A monster ate my arm,
and I was this close to dying...
But I decided I was going
to survive, no matter what.
So I used my synergist abilities
to kill a monster and ate it.
Whoa, what's wrong?
That's so horrible... It hurts to hear.
Don't worry about it.
I don't give a crap
about my classmates anymore.
I don't even want revenge.
I just want to get better
at things that'll help me survive.
I'm going to find a way back home.
I've gotta give that my all.
Back home?
Well, yeah.
Sure, a lot might've changed
about me, but I want to go home.
Oh.
I don't have a home to go back to...
I don't need that old one anymore!
I want whatever name you give me, Hajime!
Ah, man...
You wanna come with, then, Yue?
Huh?
I mean, back home with me.
It might be pretty boring, seeing
that the human world doesn't have magic,
but I think we'll work something out.
Only if you want to, of course.
Are you sure?
Status: Open!
"Skills: Elemental Affinity, Elemental Resistance,
Physical Resistance, Composite Magic,
Swordsmanship, Herculean Strength, Quick Step,"
Kouki Amanogawa, job: Hero.
Foresight, Increased Mana Recovery Speed,
Presence Perception, Magic Perception,
Limit Break, Language Comprehension"
Seems you've grown even stronger.
We will continue with practical training
within the labyrinth with the present members.
I trust you will prepare accordingly.
Yes, sir!
That is all.
Failure is not an option, huh...
Okay, everyone! We're going
to make this training a success!
Right!
God dammit!
Keep it up, Hajime.
You are way too chill!
What the hell are these guys?!
No matter how many I kill,
they just keep coming!
And there's more and more of them.
That's crazy! And what the hell is
with those flowers on their heads?
They're kind of cute.
Like hell they are!
Did you see what the one before was...
Wait, are those flowers...
Parasites.
You think so, too?
Something should be controlling them.
Yeah. If we don't kill the thing
that's controlling the flowers,
then we'll have to battle
every monster on this level...
Where is it?
Where's the source?
Hey, little miss vampire princess?
Could you stop snacking on my blood?!
I can't help it.
Yeah, right! You can't be that tired!
Well, that looks suspicious...
We should be safe for now.
Good work.
If you really wanna make me happy,
then why don't you come down from there?
Fine.
Okay. They were pretty damn desperate,
so I bet we hit the jackpot here.
Don't let your guard down.
My Sense Presence skill
hasn't detected anything yet...
Dammit!
That's probably an attack from the source, Yue.
Know where it is?
Yue?
Run, Hajime!
Did those green balls do that to her?
You're not half bad...
Hajime, I'm sorry...
What's wrong?
I gained resistance by eating those monsters.
That trick won't work on me!
Stop!
Dammit...
No!
Hajime, don't worry about me!
Just shoot!
Yue...
Hajime, shoot!
Wait, really?
That makes things easier!
Don't look at me like that.
You okay? Anything feel off?
You shot at me.
You told me to.
You didn't even hesitate.
Well, I wanted to shoot at it.
I knew I'd hit my mark, but...
But?
But if I'd shot at her without saying anything,
you'd probably get mad, so I held off.
I think you burned off... some of my scalp.
It'll just grow back, won't it? No biggie.
Want some, Yue?
I don't need it.
Makes sense, you've been sealed
away for 300 years and survived.
Aren't you hungry, though?
I was... but I'm okay.
Okay? What, you ate something?
Your blood.
Oh. That means you don't need to eat
as long as you're drinking blood.
I can get nutrients from food as well...
But blood is the most efficient way.
I get it.
Why're you licking your lips?
You taste good.
You taste ripe.
H-Hold on a sec.
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
No getting away. Time to eat.
We're finally at floor 100.
Hajime, you're being more careful than usual...
Yeah, since this is the
hundredth floor since my fall.
I figured there might be something down here.
Like what?
I dunno, just want to be safe.
If there is something down there,
it's beyond these doors.
You scared, Yue?
Not if I'm with you, Hajime.
That's what I like to hear!
"Good morning," "Good night,"
all those simple things
are so dreamlike and beloved to me
Because I finally met you
Everything is so special, thank you again
I didn't think I'd be lonely all by myself
That is, until you found me
I wasn't afraid of anything
That is, until I thought of a world without you
Can you believe it?
I miss you, I'm so fond of you
I love you, don't forget it
Shine bright like the first star in the night
and stay closer to me than anyone else
I'll never let you go
I'll never let go of that hand
Stay by my side and shine
ARIFURETA: From Commonplace
to World's Strongest