I'm so tired of waiting!
When are they going to appear?
Hurry up and appear!
Please, someone, save me!
Here they come!
Huh? Whaaaa?!
I-I finally get to meet you!
All right! We made it to the surface!
Mm-hm!
I've been waiting for you!
I finally get to meet you!
The hell is that?
A rabbitman?
She keeps saying weird crap like
"finally meeting you" and "waiting for you."
Sounds annoying. Let's go.
Wait! Please, don't go!
What a worthless rabbit.
I'm begging you, please save my family!
Your family?
Get off him.
No! If I get off,
you'll just toss me aside, won't you?!
Uh, yeah.
Why do I gotta rescue some rabbit
I've never even met before?
N-No hesitation!
Won't it wound your heart to turn away
a beautiful young lady in need?!
Glance. Glance.
Don't compliment yourself.
She has no shame.
Did that thing just roar at me?
You can't! It's horribly violent!
Run while you can!
You took out that Diheadoar... Wow!
C'mon, let go of me already!
I am Shea, the eldest
daughter of the Haulia beast tribe!
Please, save my family! I'm begging you!
Please!
The hell is wrong with you?
You don't give up.
If I don't keep this up,
the future of my whole race might...
All right.
That hurts!
Sheesh, I'll hear you out, fine.
Dank you bery mush!
And don't think you can go
wiping your face on my coat like that!
Y-You hit me again!
I can't believe you hit this beautiful young lady!
I can't believe you can say
this crap with a straight face!
Especially when you're standing in front of Yue,
who's leagues better than you!
S-Still!
I...!
I know there's one thing
about me that's better than her!
I win!
Look at her, she's completely flat!
How do you like this?
Huh? Wha?
Are you blushing? Are you totally flustered?
Huh?
Uhh, would you forgive me if I apologized?
Any last words?
Noooo, I don't wanna die!
So you were exiled from your home,
then attacked by monsters?
Beastmen aren't able to manipulate mana,
but for some reason, I can,
and on top of that, I can use
specialized magic that only monsters can use!
Specialized magic?
Yes, it's called Future Sight,
and it lets me see possible futures.
Like, if you made this choice,
this would happen, kind of stuff.
That's why I knew you two would appear!
Please, save us! If you don't,
the Haulia race is doomed!
No.
Please, wait!
I saw into the future!
I saw you were helping us!
And what am I gonna get out of it?
Huh?
Huh? Nothing, right?
You're headed for the Great Tree
in the Haltsina Sea of Trees, right?
It's always surrounded by a thick fog.
It blinds the senses
and makes everyone get lost!
So?
So if a native of the Sea of Trees
were to go with you...
Let's take her with us.
Yue?
It'll be nice to have a guide.
Thank you so much!
Thank goodness!
Look, look!
I found a fruit!
No, come back!
No!
Father!
I brought help!
Shea!
Father, everyone!
Huh?
If you're feeling well enough to get
in the way, I'd better make you work.
Work?
What, it'll be easy. I'm just gonna ask you...
...to be bait for these hungry monsters.
Go get 'em, ya worthless rabbit!
Nooooooo!
I can't take this anymore!
You're being so rough with me!
Can I ask for gentler treatment...?
Because I can use the same
powers that monsters can,
my fate was to be detested and
eventually killed by the other beastmen.
But my Father and the rest of the
Haulia tribe left our home of Verbergen,
all to protect me.
But rabbitmen have no way
to fight and protect themselves.
I never thought I'd see the day when
everyone was able to relax like this...
Thank you so much.
No need to thank me.
I promised I'd protect you
if you guided us to our destination.
Um, this is the first time I've met
someone else who can use monstrous powers.
So it's hard for me to
think of you as only a stranger.
What's the goal of your journey?
I have one goal.
To go back home, with Yue in tow. That's all.
I've made my decision!
I'm going to join you on your journey!
No thanks.
You'll just hold us back.
You didn't even hesitate!
Huh?
We want to get stronger!
We don't want to be weak anymore!
Please, Hajime, ser, we beseech you!
Well...
You're wide open!
Whaaaaa?
"Hey."
Hey.
Yeeees?
"Yeeees?"
Don't tell me you're jumping and
pouncing around because of that flower.
"because of"
"that flower?"
We can't help it! We love the pretty flowers
and tiny bugs, and all the little things!
"We can't help it!"
Th-The flower!
Ser Hajime?!
I underestimated you lot...
Listen up, you worthless rabbits!
If you don't want me to murder you all,
then go crazy and start killing monsters!
Kill or be killed!
"kill"
"be killed!"
Crimson Javelin.
I'm not done!
Flame Fortress!
I've got you!
Wind Wall!
Crystal Coffin!
Hey, wa--
I win.
Aw, man...
Wait!
Look, your cheek! There's a scratch, a scratch!
I hit you with an attack!
There's no scratch.
There was one just now...
Don't pretend it didn't happen, that's mean!
Th-That was really cold. For a second,
I thought I'd never make it out alive...
You done with your duel?
Yes, I was finally able to hit Yue!
A glorious victory!
Man, I wish you could've seen it, Hajime-san.
Huh. So, Yue, how is she?
She specializes in strengthening
her body, on a monstrous level, too.
Well, damn.
Hajime-san, please take me
with you on your journey!
Why do you wanna come with us?
W-Well, uhh...
Uhh, what?
Because I wanna be with you, Hajime-san!
I wuv you!
What?
'Ey boss, we hunted down
all those monsters you wanted.
F-Father? Your speech is...
Well, everything's different...
I told you one would be enough.
A whole lot of 'em came after us,
and they had the nerve to try and kill us...
...so we cut 'em all down.
They were so annoying,
but their screams were such a pleasure...
Hajime-san, what did you teach my people?
How to fight.
So this is the Great Tree...
It's been dead since before
Verbergen was established.
But it never rotted away.
It's stood here for ages, dead and unchanging.
This is like the one in Oscar's...
Yes, it's the same design.
Looks like this must be
the entrance to another labyrinth.
What's this?
Only to those with the four symbols, the power
of regeneration, and beacon formed of bonds
will this door open once more.
What does that mean?
The four symbols must be
the relics from the other labyrinths.
And "beacon formed of bonds" might
mean you had beastman help getting here!
And power of regeneration...
Doesn't look like that's it.
Perhaps once we clear the other four labyrinths,
we'll earn the ancient
magic capable of regeneration.
I get it.
What a pain. Guess we've gotta
head for those other labyrinths.
You hear that?
I'm heading for the other labyrinths.
That means our deal is done.
This is where we part.
You should be able to survive out here now.
Boss!
Please, let us travel alongside you.
We beseech you!
No.
We'll follow after you, then!
No, you should just keep training yourselves.
I might end up needing you
the next time I come here.
You hear that, everyone?
We're gonna get to training,
so we can be just what the boss wants!
Mother, am I a monster? Am I a beast?
A white shadow lurks in the
Sea of Trees, always shying away,
vanishing before you know it.
Is it a new type of monster
or a beast that has dwelled
within the forest since time immemorial?
Are those the kind of
stories you've been hearing?
With these big bunny ears that hear so well?
Do you not want to be a monster?
Of course I don't want to be a monster!
Why not?
Wh-Why not?
It doesn't feel good to be different.
It's scary, and lonely, and sad.
But you know something, Shea?
There are things you can do
because you're different.
Things you can do for someone else,
someone special to you.
Mother...
Let's talk about the future.
One day, you'll meet some wonderful
people outside the Sea of Trees.
Yes, I bet they'll be just like you.
Just like me?
There's no way there's
only one person just like you...
...in this big wide world.
Outside the Sea of Trees...
They're out there, I know it.
They really were, Mother...
Yue-san, do you remember our promise?
Don't "mn" me!
The promise to let me come with you!
Fine, I'll honor that promise.
Hajime, let's take this
worthless rabbit with us.
Were those the stakes of your duel?
Regretfully.
Please take me with!
You can come with me,
but I'm not gonna reciprocate anything.
The future isn't absolute! Don't you know that?
I believe that if I work hard enough,
I can change the future!
I always wonder, in the end...
When I couldn't change the future,
I wonder if I could have
done it if I'd worked harder.
That's why I don't want
to have any more regrets!
It'll be dangerous.
Then I'm glad I'm a monster!
That means I can come with you!
It'll be hard for you to
make a life in my hometown.
I don't care!
Is that all you have? Then I win!
Win?
It means my feelings won!
Whatever, weirdo.
"Good morning," "Good night,"
all those simple things
are so dreamlike and beloved to me
Because I finally met you
Everything is so special, thank you again
I didn't think I'd be lonely all by myself
That is, until you found me
I wasn't afraid of anything
That is, until I thought of a world without you
Can you believe it?
I miss you, I'm so fond of you
I love you, don't forget it
Shine bright like the first star in the night
and stay closer to me than anyone else
I'll never let you go
I'll never let go of that hand
Stay by my side and shine
ARIFURETA: From Commonplace
to World's Strongest