"The entrance to the labyrinth
is somewhere in Reisen Gorge."
Well, that's specific.
Y-Yeah, huh...
What's up? You feeling all right?
W-Well, I just need to go powder my nose.
You won't find any powder
like that down in this gorge.
Sheesh!
Well, it is on the way to the Gryuen,
so might as well hit it if we find it.
Hajime-san, Yue-san, I found something!
Come over here!
Look, right here!
Hi there, welcome!
Welcome to Miledi Reisen's
Super Duper Exciting Labyrinth!
Wh-Where's that voice coming from?
Who cares! We finally found
the entrance to the labyrinth!
Think it's real, Yue?
Mm-hmm.
Your reasoning?
I read it in Oscar's notes.
Okay, how do we get in?
Come on, it wouldn't...
No way...
Where'd she go?
She wet herself.
Please, don't look!
Did that scare ya?
Give you a scare, huh?
Looks like it's time for me to bring out
that thing you made me, Hajime-san!
Aww, sorry! These stone tablets
automatically regenerate after a while!
I'm betting Miledi Reisen wasn't
related to the Liberators at all.
She's just a scourge on humanity.
I wholeheartedly agree.
Wasn't sure if this would be much
of a labyrinth, but I guess it is.
Crimson Javelin!
Just as I thought,
we can't use projectile magic in here.
Well, that's annoying.
--Wha?!
--Let me handle this!
Hajime-san, Yue-san, now's your chance!
G-Got it.
Made it through!
How're ya doing?
This helping you clear your head?
Wow, look at how ooey-gooey she is!
Hey, how're you feeling right now, huh?
Miledi, that witch! Stop making fun of me!
I feel like we've seen
this room before. Don't you?
Definitely. Especially that thing.
Is this the first room we were in?
Looks like it.
Hey, how're you feeling right now?
What're you feeling?
Nia-san, when was
Ai-chan-sensei heading out again?
I think she said she was being
sent out sometime in the next few days.
That's not much time at all.
But maybe that's for the best.
If it were too far off, we'd all get too sad.
H-Hey, Yuuka-cchi, what's wrong?
Nothing, just thinking about how
I can't sit around here doing nothing.
So I'm gonna go with Ai-chan on her expedition.
Whoa, seriously, what's with you?
Calm down a sec.
I am calm, and this isn't a sudden decision.
I've been thinking a lot
about how I can't keep on like this.
Nagumo-kun died,
and I'm scared and confused...
But I feel like I have to do something.
Huh?
You guys have to feel the same, right?
You're serious?! You could die out there!
That guy actually died!
He did something stupid,
despite having no abilities, and now he's dead!
Sure, but that unskilled idiot saved my life.
No, he saved all of our lives.
W-Well...
And it's not like I'm
telling you all to come with me.
I just don't want to waste any time.
Hey, Yuuka, are you really going to go?
I don't have the guts to go with
Amanogawa-kun and the others,
so the least I could do
is help keep Ai-chan safe.
Well, that's an impressive door.
Think we've found Miledi's lair?
Mm.
Well, shit, then, let's celebrate.
'Cept I've got a real bad feeling
about these suits of armor.
It's okay. This will play out
to our expectations.
Does that mean... we're getting attacked?
Hey, Bedwetter Bunny.
Y-Yes, what is it?
You're tough. We'll vouch for that.
So get in there and have fun.
We'll save you if it gets hairy.
I take care of my pupils.
Yue-san, Hajime-san...
I'm going to beat the heck out of Miledi Reisen!
Carelessness will get you killed.
And three times the punishment.
Yue-san, I-I'm sorry!
Take this!
There's no end to them.
Everyone, jump!
Hey there! Nice to meet you!
Okay, hold on, you can't be serious.
It's huge...
I-It definitely feels like the boss...
It's everyone's beloved Miledi Reisen-chan!
Who are you? Miledi Reisen is
human and long dead, isn't she?
I read that in Oscar's notes.
Ooh, oh my gosh, are you the ones
who made it through O-chan's labyrinth?
I'm asking the questions here.
If you don't feel like answering,
then I'll just have to fight you.
We're only here to get
our hands on ancient magic.
I'm telling the truth!
I'm the real Miledi Reisen!
If you wanna know more,
you'd better answer my questions.
What's your end goal?
What do you want this ancient magic for?
My goal is to get home.
This insane god of yours
forced me over here, after all.
I see. That must have been tough.
We're looking for a form of ancient magic
that allows you to jump between worlds.
I'm not the least interested in putting
my life on the line for this world.
That's my answer. So, is the ancient magic
in this labyrinth rift-crossing magic?
Hmmm...
I'm not telling!
Then die!
Destroy the core! It's basically her heart!
Wow, you're pretty good, huh?
You think so?
Wh-When'd you get there?!
Take this!
Did it work?
Feel like it did, but...
I really hope that was the end of it!
Nah, that just gave me a little shiver!
If your artifact could
manifest its true power...
Azantium! Goddammit!
Get too ahead of yourself
and you'll regret it!
Dodge! Something's coming from above!
Here's what you get!
Now show me if you can survive this!
Dammit!
Grab onto me!
Okay!
Guess they couldn't handle it.
But I suppose if they couldn't handle this,
then they wouldn't be able
to beat those bastards.
I told you I've got no
interest in those bastards!
H-How?
I could tell you, but...
You sure you should be staring at me?
Force Rupture!
No matter how many times
you try, it won't work!
Both my arms can regenerate
and fix themselves!
I won't give you the time to do that!
That again?
That's not gonna be able
to get through my armor!
I know!
Freeze. Crystal Coffin!
Nice!
Eat this and die!
Looks like you didn't have enough force!
Down here, your magic won't be as strong.
Shea!
Finish her!
Nice going.
Shea, bend down for me.
Hajime won't pet your head,
but I thought that'd make you sad.
You did good.
Yue-san, I... I...
I was so scared!
I thought we were so done for!
Wait! You finally called me
by my actual name!
Hey, sorry to ruin this
nice mood you got going here...
I thought we destroyed the core!
I used the last of my power
to buy me a little time to talk to you.
I don't wanna hear anything about
these bastards you keep talking about.
It's less of a talk and more of a warning.
As you said, you were going to
get all of the Liberator's ancient magic
to achieve your end goal.
All right.
Good luck.
Well, isn't that sweet of you.
Sorry, those bastards are really bad guys...
So I just want you
to get a little bit used to it.
Whoa, hey. Why're you acting like
we're going to be fighting them?
Because you will.
Because you are who you are, one day,
you will become the God-Killer.
You're not making sense.
If they're gonna get in my way,
then sure, I might fight them, but...
That's fine.
Live your life the way you want.
The decision you make will
surely be for the better of this world...
It's over. Good work.
Thanks.
I hope you are able to live your
lives as freely as you choose to.
Hi there, short time no see!
It's me, Miledi-chan!
Wasn't that a nice speech back there?
D'aww, please, I'm not that talented
of an actor! I'm no terrifying girl!
Huh?
Huh whaa?
Tee-hee!
W-Wait, this body's really delicate!
I'll be in a real bad spot if it dies on me!
Calm down, please!
I-I'm sorry, okay?
So it was gravitic magic, huh?
Please use it well.
Oh, but you and the bunny girl
don't have the affinity for it.
You've gotta be a way higher level.
Oh, come on. You're just assuming that!
But blondie here's perfect for it.
If you train real hard, you should
be able to learn how to use it.
Mn.
There are other things you've got
to prove I got down here, right?
Like some useful artifacts
or rare materials? Give 'em here!
Y-Your lines and actions make you sound
like a plain ol' thief, you know that?!
To think that the very first people
down here would be this intense...
Fine, whatever! I'll force you to leave, then!
You bastard!
Bye, then! Good luck in the other labyrinths!
What're you looking at?
I'm definitely going
to break her apart one day.
Yue, Shea, you okay?
I'm okay.
Shea?
Hey, Shea?!
C'mon, wake up, hey!
You little--
Go drown again, you lust-crazed rabbit!
Didn't think she'd go for tongue
right after she got revived.
Welcome!
W-Welcome to the Masaka Inn.
I need a room. Add on a meal and a bath.
We'll take one room for the three of us.
A-A-All three of you in one room?!
No, we'll get two doubles.
I'll take one room with Hajime,
and Shea can be in the other.
What?! I don't want you
to exclude me from the group!
One room for all of us is fine!
I'll get distracted if you're there.
Distracted? What are you going to do?!
What do you mean, what?
Well, then you should
go have your own room!
I'm going to share a room with Hajime!
Oh, and then what?
A-And then...
I'm going to ask Hajime to take my virginity!
Huh? Huh whaa?
"Good morning," "Good night,"
all those simple things
are so dreamlike and beloved to me
Because I finally met you
Everything is so special, thank you again
I didn't think I'd be lonely all by myself
That is, until you found me
I wasn't afraid of anything
That is, until I thought of a world without you
Can you believe it?
I miss you, I'm so fond of you
I love you, don't forget it
Shine bright like the first star in the night
and stay closer to me than anyone else
I'll never let you go
I'll never let go of that hand
Stay by my side and shine
ARIFURETA: From Commonplace
to World's Strongest.