Shimizu's missing, huh?
We don't know where he's gone.
I hope he's all right...
I'm sure he's fine.
You're right.
You came back to us okay, after all.
Look, I haven't come back--
Sensei?
You're so nice to Aiko, Hajime.
Yeah, well, she's done a lot for me,
so it's the least I can do.
Yue?
I sit next to you on the way back.
You got it.
It's no fair if you get
it the whole way, Yue-san!
More importantly, why am I in the back?!
Cut it out, you useless bunny!
I'm trying to drive!
Uh, what are those?
They're human-locating automatons.
I call them Ornis.
They use a gravity stone to fly
and an induction stone to think.
They've got a peering stone inside
of them that's connected to my eye,
so I can see through them.
Whoa, what's this?
Find something already?
Is that a shield?
And a bag, too...
Looks new.
Whoa...
These tracks were made by
a large four-legged creature...
Stories say there's a huge monster
lurking beyond these two mountains.
But look at the crater left here...
I sense someone nearby.
Feels like it's human.
Does that mean someone's alive over here?!
They're somewhere behind that waterfall.
Yue.
Fissuring Wave, Wind Wall!
Bingo.
You Will?
Y-Yes, that's me!
I'm Will Cudeta!
I'm Hajime Nagumo.
The head of the Fuhren Adventurer's Guild
sent me to rescue you.
The monsters just didn't stop coming,
and they drove us into a corner...
Then, there was...
There was what?
The black dragon.
Dragon?
I-I don't deserve this!
Why is my worthless behind getting
rescued when everyone else had to die?!
I was so relieved to have survived...
I'm so glad, but...
Nagumo-kun!
What's wrong with being glad you're alive?
Wanting to live and being happy about
it is only human. Hell, it's necessary.
You're completely in the right to feel that way.
B-But I...
If you're worried about the guys
who died, then keep living on.
Drag your feet forward one
foot at a time and live on.
Live on...
Do that, and one day, you might feel like
there was a reason you survived today.
It's gotten pretty late.
Let's hurry back.
Th-There it is!
Is that it?
Retreat!
Dammit!
C'mere!
Hajime!
This guy's no ordinary monster!
Don't worry, I'll help from behind!
Heavenly Calamity!
This is it for you!
Huh?
Missed me!
Let's try that again!
Yue!
Fissuring wave--freeze!
W-We have to help!
R-Right!
Sensei! Get these guys out of here already!
B-But...
You're in the way!
Yue! Focus on protecting everyone!
I'll take him out!
Mm-hmm, got it.
If you don't want to die, follow me.
Are we just holding him back?
He's going after him again...
This is the first time something's ignored me!
Then I'm just gonna have to make sure it can't!
Ever been punched in the gut?
How'd it feel? Hurts, doesn't it?
Wh-Whoa...
Shea!
I'm on it!
Boy, this thing is tough!
I heard there were monsters out there
that were tougher than the damn mountains,
but how many mountains'
worth of strength is this?
Yue, Shea, you guys ever heard of the
expression "kick the dragon in its scaly ass"?
A dragon's only weak point
is where it doesn't have scales.
They say they're so well-defended,
when they fall asleep, nothing can wake them,
but if you attack them in one particular spot,
they'll wake up in a heartbeat.
Take it in the ass and die!
Noooo!
My rear! My precious behind!
Please, remove it!
Remove it from my rear, I beseech you!
So, you're a dragonborn?
Indeed! I am a member of
the esteemed dragonborn race!
Wild circumstances have led me here,
and while I will explain forsooth,
I must ask you to remove
that object from my behind!
Hell, no.
I'm begging you, please!
My mana is close to empty!
If I return to my original form in
this state, it could mean disaster!
Why are you here?
I will explain everything, just please,
relieve my behind of that object!
I have little magic remaining...
Yue asked you a question!
S-Stop!
Do not force it like that!
It is far too much for my rear,
far, far too much!
Dragonborn are supposedly all dead.
What's one doing attacking
adventurers out here, huh?
No, do not twist it around so!
I will tell all, just please, stop!
I was manipulated! I was no more than his tool!
He told me to kill
"that young man and his companions"!
Keep going.
I flew from my hidden village to
investigate the travelers from another world.
But on my journey to the nearby town,
I paused for a rest and
enjoyed a nap in the mountains.
Of course, I did so in my beastly form,
as there were monsters in the vicinity.
During my slumber, that man,
dressed in dark robes, appeared before me.
He likely used some kind of mind-control magic
to usurp my freedom from me.
His seemed to be an expert at his craft.
T'was impossible to resist such a spell
when it was cast over an entire day.
So you were in such a deep sleep that this guy
was able to spend all day casting this spell,
and you didn't even notice?
I can't believe you...
You're saying that because
you were "under his control,"
you couldn't help killing everyone?!
How are we supposed to even know
if you're telling the truth right now?!
You just fabricated that story
because you don't want us to kill you!
I swear, it is the truth!
Dragonborn are a proud kind;
we do not tarnish our name with lies!
No, you--
I don't think she's lying.
What proof do you have?
Dragonborn are noble and honest.
She swore on her pride.
That is how I know she is not lying.
B-But...
And...
I know what the eyes of a liar look like.
To think there is yet someone in this age
who knows of the dragonborn...
I'm the last surviving vampire.
Three centuries ago,
I was often told to look to the dragonborn
as models of royal demeanor.
Incredible! News from beyond had informed me
that the vampires had been eradicated,
but you are a princess of their kind!
It doesn't matter...
It doesn't matter,
because you still killed them!
I care not for the wars between our kinds.
However, I did take
innocent lives, that is true.
If you order me to atone for my actions,
then I will accept the punishment.
I only ask that you delay
that punishment a short while,
until that dangerous man
and his actions are stopped.
He is attempting to gather an army of monsters.
Will you give me the chance
to prevent a tragedy?
Nope, I don't care about what you want.
You've caused more
than enough trouble for me.
Make it up to me by dying.
Wait! Surely you wouldn't end this
conversation without answering my question?!
Please! I swear to you, I will repent!
You going to kill her?
She started the killing.
But she's not our enemy.
She wasn't in control.
Wouldn't killing her break
that rule that's so important to you?
I am terribly sorry to bother you.
For now, could you please remove
that hindrance from my rear?
What?
If you do not take action,
I will die, no matter what.
What's that mean?
Just try to imagine the
sight of a young woman,
her behind impaled with a thick, hard rod!
Do you think I could survive that?
My mana is running out.
I am not opposed to this new world
to which I have been introduced,
but I do not want to die in that manner!
For the love of all that is good,
please, remove it!
Ugh, fine.
S-Slowly, please!
I am not yet used to this sensation!
So rough!
This... This feeling!
Something is happening, yes,
something is swelling within me!
Yes! Yes! Just a little more!
You dumb lizard!
I asked you to be gentle,
yet you showed no mercy...
Never have I experienced this.
You saved me.
That discomfort in my behind still remains,
as does the overwhelming pain
I feel throughout...
Who knew pain was such a sweet sensation...
Hey!
My sincerest apologies.
My name is Tio Klarus,
a member of the Klarus clan of dragonborn.
This army of monsters is marching on Ur?!
Indeed. The dark-robed man intends
to use them to attack the town.
And that army numbers
well into the thousands.
N-No way!
This is more than thousands.
I'm counting five... no, 60,000.
Looks like they're already on the move.
This far out, it'll take them
two days to reach the town.
W-We have to warn them!
We'll evacuate everyone,
then call for help, then--
Hey...
Could my lord Hajime
do something about them?
L-Look. My job was to
get you back to Fuhren safely.
How am I supposed to fight
a war while keeping you safe?
Hey, Nagumo-kun? Did you get a look
at this robed man he was talking about?
Nope. I've been checking the ranks of
this army and haven't seen anything like him.
I see...
Could you look a bit more?
No.
Bye.
Nagumo-kun!
I just said my only job
was getting Will out safe.
The rest of you can stay here if you want,
but who's gonna go tell the town?
Well...
It is just as he says!
Informing the town should be our top priority!
And, given a day,
I will surely recover to full health!
Right.
Unfortunately, my mana reserves
are so dry, I can barely move.
You look at me like
I am the embodiment of filth!
Gulp.
Maybe I should've killed you after all.
Your words pierce my heart,
your fist strikes at my very core,
and your attacks violate
only my most lewd of areas!
My heart, body, and
soul fill with such pleasure!
What horrid treatment!
Such new sensations!
W-Wait up!
"Good morning," "Good night,"
all those simple things
are so dreamlike and beloved to me
Because I finally met you
Everything is so special, thank you again
I didn't think I'd be lonely all by myself
That is, until you found me
I wasn't afraid of anything
That is, until I thought of a world without you
Can you believe it?
I miss you, I'm so fond of you
I love you, don't forget it
Shine bright like the first star in the night
and stay closer to me than anyone else
I'll never let you go
I'll never let go of that hand
Stay by my side and shine
ARIFURETA: From Commonplace
to World's Strongest.