Hya-hoo!
Sheesh, Shea sounds like she's pretending
to be from the wastelands of the North Star.
Butt up! Rabbit time!
Ramming time!
Hya-hahaha!
Papa! Myu wants to do that, too!
There's no way we're letting you do that.
Aww!
Don't interrupt him.
I'll help you get on it later,
so sit tight till then.
Papa's worried about you, Myu.
That's why he's overprotective.
You're such the adoring parent!
This unexpected gentleness is quite exciting...
Big Sister Yue, Big Sister Tio's
doing that heavy breathing again.
She's sick, and there's no cure.
Don't pay her any mind.
Hya-hha!
Papa? What's wrong?
Nothing, I've just been here before.
It's only been four months,
but it feels like years.
Is the guild leader here?
Hmm? You adventurers?
I'm Loa Bawavis.
We've got a letter for you
from the Fuhren guild leader.
Thank you.
Huh. According to this letter...
...sounds like you went on quite the rampage.
That's just how things turned out.
Hard to believe newbies like you took out
an entire army of 60,000 troops in one day
and destroyed an evil organization
in the course of an afternoon,
but I've never known Ilwer to lie.
Urgent message!
There's a Demon in the labyrinth!
And who are you?
Do you know him, Hajime Nagumo?
Y-You're... Nagumo?
As always, you've got as
much presence as a ghost, Endo.
This is Hajime Nagumo, a gold-rank adventurer.
You're part of the Hero party, yes?
I-I'm Endo.
Hey!
A-Are you really Nagumo?
I-I mean, you look like
you've changed a whole lot,
just from your appearance and stuff...
Yeah, I crawled up from the pits of hell.
No duh I've changed a bit.
A bit? You're a totally different person!
But okay. I'm glad you're alive...
Wait, so that means you're tough
enough to survive down there, right?
Yeah, that's about right.
Please, Nagumo!
Come into the labyrinth with me!
You have to hurry, or they'll die!
Everyone's gonna die!
What's going on?
We've explored so much of the labyrinth,
so why haven't we encountered any monsters?
Maybe the ninetieth floor
just has no monsters on it?
Kouki, want to head back for now?
Shizuku?
I've got a bad feeling about
this place for some reason.
Maybe Captain Meld
knows something about that.
Still...
This is monster blood, right?
It's blending in with the color
of the ground, so it's hard to tell...
But there's a lot...
And it's fresh.
This must mean there's an even
more powerful monster around here.
And that monster attacked another monster?
Not only that, but it's hidden its tracks.
If there are only tracks in this area, that
means it didn't have time to cover them up...
That, or...
It's a trap.
A demon?
You there, wearing the stupidly
shiny armor, you're a hero, yeah?
Wanna join up with us?
Wh-What? What're you talking about?
I'm asking you to join us.
I refuse!
You could join up with
all your friends, you know.
My answer's not changing!
You know...
One of your friends took us up on our offer.
You won't fool me!
None of us would have done that!
Are you sure about that?
Fine, then. If you won't accept,
then I have no use for you.
I'll let the monster have you.
Shizuku! Suzu!
Bathe in protective light!
Turning tide and heavens, Divine Intervention!
Get away from Shizuku!
I ain't lettin' you!
Engulf mine enemies, O crimson mother!
Reckless Blaze!
What's with these things?!
Where'd they come from?!
W-Watch out, everyone!
No way...
No!
Let the light of protection
grow tenfold, restored by my will!
You think I'm weak?!
Divine Intervention!
Wh-Why the hell are these monsters so strong?!
Hiyama-kun!
I'm gonna cut through them!
You keep the others safe!
Y-You got it, Yaegashi!
Wha?!
She can heal them?!
They're on a totally different level than
all the other monsters we've encountered!
What should we do, Yaegashi-san?
Endo-kun...
There's something I have to ask of you
and your particular abilities.
Send a message to Captain Meld.
Because you're an Assassin,
you should be able to sneak out
without them noticing you and get to Meld.
Me?!
I can't do this myself.
I'll get it to him, I swear!
I swear!
I swear...
And what the hell is with this girl?!
Papa!
Why the hell are you taking things out
on my daughter, you little prick? Huh?
I'll kill you!
Hajime's totally her Papa now.
He didn't even think twice
when he called her his daughter!
But will he be able
to let his lovely daughter go?
That was scary, huh?
What'll it be, Hero?
At this rate, you're done for.
I won't give in, and I'll prove that to you!
Limit Break!
O light, fill my will, sharp as a blade's edge,
and slice through my enemies!
Blinding Edge!
By mine eye, all that is known
to my enemy shall be shut closed.
All that will remain is their demise,
a cold graven image.
Let my enemies be crushed
and returned to the earth!
Crashing Gaol!
Taniguchi, stop her!
G-Got it!
Enemies of God mayst
not tread upon His holy ground!
Herem!
Suzu!
Protect Suzu!
Taniguchi!
Heed me, O wind!
Blustering Blast!
I-It can't be!
Suzu-chan!
Kouki!
Dammit!
Let's retreat!
They killed one of our own,
and we're just gonna run?!
Calm down!
I hurried to Captain Meld
to tell him about the demon.
The Captain is protecting a
teleportation circle to the 70th floor!
Captain! It's me!
Whoa, Kosuke!
Where are the others?!
The others, they're...!
Don't cry, Kosuke.
You did what only you could do.
Thank you for delivering the message.
Yaegashi said they'd
come back on their own, but...
But I'm gonna go back to them!
N-No, it noticed me?!
How much longer are you
gonna keep embarrassing yourself?!
Go on already!
Huh?!
Don't space out!
Tell the people up above about the demon!
B-But what about you, Captain?!
Destroy the circle on the other side!
We'll protect it with our lives!
B-But...
That's this coward's final wish!
Survive, Kosuke!
I'll show you the strength of the
Heilich Kingdom Knight's resolve!
He wanted me to survive...
He did it for me, he...
Here.
Th-Thank you.
You owe me big time.
H-Hey!
Maybe we should just do as she says already?
What're you saying?!
I-I also think we should do as she says!
Not you too, Eri!
I just don't want all of us to die!
Don't trust that demon!
Look, if we keep trying to run away,
how many of us are gonna survive this?
Just accept the reality
of our situation already!
If we want us all to survive,
we have to do as she says...
Just think about surviving...
Meld-san!
From the very beginning, this was our war.
I'm sorry...
Meld-san!
No, Kouki!
If you use Limit Break now,
your body won't be able to take it!
A demon, huh?
Hajime Nagumo, if what Ilwer says is true,
then I've got a request for you.
You want me to rescue the heroes, is that it?
Nagumo!
They're your friends!
You'll go save them, of course you will, right?
Don't go assuming they're my friends.
Huh?
I'll give it to you straight.
To me, the lot of you are no more than
strangers who happen to share my homeworld,
and nothing more.
Wha?!
How dare you do that to Meld-san!
Die!
I'm impressed. Have you finally
gotten it into your thick skull now?
You're trying to kill someone.
I-I'm...
You really have no self-awareness, do you, boy?
We are at war!
Kouki!
Please, Nagumo, save them...
Save all of them...
I'm going to protect you, Nagumo-kun.
You gave me a chance when you
rescued me, so I'm not gonna waste it!
So why did you have to kill him?!
My papa's strong,
so he can save them for sure!
Are you sure you don't want to save them?
What will you do, Master?
Do what you want, Hajime.
I'll follow you no matter what.
You guys...
I'm sorry, I can't...
I don't have much mana left...
You're not like the other heroes.
You actually came prepared to kill.
Kouki didn't have that,
and it held our party back.
But I'll make up for it!
Shizuku-chan?!
I really don't like being all on my own!
Shizuku-chan!
Go back, Kaori! You can't stay here!
It doesn't matter where I go.
If it doesn't matter, then I want
to be by your side, Shizuku-chan...
Kaori...
I'm sorry, I couldn't keep
my promise, Nagumo-kun!
What happened?
You two're still good friends, huh?
Hajime-kun!
"Good morning," "Good night,"
all those simple things
are so dreamlike and beloved to me
Because I finally met you
Everything is so special, thank you again
I didn't think I'd be lonely all by myself
That is, until you found me
I wasn't afraid of anything
That is, until I thought of a world without you
Can you believe it?
I miss you, I'm so fond of you
I love you, don't forget it
Shine bright like the first star in the night
and stay closer to me than anyone else
I'll never let you go
I'll never let go of that hand
Stay by my side and shine
Arifureta: From Commonplace
to World's Strongest