Ashinoko Skyline
And so, the 86 arrives at the gate
with 15 seconds to go.
Up goes the board.
Ten seconds to go.
Five. Four. Three. Two. One.
Ashinoko Skyline
And he shoots away like he's been launched!
Katagiri Kanata has begun
his Ashinoko GT run!
Aren't you gonna watch, Mom?
I'll pass. Watching Kana-chan
race is bad for my heart.
It's nowhere near as
dangerous as you think, dear.
Especially considering
how talented Kanata-kun is.
Dad, don't you think it's about time
you stopped using "kun" for Kanata?
You're the only one in the house
who's so formal with him.
Right? Tell him to cut it out.
Ah, it's fine.
The truth is, as a gearhead
and motor racing fan,
I respect Kanata-kun too much
to address him so casually.
Here at Ashinoko, said to be
the toughest course in MFG,
Katagiri Kanata's unleashing
all of his technical prowess!
The White Reaper
Descends
Won't be much longer now.
Bit by bit, the scenery's
starting to turn white.
Volcanic ash from Mount Fuji
gets carried by the wind,
and for some reason,
clings to that area.
All that particulate gets between the road
and the tires, making it real easy to slip.
They call it the "Descent of the White Reaper,"
also known as the Slip Trap.
No matter how much they try to clean it up,
it always seems to accumulate.
It's one of the seven wonders of MFG.
Booth to Kanata.
You're about to enter the death zone.
You'll need to ease up. Over.
Roger.
I can feel the mu of
the road starting to drop.
I'll alter my driving to suit. Over.
What does he mean?
That wasn't natural slippage.
He swung the back end
into the corner on purpose.
Are you telling me...
Hey, Ogata. What's up
with the 86's traction control?
That looked nuts. You sure it's working?
You've got it wrong.
Kanata asked me to switch it off.
Say what?
So he's drifting like that on purpose?
Is he seriously trying to rally
his way through the death zone?
Would you look at that?
The attention flag the 86 lost on
entering the death zone has returned!
He got an attention flag by drifting?
I've been doing this for three years
and never managed that.
As breathtaking as this drifting may be,
perhaps more notably,
I can't recall anyone ever getting an
attention flag inside Ashinoko's death zone.
The computer at HQ has given
this drifting tactic its seal of approval!
He's shifting the car's weight
and swinging the rear out
in order to compose any line he wants
using minimum steering angle.
That's definitely Fujiwara Takumi's
zero-counter steer drift.
It's as if Project D's invincible downhill ace
has appeared on the Ashinoko course.
So he enters the corner with enough yaw
to prevent unpredictable understeer...
and he's able to take such an aggressive line
because he's 100% sure he won't oversteer?
I just can't believe that way's
actually faster, though.
No, it definitely is. Check it out, Shun.
And for a second time,
he's making huge gains in the death zone!
He's up to 10th!
Katagiri Kanata is not be trifled with!
The White Reaper that is the bane
of every MFG driver's existence,
is smiling down angelically upon
this young man for some reason!
I can feel the grip normalizing.
I'll be out of the death zone soon.
The 86 is exiting the Slip Trap!
And as its tires regain their grip,
they reach their speed rating once more.
He's now on a downhill section from
Kojiri Pass junction to the floodgates.
And the 86 is zipping along
like a fish through water!
Single digits? Are you kidding me?
Am I gonna get beaten by Kanata
in his second freaking race?
Car 86 has risen from 16th place
in the opener to a qualifying spot!
Ninth place? Seriously?
To perform like this against
the best racers in the Godly Fifteen...
It just doesn't make sense.
He rounds the Port Kojiri hairpin
in a prospective ninth place!
This really is unbelievable!
Even though it has likely had updates,
the 86 still only has a 2-liter NA engine.
So how is it achieving this kind of pace?
What does he mean by a "2-liter NA," Dad?
Well, you see...
It's an engine that produces
2,000 CCs of displacement.
NA stands for "naturally aspirated,"
which means it doesn't
have a turbocharger.
What difference does a "turbo" make?
It basically gives you two to three times
the amount of displacement force.
So you're saying Kanata's car
is way down on power?
Well, more or less, yes.
So how's he running
so high up the leaderboard?
Is he using some Harry Potter
magic or something?
Hm. That's not a bad way of putting it.
The 86 rhythmically cuts through
the woods on Ashinoko's eastern coast.
This section piles on the
lateral Gs in both directions,
requiring precise pedal work
to get you through.
And he's maintaining his position.
But how secure is the margin
the 86 built up in the death zone,
given its lack of power?
Katagiri Kanata's
cornering wizardry continues!
He's still not pulling out all the stops yet.
MFG's courses are all really distinct,
putting different demands on
the suspension in each instance.
I used all the know-how I've built up over
my career to fine-tune the 86's underbody.
Hell, you could practically
call it an Ashinoko Custom.
The chance to shake up MFG, which was built
on the bones of the old Gunma street scene...
What more could an old
Kanagawa racer like me ask for?
I think one of the traits
of Kanata's driving
is cornering in a way that draws out
the lateral Gs for as long as possible.
It's nothing like the
V-shaped lines the rest of us use.
He uses his tires in
a completely different way.
And the changes made to the 86's
suspension perfectly fit his style.
Customized by the suspension
wizard himself, Okuyama Hiroya.
Can it really produce results like this?
The 86 leaves Sector 2
and enters Sector 3.
It's all downhill from here to the lakeside.
And he's now in seventh!
Just how far up the
leaderboard can he climb?
It feels like Katagiri Kanata
has had an attention flag on him
longer than course record
holder, Sawatari Koki!
The attention flag gets put on
good drivers by a computer, right, Dad?
That's right.
Does that make sense, though?
The commentary makes it sound like Kanata's
doing better in seventh than the guy in first.
Well, the thing about that is...
the computer system's designed to make
a judgment based purely on technique.
So it doesn't always match
what the stopwatch says.
In racing, even the most talented
driver in the world isn't enough
to be competitive on their own.
The driver's technique and the car's strengths
both need to excel in order to win.
Do you understand?
I think I do, yeah.
But that's not fair. I feel bad for Kanata.
It's full throttle down Relay Straight,
then it's a 2 km long hill climb
up to the finish line!
Given how underpowered it is,
this may be the toughest
test for the Toyota 86.
This is the longest, harshest climb
on the Ashinoko course.
It's bad news for Kanata and the 86.
The fact that it's so close to
the finish line only makes it worse.
During the actual race, he'll be at
a disadvantage in any battles to the line.
He lost a place!
No matter how great he is in the corners,
there's nothing he can do about this.
In all the technical sections,
he can match or even outperform
the rest of the Godly Fifteen.
But here, the cars with more horsepower
will gradually leave him behind.
Hang in there, Kanata!
You've gotta hold onto eighth!
You're almost at the finish line!
MF Ghost
MF Ghost.
The 86 squeezes out its last bit of
acceleration as it presses forward!
The finish line's within sight!
Eighth! He comes home
in a prospective eighth place!
And with this, Katagiri Kanata's driving
ability can no longer be doubted by anyone!
Eighth place is still impressive, right?
You're unbelievable!
That was awesome, man.
Where'd you learn to drift like that?
My teacher at the academy taught me.
He was a drifting master.
His technique was honestly godlike.
What I can do is child's play by comparison.
They teach drifting at
overseas racing schools?
No. It wasn't part of the regular curriculum.
These were special after-class lessons.
He used to take me to
rally courses on the weekend
with cars that had soft suspension,
so that I could get a knack for
weight shifting on roads with low mu.
Sometimes, I'd sit in the passenger seat.
Sometimes, he would, and give me advice.
We'd drive around like that
whenever there was no class.
I believe that's why I don't have
much trouble with MFG's street courses.
We would sit in a field for lunch
and laugh ourselves silly over nonsense.
It really was a lot of fun.
There weren't many half-Japanese
students at the academy,
and I think my broken Japanese
caught his attention.
I never knew my father,
and at times, my teacher felt like one.
I see.
Really brings a tear to your eye.
This car has enough power to outperform
every other vehicle in this event.
That is not in question.
And I'm fully aware that the same
can't be said about me personally.
But while you lose certain things
with age, you gain others.
It's those things I will have to use to fight.
Racing is the sum of all parts.
And it'll be a cold day in hell before
I let snot-nosed brats make a fool of me!
Well, we can be pretty sure that
Kanata's qualified for the race now.
How about we go celebrate? My treat.
You guys have gotta be hungry.
Bravo! More organ meat?
You really love your offal,
don't ya? Just follow me.
Here you go. Your ten-don.
Excellent! Japanese tempura!
This place is famous.
Everyone in Odawara knows about it.
Try the aji sushi, too. It's good.
I think Japan might have the biggest variety
of seafood of any country in the world.
Makes sense, considering
it's an island with ocean on all sides.
It has that in common with England, but...
In terms of scale, our seafood
culture simply doesn't compare.
This tempura bowl is incredible!
It's touched something inside me!
I like how your bowl dishes all have "don"
at the end, like ten-don and gyu-don.
Hey, you live near Enoshima, don't ya?
You oughta try the shirasu-don.
You'll be shocked how good it is,
despite its simplicity.
Shirasu-don?
Ninth place.
But Kanata will probably be fine.
Hey, Kanata.
How late are you working today?
I've got an early shift, so only until three.
That's around when I'm headed into Kamakura.
Let's meet up and do some more searching.
Okay.
I'd also like to go try shirasu-don.
Care to join me, Ren?
Sure! I'll let Mom know we'll be eating out.
Thank you, Ren. I'm looking forward to it.
I am, too.
I've got a date with Kanata!
It's the final day of qualifying
for the Lake Ashinoko GT.
And it's time for the
top-billed driver to set off.
Let's all keep our eyes on this one.
For the man said to be the fastest in MFG
history, Michael Beckenbauer, is on the move!
The 12 flashes through the death zone.
He's a mere two-tenths down
on first-placed Sawatari Koki,
making him provisional second!
I heard that people have been raving about
the lunatic who drifted through every turn.
But against suspension crafted
by the gifted test drivers at Porsche,
his efforts will amount to nothing!
The 12 car traces a graceful line.
There's no hint of disorder!
It's nothing but smooth speed!
Kamakura Station
And yet, this seems odd.
The pace he's setting...
What are we seeing here, folks?
He seems to be deliberately
maintaining a pace
that keeps him two-tenths
behind the course record.
Is it a coincidence or a demonstration?
What is this strange sensation I'm feeling?
This is incredible, Michael.
It's playing out just like you said.
You were two-tenths behind
at the last checkpoint.
It's almost like
you're directly behind Car 4.
That's because I am.
He might not actually be here,
but I can see the 4's tail.
I'm letting him be my pacemaker.
I'll save top gear for
the climb in the last 2 km.
I'll take it easy until then.
There's no need to try any harder.
That said, I don't intend on letting
anyone else take the top time.
That was the only rule I set for myself.
I can almost see the sparks
flying between them.
It's a real clash of egos out there.
I didn't think we'd see a fight for pole
between a Cayman and an Alpine.
Yeah. The status quo from the days of
the "rich man's regulation" is falling apart.
Out of Sector 1 and into Sector 2!
He's now three-tenths behind the 4!
The invisible nose-to-tail conflict continues!
So that's his plan? Not exactly a bold one.
That's fine, I guess. He can have pole.
But I look forward to rubbing that
stuck-up nose of his into the dirt in the race.
I'm not scared of Beckenbauer.
He's merely well-rounded,
and that's all he'll ever be.
The gap of three-tenths is still intact!
I've got goosebumps at this point, folks!
We're seeing a ghostly dogfight
between Cars 4 and 12!
Gotta be honest,
Kanata Rivington is far scarier.
That guy's got no limiter.
He's out there driving with a 2-liter NA
and an old-fashioned three-pedal system.
And he gets ninth in a car like that?
How has no one else
realized how insane that is?
Sorry! Were you waiting long, Ko-kun?
I tried to hurry, but it just didn't work out.
And now, the Relay Straight!
It's only a 2.5-liter engine, but the 7-speed PDK
powertrain gives it a remarkable top speed!
Shibuya gets so crowded on Sunday.
Where should we go?
Isn't that obvious?
Lunch and karaoke can wait.
I saw that coming.
That's why I wore cute underwear.
The final two klicks is a hill climb!
The Cayman's superior displacement
is giving it a clear edge!
Will we see Beckenbauer
shift up a gear late in the lap?
And there's the attention flag!
The gap between him and
Car 4 is shrinking to nothing!
Goodbye, Sawatari. I'm moving on ahead.
And there he goes!
For the first time in his run,
he's ahead of the 4!
He's finally overcome him! Beckenbauer
moves up into provisional first place!
And just like that,
he's got a one-second lead!
It was never in doubt! This German-made
cyborg has proven his mettle!
Michael Beckenbauer
takes pole with authority.
But Sawatari Koki in second had previously
set a fantastic new course record!
And amid this clash of the titans is
Katagiri Kanata, who secured tenth.
Kamakura Station
This new class of "speed stars" is
looking to upset the hierarchy in MFG!
Things are bubbling up nicely
heading into the Lake Ashinoko GT race!
Next Time, Turn 14: The 4x4 Attack.