So he's drifting like that on purpose?
Is he seriously trying to rally
his way through the death zone?
Would you look at that?
The attention flag the 86 lost on
entering the death zone has returned!
That's definitely Fujiwara Takumi's
zero-counter steer drift.
It's as if Project D's invincible downhill ace
has appeared on the Ashinoko course.
I heard that people have been raving about
the lunatic who drifted through every turn.
But against suspension crafted
by the gifted test drivers at Porsche,
his efforts will amount to nothing!
And now, the Relay Straight!
It's only a 2.5-liter engine, but the 7-speed PDK
powertrain gives it a remarkable top speed!
It was never in doubt! This German-made
cyborg has proven his mettle!
Michael Beckenbauer
takes pole with authority.
But Sawatari Koki in second had previously
set a fantastic new course record!
And amid this clash of the titans is
Katagiri Kanata, who secured tenth.
Kamakura Station
This new class of "speed stars" is
looking to upset the hierarchy in MFG!
Things are bubbling up nicely
heading into the Lake Ashinoko GT race!
And Wakana was just being so yabai.
Sorry. I still don't quite get
when it's appropriate to use "yabai."
Really?
Hm, let's see... You can use it to describe
some really good music, for example.
Or when the food at a place you've never
been to is so good, it surprises you.
Oh, I get it.
Other than that... Lemme think...
You can use it when someone's
fashion sense is kinda gross.
Or when you get a bad score on a test.
But those examples are the
total opposite of the last two...
I think that word might be a bit
too complicated for me to master.
I want to ask you something, Ren.
What's up?
I'll be getting my pay
from my part-time job soon.
Oh, payday, huh?
I'd like to use that money to repay
the Saionji family for their hospitality
by taking you all out for dinner.
You can't do that.
You worked hard for that money,
so you should spend it on yourself.
No. I decided on it a while ago.
I wanted to ask you to help me
choose what restaurant to go to.
Are there any places your family
really likes and visits a lot?
Kanata, you're such a sweetheart.
Sure. It's the least I can do.
I bet Mom and Dad will be thrilled, too.
I really hope they will be.
It's a surprise, though, so try to
keep it a secret until the day itself.
Fish
Here you go.
Your plain shirasu-don.
Even better than I expected.
How is it usually eaten?
I recommend adding
a little bit of soy sauce.
Try it with some rice. It's really good.
Time to eat.
Close your eyes and... go.
It's surprisingly good.
Looking at it, I never would've
imagined it'd taste so good.
Right? Pretty "yabai," huh?
Very "yabai."
By the way, Ren, what exactly is "shirasu"?
Well, shirasu's just shirasu.
Little fish, basically.
Are they baby fish? Or full-grown ones?
Uh, that, I don't know.
Let me look it up.
"Shirasu" is actually a generic term for
juvenile whitefish with no body pigment.
That mostly means sardines,
but also includes pacific herring and eel.
Wow.
Please enjoy.
Thank you so much.
I had no idea.
That was pretty educational.
I'm sure of it! That's MFG's
super rookie, Katagiri Kanata!
And he's eating at my place! This is awesome!
Thanks for the food.
Thank you for coming.
We'd love to see you here again. And...
Good luck in the Ashinoko GT.
So he knew who you were.
That's never happened before.
I'm a bit shaken up.
I told you, didn't I?
There's 30 million people around
the world who know you now.
Maybe you should wear sunglasses to hide
your face like celebrities do overseas.
That wouldn't be very cool.
MF Ghost
The 4x4 Attack
First and second set
new course records, huh?
It's incredible. And they both beat
the old record by quite some way.
What about the unofficial
"phantom" course record?
Comparing with that lap time,
they still slightly improved on it.
I see.
So someone managed to beat Keisuke's
all-out "super lap" in our fourth season, huh?
Incidentally, what's the
weather forecast for race day?
Looks like a pretty high chance of rain.
Oh, good grief. Racing in the rain is
always a mess. We'd better be ready.
Yes, sir.
Speaking of rain...
The downhill ace of Project D was a pro
at dealing with wet conditions.
I guess we'll get to see if the same
is true of his apprentice.
Ugh, racing in the rain?
Front-engine, rear-wheel-drive
cars and rain don't mix.
We're gonna be hugely handicapped up
against the 4x4s and mid-engine cars.
The new suspension looked
really promising in qualifying, too.
It's not fair!
Oh, that reminds me.
I'd better give Okuyama-san a call.
Best to get some advice on
the best setup for rainy conditions.
I wonder what'll happen if it rains tomorrow.
Will I have to do the mini-concert and
the leaderboard updates while soaked?
This sucks.
Good afternoon to the 30.12 million
MFG fans all around the world.
I am Tanaka Yoji, your commentator.
The June rains are gracefully
rippling the surface of Ashinoko Lake.
It seems MFG's second round, the Ashinoko GT,
will be a rain-soaked battle.
On guest commentary today, we have
Ikeda Ryuji, the chairman of Zero Academy.
Hello.
As well as serving as a city councilor
for his hometown of Odawara,
he actively works with youths to improve
their health and wellbeing through motorsport.
You can also often
find him clad in vestments,
serving as head priest in
his family's Buddhist temple.
A hat-trick of professions for
this modern-day Renaissance man.
Ikeda-san, thank you for joining us.
It's a pleasure to be here.
Okay. The dampers are all set.
It wasn't raining further down
the mountain, but it is up here.
That's Hakone for you. The weather's always
different between the peaks and the base.
You amuse me, Ogata-san.
Why do you look so worried?
What do you mean, man?
This is about as serious as it gets.
The stress is turning my stomach.
Racing on public roads
in the wet is madness.
I'd honestly rather they
just cancel the whole thing.
I get the feeling pretty much
everyone involved feels the same way.
And considering you're in
a front-engine, rear-wheel-drive car,
it's gonna be especially
squirrelly on the wet roads.
Ogata-san, the rain plays fair.
It falls the same on all 15 cars.
I don't see it as a problem.
If anything, rain is often a help to me.
The Angels wrap up their rain-soaked
performance and rush to the tent.
The sight of them singing while soaked
sure left a different impression than usual.
I get the feeling fans of the Angels will
preserve the video of that one for a long time.
I get workers' comp
if I get sick from this, right?
Oh, and it looks like the
drivers' meeting has concluded,
and they're all making
their way to their vehicles.
Good luck, Aiba-senpai.
Yeah. You, too.
Ogata here. Can you hear me okay?
Loud and clear.
I left a dry towel on the passenger's seat.
Make sure to wipe your soles.
If they're wet, it'll change
the feel of the pedals. Over.
Roger.
It's now just five minutes
until the scheduled start time.
Here's a question, Ikeda-san:
What does a driver have to
keep in mind going into a wet race?
In a word, they need patience.
In the wet, the way the tires react on public
roads can change from moment to moment,
so you need to constantly evaluate your grip
while grappling with the competition.
Not only is your visibility limited
by the spray from the cars in front,
you're also in a persistent
tug of war with your car.
And as the difficulties mount up,
it becomes a question of maintaining
a calm, rational state of mind.
Getting overly aggressive in a race
like this won't yield results.
I see. It sounds like this race will
prove to be a real mental challenge.
Exactly.
These 15 drivers in their cockpits
waiting for the signal to go
will face a level of pressure
that's incomparable to a normal race.
The Angels are all lined up.
One minute to go.
The 12 car in pole position is being
guided slowly out of the gate by a drone.
Then comes Sawatari in the 4,
Ishigami in the 1 car, and Akaba in the 2 car.
Maezono's next in Car 13, followed by
Oishi in the 3 car, then Taylor in the 8.
After that, it's Sakamoto in the 5,
Otani in the 7 car, and Katagiri in the 86.
Good luck, Kanata.
All I can really do is pray for you.
I have to admit...
When Kanata's in serious mode,
he's so cool, time seems to stop.
He never looks like that at home.
Bringing up the rear,
the 23 passes through the gate...
And the drones all signal
for the race to begin!
MF Ghost
MF Ghost.
And the order is suddenly shuffled!
The spray from the intense rain is
making it hard to tell what's going on!
With their superior traction, three 4x4 cars
seem to have won the dash away from the line!
Oishi in the 3 car
overtakes Maezono in the 13.
And Sakamoto in the 5
sails past Taylor in the 8 car.
At the back, Aiba in the 10 car
pulls ahead of Kitahara in the 18!
The handicap system in the regulations
Ryo Takahashi came up with
is generally believed to be
pretty harsh on 4x4 cars in the dry.
But when moisture's involved,
this level of traction becomes an advantage.
I'm gonna establish a real lead this time.
Moments like this are
what 4x4 drive is meant for!
Ashinoko Skyline
There's been a change of position.
Moe-chan, Mami-chan,
if you'd do the honors.
What? Already? But they only just started.
I'll hold the umbrella for you
so you don't get wet.
Hang on a sec.
My butt's not ready.
Beckenbauer leads the way!
And Sawatari in the 4
is sticking to his bumper!
The finish line awaits at the end
of three laps totaling 75.9km,
with 15 drivers kicking up
a fine mist in their wake!
I love the rain. All the power
in the world won't help you in it.
It's like being forced to lay down your
weapons and duke it out with your fists.
Who's really the fastest here?
It's time to clear that up.
Don't take me lightly, Sawatari.
I have absolute confidence in
my ability to deal with wet roads.
There isn't a single factor that will
make me lose to a Japanese driver.
I might've lost out to that 4x4 Huracán
in the dash away from the line,
but that won't matter
once I've picked up enough speed.
I've got the Lambo in front of me,
and the Ferrari in front of that.
I'm in a position to take on the
Italian manufacturers that rule the roost.
I'm gonna show 'em
what a Honda is capable of!
Another question for you, Ikeda-san:
How do you suppose this rain will affect
the road conditions in the death zone?
I expect it'll be horrendous there.
The rain will prevent
any new ash from building up,
but anything already on the road will turn
into a free-flowing sludge so slippery,
the drivers will be severely limited by it.
I'd say the death zone will require the
utmost caution, especially on this first lap.
The column of spray makes its way
through Ashinoko Skyline.
The leading group
plunges into the slip trap!
Battling understeer,
the 3 car ends up going wide!
The 13 moves ahead
like it slid right past him!
Holy crap!
I thought I was being careful,
but I still ended up sliding that much?
That was some pretty
sloppy steering, Oishi.
It just goes to show that four-wheel drive
is no help when going into a corner.
He's not drifting like
he was in qualifying, huh?
Seems like he's pretty fast
even without doing that.
He's got a big bag of tricks
for such a young guy.
But me and my car are no slouches
when it comes to cornering, either.
Why don't you show me exactly
how a "super rookie" races?
I'm sliding all over the place.
It's so damn slippery!
Oh, crap, this is so much fun.
I love this sorta thing!
While their tires scrabble for grip
on the death zone's asphalt,
the chosen 15 are proving their mettle
by fearlessly keeping their foot on the gas.
The 12 and the 4 are extending their lead!
The 1 car can't stay with them!
The Godly Fifteen are stretching out and
breaking up into a number of smaller groups.
Ikeda-san, has anything caught
your attention about the race so far?
I think so.
Personally, I'm paying close attention
to the 86 in the middle of the pack.
It's the one car that didn't alter its
driving style on entering the death zone.
The way it is so steady
through this section is almost eerie.
Katagiri Kanata actually rallied his way
through the death zone in qualifying,
setting a new record for that sector.
Compared to that, he's now demonstrating
a completely different kind of control.
That's just it.
The way he's driving seems to scream,
"The race has only just begun,"
and I find that more than a bit unsettling.
The leading group roars past
the Kojiri Pass junction,
and the course turns downhill from here.
They can't afford a moment's
carelessness from here on.
A single mistake can cost you your life
when racing downhill in the rain.
We invested a lot in this GTR,
but all this rain is
making it a handicap.
The traction control and
stability control keep butting in.
I can't believe a 2-liter NA
is pushing me this hard.
But in these conditions, even someone
who's good at zipping downhill
can't fight physics
and take the corners any faster.
If I keep my line tight
into and around each corner,
he'll be forced to sit
behind me, feeling frustrated.
Hey now. What the hell is he planning to do?
Around the outside?
Don't screw with me.
I don't have the grip.
The roads are so wet...
So how is he going so fast?
It's impossible!
Next time, Turn 15:
The Relay Straight Yin-Yang.