Morning.
Good morning.
You couldn't sleep?
Not a single wink.
Are you saying it's my fault?
Mai-san is too audacious.
How can you sleep so soundly?
I've been to many places for filming
since I was little.
Besides, Sakuta sleeping next to me
is like nothing.
That's good to hear.
I'll have to pull all sorts of pranks on you
the next opportunity I get.
Like you'd have the guts to do that.
We're heading back to Fujisawa,
then to school in the afternoon, right?
I'll get ready, so step outside for a bit.
It's the next morning,
but like before, Mai-san can't be seen
by anyone other than me.
#3 - The World Without You
What's he up to?
When I asked him yesterday,
he said he's totally fine.
It's just like normal.
So are they the ones who can't see you,
or are you actually invisible?
I'll check my classroom.
Azusagawa.
I have bad news.
It looks like everyone other than us
have forgotten about Sakurajima-senpai.
At the least, Kunimi didn't remember.
Really?
Oh, is that so?
Yesterday's—
Hey, you know who
Sakurajima-senpai is, right?
Huh? Sakura?
A third year, Mai Sakurajima-senpai.
Hold on, Tomoe.
Why is the Hospitalization Senpai...
Huh? I don't get it.
Sakura-what-senpai?
Let's go.
Why have you forgotten?
I'm talking about the celebrity,
Sakurajima-senpai!
Hey... Hey!
There's one possible reason...
Did you sleep last night?
Not a wink.
I didn't get one, either.
It may only be a result,
but there may be a reason in that.
By "that" do you mean how we didn't sleep?
Do you recall our previous chat
about measurement theory?
Schrödinger's Cat...
To be honest, I thought it was ridiculous.
But when it's presented before my eyes like this,
I get a chill up my spine.
What does? Adolescence Syndrome?
No...
The fact that she was treated
like the atmosphere
before something like
Adolescence Syndrome kicked in.
I, myself, took hints,
and accepted the condition that everyone
was unconsciously ignoring Sakurajima-senpai.
On the other hand, you could do that
because you didn't have any doubts.
But that's exactly why I think our clue
is this atmosphere we have at our school.
Sakurajima isn't being observed by anyone
at school, so her existence hasn't been confirmed.
For her, this school is the same as that box,
with her as the cat inside.
If recognition and observation are the keys,
then sleep, where consciousness is inoperative,
acts as the catalyst for memory loss.
I'm content with that train of thought.
In other words, that means...
If I had fallen asleep last night,
by now I'd also be...
Is something wrong?
No...
You have work today, right?
But...
You need to take care of things like that.
I'll be fine.
Well then, see you tomorrow.
Nobody is looking at Mai-san...
Mai-san isn't being observed by anyone,
so her existence hasn't been confirmed.
So she's disappearing.
Because if nobody recognizes you,
it's the same as not existing in this world.
But, if you're saying that
the school is where it started,
why are people not connected to the school
also unable to see Mai-san?
Perhaps she took the atmosphere of school
to the outside, as well.
Even if that wasn't the case,
atmospheres can easily spread.
Everyone inadvertently
takes hints nowadays.
An atmosphere is invisible.
But that atmosphere does indeed exist.
Atmosphere is a ridiculous thing
to fight against.
You can't be conscious of other people
while you're sleeping, after all.
At the time you lose consciousness,
you become engulfed
by the atmospherization phenomenon.
I'll forget if I sleep.
Big Brother, what are you drinking?
I have midterms for the next three days.
Kaede, you should sleep now.
I have to do this while I'm clear-headed.
What is written hereafter is
truly something unbelievable, but...
Everything is the truth,
so make sure to read until the very end.
You have to!
"May 6th. I met a wild bunny girl."
Your face is a mess.
Mai-san, you're beautiful as always today.
Your tie is crooked.
Didn't think I'd be able to play newlyweds
with you this early, Mai-san.
Make your face the only stupid thing here.
You're taking the exams as well?
You can cheat as much as you want.
I don't have to do that to do well academically.
But it's useless, since they won't pass
an exam sheet to me.
Yet still you go to school.
You're so serious.
I wouldn't have anything to do
if I stayed home.
Besides, maybe someone other than you
will be able to see me today.
MAY 27th - FIRST DAY OF EXAMS
I can't. Don't sleep.
If you sleep, you'll forget.
Don't sleep!
Azusagawa, are those dark circles
under your eyes from cramming all night?
Futaba...
Do you remember?
Huh? What do you mean?
No, It's fine.
See ya.
So your hypothesis turned out to be right.
This turn of events really gets me going.
Isn't there a way?
Quantum Physics for Dummies
Something... anything!
You look like a zombie or something.
MAY 28th - SECOND DAY OF EXAMS
What did you buy?
Uh...
I knew it, you're not sleeping.
Now, sit down.
Tomorrow's the last day of exams, right?
I'll look over your studies.
I'll do my best
if you teach me as a bunny girl.
If I did that, your brain would be filled
with lewd thoughts and you wouldn't study, right?
You wouldn't be able to study like that.
I didn't think about that.
I'll give a reward if you get
a perfect score on your test.
Is that one of those
"I'll do anything for you" things?
Even if I say "anything,"
I couldn't really do anything for you, could I?
Then I'll settle for "taking a bath together."
That's a no-go.
Then how about we go on that date to Kamakura
that we couldn't do the other day?
That's fine, but are you really okay with that?
Mai-san would like something
a bit more extreme, I see...
I didn't say such a thing.
Oh, this wakes me up!
Seriously, you're so cheeky
for being younger than me...
Let's start with modern Japanese,
doing kanji problems.
Write the kanji for "hoshou" in the sentences,
"Nobody is here to guarantee a future for Sakuta,"
and "There is no security
for Sakuta in his final years."
Teacher, I sense animosity
in the example phrases.
Don't care, write them down.
hoshou (security) / hoshou (guarantee)
Now, which "hoshou" is the one for
"Nobody is here to guarantee a future for Sakuta"?
Let's see...
Sorry, can I get a hint?
This one means "take on responsibility,"
and this one is something like "protect."
Which means,
"I guarantee Mai-san's happy future" is this one,
and "There is substantial security
in the couple's future" is this one?
Don't go changing the sentences
on your own.
How's your little sister?
Looks like she's already asleep.
Mai-san, are you an only child?
I have a sister.
A girl born from my father's remarriage
after parting ways with that mother of mine.
Is she cute?
Not as much as me.
Wow, you're so childish.
Do you like girls who say someone else is "so cute"
even when she's fully aware that she is cuter?
That's the type I don't like.
Right?
That doesn't mean you should say that
about your sister...
Oh, good.
Looks like it's taking effect.
I can't... sleep just yet...
You really put in a great effort...
You put in so much effort just for my sake.
No... Not yet... This can't be how...
You've done enough. It's okay now.
Not okay...
I was alone in the beginning,
so I'll be all right.
Sakuta forgetting about me isn't much.
But still, thanks for everything.
And, I'm sorry.
Good night, Sakuta.
Goodbye.
—ther. Big Brother. It's morning.
It's the last day of your exams, right?
Won't you be late?
Oh, you're a lifesaver, Kaede.
Thanks for waking me up.
Wh-What is this?
Maybe I thought about having you wear it?
N-Not wearing this!
It's too soon for Kaede
to be wearing sexy clothing like that!
MAY 29th
"What is written hereafter is
truly something unbelievable, but...
Everything is the truth,
so make sure to read until the very end.
You have to!"
What is this?
"May 6th. I met a wild bunny girl.
It was my senpai,
a third-year at Minegahara High School."
It was that celebrity..."
I guess this is what I'd call my dark past.
I do remember going to Ogaki,
but I think I was traveling alone...
Am I supposed to fill in the name
of my girlfriend when I find one?
You look much better today.
Up until yesterday, you looked like a zombie.
Are you the type that crams
the night before exams?
Nope, I'm the type
that gives up and hurries to bed.
Thought so.
What's wrong?
No, I just had a feeling
someone was looking at me...
Yo.
Here.
- A love letter?
- It's not.
"Suppose that all matter is confirmed to take shape
as matter in this world once someone observes it."
What is this?
I don't know, either.
I saw it in my textbook this morning...
...along with this.
Don't think about it.
Just hand the letter over to Azusagawa.
See ya. I definitely handed it to you.
"...if her disappearance is based on
the unconscious ignorance of the students,
all you need to do is create a reason
for existence that overrides it.
In other words, your love needs to override
the ignorance of every student put together."
Love, huh?
Problem #2 - Read the following excerpt,
and answer the questions that follow.
Become the hoshou (guarantee) person for him
Hoshou (secure) the safety of the country
Sazukeru (entrust) technology to your juniors
Write down the kanji for
the underlined words in katakana:
hoshou (guarantee)
hoshou (security)
This one means "take on responsibility,"
and this one is something like "protect."
Write the kanji for "hoshou" in the sentences,
"Nobody is here to guarantee a future for Sakuta,"
and "There is no security
for Sakuta in his final years."
hoshou (security)
What?
What's wrong, Azusagawa?
Gotta take a dump!
Something important came back to mind...
The memories of someone I cherished
have returned.
From here on,
I must face the atmosphere.
The atmosphere that won't move,
even if I push, pull or slap it around.
The atmosphere surrounding the school.
It's easy to "follow the leader"
as a lifestyle.
Deciding if everything is good or bad
on your own uses a ton of calories,
and to have a will of your own,
it can hurt to be denied.
To that point, you stay safe and sound
being the same as everyone else.
You don't have to see
what you don't want to.
You don't have to think about
You can leave everything to someone else.
But...
There's no reason to torment someone
just because everyone else is doing it.
Because everyone is doing it,
because everyone says so...
That doesn't make it true!
Who's this "everyone" anyway?
She always treated me
as the younger one and teased me.
She blew up whenever she tried sexy talk,
and her face would get completely red.
She was so obstinate and put up a front,
trying to hide those mistakes.
Selfish, a queen, whimsical,
and yet surprisingly naïve.
A senpai one year older than me...
I won't let people ignore her anymore.
I won't let people look and pretend not to.
I'll engrave her into everyone's memory
so much they won't be able to!
I'm not gonna take hints anymore.
It's so stupid!
All right, guys! Listen up!
Class 2-1, attendance number 1,
Sakuta Akutagawa!
To Mai Sakurajima-senpai, in class 3-1...
I'm in love with you, Sakurajima-senpai!
Damn it, I knew it'd be like this.
So much lost from humiliation
with nothing to gain!
This is exactly why I didn't want
to go up against the atmosphere!
Bastards!
Mai-san, I love you!
I love you, I love you, I love you,
I love you, I love you!
Mai-san, I love you!
I want to hold hands
along Shichirigahama Beach!
I want to see you in
that bunny girl outfit one more time!
I want to hold you tight!
And I want to kiss you!
In other words, Mai-san...
I love you very, very, very, very, very much!
You don't have to say it
in such a loud voice, I hear you.
You're being a nuisance.
I figured, since I had the chance,
I wanted everyone in the world to know.
You're such an idiot.
Better than someone pretending
to be smart, right?
You really are an idiot.
You'll get more weird rumors about you
if you stand out doing something like this.
If the rumors are about being with Mai-san,
I welcome it.
That's not what I mean...
Idiot... Idiot Sakuta!
Ow!
Eh? Why?
Liar! You said you wouldn't forget!
That you'd absolutely never forget!
Sorry...
I won't forgive you.
No way I'll forgive you.
Then I won't let go until you do.
Then I'll never forgive you
for my whole life.
Eh?
What, you don't want that?
After making me say all of this...
Um... Your foot...
You're happy I'm stepping on you, right?
Sorry, I'm so sorry.
I'll reconsider my words, so please forgive me.
Anything else to say?
I'm happy to be stomped on by you.
Those aren't the words I want to hear.
I love you.
Are you sure?
I lied. I love you very much.
Hey, Sakuta.
What?
Tell me that again in a month from now.
Why?
If I answer now, I'll feel like I was steamrolled
into this from momentum and ambience.
Personally, I'd like to kiss you
right here on the spot.
Maybe our hearts are racing
due to the situation we're currently in.
You're unexpectedly calm.
Well, since I can't wait a month,
can I tell you every day?
That's fine, but you have to do so
for a whole month.
If you can't, then I'll take it
that you changed your mind.
Everyone really loves to take hints,
don't they?
That rumor about Sakuta
hospitalizing some classmates...
It's all silly nonsense!
How does Sakurajima-senpai
know about that?
Wait, what kind of relationship do they have?
You wanted to tell everyone, didn't you?
Thanks to you, everyone
is totally paying attention to me.
Getting lectured in the faculty office
will be such a drag.
It's fine.
I'll be scolded right there next to you.
Well, in that case, it can't be that bad.
You two over there!
Get over here!
And thus, the world regained Mai Sakurajima.
JUNE 2nd
As I thought,
your heart is made of iron, Sakuta.
If that was me, I'd die from embarrassment.
Nothing less from you, Azusagawa.
What a young rascal.
What's that supposed to mean?
When the rumors about hospitalization
were going around the school,
you said fighting the atmosphere was stupid.
Did you forget about that?
You did say that.
You couldn't be serious
for something about yourself,
but you'll face any embarrassment
for a beautiful senpai.
What is this guy, if not a young rascal?
Hey, in the end, can we say
that your hypothesis was right?
Who knows?
Illusions shown by unstable psyches or strong
preconception that come from adolescence...
If that's what Adolescence Syndrome is,
then scientific inspection won't be reliable.
But it could be that our world is so simple
that a confession of love can change it.
Just like how you proved it.
Maybe so...
But this wasn't the final incident
concerning Adolescence Syndrome.
After Schrödinger's Cat, Laplace's Demon...
No... Laplace's Petit-Devil appeared.
Nothing less from you, Senpai.
What a rascal.
Next time
#4 There is No Tomorrow for Rascal