I understand the circumstances now.
It's tough being a high-school girl.
Is that all?
You'd get ecstatic if I scolded you, Sakuta.
It seems not giving a punishment
is a punishment in your case.
But it's not sitting right with me,
for some reason.
You hate lies like pretending
to be dating, don't you?
I don't think anyone would like lies
of this sort...
That's why it's not sitting right with me.
What are you hiding?
Actually, I've been getting excited
looking at your legs for the past few minutes.
I-I already knew that.
Just hurry and spit it all out.
Koga said the same thing
as when Kaede first stopped going to school.
That she was embarrassed.
She said she wouldn't have a place in her class
if her friends found out Maesawa asked her out.
She didn't want to be embarrassed
about people thinking she's a loner.
How boring.
I talk seriously, and that's your reaction?
I can't complain if you bring up
the bit about your little sister.
I'll let you off the hook this one time.
Thank you very much!
But, let's see...
Simply letting you go
won't do much for the future,
so show enough faith to be worth it.
What do you want me to do?
You should at least think of that yourself.
Then...
Hey, what the!?
I'm showing some faith.
No, that's your libido!
Th-Then how about a date?
We can go look at the hydrangea
in Kamakura next Sunday—
I'm in Kagoshima for a week,
filming a drama starting tomorrow.
Kagoshima? I'm jealous.
I'm not there for a vacation.
Oh, right. You can have this.
They gave me the outfit I wore
during a fashion magazine shoot.
So I should treat this as a substitute for you
while you're in Kagoshima?
It's for your sister!
She'll be 15 this year, right?
Maybe dressing up will spark
a little interest in leaving the house
Wh-What is it?
I'm so happy that
you're looking out for Kaede.
I'll fetch her right now.
What are you doing?
I-It's not what you think.
I wasn't pretending to be a ninja.
I thought you were just eavesdropping on us.
Well, it works out.
Eh?
Good evening.
G-Good evening...
This is from Mai-san.
Why don't you try it on?
Yup. So cute.
I've never worn anything like this,
so it's embarrassing...
You should thank Mai-san.
Th-Thank you very much.
You're welcome.
U-Um...
What is it?
Can Kaede call you "Mai-san", too?
That's fine.
And I'll call you "Kaede-chan."
Sure!
Thanks for everything today.
Why are you thanking me again?
It's been a while since Kaede spoke
with anyone other than me,
since she's cooped up at home for so long.
When you're so honest,
it's not worth toying with you.
I hope "pretend" doesn't turn into "serious."
What?
That first-year.
You're going on a date
after work tomorrow, right?
My heart is only for Mai-san,
so it'll be all right.
If you don't get it, forget it.
Eh?
Good night.
JUNE 29th
Kunimi, there's a guy named Maesawa
on the basketball team, yeah?
Hmm? Oh, you mean Yosuke-senpai.
What kind of guy is he?
What kind of guy?
Well, he's probably the best
basketball player at our school.
Plus, he's pretty popular with the girls.
Keep giving me more info
so I can hate him even more.
What's up with that?
It's hard to explain, but if he's
a good person, it'll haunt me.
Well, I don't want
to badmouth people too much,
but yesterday, coming back from practice,
he was saying he'll dump his girlfriend
because she wasn't giving it up.
Wait, he has a girlfriend?
He does.
Some third-year from another school.
And he says a lot of demeaning things
about his past girlfriends, too.
Makes me think how I don't want
to end up like that.
Thanks for the valuable info.
Now it won't haunt me.
S-Sorry to make you wait.
Your face is all red.
And you're five minutes late.
I-I couldn't help it.
I had to get ready and stuff.
Get ready, huh...
Well, you sure are cute.
D-Don't tell me I'm cute.
Minus points for not wearing a miniskirt,
but since you have bare legs,
I can forgive you.
You can't look at just my legs, either!
Oh, that's right, your ID.
I thought about telling you I was gonna be late,
but I never got your ID.
Don't have one.
Eh?
I don't have a smartphone,
nor a flip-phone.
What do you mean?
I dun git dat at all!
How do you live!?
Do people without smartphones die?
They die!
Starting off with a yawn?
I haven't slept much.
Because you're looking forward to the date?
I was with everyone in the group chat
till past 2AM yesterday.
Then I watched funny animal videos,
until I noticed it was morning already.
That, and preparing for the date a bit.
Why don't you hurry and get sleep?
Everyone else was awake,
so I couldn't go to sleep before them!
You can watch funny animal videos
when you have time to kill, right?
Everyone said they already saw it.
I'm in trouble if I can't join in
on the conversation!
Rena-chan recommended them, you know?
Rena-chan again...
Oh right! My impressions!
Your eyes look dead, Senpai.
It's the same as usual.
So they're always dead?
For our closing act, we'll be attempting
a dive from the springboard!
That penguin over there
is a bit like you, Senpai.
It looks like one's sleeping...
We'll have this one give it his best.
Then are you that
energetic penguin over there?
Actually, the penguins become so engrossed
in eating that they often slip and fall.
I'm not that one.
I'm the penguin that follows the others.
Now, here we go. Three... Two... One...
It has a big butt, too.
I was being serious...
Success!
It looks like he's finally gotten up,
but the show's over now...
He's fine with everyone laughing at him.
Just like you, Senpai.
What's wrong?
You know...
I wasn't like this back in middle school.
It's a...
Bumpkin.
That's why I didn't want to show you!
Weren't you the one who showed me it?
Dad got relocated,
so I ended up moving here from Fukuoka.
I was in an unnoticed group in class,
so I thought, in Tokyo, they'd say I wasn't cool,
wouldn't make friends and get bullied.
So I did some research.
I wore makeup for the first time,
and got my hair done at a fancy salon.
I bought and wore clothes
from fashion magazines.
I worked on my accent, too.
And this is what I ended up with.
Do you not like who you are right now?
I like it. I like it a whole lot.
Then why agonize over it?
It's bothersome.
You're just being immature, thinking like
"This isn't who I really am," right?
Y-You're right, but...
- It's annoying.
- You're horrible!
No matter who you were before,
how you look right now is who you are.
No matter the reason, you ended up that way
because you wanted to and worked for it, right?
Y-Yeah.
And you like who you are now, right?
Yet you say, "This isn't who I really am"?
That's even more messed up.
I feel a bit frustrated,
because I feel like you talked me into this.
Let's go.
Come on, next is Enoshima, right?
Yup.
Someone you know?
A classmate, Yoneyama-san.
Yoneyama-san!
Koga-san...
A-And "came full circle and acceptable" senpai.
That sentiment really is spreading.
Sorry...
Are you looking for something?
Y-Yeah...
I'll look for it with you!
Y-You don't have to.
You're in Kashiba's group, Koga-san.
It's faster if the three of us look.
You heard Senpai.
Yeah.
I'm looking for a phone strap.
My friends and I got matching ones.
It has a jellyfish charm on it.
You're sure you dropped it
somewhere around here?
I-I'm sorry, I'm not sure of that, either.
You don't have to apologize.
Senpai is a strange guy, but he's not scary.
Yeah...
Isn't that it?
Wow!
Hey, hold on—
Koga-san!
Hurray!
Are you okay?
JUNE 30th
Did you catch a cold?
Senpai.
I heard from Rena.
I'm totally fine.
Want some mandarin oranges?
It's against school rules
to leave campus during class.
So you don't want it, I guess.
I'll eat it.
I can do the "say aah" thing, if you want.
It's hard to eat that way, so no.
Hey, Senpai. Why did you go along
with my unreasonable requests?
Because you were desperate
when you asked.
Even though you hardly know me?
We did kick each other's butts.
Sheesh, I'm asking a serious question.
But I did think you were
a good girl back then.
And because you're cute, to be honest.
There you go, joking again.
I don't know if I'd do the same
if you were ugly.
Guys are just like that.
I'm sure you would have, Senpai.
If you have a cold, just stay home.
If I stay home, I won't be able
to keep up with everyone's conversation.
After just a day?
That one day is life-threatening.
It's the same if you're sleeping
in the nurse's office.
Even now, I'm worried about everyone's opinion
of me since I'm in the nurse's office.
You're excessively self-conscious, Koga.
You're the strange one, Senpai.
Everyone looks at you funny
and makes fun of you.
How are you okay like that?
It's not like I live
for all of humanity to like me.
I want everyone to like me.
Or rather, I don't want them to hate me.
I don't mind if I only had one person.
Even if the whole world hated me,
I could keep living if that person needed me.
Here. A thank-you gift for a couple days ago.
Why canned peaches?
Because you have a peach-shaped butt?
No more perversion!
I think I'll savor this tonight,
imagining it's you.
Y-You dummy!
I'm telling you, my butt isn't that big!
Oh, come on, no need to be humble.
That doesn't sound right, either!
Senpai, how did things
with Sakurajima-senpai turn out?
Still no reply.
Wait, she hasn't rejected you yet?
If that whole loop thing didn't happen,
she'd say it's okay for us to start dating
during lunch break that day.
- You're kidding.
- It's true.
You've got to be kidding.
We're talking about Sakurajima-senpai here!
She's in show-biz!
Did she say she loved you?
She... hasn't said that yet.
See? It's just you, Senpai.
Next time I ask her out,
I'll try my best for her to tell me that.
What's up, Mai-san?
I thought you might want to hear my voice,
so I called you for your sake.
Actually, I was just thinking about you.
I hope you have your underwear on.
Though it's natural for you
to do things like that thinking about me.
I'm buck naked!
Y-You pervert!
I'm kidding.
I just got out of a bath,
so I'm only wearing underware.
Don't tell such stupid lies.
I might be indebted to you
on restless nights, though.
Yeah, yeah, do as you wish.
Anyway, how are things over there?
Was the date with your cute little girlfriend fun?
In a way, I suppose.
Oh...
What was the right answer to that question?
How about bolting out of your house
and coming down to Kagoshima to see me?
And when I do,
I need to hug you buck naked, right?
Such a mood killer.
Mai-san, is the filming fun?
It's fun.
Are there any jobs you want to do, Sakuta?
Well, I think I want
to be Santa Claus in the future.
Because he doesn't work
364 days out of the year?
You got me.
Say dumb things and you'll become dumb!
JULY 5th
Futaba.
Yo.
Kunimi...
Need something?
Sakuta's not in the classroom,
so I was wondering if he was here.
Isn't he with that first-year?
Oh, over there!
I'll let Azusagawa know if he shows up.
Futaba, you here?
Sorry to bother you.
Are you an idiot!? You must be an idiot!
Don't be oddly considerate of me!
Kunimi will catch on!
If he was going to notice with that,
he would've caught on long ago...
...to your feelings.
That'd be problematic.
You guys seem to be busy,
so I'll talk to you later, Sakuta!
He really was handsome as always.
So, what does Azusagawa
the not-so-handsome rascal want with me?
Yeah...
I haven't relived the same day since then,
so I was wondering what it actually was about.
Perhaps it's exactly what you said it was.
The first-year that is your
supposed girlfriend was Laplace's Demon.
She kept rolling the dice until
a future convenient to her occurred.
And...
Since she's satisfied with her current condition,
there's no need to relive it anymore.
But she's not aware of it at all.
If she was, that'd probably
make her a real demon.
Kamisato.
I thought I said this before,
about not getting close to Yuuma.
I think what you said was,
"Don't talk to him."
That's the same thing.
That, and what's with the girl
in the physics lab?
What is she to Yuuma?
They seem to be chatting often.
Why don't you ask Kunimi?
You're friends with her too, right?
Just answer me!
Why are you so irritated?
You constipated?
Die! Just die right now!
You really are the pits!
Get some dietary fiber!
JULY 6th
Kunimi, it's annoying, so I'll say this up front.
Your girlfriend picked a fight
with me again yesterday.
That's unfortunate.
You really have to choose
between me or her.
What is that not-so-ultimate ultimatum.
All right. I'll call her tonight about it.
Seriously, I'm counting on you.
Anyway, Sakuta...
Is the thing about you dating Koga for real?
For real.
Seriously?
Actually, it's more like a trial period.
Then I should have mentioned this yesterday...
It's about Koga.
What is it?
There are bad rumors about her.
Like how she's easy, a whore,
screwing you all the time, stuff like that.
What's up with that?
I found out from
the basketball team's group messages, too.
Sakuta, you asked about Yosuke-senpai
the other day, right?
Futaba, do you ever have thoughts like,
"What if, back then..."?
For you, that would be about your little sister?
Yeah. Is that bad?
It's not bad,
but I'd say it's not like you to do so.
It's not that I really want
to do everything over, per se.
I just want to stop thinking about "what if's",
since it's useless to think about them.
I see. That IS like you.
You know, Futaba...
What?
Would I have a chance of winning
against someone who's not only bigger than me,
but works out on an athletic team?
Who knows?
Humans aren't ordinary monkeys.
Maybe you can win if you used your brains?
This is Mai Sakurajima.
I just got back from Kagoshima.
Thought I'd let you know.
JULY 7th
I totally messed up my bangs!
Isn't it like terrible?
Don't have such a morbid look on your face.
Senpai...
Is that her?
First-years nowadays get it on often, huh?
Huh? Did you laugh at me?
I'm still laughing. What of it?
You messing with me?
No, I'm just making fun of you.
Senpai!
Huh? Ya wanna go?
You're not being fair!
No, that'd be you.
So uncool.
Who isn't cool!?
You should go wash your face.
Huh?
I stepped on some poop yesterday.
D-Don't mess with me!
You're the one messing with others.
If you don't want to attract attention,
don't do stupid stuff.
Your way of life is so uncool.
Senpai, that's enough!
No, I have to say one thing.
Getting screwed all the time?
Gimme a break!
I'm a virgin!
Wai— Sen—
Senpai, that's going too far!
Like I care!
That was going way too far!
I think I understand a bit
of what you said before, Senpai.
If the whole world was your enemy,
if one person needs you kinda thing.
"Kinda thing?"
At least remember things properly.
It really felt like I was your girlfriend.
Like I was being cherished.
I promised you that I would for the first term.
You normally wouldn't go so far
for the sake of a fake girlfriend.
I'm a perfectionist.
What's that? Mega lame!
What's that mean?
You can't even tell dat?
I meant boring.
Oh, it's from Rena.
She wrote, "I'm so disappointed
in Maesawa-senpai."
If some poop on his face makes her lose interest,
her admiration was just that superficial.
Oh, there's something I'd like to say.
- Bathroom break?
- No!
I-I've, um...
...never done anything like that.
Like what?
I'm still a virgin!
You're so horrible for laughing at me!
You thought I'd really believe a rumor like that?
I didn't, but I'd feel bad if you did, so...
But didn't you say you used
to have a boyfriend at some point?
I mean, everyone said they had boyfriends
back in middle school.
And they were like, "Of course you had one too,
right Tomoe?" kinda thing...
I see.
Besides, if I said I never dated anyone,
I thought you'd make a fool out of me.
What exactly are you fighting, Koga?
I don't know.
You know, Senpai...
How should I pay you back for all this?
Well, when all the lies are over,
you can be my friend.
It's fine if you don't want to.
No.
You're hopeless, so I'll be your best friend!
As expected of you, Sakuta.
You're such a rascal.
Next Time
#6 This World You Chose