I will kill all my enemies...
Even if they happen to be...
...a god.
Your Majesty, though the
delays are quite regrettable,
we are still relieved to hear
that the Hero is on his way back.
Yes. I hear that the demons
are becoming more active as well.
We will be needing the Hero's powers soon.
Is something wrong, Princess Liliana?
You seem ill at ease.
N-No, Pope Ishtar, I'm fine...
Kouki-san and the others were summoned
to our world by an act of God.
The Hero has returned.
They were summoned to
protect us humans from the demons.
Without a way to go back
to their original world,
Kouki-san and the others had
no choice but to obey the will of God.
A horrible accident happened during
their training to prepare for war.
No more...
Lily!
Shizuku!
I was worried by how long it took you
to return from the Great Orcus Labyrinth.
We're fine. How about everyone else?
Yes, the Second Party members
were all training hard every day.
"We can't just sit idly by and rely
on Kouki and the others all the time."
"We have to be strong too."
That's what they said.
Hey, Eririn, want something to drink?
Eririn?
Sure, let's drink something.
Shizuku, if you didn't return,
they said they would go out to find you.
They truly care about their friends.
Hey, what's the matter with you?
Why are you in such a bad mood?
Were the monsters you saw
down there really that bad?
It's not the monsters... It's him.
He's worse than the monsters.
Kousuke! Where are you, Kousuke! Kousuke!
Now that you've mentioned it,
yes, Kousuke is missing.
Kousuke! Where are you?!
--Kousuke!
Um, I'm right here.
You really do blend in with
the background, as always.
Can I cry now?
I'm sorry I worried you. I'm glad
to see everyone's in good spirits.
Yes.
What about Kaori?
Lily, about that...
I see.
So Kaori is with Nagumo-san.
Yes.
Is that why Kouki-san seems so out of it?
Well, that's probably part of it, but...
Nagumo-kun ended up
saving Kouki again, so...
I see...
That said, he is "The Hero" after all.
We can't let him stay sad for too long.
Indeed.
If it comes down to it, I'll handle him.
I'm truly glad to hear Nagumo-san is safe.
It would have been best
if he could come back with us,
but he said he's searching for another
way for us to go back to our world.
I'm a little disappointed
that I couldn't see him.
You'd be surprised if you did. He looks
totally different, among other things.
By now, I'm sure he's...
It's quite terrible outside, Tio-san.
If it wasn't for Hajime-san's Brise,
we would have been in a lot of trouble.
Indeed, Shea. This is not a place
I'd enter if I had any other choice.
It's so different from
the last time I was here!
It's so cool, and my eyes don't hurt!
Papa is so awesome!
That's right. Papa Hajime is awesome.
Do you want some cold water, Myu-chan?
I do! Thank you, Big Sister Kaori!
Hey, Shirasaki...
K-Kaori, please stop calling me
"Papa Hajime." It feels weird.
Huh? But that's what Myu-chan
calls you, and you don't seem to mind.
It's okay when Myu says it.
Having a classmate call me that, though,
I have to say, is uncomfortable.
Really? Well then, I won't say it, but...
But one day, when I have a baby, then...
Sorry.
I have a previous engagement,
already promised.
Introduction to his parents,
Our happy family life plans are all set.
We also have plans to go on
a date in Hajime's hometown.
There's so much that I know
about Hajime-kun that you don't, Yue!
Like his future aspirations,
his hobbies...
Yue, do you know about Hajime-kun's
favorite anime and manga?
Well... That doesn't matter now.
Those things don't exist here.
Really? Can't you see that Hajime-kun
looks like an anime character now?
His weapons, too. That new one
he's making... The Cross Bit, was it?
That's totally based on the Funnel, right?
K-Kaori?!
How can you act like you've won
without knowing anything
about the things he loves?
Bold words, Kaori.
Then I'll tell you about
what Hajime loves...
...to do, in bed.
B-B-B-B-Bed?! So, you've already...?!
Yes, let that sink in, how far ahead I am.
Big Sister Yue and Big Sister Kaori
are always fighting!
I don't like it when the big sisters
aren't nice to each other!
Aren't you ashamed of behaving
like that in front of Myu-chan?
It's bad for her education.
Please restrain yourselves.
How regrettable, for Shea to scold me
and actually have a good point.
I'm sorry, Myu-chan, Shea...
Master, there seems to be
a disturbance up ahead.
Those are sand worms.
Sand worms in the Gruen Desert
are very common, but...
What are they doing?
It's almost like they can't decided
whether or not they should eat their prey.
Yeah, that's how it appears.
Is that a thing?
They eat anything, I don't think
they'd ever hesitate in front of a meal.
Hold on!
Hey, pervert! Get your breasts off me!
I can't help it!
Hey, Kaori!
You of all people, what are
you doing in this situation?!
It's dangerous! The danger is dangerous!
I'm clinging on because
the dangerous danger is right there!
Damn you Kaori, a surprise attack
to get ahead of me? Well played.
I'm sorry! I had the purest of intentions!
I just wanted to see
what it felt like to be clingy!
And also, if possible, to enjoy Hajime?
Yes, correct... Wait, no!
Don't phrase it like that!
I'm not a lewd person like you, Yue!
You call me lewd? Well, I can't deny
that I am, when I'm alone with Hajime.
Will you two just shut up for a bit?
Also, Yue, no more "nighttime" talk.
We're running backwards!
Papa Hajime is such a good driver.
I said stop calling me Papa!
Hajime, I want babies.
Hey! Save the fun for the inn!
Will there be fun for me, too?
I'll throw you out into the desert.
Why are you so harsh to only me?!
Come to think of it, this is
the first time I've used this.
I didn't know Brise
had something like this.
Hajime, you're a genius.
Master is truly great.
Dammit!
Make sure Myu doesn't see this.
Now, let's find out what's going on.
They're looking at us.
Is that bad, Hajime-san?
There seems to be a much bigger crowd.
Just watch.
Hajime-kun, look!
A person?
Was that what the sand worms were after?
Hajime-kun, would it be
all right to go over there?
Well, we do have Myu-chan with us.
Yes. It would be very risky.
Myu is fine!
I guess, as a Priest,
you want to save him.
Yes.
Myu, stay in Brise with Shea.
Hajime-kun!
I'm curious to know
why he didn't get eaten.
Is this...
"Status: Overloaded mana,
unable to release mana"
A mana overload?
Some sort of ingested poison is causing
this person's mana to go berserk?
Kaori, what did you find?
I'm not certain, but it seems
like he ingested something
that's causing a state of "mana overload."
Mana overload?
He's unable to release the extra mana,
so the forced overload coming from inside
is causing pressure on the body,
which can't handle it.
If we don't do something,
his organs and veins will rupture.
Heaven's blessing,
I hereby request recurrence...
Consecration!
It had no effect. Why?
If it can't be cleansed, is it that
deeply dissolved into his body...?
Kaori?
May the grace of light bless you
in this holy sanctuary.
No evil shall pass
so long as I hold the gates.
Sanctorum!
High-rank light magic, "Sanctorum."
It allows the caster to transfer mana
from one person to another,
to prevent mana depletion.
It can also be used to forcefully
drain mana from someone.
I guess she's using it to drain out
the overloaded mana from this man?
And the drained mana goes into
the Holy Crystal ring I gave her. I see.
I don't think he's in
immediate danger anymore,
but the root cause
hasn't been resolved yet.
If I drain too much of his mana,
he might die from emaciation,
so I've only drained
enough to ease the pressure.
So, he's still...
Unless we do something,
he'll go into mana overload again,
or the fatigue could
cause him to weaken and die.
I've never seen symptoms
like these in anything I've studied.
Yue, Tio, do you have any ideas?
I see.
Kaori.
Just in case, do a diagnosis on us, too.
If this is an unknown disease,
it could be airborne.
A goddess?!
I see.... I must have died,
and I'm going to meet God...
Oh, dear goddess...
Hajime-kun?!
Stop spewing nonsense and get up already.
I-I'm alive?!
I thought I was done for, but it
seems God has not forsaken me yet.
Hajime-kun, maybe we
should bring him inside the car.
Yeah, it's way too hot out here.
It's not hot... Where am I?
Is this a divine sanctuary?
Here.
Have some water.
It's cold!
First of all, thank you
for saving my life.
If I had died out there,
everything would have been over.
My name is Bize Feuward Zengen.
I am the son of the duke, Lanzwi Feuward
Zengen, of the Dukedom of Ankaji.
The Dukedom of Ankaji?
The important trade hub for
the seafood coming out of Erisen,
the city on the ocean.
Yes. Erisen is where
Myu was born and raised.
Mama is waiting for me there!
Master, Ankaji is the town
we were headed towards.
Yes.
I guess that town is in trouble.
Tell us about what's going on.
A few days ago, the citizens of Ankaji
began to collapse from fever.
A poison that causes mana overload
was found in our drinking water...
Our oasis was polluted by this substance.
The oasis is protected, maintained,
and managed with the utmost care.
How did this poison get in the oasis?
Who could have done this?
However, there is a cure.
It involves a special
mineral called Stillstone.
Stillstone has the effect of calming
a person's mana when ingested.
It is a precious mineral, mined in
small amounts in the Gruen Volcano.
The Gruen Volcano? That's...
But the adventurers
of Ankaji have all fallen ill.
The average adventurer
wouldn't even be able
to get past the sandstorm
surrounding the volcano.
Even if a powerful
adventurer was available,
seeing how we're almost out
of safe drinking water...
So in a nutshell, you set out to call
for help, but you also collapsed,
so Ankaji is in really deep trouble now.
Someone needs to cleanse the oasis
and bring Stillstone
from the volcano, correct?
Yes! You are Gold-ranked adventurers,
and you are a goddess.
This must truly be God's will!
He must have sent these
goddesses to save us, and...
God, huh?
I would like to officially ask you,
as a deputy of the Duke of Ankaji,
please, lend us aid!
Papa.
Aren't you going to save them?
Myu.
Well, we were going
to stop by Ankaji, anyway.
Hajime-kun!
We're going to get busy again.
Then let's hurry!
Yes!
We want you to go directly to
the volcano to mine the Stillstone,
but perhaps it is best to first travel
to the royal capital to get water--
There's no need
to go to the royal capital.
We should be able to get water.
We're heading to Ankaji right away.
Should be able to?
Right, Yue?
Yes, Hajime.
Can you stop melting away
into a world of your own?
I know, right? It's always
just the two of them. Not fair!
Not fair!
General Freid! Is it true
that Cattleya was defeated?!
Mikhail.
It can't be true!
Cattleya could not have died!
She had so many monsters
by her side, and...
The mission at the
town of Ur was also a failure.
Ur, too?!
The operations were partially successful.
Sixty thousand monsters were recruited
and were about to lay waste to
the town and kill the Fertility Goddess.
But an "Irregular" crushed our plan.
An "Irregular"?
Just four individuals wiped out
the entire monster army.
Reiss, who was on the mission,
lost an arm.
Impossible. Reiss, too...?
The four Irregulars left Ur and went
straight to the Great Orcus Labyrinth.
Just when Cattleya was
about to encounter the Hero.
So these Irregulars killed Cattleya...?
Our enemies are stronger
than we anticipated.
I will head to the volcano now.
I must acquire a new Age of God magic
and grow stronger. At any cost.
General Freid...
All in service to our king
and for the God we worship.
Mikhail, defend our home while
I am away. War is coming, soon.
I will avenge Cattleya's death.
You have crushed the sacred mission
given to me by my God.
You will pay dearly for that,
my unseen enemies.
The moment you see me is
the last moment of your lives.
There is no place on
this world for heathens
or Irregulars.
Next episode, "Burning Light."