Hurry up!
Stay sharp!
A woman?!
Not a dragon?
Tio!
Are you all right?
Kaori...
Yes, I'm actually quite fine.
Just a bit tired.
Tio... What about
Hajime-kun and the others?
Why are you alone?
Calm down, Kaori.
What about that volcano eruption?!
So Hajime-kun is...
Yes, they should be
catching up with us soon.
Master was not pessimistic
in the slightest.
I'm sure he had some plan to get out.
Kaori, I have a message from Master.
From Hajime-kun?
Yes. Well, to Kaori and Myu both,
to be exact, but...
"See you later," he said.
Kaori?
Right, yes. Good...
He should be all right then.
Even if the situation
seems hopeless to others,
Master will survive and
act like nothing happened.
That we can believe, without a doubt.
Yes.
Aren't we going to go pick up Papa?
We need to believe in Papa Hajime
and do what we need to do on our side.
Only then can we go pick him up.
Oh, but we can't take Myu-chan
to the Grand Gruen Volcano.
In that case, why don't
we head over to Erisen first
and reunite Myu with her mother?
Right! That's what we'll do.
How many days has it been...?
Hajime, how are you feeling?
I'm fine. It'll just take me
a while longer to fully recover.
How about you, Yue?
I'm fine. Shea shared
some of her blood with me.
Oh, Yue-san, why are you sitting on me?
Because there's a Hajime there.
The poison from the Burning Light
is almost gone. That's good.
I told you, I'm fine.
But I'm still worried.
I'm glad we have a chance to rest up,
though the location isn't ideal.
Yeah, that was a crazy chain of events.
I don't know if we're
really lucky or really unlucky.
Hajime-san! It's close!
Good, we're safe for now.
Hajime, look.
A magic circle.
This is... a magic that controls space?
The secret to that instant movement trick.
Oh, you mean how
he suddenly appeared behind us.
I sincerely hope that the future of
humankind will be based on free will...
Naiz Gruen.
Simple.
It's like he tidied up his life.
It doesn't seem like Naiz-san left
anything behind other than the magic.
So, we got the proof
of conquest and the magic.
Now to get out of here...
Right, but Spatial Magic is hard
to use, we can't use it just yet.
You do have a plan, right?
The outside is probably
completely full of lava by now.
We'll swim through the lava.
Hmm?
Huh?
Please don't look at me like that...
I actually made a ship
that can travel underwater.
The Sunken Ruins of Melusine is next,
and I was sure we'd need one for that.
I was a bit worried about whether
or not it could withstand the lava, but...
Looks like it'll do fine.
Huh?! What's going on?!
Dammit, I lost control.
If this were an eruption,
we'd just get tossed outside
and all would be good, but...
Seems like we're getting pushed
straight down... Or no, diagonally down.
You mean we're going deeper underground?!
Yue, Shea, I don't think we're
getting out of here very soon.
Seems like we have to take
this trip to wherever we end up.
I'll be by your side until the end.
As long as I can do that,
I'll have no regrets.
Literally come hell or high water, huh?
I'll also follow you two
to wherever you might go!
Dammit, it's out of ammo!
I got this.
Yue! Take my blood.
No, I can still...
Yue...
Have you two forgotten about someone?
Use my blood, please!
What about Shea?
She gave me a lot of blood, so I don't
think she'll be getting up anytime soon.
I see...
Hmm? Are you awake? How are you?
Thank you for your totally natural
reaction as if nothing happened.
I am absolutely fine. Oh, indeed I am!
That's good to hear.
I wonder where we are?
Who knows?
I'd like to run some tests,
but the Treasure Trove is with Tio.
We travel wherever the wind takes us.
Doesn't that mean we're lost?
Hmm?
Who are you?! Why are you here?!
What is this thing you're riding?
You won't get us to lower our guards!
Is that the trick you
used to kidnap the girl?!
Are you here to
steal more of our children?!
Are you talking about Myu?
Oh, in that case, we--
Silence! Who allowed
you to speak, rabbitman?!
Nice shot.
Wait, something just...
What is it?
--Papa!
--What is this?
No way.
Papa!
Myu?!
Myu...
Sorry, Papa...
Can you promise that you won't do
something dangerous like that again?
Yes, I can.
All right, then I forgive you.
Papa!
I'm so glad... I'm so glad!
Sorry to worry you. But as
you can see, I'm totally fine. So...
So stop crying. Seeing you cry is...
bad, in lots of ways.
Well, then...
Just a little while longer...
What?!
H-Hey! Tio!
I believed in you!
I totally believed in you, but...
But being together with you, it's...
Please give me some
of your time, my master!
Please, master! Give me a reward!
"Erisen, City on the Sea"
Hey, that girl, is that...?
Yeah, it is. She's Remia's daughter,
the one who got kidnapped.
I authorize the completion of the mission
given from the guild branch master.
Thank you, gold-rank adventurer,
Mr. Nagumo.
I'm sure you have tons
of questions, but for now,
can we take her to her mother?
I guess I have no choice.
The sighting of the dragon out at sea,
and that ship-like vehicle...
As a soldier of the kingdom,
I cannot ignore those things.
I'll be staying in Erisen for a while.
How about we chat about it next time?
If there is an opportunity to talk,
then that's fine.
I'll ask again after you've settled down.
The talk is over!
If you're going to continue to loiter,
I'll arrest you all for interfering
with a soldier's duties!
Papa, I'm going home! Mama's waiting!
I wanna see Mama!
Yeah, let's hurry and go see her.
Papa! This way!
Yeah, yeah.
Hurry!
Remia, calm down!
You can't go with that leg!
Come on, Remia!
We'll bring Myu back, we promise!
No! If Myu is back, I have to go get her!
Mama!
Myu?! Myu!
I'm sorry... I'm so sorry
I couldn't protect you, Myu...
It's fine, Mama.
Myu is right here. So, it's fine.
Myu...
I'm so glad!
Mama!
Your leg! What happened?
Are you hurt? Does it hurt?!
Papa! Help Mama! Mama's leg hurts!
--What?! Myu, what did you just say?
--Papa! Hurry!
Oh? Oh? Did you really say Papa?
P-Papa?! Does she mean me?!
No way! It has to be me!
No, she's talking about me!
Papa, Mama is...
Don't worry, Myu. She'll be fine.
So don't be worried.
Yes...
Sorry about this, excuse me.
Huh?
Oh?
Remia is getting re-married?
It can't be...
Remia is finally seeing
someone again? That's great!
I see. So, you got hurt by
the guys who kidnapped Myu...
How is she, Kaori?
Good, she'll be fine.
I can heal this properly.
I'd like to spend a few days and take some
time with her to avoid any side effects.
It might be a bit
uncomfortable until then,
but I will heal this, please rest assured.
Oh my, oh my. I was told
nobody could fix this wound.
I don't know how to thank you...
So, um, how did you meet Myu?
And also...
...why does Myu call you Papa?
It's a long story but...
It's thanks to you that I was
able to reunite with my daughter.
I will repay this debt,
even it takes the rest of my life.
Don't worry about it.
You're Myu-chan's mother, after all.
Right.
Don't worry about it.
I heard you're planning on
staying in town for a while.
In that case, please stay in this house.
Myu would like that, too.
No, we're fine.
There was a good inn near the pier.
I want to run maintenance
on the ship, too.
Oh my, is Papa distancing himself
from his daughter? That's not right.
Papa... are you going away?
Huh?
I understand that you'll
have to leave at some point.
That's why, while you're here,
I want you to be her Papa.
That said, we don't have
to limit it to the day you leave.
You can be her Papa forever,
since after all, I do intend
to repay you with my life...
Please don't make jokes like that...
I can feel the temperature drop
from all the cold stares.
Oh my, you sure are
popular with the ladies.
But it's been five years
since I lost my husband...
Myu, you want a Papa, too, don't you?
Huh? Papa is Papa.
Did you hear that? Papa.
Hey, emergency meeting!
This one's going to be rough!
She did say she was going to
report to the king first...
Sensei! Long time no see!
What?! Yaegashi-san?!
I'm sorry about Shimizu-kun.
But still, I'm glad you survived, Sensei.
We really have to thank Nagumo-kun.
He went to save you and the others.
And he saved a little girl, too...
Yes.
Perhaps he's remembering
his previous self.
Either that, or he's still changed,
but ever-growing.
What a reliable person.
Ahem!
Sensei? You told me earlier that you
were saved from a dangerous situation,
but how exactly?
Huh?!
I mean, since you said you almost died,
it makes me curious
about how you recovered...
W-W-W-Well, about that...
Sensei, did something happen
between you and Nagumo-kun?
No! I mean, what do
you mean by "something"?
He and I are a typical student
and teacher! Ain't no doubt!
Sensei, please calm down.
You're speaking nonsense.
Nagumo-kun, what did you do to Ai-chan...?
Sensei, what happened when
you made the report to the king?
Nagumo-kun has officially
been branded a heretic.
Why?! That's far too thoughtless!
I agree completely. Even though he's a
strong force that won't obey the church,
he did save the town of Ur after all.
But still, no matter how much
I objected, they didn't listen.
They're not supposed to be
able to ignore my objections...
If they're branding Nagumo-kun a heretic,
doesn't that mean they're denying
the Goddess of Fertility, too?
Clearly, there's something wrong.
Come to think of it, the king and other
officials seemed... somewhat odd.
That's concerning. What are they thinking?
Nagumo-kun is so strong.
Who will they send after him?
Yaegashi-san. There's something
that Nagumo-kun revealed to me.
Revealed?
Yes. About the god that
the church is worshipping
and what Nagumo-kun's goal is.
I don't have any proof,
but it's important...
I'd like to talk to you all
about this as soon as possible.
Next episode,
"Memories from the Bottom of the Sea."