In order to explore
the Sunken Ruins of Melusine,
we decided to leave Erisen for a while.
Hajime-kun?
The Sunken Ruins of Melusine...
They're supposed to be
around here somewhere.
Nature looks the same everywhere.
It's just like the sunset
I saw by the ocean in Japan.
It feels like such a long time ago,
though it hasn't even been six months yet.
Our time here has been too hectic.
Yeah.
Oh, the moon.
Hajime-san, what are you doing?
Isn't that the proof of
conquest from Gruen?
It is.
Wow, it's glowing with light!
That's pretty.
Yes, a bit mysterious.
It's a pretty presentation, unlike
the tastes of some other Liberator.
Indeed. This feels like actual fantasy;
I'm actually a bit moved.
I see, no wonder why I couldn't
find it when searching normally.
It was dumb of me to hope
I'd just stumble upon the entrance.
The flow is quite strong.
Another turbulent boat ride?!
Hajime-kun?!
It's fine.
Something's approaching from behind.
Well, it has black-red magic power;
it must be a monster.
A good moment to test my new weapons.
Good, looks like I was able
to make it more powerful. Success.
Oh, Hajime-san! Another one!
That's the fifth one. Five pentagram
symbols and five locations,
and this pendant
with some light left in it...
Coming to this place using just magic
would have been very difficult.
We would have had to notice this pattern
right away or run out of magic power.
We really have to thank Master's ship.
Indeed.
I guess this is the real starting point.
This feels more like just a cave,
not a "Sunken Ruin", but...
I'm glad it wasn't entirely underwater.
Yue.
Let Yue handle it.
What is it?
Huh? Oh... Um, it's nothing.
I see.
Looks like there's
something on the ceiling.
What is this?!
Yue.
Hajime... This is a bit embarrassing.
The water is getting gradually deeper.
This is good for you too, isn't it?
Yes, but...
Yue-san, you're looking quite cute.
Yes, the position most
recently occupied by Myu.
Oh? So, should I call you
Yue-chan from now on?
Perish, Kaori.
Why are you so violent to only me?!
Hey... Don't you think they're too weak?
Too weak?
Yeah, for monsters in a Great Labyrinth...
What?!
I'll do it!
What?! What is this?!
Shea, don't move!
More incoming!
Um, Hajime-san, I got burned.
Can you rub some medicine on me?
Are you seriously trying
to do this right now?
Yue-san and Tio-san seem to be on a
rampage, I thought we had some free time.
Bring cleansing and healing...
Heaven's Blessing.
Oh no... There goes my shot at
getting him to touch my breasts...
Hajime, it looks like
this jelly melts magic.
I see. I was wondering why
my flames lost power so quickly.
I guess even the magic
powering the flames are...
Hajime-kun!
What is that thing?!
This is finally starting
to feel like a Great Labyrinth.
Yue, go on the offensive!
I'll handle defense! Herem!
It's not over!
What is this? I'm getting monster
readings from the entire room.
So this is what a
Great Labyrinth monster is like...
Master, we can't let
it regenerate forever.
Where is its mana crystal core?
Now that you've mentioned it,
it's transparent,
but I don't see a mana crystal.
Hajime?
It's not there.
That thing has no mana crystal.
No mana crystal? Are you saying
it's not actually a monster?
What I'm seeing through my Demon Eye
is that it's black-red colored overall.
As if the whole jelly-like body
is one big mana crystal.
The whole body?
The whole room is the same color.
Maybe we're already trapped in its belly.
Time to eat!
There's no end to this!
How persistent.
Isn't there anything we can do?
Let's regain our footing!
There's an open space
underneath the ground here.
I don't know where it leads!
Brace yourselves!
Are you all right, Kaori?
Yes, I guess... Where is everybody?
We got split up.
They're all carrying smaller versions
of the Treasure Trove.
They should be able
to manage on their own.
Hey, Hajime-kun...
Why did you save me?
What are you talking
about all of a sudden?
Why did you save me, and not Yue?
Well, I thought you'd die on your own,
but Yue can take care of herself.
Also, I could tell from her look
that she wanted me to save you.
You trust her.
Of course. We're partners.
Ouch! What are you doing?
Stop wasting time being depressed,
we need to move.
We're still in a Great Labyrinth.
I was just spaced out for a moment.
Sorry.
What are we going to do now?
We just keep exploring until
we reach the bottom. What else?
Yue and the others are
probably doing the same.
Right...
Is this...?
A ship graveyard or something?
They all look like warships.
Yes...
But the biggest ship seems different.
Doesn't it look like a passenger ship?
What's going on?!
Hajime-kun! Around us!
What is this?
A-Am I in a dream?
What?!
I'll block this! Holy Shield!
I see.
I guess this isn't just a normal illusion,
but it's not entirely real either.
Hajime-kun?
Physical attacks have no effect,
but attacks including magic power work.
Seriously, what is this?
Are you all right?!
Huh? Why...
I guess the effect is the same
as long as magic power is involved,
no matter the effect or attribute.
So... Did I just kill that person...?
This isn't real. Just think of it as
an illusion that you can manipulate.
Right, yes...
I'm sorry, I was confused
for a moment, but I'm fine now.
You're always apologizing.
What? Did you say something?
No, it's nothing.
For our god!
Hail Ehit!
Heathens! Die before the glory of our god!
Kaori! We're jumping!
What?!
So, how do we get out
of this creepy place?
Maybe there's an exit?
Maybe one of the ships is an exit?
There are hundreds of ships;
we can't search every single one.
The war would end by
the time we're done searching.
Then... Maybe we can end the war?
End? Oh, you mean,
kill them all, for starters?
Oh, uh, that's not what I meant...
I like that idea. Let's go, Kaori.
What?! No, wait!
Hajime-kun, what was that?
I'm sure it's related
to these derelict ships, right?
It's probably a recreation of a war that
took place in the past, using magic.
With the added twist of attacking
the explorer of the Great Labyrinth.
I see...
That could be the concept
of this particular Great Labyrinth.
Concept?
Tio mentioned it.
Each Great Labyrinth has
a concept, set by a Liberator.
If that's true, then this one would be...
To show the tragedy of what
the crazed god can bring about?
Something like that, probably.
I'm sorry, Hajime-kun.
Don't worry about it. I know how it feels
to get almost swallowed by insanity.
I almost went insane
at the bottom of the abyss.
But you didn't, thanks to... Yue?
Who knows what would have
happened to me if I didn't meet her.
I'm jealous.
I wish I was the one to hold
you together and protect you.
That said, I don't know what
I would have been able to do.
I couldn't even keep a single promise...
Oh boy. Yue is quite a tough rival.
Ever since we came here,
you've been apologizing and
smiling like that the whole time.
What? Uh...
Hey, Kaori. Why did you come along?
Do you mean...
Are you saying I'm dragging you down?
You're dragging me down.
Kaori, what do you think about Shea?
Shea?
In the beginning,
we really treated her roughly.
I could only see Yue as someone special.
I hoped Shea would just give up quickly.
But Shea... She cried,
laughed, and got angry,
but always seemed to enjoy it.
She couldn't use magic,
she got easily overpowered,
but she always held her head up.
She never surrendered
to her feelings of inferiority.
I... I'm not surrendering...
Did you notice? After coming here,
you've been apologizing nonstop.
You're also smiling differently.
Kaori, don't look down.
Face me and look into my eyes.
I'll tell you again. I love Yue.
Even if someone else became important
to me, Yue will always be special.
If hearing that only gives you pain,
if all you can get from comparing
yourself to Yue is a sense of defeat,
then Kaori, you shouldn't be around me.
I have to speak to everyone
about something important...
Nice to meet you, Aiko Hatayama.
I have come for you.
Um, nice to meet you too.
What do you mean by "come for me"?
I have to eat dinner with my students...
No, you are going to the Divine Mountain.
What? What are you...
I see, you do not call yourself
a deity for nothing.
I am impressed that you resisted my Charm.
S-Step back!
I have no choice.
Do not worry; I will not kill you.
You are a useful pawn.
Besides...
I have to let someone know...
Next episode, "Someone Important."