I agreed to let you come
along because, like Shea,
you yourself believed that coming
with me was what's best for you.
You understood I had feelings for another,
but still you wished to stay with me.
Then you should do what you
wanted to do. That's what I thought.
But now, you don't
appear that way anymore.
Please, think about this again.
Why did you come along? Should you stay?
If it comes down to it,
I'll take you back to Yaegashi myself.
I, I...
Quite a feat, building such
a huge ship out of wood.
This again...
Kaori, keep it together.
This is going to be another terrible play.
Yes, I'll be fine.
Is this... A party?
Yeah, and not just with humans,
there are demons and beastmen here, too.
And it seems rather extravagant...
Everyone!
You all have prayed for peace and
risked your lives in war to achieve it.
I am truly happy to be able
to gather you all here today.
We were able to end this war,
with a peace treaty no less,
in my generation.
A whole year has passed, and now
I can witness this sight before me.
I cannot help but feel moved.
Is this a celebration
for the end of a war?
Given the context, that seems
to be the only explanation.
Maybe our assumption about the
theme of Melusine's trial was wrong?
I didn't know something
like this happened.
They must have worked tirelessly to
achieve peace. A great undertaking indeed.
Yes.
They couldn't have gotten
over every single grudge.
But still, they're smiling
together like that.
It has been one year since the peace
treaty was signed, which makes me think.
About how foolish this has been.
Yes, truly foolish. Exchanging
a toast with filthy animals,
discussing the future with heathens...
It was all the pinnacle of foolishness.
Do you understand?
Yes, I'm talking about you!
W-What are you talking about?!
What's going on with--
Your Highness?!
So, everyone.
Like I said at the beginning,
I'm truly glad to see
that you've all gathered here.
Evil races, forsaken by our god,
claiming to create a nation
and pretending to be on equal footing with
us humans... Such a despicable situation.
Fools who have turned their backs against
Ehit, the one and only god and creator,
to worship some worthless pagan god,
no longer need to be tolerated,
starting today!
There is no peace
without total annihilation!
That's why I'm truly glad
I could wipe out the authorities
of every nation today!
Now, true believers!
Unleash the judgment of our god!
Oh, Ehit, my lord!
Are you watching?!
Kaori...
A woman?
Stop!
Kaori, take a break.
No, I'm fine. That was hard to watch...
But anyway, is that it, though?
We didn't do anything.
I guess the idea is, to move forward,
we should go into the ship.
Maybe the point of that last vision
was to just show us what happened.
Show what kind of madness that god can
create, and then make us search the ship.
It's quite a nasty setup,
especially for locals from this world.
It would make them unable
to believe in their own god.
That last vision...
Even though the war ended,
that person betrayed everyone, right?
Seems so.
But didn't it seem a little strange?
When he came up to that stage, everyone
looked up at him with respect and love.
If he had been hiding such a
deep hatred of beastmen and demons,
would he have been able
to gather that much respect?
Yes. The way he spoke,
it seems more natural to think that
something happened to make him
suddenly change during
the one year after the war.
Well, it's god-related, that's for sure.
String?
And now there's a physical trap?
These Liberators are all quite awful...
What?!
Kaori!
Kaori, don't move!
What a damn bother!
Is that it?
Kaori! Where are you?
I'm here, Hajime-kun.
Kaori, are you all right?
I was so scared...
I see.
So, could you please console me?
W-What are you doing?
What?
Killing an enemy, of course.
Like you just tried to do.
Hajime-kun, why did you do that?
Stop talking in Kaori's voice.
Stop moving in Kaori's body.
I can see through you, the piece
of trash infesting in Kaori's body.
You might understand, but there's
nothing you can do. This woman is...
Wait! What are you doing?!
This woman is yours!
Are you going to hurt her?!
Stop talking.
Magic ammunition won't hurt Kaori's body.
It'll only cause pain to you,
the thing haunting her.
If you destroy me, it'll break her, too!
Is that what you want?!
Yes, good--
Are you insane?!
Don't you care about this woman?!
Even if I stopped attacking, you're
not going to give Kaori her body back.
And you said it yourself. If I don't
destroy you, Kaori's soul is fine, right?
Then all I have to do is make
you want to leave her body.
I'll just torture you while
being careful not to kill you.
What...
You threatened someone important to me.
Don't think you can
just vanish painlessly.
I'll do everything in
my power to keep you alive.
Y-You...
You will feel every form of pain.
But I won't let you go insane either.
You're my enemy, but...
I won't ever kill you.
Don't worry. I'll send you off properly.
That thing seems
to have left completely...
What are you doing?
Giving my answer, I guess.
Answer?
Yes, to the question
of why I came along
and whether I want to stay.
I love you, Hajime-kun. Truly.
That's why I want to stay with you.
Won't you just be tormented, though?
You're not like Shea.
You don't want Yue to be part of this.
Yeah, I do want to
have you all for myself.
I want to be your only one.
I will be jealous and
will feel inferior to Yue.
Kaori...
It'll feel painful for me at times.
Then...
But I know for sure that
I'll regret backing off here.
I know for sure that the best thing
for me is to stay by your side.
If that's what you want, Kaori,
then I have nothing more to say.
Yes...
Hajime-kun, can you repeat
that thing you said earlier?
What thing?
What did they threaten
that made you so angry?
Hmm. I don't know
what you're talking about.
Come on! Just say it!
What's this?
Is that a magic circle? Did we reach
end of the dungeon already?
Is that a problem?
No, I just didn't
expect it to end so soon.
If feels a bit too easy,
compared to the other labyrinths.
I think it was hard enough.
Besides, for the people
who grew up in this world,
who have strong faiths,
if they were shown that madness...
It could be enough to break them, I see.
Good timing.
Hey, everything all right on your side?
Yes. And you...
Are you hurt?!
Kaori-san, are you all right?
Are you injured?
What about your healing magic?
I'm fine, thank you for your concern.
I'm actually mostly just being spoiled.
Hey Kaori, can you walk now?
Actually, I was able to the entire time.
Get off. Now.
So, what happened? Hmm? Speak up, Master.
Did you do the lovey-dovey
with Kaori? Lovey!
Oh, haven't felt that in a while...
So, what happened?
I just shared a little kiss
with Hajime-kun.
What? Really?! Who started it?
I did.
Hajime-kun got angry for me, so
I couldn't hold back, and I went for it.
Wow, just like me!
Ah.
I thought you'd turn tail and run.
Yes, Hajime-kun recommended
that I do the same.
But the differences between Yue and I
are kind of old news anyway.
So you're taking a "so what" attitude?
You could say that.
After all, me coming here
was already an act of defiance.
When the gap between us became apparent,
I just forgot about that for a moment.
I definitely showed him
a miserable side of me.
You should have just given up.
Are you threatened by me?
Don't get carried away.
I know I'm someone important
to Hajime-kun now.
Now I'm going to try
to become someone special.
No matter what anyone says.
I see. In that case, I will accept
your challenge, just as before.
Yeah!
Found it. The power of restoration.
Please, don't cling to that god.
Make your own decisions,
move forward on your own feet.
Happiness only comes
to those with a free will.
The proof of conquest...
Now we have four of them. We can take
on the labyrinth at the Sea of Trees!
What? Forced ejection?!
Yue, spatial magic!
Where are we?
No!
Not only is it unkillable, it melts
anything and can even control the sea?
What are we supposed to do?
Now what? Last time,
we attacked it with fire.
I know!
We can assume we can't
use Yue and Tio's fire magic.
In that case...
Hajime, any ideas?
There's only one way
to use fire while underwater.
We'll vaporize that jelly faster
than it can regenerate.
If it works, we should
be able to take it out.
Really, Hajime-kun?!
But I need time.
I just need three minutes.
If we can just hold
on for three minutes...
It's trying to swallow us whole!
If it comes down to it,
I'll transform to protect everyone!
Dammit, I need more time...
Hey, Hajime, my boy.
Lemme give you a hand.
Leh-san?!
That's right,
it's Leh-san, your old buddy.
What are you doing? You can take out the
Devourer if you have three minutes, right?
I don't understand, but thanks!
Hey there, Shea.
Leh-san? What's going on?
Well, I was just hanging around when
I noticed a huge and familiar magic power.
After sensing trouble, I rushed in.
Those fish... And the "Devourer"?
I guided those fish using my powers.
Huh.
The Devourer is an ancient monster
that lives in the sea,
a natural disaster of sorts.
Some say it's the ancestor of monsters.
It's done!
Eat up and die!
Warn me before making explosions!
I'm sorry, Leh-san!
It's been three days since Ai-chan
went to the Divine Mountain...
Ishtar-san said she'd be back very soon.
Lily won't come back either.
The king said there's
nothing to worry about, but...
Speaking of which,
Nia-san is gone too, right?
Yes...
It's concerning when these things
happen all at once like this.
Hey, let's go ask
the guards what's going on.
I thought so too,
but I couldn't find them anywhere.
What's wrong?
Meld-san.
It's about Ai-chan...
I heard Aiko went to the Divine Mountain
to discuss the issue of Hajime Nagumo.
She went and hasn't come back.
Hasn't come back?
All her guards are gone, too.
Several others have suddenly gone missing.
I knew it...
Actually, we're doing
our own investigation, too.
My lord feels that what you are
trying to do is an inconvenience.
He believes that what your student
is trying to do is far more interesting.
Therefore, until the right time comes,
you will temporarily leave
my lord's game board.
Next episode, "A New Vow."