The invasion of the royal capital
was orchestrated by Eri Nakamura,
who had a shared interest with the demons.
Using her natural talent in necromancy,
she used the corpse of the female demon
that she encountered in the Orcus
Great Labyrinth to carry a message.
That is how she managed
to get in contact with the demons.
Then, in exchange for helping
the demons access the capital
and murdering the knighthood
and her classmates,
she asked for freedom
for herself and Kouki Amanogawa.
Also, it is believed that she did not
murder all of her classmates at once
because her unique magic,
"Spirit Binding,"
can only be used one at a time,
immediately after the target's death.
The invasion was a failure, and Eri
Nakamura escaped with the demons.
The brainwashing and murder of our king
is believed to be the work of the nun
from the Divine Mountain, who also
kidnapped Aiko Hatayama, not Eri Nakamura.
However, this nun is still missing.
We are seeking more information.
Out of the transferees, we've lost
Daisuke Hiyama, Reiichi Kondo, and...
...Kaori Shirasaki...
Where's Sensei?
Aiko-san is taking a break now.
I see.
Hajime.
Kaori will be fine. Please go to Aiko.
Yue...
I'm sorry.
Nagumo-kun.
You don't have to smile.
You care about your students more
than anything, and I killed them.
I'm sure that's weighing on your mind.
To be honest, it's not something
I can easily get over.
What Hiyama-kun did can't be forgiven,
but I wanted him to live
to atone for his sins, if possible.
But I also understand the anger you felt.
Besides, I have no right
to criticize you, Nagumo-kun...
Sensei, you just helped. Don't blame
yourself as if you did it all on your own.
That doesn't matter!
I helped Tio-san with the full knowledge
that it could kill them!
Do you regret it?
No.
I knew what I was doing with Tio-san.
I couldn't let the church
continue doing what it was doing.
I wanted to help you.
I had to stop them from doing
horrible things to my students.
So I... I don't have any regrets.
Sensei, will you continue
to be our sensei?
Huh?
If you can continue to be our sensei,
can I make a very selfish request?
Selfish request?
I want you to keep feeling guilty.
I want you to carry that weight.
When you fight properly,
carry the weight properly,
worry properly, and complain properly,
that's very human, blindingly so.
Those are emotions I can no longer feel,
so you can be my example
of what it means to be human.
I'll keep my eyes on you.
That way, when I make it back to Japan,
I can live a proper, human life.
Nagumo-kun...
That said, if you're in too much pain
and feel like you're about to break,
and there's nobody else to rely on...
In that case, you can cry on my back.
You... You're such a...
All right, then, I'll take you up on that.
Here you go, Sensei.
Stop!
You seem tired from
your workout, Kouki-san.
Lily... No, it's nothing.
You, on the other hand, haven't slept much
at all these past five days, have you?
I'm still all right. It's a lot of work,
but the people who are truly hurt
are the citizens who've lost
their loved ones or livelihoods.
Well, you've also lost your father--
It's all right.
I'm sorry.
How is Shizuku?
The same.
She behaves normally most of the time,
but oftentimes,
she'll look up and keep staring.
She's waiting for them.
To be honest, I can't trust Nagumo.
I'm actually hoping
Shizuku doesn't see them.
K-Kouki-san! Up there!
Is something coming from above?!
What? What are you saying?
Everyone, watch out!
Something's coming from above!
Nagumo-kun!
Hey, Yaegashi. Good, you're alive.
Nagumo-kun, where's Kaori?
Why isn't Kaori here?
Umm, well, she'll be here any moment now.
But, well, she looks
a little different now.
It's totally not my fault,
so don't get mad at me, okay?
Wait, what? What is it? What?
I'm worried now.
What are you talking about?
What did you do to Kaori?!
Hajime-kun!
This voice?!
Catch me, please!
Huh?
Who are you?!
Wait, Kouki!
Shizuku?
Kaori...?
Kaori, is that you?
Yes! It's me, Kaori!
Kaori Shirasaki,
Shizuku-chan's best friend.
I might look a little different,
but I'm very much alive!
Kaori...
Kaori!
I'm sorry I worried you.
I'm fine. Everything's fine.
I'm so glad, I'm so glad...!
So, what is going on?
To explain simply,
we used magic to protect Kaori's soul
and implanted it in Noint's repaired body.
I see. I don't get it.
Well, Shizuku-chan. We learned
before that the magic we normally use
is an inferior copy of the magic from
the era called the God's Age, right?
Yes, the magic that's mentioned in the
creation mythology of this world, right?
The magic that can work
on a more fundamental level,
unlike the elemental magic we use now...
Wait,
are you saying Nagumo-kun can use
God's Age magic to manipulate souls?
So you used that to protect Kaori's soul
from death and put it in another body.
Yes. I knew you'd get it, Shizuku-chan.
But why that body?
Was Kaori's original body ruined?
We fixed Kaori's body perfectly, and we
could have put the soul back there, too.
Then why...
Because I asked.
Huh?
I wanted to be stronger.
You know Kaori.
She won't stop once she starts asking.
Kaori's original body is stored
in a frozen state using magic.
She can go back to it whenever she wants.
I see.
Kaori always did do the craziest
things, but this one takes the cake.
Sorry I worried you.
It's fine. You're alive,
that's what matters.
Nagumo-kun, Yue-san, Shea-san, Tio-san.
Thank you very much
for saving my best friend.
I will never forget this debt.
If there is anything I can do, please ask.
I will do whatever it takes
to pay you back..
You're so righteous, as always.
Well, don't take it so seriously.
We saved our friend, that's all.
That said, you did care
about my feelings, too
and used your precious medicine on Kouki.
If you broke down, Yaegashi, that
would make Kaori annoying to deal with.
Annoying? That's mean, Hajime-kun.
Besides...
According to a certain sensei,
I should avoid living a sad life.
I can't do everything,
but I can do some things.
Nagumo-kun...
What do you mean?!
Are you saying we've been pawns
in the god's game this whole time?!
Why didn't you tell us sooner?!
If I told you, would you have believed it?
That god is crazy and
what you all are doing is meaningless.
Not only would you have not believed me,
you probably would have criticized me.
But... if we're going to be fighting
alongside each other from now on...
Whoa, hold on. I'm not going
to go after the guy to fight him.
Wait, you don't care what happens
to the people of this world?!
I don't have any power to wield
for people whom I've never met.
Why not?! You're stronger than me!
Since you have so much power, shouldn't
you be using it to do what's right?
Since I have power. Right.
That's why you end up with your face in
the dirt at the most important moments.
What?
You don't do things because
you have the power to do so.
You have to want to accomplish something,
then gather and wield power to do it.
Your willpower is just too weak for that.
Hajime.
What is it, Yue?
Are you going to leave them like that?
They have their sensei with them,
it should be all right.
That's not what I mean.
If we leave them now,
are you going to be okay?
Yes.
That's good to hear.
Hey, Shizuku-chan!
Kaori, can we sit with you?
Of course.
Excuse me, great sister!
Great sister?
Nagumo-kun, where are you going next?
You're going to a Great Labyrinth, right?
Yes, the great forest to the east.
The Great Labyrinth is there.
In that case, you will be passing through
the Empire's territory, correct?
Lily.
I guess so.
In that case, may I come along?
Why?
After the invasion, we have so much
we need to discuss with the Empire.
We need to meet
with them as soon as possible.
I don't mind taking you along, but
I'm not going into the imperial capital.
I definitely won't be joining you
when you meet the emperor.
Of course, I wouldn't ask so much of you.
In that case, we're coming along, too.
We can't leave Lily
in the hands of someone
who doesn't care
what happens to this world.
We'll provide protection along the way.
If Nagumo won't do anything, then
I have to be the one to save this world!
To do that, I need power!
The power of God's Age magic!
If I follow you,
I can get that magic, right?!
I mean, I can tell you where it is.
Go ahead and get it on your own.
You, follow me? That'd be such a bother.
But, Nagumo-kun, didn't you
say that in our current state,
if we went to the labyrinth,
we'd all immediately die?
Huh? Uh... I mean, I was useless,
but I was able to pull it off.
I'm sure you'll be fine. Yep.
It's impossible, isn't it?
Can I join you, too? As a favor.
Just having one God's Age magic
would make a world of a difference
when tackling the other Great Labyrinths.
Me too, Nagumo-kun. I want to be stronger,
so that I can talk to Eri again!
Please, Nagumo. I want to at least be
able to protect myself and my friends.
Nagumo.
We leave at dawn.
Thanks Nagumo-kun!
We're definitely clearing
the Great Labyrinth!
Oh, yeah!
--Hajime-san, are you sure?
--As long as we work together...
Yeah, I thought they'd get in the way,
but if coming along can grant them powers,
I'm starting to think
that's not such a bad idea.
Hajime, so terrifying.
Master is truly great. His thinking
is beyond human boundaries.
What do you mean?
He's trying to use his classmates
as meat shields and bait.
Huh?
Hajime.
Here, here.
Hajime-san, say ah!
H-Hajime-kun...
Me too! Ah!
Master, please eat mine, too. Say ah.
Just this once.
What is this atmosphere?
I've never been so uncomfortable.
Pervert.
Wh-What? No! Why would you say that?!
I'm just eating normally!
You're enjoying the taste of Hajime.
No I'm not! Look at Tio!
She's the pervert!
Look at how she's licking
that fork like nobody's watching!
Tio, stop that immediately.
I can't help it.
Master still won't kiss me.
Oh! I remember! Master! I demand a reward!
Huh?
I helped protect your sensei.
I deserve a reward.
What's that?!
Not fair!
What do you want? I'll warn you,
I'll only do what I can do.
Don't worry, I won't be unreasonable.
I just want you to brutalize my rear,
like you did when we first met.
Denied.
Why?! That's totally reasonable!
I just want you to pierce my behind with
a dark, stiff, thick rod, like before!
Stop intentionally inviting
a misunderstanding!
Well, is it really a misunderstanding?
She's not actually lying.
It really did pierce her.
Yeah, Nagumo-kun didn't hold back at all.
Hajime-san, "misunderstanding"
is a bit of stretch.
Hajime, you're responsible for
her perversion. It can't be avoided.
N-Nagumo-kun...
What did you do to poor Tio-san...?
Huh?
All right, Tio. Here's your reward.
Let's go with this one. It's harder,
thicker, and heavier than the last one.
W-Wait, Master! What I meant was...
Don't be so modest.
You'll be instantly
and eternally satisfied,
you won't even have time to moan.
The master is serious!
Yue, Shea, Kaori! Please stop Master!
Hajime?
Hajime.
Today is going to be another long day.
Let's wrap this journey up
quickly and go pick up Myu.
You two are alone again.
Not fair! Why always only Yue?
Good morning.
Come on, Nagumo! Let's go!
We're clearing the Great Labyrinth!
I can't wait!
You all are too eager.
Nagumo-san, thank you for your help.
Yeah.
We'll take care of the capital.
Everyone, please be safe.
You too, Sensei.
Well, here we go.