I've brought him.
Come in.
Well, well. If it isn't King Albert.
Dolph!
What's the meaning of this?!
I hoped to enjoy a meal together with you.
Ah...
Unfortunately, it seems
there won't be any for you.
Restrain him.
Yes sir.
So that's what you're after?!
Now, what do you say we end
this game of hide-and-seek
with your cute princess, King Albert?
No... Albert.
Did you spot her?
No, not yet.
I'll look over here.
Listen up, men. We're after the wood cube.
Try to not kill the princess.
You think you can get away with this, Dolph?!
Get away?
Just who will there be to punish me?
I'm afraid you have no allies anymore, Albert.
This little trip around the world of yours...
To me, it was the perfect opportunity.
Everyone here besides you and
the Princess are my underlings.
But why?! Why betray me, Dolph?!
That's not very kind of you, Albert.
I'm very thankful for all you've done for me.
You took me in and raised me from an orphan...
...and even appointed me as
the commander of your kingdom.
Then why?!
Did you think, all this time I supported you,
that I had no ambitions of my own?
This is God's just retribution, Albert.
Lord Dolph!
We've found the Princess!
Okay! On my way!
In that case, you best be quick to think
of your dying wish, King Albert.
You traitorous scum!
What are you doing, you fools?!
Have you forgotten your place?!
Well, well. If it isn't Princess Starla.
It's such a pleasure to see you.
Dolph, you bastard!
Do you have any damn clue what you've done?!
As usual, such a vulgar mouth despite that face.
Of course I know what I've done.
I've taken King Albert's wood cube.
Once I have yours as well,
I'll be able to revive the ancient weapon.
That is, all so I can become
the next king of Fey Kingdom!
You'll find no allies anywhere here.
You have no escape.
Now, hand it over without a fight!
H-He's dead!
Princess! Hurrah! Princess! Hurrah!
Princess! Hurrah!
You bastards!
You'll owe me for life!
All right! Take me to my father!
Wood cube?
Wasn't the Princess protecting this?
No... Could this really be?
Huh?
Wh-What?!
Th-This could make me the king!
N-No... Hold on. Calm down. I need a smoke...
I've served as a solder for 12 long years.
I thought... this would be the rest of my life.
But now, my chance has come...
Forget it.
Even if I become the king,
it's not like I have any plans.
And even having both of the cubes,
I wouldn't know how to call the ancient weapon.
Ah-choo!
Nooo!!!
"My Ordinary Life 27"
Good morning...
"Lottery"
Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes!
Mio! I win third prize
in the lottery! 100,000 yen!
Seriously?!
Are you gonna treat me?
What should I do? What to buy?
A house or something? Yeah, right.
Yuuko...
Hmm?
This... is from last year.
"Toki" "Haya"
Don't sweat it.
Lotteries are, like, impossible to win.
"Present"
It's fine... You don't have to console me...
Besides, it's your birthday today, isn't it?
Here.
Huh? Really? A present?
Thank you!
Can I open it?
Yeah, but it's nothing much.
Just something we had around the house.
That's fine! It's the feeling that counts!
"Octopus & Wasabi Flavor"
"Octopus Wasabi"
"Faculty Room"
"Faculty Room" Miss Sakurai?
Ah, Mr. Takasaki. Good morning.
Good morning.
Miss Sakurai... Can you do anything
about that Aioi character?
"That Aioi character"
Miss Sakurai... Can you do anything
about that Aioi character?
"That Aioi character"
She doesn't even try
to do her homework.
Uh, I-I'm sorry!
I think a stern talking from her
homeroom teacher might help.
Uh, sorry... I'll see if
I can say something to her.
W-Well, I need to get going
to my first period class.
I'm counting on you.
Excuse me.
I'm so sorry!
Are you all right? Did any spill on you?
No, I'm perfectly fine.
"My Ordinary Life 28"
I so just want to protect her!
--I'm really so sorry!
--It's been 26 years of my life
--No, no. It's nothing at all.
--lacking with any presence of a woman.
To me, Miss Sakurai is like a bamboo shoot
suddenly sprouting in the garden.
No, no. It's not right for a teacher like me
to bring love into the workplace.
Keep it together, Manabu Takasaki!
Did she forget this?
Miss Sakurai!
You forgot your black folder.
Oh, thank you, Mr. Takasaki...
But I have my folder right here...
Eh?
Mr. Takasaki! Where are you taking my folder?
Ah! I-I'm sorry.
Well then, excuse me.
My black folder...
I wish I could invite her to pick mushrooms.
I wonder if Miss Sakurai even has a boyfriend?
Judging by no ring on her finger,
I can't imagine she's married.
Does that mean I still have a chance?
What's her favorite music?
Her favorite animal?
Her favorite sport? Her favorite vegetable?
Ah! What am I thinking?!
I'm impure! That's impure, Manabu Takasaki!
How can I be a role-model
to the students like this?!
Mr. Takasaki? Are you troubled by
some situation with the students?
But, it should be fine if
I just ask her favorite food.
"What's your favorite thing
to eat, Miss Sakurai?"
"Um, I like almost everything."
"Oh, really? How about shiitake mushrooms?"
"They're good grilled or boiled."
"That's true... What about fried?"
"Of course! Fried is okay, too!"
"I bet they taste good fried."
I can do this!
Act natural. Just act natural, Manabu Takasaki.
Nice and calm, just like
I'm talking to my eggplants.
Miss Sakurai?
Yes? What can I do for you?
Sorry for stopping you over and over again.
I don't suppose you have a boyfriend?
What the hell am I saying?!
I'm a moron! A huge moron! I'm an idiot!
I don't have one.
I don't have one... I don't have one...
I don't have one...
Sp-- Sp-- Sp--
"Takasaki" Sp-- Sp-- Sp--
Sprouting!
U-Um, Mr. Takasaki?
Sorry for asking a silly question.
It's all right in the end!
Miss Sakurai. Best of luck with
your first period class.
Thanks. I hope yours goes well, too.
Thanks.
Well, excuse me.
I hope yours goes well, too...
You're very spirited today.
Helvetica Standard.
Wait! Please!
G-Give me back my scythe!
If I don't pawn off this scythe
for food, I'll starve and die!
Oh no, a river!
I did it!
Please give it back to me!
Oh, crap!
First comes rock, then your hand delivers...
What's it gonna be, no cheats!
Rock-paper-scissors!
Yay! I won!
Thanks!
...and that's not all!
...add coconut milk...
...for tomorrow's weather...
Miracle's in a pinch!
But I've got more where that came from!
"Imagination" "Octopus Wasabi"
"Imagination"
You know what I bet you've
never ever thought about?
What? What?
Travel diaries of a quirky office lady.
Just a little.
"Rushing On a Train Is Dangerous"
Mio! Mai! The train is leaving! Hurry!
W-Wait! No!
Sweet!
We're somehow safe!
You're the only one that made it.
Selamat Tinggal...
[Malay for "Goodbye."]
"What to Pick?"
Keep the orders coming.
One albacore.
--Yellowtail. A hamachi.
--Keep the orders coming.
Tuna and a fluke fin.
One eel for me.
So, one albacore and...
I forget.
He forgot...
"My Ordinary Life 29"
Oh, hello!
H-Hello... Um, what do you want?
Well...
H-Hey! What do you think you're doing?!
Well, that's so weird and interesting!
I-It's not weird at all! It's totally normal!
Keys are the latest big accessory!
How'd you do that?
--Tell me, tell me!
--Give it back! Give it back to me!
--Just let me see it!
Fine. I'll just do this.
Bye.
Why?!
Sorry, sorry! I'm just kidding.
It's not funny at all! Give it back to me!
Which is it?
In your bag!
Wow! You're right!
Now for question two!
Eh...?
Kenta's mom went out and bought ten apples.
Out of those, she later ate three.
She then gave four of the rest
to their neighbor Yumiko.
So where is your arm?
In your bag!
Wow! Another perfect answer!
Please, give it back to me.
And now, for the final question.
If you get it right, you can win an arm.
Eh?! It was mine to begin with!
Don't you want an arm?
I do...
All right. Start by saying "Bag" ten times.
Bag, bag, bag, bag, bag,
bag, bag, bag, bag, bag!
What sits behind the picture when you draw?
A ba-- I mean, a board!
Bzzt!
Eh?!
The answer is "paper."
N-No! That's not fair!
Just kidding! Just kidding...
Would you please stop following me around?
All right, all right. Sorry.
Oops. It came off.
It came off!
Mio!
Walk home together?
Hmm? Coming back from college, Sis?
Wow... You won't believe the weird girl I met.
What was she like?
Her arm came off.
Eh?
There was a key on her back.
What's that mean?
I'm not joking either.
Eh? That's weird.
"Word-Time"
I want people to see me and think
"Oh? He looks pretty cool."
"My Ordinary Life 30"
Nano! Here it comes!
"My Ordinary Life 30" Okay!
Magic ball!
Well, she's just a kid. What'd you expect?
I win!
I lost!
What's with these guys?
This is totally not how to play.
Sakamoto! How many points do I get?
What?!
I'm throwing it, Hakase!
Okay!
She hasn't even thrown yet!
I-Is she trying to kill someone?!
Sakamoto! How many points was that?
You, too?!
She swung again!
You're up next, Sakamoto.
Why do I have to?!
I can't even hold a bat with these hands!
Aww...
What did you think I had for hands?
Can't you see how soft and
squishy my paws are?
Kids like you are so...
Well, you know...
Playing with you two is dangerous,
so I'll just watch.
Don't count on me to play.
Why don't you just play catch?
Okay!
Got it, Coach!
"Coach"?
Coach! We only have one glove!
You don't need one, do you?
Coach! My hand won't fit in the glove!
It goes on the other hand!
Coach!
You guys are hopeless without me.
Hakase! Here it comes!
Bring it on!
Aw, geez. Where in the world did it go?
And then the teacher got mad at me.
Well, you can't really blame them.
Agreed.
Mai, you think so, too?
They didn't need to take it that far.
Maybe not, but you need to be careful now.
Yeah, who knows what will happen next.
Oh, thank you.
Oh! Gentleman!
So do you mind letting me borrow it, Mai?
Sure.
--Oh! That's perfect!
--I wonder if that's the girl my sister met?
--I'm so glad that we're friends!
"Birthday Present"
"Octopus Wasabi"
Wake in the morning, teeth get a brushing
Before you know it, it's ten at night
Another day was full of laughter
Another day filled with joy
Goofing with friends and acting so silly
Making a ruckus and then I see
A glimpse from you and then our eyes meet
Coincidence, or not?
I won't ever admit it's first love
That's not something I would say
Hey, I'll see you again tomorrow too.
When I close my eyes I see
My vision sparkling, filled with you
Wasn't it so much fun today?
Ah, I think I'm in love
I'm so happy I'm so happy
Nice to meet you, awakening love
I'll see you again tomorrow too
Good night
I'll see you again soon in my dreams
I'm Wood Cube.
Only my master is able
to obtain the ancient weapon.
The next My Ordinary Life is Episode 8.
"Narration: Norio Wakamoto"
Look forward to it!