"Shinonome Lab"
What a beautiful day!
It's about time I wake Hakase up.
Maybe I'll go for a stroll
somewhere after breakfast?
Huh? Hey!
I realized just this very moment
I think I might have fallen in love
24 hours a day of you you you
I can't get you out of my head!
Something (something) feels different now
With you (together) it's awkward conversation
Is it (mutual love) no it's one-sided love
Uh-oh I think our eyes just met!
What is this anxious nervous feeling?
My train of thought is tangled with confusion...
This kind of thing is a first for me
Could it be a fever and I'm sick?
With a sudden twist it's awakened love
There's a fire in my cheeks and my face is all red
Th-Th-This can't be real, my hands are trembling
Is this what people mean when they talk about "love"?
I-I-I'm stuttering non-stop talking to you
Awkward silence and then mumble-mumble-mo
I wanna (I wanna) know how you feel about me
O-O-O-One one-sided love
First love! Every day on the path to school
Sparkle-sparkle dazzling I DO fall in love!
It's like I'm flying through the sky
O-O-O-One one-sided love
"My Ordinary Life 31"
Mio, Mai! Selamat pagi!
Oh, Yuuko. Good morning.
Good morning.
It's so sunny today.
Even though yesterday they said it would rain.
This type of weather is perfect
for buying a keyboard.
Get it?
Wh-Wh-What? No reaction?
Th-These guys... They're so calm it's scary!
But maybe... Could they think
I really want to go buy a keyboard?
Oh well. What a shame.
Maybe that joke was too hard for them.
I'll just have to make my jokes
easier to understand.
Okay!
Gosh, it's so hot out!
But the weather's been so spotty...
...it'll give you patchy hair loss!
Get it?
Gah!
Scary! So scary!
The virtual world is scary!
But, yeah...
It wouldn't be very funny if
someone you know is going bald.
Come back!
No more jokes like that.
All right!
Is it time I unsheathed it?
My secret weapon?!
Hey, hey!
What's a thousand-leg insect
that always asks for help?
That would be...
A centiplead!
Get it?
I'm shocked!
I'm so shocked...
What's with these two?
How can they keep such poker faces?
No, wait!
What if... they just didn't hear me?
Shucks! I guess it's nobody's fault, then.
Okay!
Hey, hey, hey!
What's a thousand-leg insect
that always asks for help?
They call it... a centiplead!
Get it?!
I-I didn't think they'd be such tough guys...
No... At this point they're more like monsters!
Maybe...
This is their way of saying
this isn't good enough?
That I can... That I caaaan...
...do better?!
If I give up now...
If I admit defeat here...
I'll betray their expectations!
So...
I won't give up!
I'll never back down!
A tree fell in the forest, but don't worry!
It's oakey-dokey!
My bomb shelter is a blast!
Mimes use "V" as a conversation peace!
I'm sorry, mascara!
Let's make up!
So basically...
You can just substitute the X in the equation
then plug and chug the answer.
Then this Y over here...
"Attack the stones. Protect your balls."
"Go+Soccer Club 5" President.
Ogi! It's been so long since
you've shown your face!
You've been like a ghost
these past three months.
How are you? Good?
Yeah...
You came at the perfect time!
We're totally bored here!
Want to play a game?
How about it? Some Ready-Set-Go?
I came to leave the club.
"Popcorn"
"Word-Time"
Why is it that right before a movie starts,
you get the sudden urge
to clear your throat?
But then, they just--
Weboshii! Fe!
Have you seen Sasahara?
Sasahara?
Yeah, I saw him going up the stairs to the roof.
Thanks!
Misato's so busy this morning.
That's youth for you.
Should we go and spy on her?
We might get to see something really juicy!
"My Ordinary Life 32"
In the deep blue sky, clouds drift
and linger above. It was a right hand.
Sasahara.
What a masterpiece!
Hey, Sasahara! Do you even
know what you've done?
The weather was nice so I wrote
a poem up here on the roof.
That's not what I mean. It's this. Look.
Don't you even recognize it?
Is that not one of mine?
Why do you have it, Misato Tachibana?
Don't misunderstand!
You tossed it like trash so I picked it up.
No, no. I never tossed it.
I dropped it by accident.
And this is not trash.
It's a handker--
Shut up! Everything of yours is trash!
How did you know it was me who dropped it?
Your house is in the opposite direction.
And you even ironed it.
D-Don't be stupid. You've got it all wrong.
I was wandering around
thinking about the world.
I just ended up near your street, that's all!
Thank you for this, Misato Tachibana.
You sure drop a lot of things in the morning.
I must not realize it myself, I suppose.
It'll be a problem if you keep
littering around the city!
B-But I guess I could just pick up after you...
Don't get the wrong idea!
I'm only doing it to keep our streets clean!
Geez... Misato is the same as ever.
Weboshii...
What should I do with this?
Wh-Why did you pick that up?!
What should I do?
Just leave it somewhere!
But what should I do?
I said just leave it somewhere!
Things that are cool!
Super-car bicycle!
"Warning"
I give up...
"Daiku Security" I give up...
"Daiku Security" It's over...
"Daiku Security"
Help isn't coming.
"My Ordinary Life 33"
"Emergency"
There's no God...
No Buddha...
Yesterday...
"Ady-Ade-Adios"
...was pork cutlets?
Well... Whatever.
"Open" "Close"
Huh...?
How long has it been...?
I think I...
I fell asleep.
Well... Whatever.
Should we play shiritori?
Mandarin.
Oh... Sorry.
Say that again?
That's okay...
K... K... K...
Can I say something random?
Eggplant.
Eggplant!
She's dead!
Help isn't coming!
Sleep paralysis...
"Go+Soccer Club 6"
Now it's just you and me, Sekiguchi.
If we don't get a third member,
our club will get disbanded.
If only we could think of a way
to recruit some more members.
President?
What does our club even do?
Oh, man! I thought you had
a good idea or something!
We don't do anything really.
"Start"
"Start" On your mark.
Get set!
Bang!
Helvetica Standard.
Hey! Quit it!
Stop pulling my uniform!
Come on already, Seki!
Give me your uniform!
B-But I didn't even score one point today!
It's fine! This is the last uniform
you'll wear before you retire!
But my uniform is worthless
since I can't even score a point!
That's not true!
You're the one that inspired me
to get into soccer!
Wait! Fine, fine already!
Just let me take it off on my own time!
Let go of me first!
All right...
Got you!
"This is my way of living!!"
I'm sorry...
"Tail"
Got it? You need to start
respecting your elders.
Okay...
Sheesh. What a difficult child.
Shoot! This is so much fun!
I got it! I got it!
"Go+Soccer Club 7"
At first I wanted to make a brand new sport
combining Go and Soccer.
That's why I formed this club.
But...
That's as far as I took it.
"My Ordinary Life 34"
Draw a boomerang...
Draw a triangle... Draw a rectangle.
Hakase! It's time for bed!
Okay!
Hakase, were you eating snacks?
I didn't eat anything.
Why are you looking away from me?
I think because it's away from you.
You're not making any sense.
"Yummy Snack"
"SnaQ"
See, look! Why are you
eating snacks before bed?
That... wasn't even me.
Who's the one with crumbs all over her face?
I think I caught a cold.
What's that? How many times have
I told you no snacks before bed?
It's not my fault!
Sakamoto forced me to eat them!
Look at his snot bubble. Funny.
Don't try to change the subject!
Geez...
You need to brush your teeth before you sleep.
I brushed my teeth already!
That was before you ate all those snacks.
Yes, but I did brush my teeth.
What are you embarrassed about?
Brushing once is good enough, isn't it?
No, it's not. You ate snacks afterwards.
Did you even brush your teeth?
I brushed them properly.
But... But...
I'm all ready and set for bed.
You're the only one here who isn't.
But you're a robot and
won't even get cavities!
Nano! Um, um...
Maybe you'll get a small cavity...
Is that true?
It's true.
It's a lie...
Oh! But you might rust or something!
Rust...
Um, I'll add a feature to let you get cavities!
Don't worry! I'll really add it!
Is that a promise?
For real this time!
Come on, Nano! Let's go brush our teeth!
Okay. But that's twice now for me.
It's already ten o'clock!
It sure is.
--Today was so much fun!
--Yeah, yeah...
So happy!
Wake in the morning, teeth get a brushing
Before you know it, it's ten at night
Another day was full of laughter
Another day filled with joy
Goofing with friends and acting so silly
Making a ruckus and then I see
A glimpse from you and then our eyes meet
Coincidence, or not?
I won't ever admit it's first love
That's not something I would say
Hey, I'll see you again tomorrow too.
When I close my eyes I see
My vision sparkling, filled with you
Wasn't it so much fun today?
Ah, I think I'm in love
I'm so happy I'm so happy
Nice to meet you, awakening love
I'll see you again tomorrow too
Good night
I'll see you again soon in my dreams
"A Trivial Miracle"
Sheesh...
I wish Sasahara would take
things seriously for once...
We're identical twins, dude!
Dude!
H-Hot, hot, hot!
Hot, hot!
Th-The next My Ordinary Life is Episode 9!
"Narration: Tomokazu Seki"
L-Look forward to-- Hot, hot!