"Vacant Lot" "No Dumping"
It's so sparkly!
Hey. What are you doing?
Ah! Ah, Sakamoto!
Ah! Don't go over there!
You've been shedding so much lately.
Your hair might get all over it.
What's the deal? Am I a nuisance now?
I'm changing, so please step outside.
Greatest friendship
Super duper harmony
(na na na na na na na)
Hey! I'll say it
You are my best best friend
(bright) Every time I poke fun and tease you
(shine) You come and tease me back some more
(lan lan lan) There ain't
no better feeling in the world
(why) Even when bad things sometimes happen
(fine) I forget all of them around you
(lan lan lan) We'll forever let the good times roll
It's not a problem being with you
every hour of the day
As if we're twins, child-parent,
or a pair of cloned cells
Doesn't a friendship this good
make love not so needed anymore?
Wait hold on this and that
are totally totally different things
(fight) Even after we've had a fight
(down) Or when I feel down in the dumps
(shock) All the times I wanted to be alone
Before I know it there sitting beside me
my wonderful friend till the end
Why is it, I wanna be at your side?
Whenever we're together,
time flies 100 times faster
It's so fun with you,
I think it's almost too much fun
It's cuz you're such a good friend! Hey!
(na na na na na na na)
What's going on? Uh-oh we're synchronizing man!
It's always a wild time,
we make the people 'round us crazy
What time is it now? I think it's yodelayheehoo
What's that even mean?
SO-RE-DO-SHI-RA-
Unbelievably, how to put it, awesome!
No matter what happens
we are gonna be friends! Woohoo!
Greatest friendship
Super duper harmony
cha chara chara cha cha-n
"My Ordinary Life 56"
Sakamoto!
Look! It fits me perfectly!
Th-That's because it's made to fit,
so of course it does.
How is it?
Well, it looks good on you.
That's not what I mean! That's not what I mean!
D-Does it...
...make me look... like a normal girl?
Well, I guess you look like
the other girls around here.
Sakamoto!
I love you, Sakamoto!
I love you!
Ah! Your fur will stick!
What's with you today?
It's school! School!
I might even make some friends there!
You're not making any sense.
Oh, hey, Nano.
After school, do you want
to grab some ice cream?
Sure, I'd love to go.
What about some karaoke afterwards?
Huh? Um...
But I've never been there before...
I'll show you what to do!
Let's all go together!
S-Sure...
Okay...
Just like that!
--Morning, Nano.
--Oh, Hakase!
Good morning!
Look at this, Hakase!
How is it? Does it suit me?
Um... Yeah! It's cool!
Hakase!
Hakase looks good, too! In pajamas!
Am I cool?
Hakase is very cool!
She's wearing the same as always.
Sakamoto!
--Sakamoto is cool, too!
--Not you too!
Handkerchief, check!
Student card, check!
Textbooks, check!
Notebook, check!
Pencil box, check!
Mechanical pencil, check!
Pencil lead, check!
Good! I didn't forget anything!
Hakase?
You did forget something.
Eh? What would that be?
What if you get hungry?
Snickers!
Hakase!
I left breakfast and lunch in the kitchen,
so eat those when you're ready.
Okay.
Also, I'll do the laundry when I get home
so you don't have to worry about that.
Hey, what time will you get out of school?
Around 3:30 I think.
I'll shop for dinner on the way back,
so I should be here around 5 o'clock.
Five o'clock...
Hmm?
I didn't tell you that?
By 5 o'clock, it's nighttime...
Yes, but that's how school works.
I'll be go--
Um, Hakase?
On second thought, you can't go!
What? You just said I'm allowed to go!
You can't go!
--You're kidding! I'm going to be late for school!
--You can't go! You can't go!
Give me back my bag!
My left hand!
Roll, roll, roll, roll, roll, roll, roll!
Hey, Brat! Don't be absurd, you hear?
Hakase...
How about we do this?
Tonight, I'll make your favorite omurice for dinner.
Um... And I'll pick you up some
shark castella on the way back!
Uh... And...
I'll throw in strawberry juice, too!
Roll, roll, roll, roll, roll, roll, roll!
Also...
Also?
The Akutagawa Prize, too?
Th-That's impossible!
"Egg Tofu"
I was worried there for a second,
but I'm glad that Hakase eventually caved in.
This is a huge step for me
towards becoming a normal person!
"No Trespassing"
Shoot! I totally forgot!
What about the key on my back?!
Things that are cool!
All right!
Let's do this!
Oh! An energetic upperclassman!
What should I do...?
No matter how much I think about it,
I don't know what to do...
And now I've made it this far...
Well then, I'll now introduce
our new transfer student.
Shinonome?
Yes!
I-I knew everyone would notice my key!
Here.
Shinonome, please write your name on the board.
My key is totally standing out!
I need to fool them somehow!
"Nano Shinonome"
M-M-My name is Nano Shinonome!
"Nano Shinonome" U-Um!
"Nano Shinonome"
You see, um, about this key on my back...
It's... uh... Actually!
It got stuck in me coming here!
Shoot!
I screwed up!
Um, well... You see...
Actually, you know what?
That's a lie!
Shoot!
What the heck am I saying?!
What should I do? Um, um...
No, it's not like if you wind it up my thumb
becomes a USB or anything robotic like that...
I'm done for!
"Fortune"
♪ To-mor-row the wea-ther will be nice! ♪
"My Ordinary Life 57"
Come on, Sekiguchi.
"Go+Soccer Club"
Stop reading books and let's play something.
"Go+Soccer Club President Daiku Kenzaburou"
I even bought the Game of Life for us to play.
"Go+Soccer Club Member Yuria Sekiguchi"
Man, I'm so bored...
Maybe I'll play some Go,
seeing as how it's the Go+Soccer Club.
Though I'm awful at Go.
Excuse me!
Um, this is the Go+Soccer Club, right?
Yeah...
Are you accepting new members?
Of course we are!
What's your name?!
I-I'm a first year, Makoto Sakurai.
Oh, really?
I'm the second year president, Daiku Kenzaburou.
This here is first year, Sekiguchi.
"Helvetica Standard"
Come and have a seat!
S-Sure.
So? What do you wanna do?
How about the Game of Life?
"Game of Life"
Um... Aren't we going to practice?
Eh?
For Go+Soccer.
Actually, Go+Soccer is just
an imaginary game I made up.
We don't really do any sport.
Basically, we just play around together.
It's like a recreational club.
Oh...
Hmm?
But I... In middle school,
I was in the Go+Soccer Club.
Eh?
I had no idea there was
a Go+Soccer Club at this school.
Yeah. I only realized it when I saw
the banners hanging in the school.
To be honest, in middle school I was the MVP!
"Attack the stones. Protect your balls."
"Curious"
Sh-Shinonome?
Y-Yes?
U-Um, there's something I was curious about...
Um, it's that thing on your back...
Eh? Uh, th-this...
Eh? Um, uh...
--Uh, um, ah...
--Well, uh, um...
"My Ordinary Life 57.5"
Um... What do you do in Go+Soccer?
Hmm... It's a bit hard to explain with words.
I know. I'll give a little demonstration.
First off is the lifting.
After lifting, the Go stones!
And then...
Go stones into the...
...solo suplex!
And there you have the avalanche joseki!
Three Star Point!
That was incredible...
I made this club without
thinking anything about it...
But this is...
...way cooler than I ever imagined!
"Shoe"
Hey, wait up!
What's gotten into you?!
Where are you going, Buddy?!
"Word-Time"
Sakamoto!
Hey! Idiot! Stop it!
Sakamoto! Sakamoto!
If asked what it is... It is spinning.
"Buddy"
"Pawn"
"Promoted Pawn"
"My Ordinary Life 58"
I can't believe I screwed up
big time on my first day.
I bet everyone thinks I'm crazy now.
Nano, you brought a lunch?
U-Uh, yes.
It looks tasty.
Do you always bring one?
Y-Yes!
It's normal to!
I'll let you see it.
I-It's cool.
Isn't it?
Mio, sorry for the wait.
You're so late, Yuuko.
Lunch break is almost over.
Sorry, sorry!
On the way, a car and dog stole my shoes
and it was such a pain to get them back.
I don't really get it,
but that sounds like quite the adventure.
Well, all that matters is that you made it back.
Huh? Where's your lunch?
Hmm? I ate it while walking back.
Eh? What'd you have?
Twice-cooked pork lunch box.
Whoa! Twice-cooked-- Well, whatever.
Um, hey, Nano.
Want to eat with me there?
Eh?
You can tell us more about you.
U-Uh...
I wonder if they think I'm a normal girl?
M-Maybe we can even become friends?
Hey, what's that thing on your back?
Th-This isn't suspicious or anything like that...
Could it be that Nano is actually a robot?
Don't say stupid things like that.
Sorry, Yuuko's an idiot.
Oh. We're almost out of time.
Sorry, Nano. I'll have to scarf it down today.
There we are.
Hey, Yuuko. What's this?
Fried mackerel.
What did I ask you to get?
Huh? Fried mackerel, right?
Fried macaroni!
Uh... Oops.
Did I mishear what you asked for?
Sorry, sorry!
This is not some cute problem!
It's a critical issue!
But they're so alike.
They even sound the same.
But that's not...
Whatever. I don't care anymore.
So? Where's my rice?
Hmm? What do you mean?
My white rice!
Eh? That's all there is.
How am I supposed to eat this by itself?!
Huh? You're the one who asked for fried mackerel.
Fried macaroni!
Fried! Macaroni! Get it?!
Oh. Got it, got it.
But, hey. You can use this incident
as good material on your blog.
I don't have a computer!
Sheesh. Don't get mad at me
for that wasted opportunity.
Fine, I get it. I'll run back and buy it again.
Gimme money.
Why am I the one who has to pay?!
Because I don't have any money.
Fine, whatever.
Just hurry up and come back, okay?
Lunch is almost over.
Okay, okay.
...is all I have.
Eh?
One peso is all I have!
All I've got is an Argentine
peso that I saved as a souvenir.
Eh?
All I have is an Argentine peso!
Argentine peso?
This is all your fault in the first place!
You're the one who should pay!
I bought my lunch, too, so I spent all my mon--
What am I supposed to do about my lunch?!
Uh, um...
How about... Mackerel?
Mackerel!
--Mackerel?
--Geez!
You always manage to piss me off somehow!
You're always asking to copy my homework!
How about you do it yourself for once?!
You idiot!
My being an idiot has nothing to do
with you not getting lunch.
It totally does!
How so?! Say it, then!
You're an idiot for mishearing me!
Hmph!
Everyone's guilty of mishearing sometimes!
Don't get all pissy about it! You're so bitter!
I didn't eat breakfast!
This is a matter of life and death!
An idiot like you wouldn't understand!
I'm not an idiot!
You just said you were an idiot earlier!
Just so you know, I'm never letting you
copy my homework again!
That's fine, that's fine! If you forget yours,
I'm not letting you copy mine either!
Who would ever want to look at
your crummy homework?!
You didn't even apologize once
for buying the wrong thing!
Get on your knees and bow! Get down!
Fine, fine! All I have to do is bow, right?!
Here's your bow!
I'm so sorry, okay?!
There, I apologized!
Well?! Are you happy now?
Huh?! You call that a bow?!
That's right, it's not a bow. It's a stretch!
A stretch!
Why won't you just bow?!
Because you've made me mad!
Aren't you the big idiot here?!
What about those weird drawings you did?
Those... weird drawings...
You moron! Those were...
What were those weird drawings? I don't get it.
I don't get it! Draw something that makes sense!
What's with you?!
You moron!
You moron! You moron! You moron!
What the heck?! You're the moron
sketching those weird drawings!
Come on, eat it already!
Here's the fried mackerel you wanted!
I wanted fried macaroni!
Get on your knees and bow!
Put your head on the ground!
I already bought it so what's it matter?!
Apologize like a human being!
You worthless person!
Fine!
I'll show you then! A real bow!
Here it comes...
A real bow!
What about an apology for the mackerel?!
You're apologizing, aren't you?!
Say it! Say you're sorry for the mackerel!
Come on! Hurry up and say it!
I'm an idiot and I'm sorry!
Say it from your heart, you worthless person!
Come on, hurry! Say it, you moron!
Apologize already, you jerk!
Worthless! Idiot! Moron!
Enough! Stop calling me an idiot, Mio!
What do you even know about me
in just half a year?!
Right back at you! You don't know
anything about my drawings!
I do, too! If you're so damn good at it,
why don't you become a manga artist?!
Wh-What are you saying? Are you an idiot?
Huh?! It takes one to know one!
You idiot!
You just called yourself an idiot.
I did not!
You did!
But...
That side of you... isn't so bad...
Huh? What are you saying? You're too smart...
Sh-Shut up! You... smile too nice!
Wh-What?! You draw too good!
Shut up! You run too fast!
You're too smart!
You're too positive!
Then you're too smart, too!
Amazing!
"Go! Go! Go+Soccer Club"
"Youth" "Go! Go! Go+Soccer Club"
"Spirit of Black & White!!"
Captain! We tried so hard!
Don't cry. There's always next year.
I'll win for him!
Woo-hoo!
That was the past...
"Shinonome Lab"
Hey, hey, Nano! Was school any fun?
It sure was.
So much happened...
It's like...
It's like? It's like?
Having friends is such an amazing thing!
That is amazing!
Good grief. No one makes any sense around here.
What, what?
Hakase!
What?
Please take the key off my back!
No.
Wh-Why won't you do it?!
It's a huge hindrance to my school life!
Today, people suspected I was a robot!
I won't be able to make friends like this!
You can, too. It's cute.
It's not cute!
It's cute... Your key.
Just hurry up and serve my meal.
Hakase!
Right now, if any wish could be mine
I would wish for wings
Give me white wings on my back
Like the wings of a bird
I want to open my wings and fly
Fly away into the sky
To an open, free sky, without sadness
Flap my wings and soar
Soccer ball here...
I'm kicked, kicked, and kicked some more.
Kicked and crushed until I deflate
and then put to rest!
"Narration: Shigeru Chiba"
The next My Ordinary Life is Episode 15.
Look forward to it!