I wonder if she can do mental math?
Who can?
I'm talking about Nano.
"My Ordinary Life 59"
You think she has a math feature
since she's a robot?
What are you talking about?
There's no way she's a robot.
Really? But check out that key
sticking out of her back!
You think that's all it takes to be a robot?
You've gotta be kidding me.
No! Just think about it for a second.
She's a robot! A robot!
Isn't that sweet?!
It's like... Isn't that sweet?!
What's that? You're not making any sense.
I've been wanting to look into
whether Nano's really a robot or not.
Eh? You should just let it go.
It'll be fine!
I've got a fail-proof plan!
Greatest friendship
Super duper harmony
(na na na na na na na)
Hey! I'll say it
You are my best best friend
(bright) Every time I poke fun and tease you
(shine) You come and tease me back some more
(lan lan lan) There ain't
no better feeling in the world
(why) Even when bad things sometimes happen
(fine) I forget all of them around you
(lan lan lan) We'll forever let the good times roll
It's not a problem being with you
every hour of the day
As if we're twins, child-parent,
or a pair of cloned cells
Doesn't a friendship this good
make love not so needed anymore?
Wait hold on this and that
are totally totally different things
(fight) Even after we've had a fight
(down) Or when I feel down in the dumps
(shock) All the times I wanted to be alone
Before I know it there sitting beside me
my wonderful friend till the end
Why is it, I wanna be at your side?
Whenever we're together,
time flies 100 times faster
It's so fun with you,
I think it's almost too much fun
It's cuz you're such a good friend! Hey!
(na na na na na na na)
What's going on? Uh-oh we're synchronizing man!
It's always a wild time,
we make the people 'round us crazy
What time is it now? I think it's yodelayheehoo
What's that even mean?
SO-RE-DO-SHI-RA-
Unbelievably, how to put it, awesome!
No matter what happens
we are gonna be friends! Woohoo!
Greatest friendship
Super duper harmony
cha chara chara cha cha-n
Nano?
Y-Yes?
A question...
What's 3,260 plus 260 divided by 320?
Um...
Three thousand two hundred sixty plus...
If it's too hard... you could just calculate it...
What, Yuuko? That's your fail-proof plan?!
Sorry...
Well, then if it's all right with you...
She took the bait!
It's an abacus!
Um... First to wipe the slate clean...
She's doing it!
Uh...
One, two, three...
B... B... B-B-B-B-B-Beginner!
Um, 3,260 plus...
She's not even using the abacus!
H-Hey, Yuuko!
A-Aioi?
Are you okay?
I'm fine...
I get the feeling I made a miscalculation...
Sheesh. I told you she's not a robot.
Are you all right?
Do you need a drink?
Could it be?!
Is this it? Could it be?!
Could it be?! Unleash the oil!
It's just soup! Plop!
Yuuko!
Ah! Um...
Minakami?
Here.
The fastball!
Oil!
For you.
Are you sure?
Thank you very much.
It's a whiff!
This is for you, too.
Trick pitch!
Monkey wrench!
Oh, thanks. I fancied one of these.
To eat?!
Another whiff!
H-Hey.
Would you two cut it out?
Can't you see you're bothering Nano?
It's skinship.
Well, we just wanted to
become friends with you.
Sheesh. You're not getting closer,
you're scaring her away.
S-Sorry.
Good grief.
No. Please don't worry about it.
Huh? But...
Oh, right!
If you don't want the soup,
I'm going to drink it.
See? Nano doesn't seem to care one bit.
What are you talking about? Sheesh...
--Did my silver cap come loose?
--Put yourself in Nano's shoes, would you?
Give it a break.
"Cleaning sucks"
I need to know.
How was such an advanced technology devised?
That transfer student who
just started... Nano Shinonome.
Her demeanor...
Yes, and her key.
"Open & Close Door Quietly"
"Do Not Open"
Yes, and her key.
"Open & Close Door Quietly"
"Do Not Open"
No matter how you look at it, she's a robot.
Why wasn't such an advanced robot announced?
Why has she come to our school so nonchalantly?
I must find out.
I need to know more about her.
And then...
I want to make her my own.
"My Ordinary Life 60"
Ms. Nakamura?
I've brought the books you asked for.
She came!
Good! Time for action.
Well then, I'll excuse myself.
Shinonome, wait up!
What do you say? How about a cup of coffee?
Huh? No, I don't want to be a bother.
Come on, don't be such a bummer.
I just warmed up a cup.
It's thanks for carrying the books here.
Just drink it.
Well, just one cup.
First we'll see if this sleep medicine
works on her or not.
If it doesn't, I'll get her in the back with
the Mr. Short Circuit I made yesterday.
Here, drink.
Thank you.
I drank it!
Resist...
Resist!
Well, I'll be going.
I need to at least...
Mr. Short Circuit...
Yeah, yeah.
The science teacher Nakamura fell over, I guess.
Nakamura sure falls over a lot.
Today was quite dangerous.
But Aioi and Minakami seem like
really nice people, too.
Maybe we can even be friends...
Eat this!
Rocket punch!
Ka-boom!
Taste my rocket punch's maximum power!
"Shinonome Lab"
"Shinonome Lab" Hakase! Hakase!
Hakase! Hakase!
Nano! Welcome home!
Why did you say it twice?
Rather, more importantly...
Hurry up and take this off of me.
"My Ordinary Life 61"
Why?
Why, you ask?
Because, it makes it hard to sit in a seat!
With it, everyone looks at me funny.
People even took a video of me!
I don't know how, but somehow I fooled them.
But it's cute...
As long as I have this key, no one
is going to treat me like a normal girl.
It'll make you popular!
No, it won't!
I want to have a normal school life--
Sheesh!
Why did you give me this weapon?
I'm so glad it didn't come off at school.
Why don't you want to be found out as a robot?
Because everyone knows that's not cute at all.
Robots are cute!
They are not cute!
They're cute!
Is this gun cute, too?!
It's cute!
And my thumb USB from before?
And sweet buns from the forehead?
I said it's cute!
Geez!
Hakase, you mad scientist!
I said it's cute!
All I want is to be a normal girl!
Yay! It's chikuwa!
Chikuwa is tasty, right?
Three...
Two...
One...
Four o'clock! Four o'clock!
"Daifuku Fair 1"
Hey! It's daifuku!
Real cheap!
It's daifuku!
Mr. Nakanojou!
Keep up the good work!
Daifuku doesn't speak!
I'm sorry.
"Daifuku Fair 2" I'm sorry.
"Daifuku Fair 2"
I just can't wear this mask
without getting into it!
I'm putting my life on the--
Don't make me say it again!
Damn.
I screwed up big time.
"Ms. Nakamura, Mr. Short Circuit"
Sleeping medicine may have been too rash.
After all, she's a robot.
If I don't get her in one big blow,
she's not going to faint.
That's where this comes in!
The device I didn't get to try,
robot disabler, Mr. Short Circuit!
This time I'll knock her out
and capture her for sure.
It's almost time.
Run away!
Ms. Nakamura?
J-Just a minute!
You have to fasten your top button!
Shut up.
I can have it however I want.
No! Don't forget: I'm the student counselor.
Gah, seriously? Who do you think you are?
How rude! Here, let me get it.
I can do it myself! You're embarrassing me!
Uh...
What's going on?
"My Ordinary Life 62"
But you won't fix it yourself, Mako.
Shut up.
Mako?
Come on.
What are you doing, idiot?
"Idiot"
"Idiot" Cut it out!
Hold still and I'll fix you up.
"Idiot" "I'll fix you up"
Idiot?!
I'll fix you up?!
Geez.
Stop groping me in school, okay?
G-Groping?!
--What's their relationship?!
--Look, you broke it.
Well that's a relief.
See ya. I've got places to be.
Wait a minute!
If you dress that sloppy,
everyone will make fun of you!
What the heck?
You're the one who dresses sloppy at home.
At home?!
D-D-D-Dress sloppy?!
Dress sloppy! Yeah!
No, no, no! What am I saying,
yeah? Am I an idiot?!
Since when is a Chinese dress sloppy?!
What's normally considered sloppy?!
What am I thinking?!
I should be ashamed to be a teacher!
What's normally considered sloppy?
What's sloppy?
Dress sloppy!
Enough!
Enough! I'm an idiot!
It's fine. I'm leaving.
What about your button?!
"The Life of Oguri Cap"
The Life of Oguri Cap!
I'm an idiot!
It's fine. I'm leaving.
What about your button?!
I-I've gotta chase them.
Mr. Takasaki!
Nakanojou fainted over in the science room!
Eh?!
We need you to come right away!
Hey, wait up!
It doesn't matter!
This is bad. Listen up...
Yes?
Nakanojou never fainted!
Ehhh?!
That's right! He might be napping!
But his eyes turned all white!
Ehhh?!
Draw them in!
I'll give it a shot.
Ehhh?!
Wait!
What's that?!
Tell me what that's all about!
Stopping this illicit relationship
is more important!
As a teacher, I can't... Um... With a teacher!
But that's just Ms. Sakurai's younger brother.
Let's go.
Okay!
Here we go.
It's time to hurry.
That's...
...my duty as a teacher!
It's this way!
Hop!
"Love-Like"
"Take-Out"
Next stop is Tokisadame Station, North Gate.
The bus will stop.
You're not even the next stop.
Man, I just wanted to push it.
Didn't you push it last time?
Someone wanted to get off,
so it worked out in the end.
I see how it is. You were just helping.
See? Someone got off here, too.
Good job!
Mom, don't we have
a tear-off calendar somewhere?
Isn't it in the closet?
"Calendar" "Tear-off Calendar"
"Shinonome Lab"
"Shinonome Lab" Hakase! Hakase!
Hakase! Hakase!
Nano, welcome home.
Would you please take off my key already?
It's becoming a real nuisance
in my daily school life.
In today's gym, I had
to belly roll over the high jump.
When we were playing soccer,
it even put me offside.
I'll take it off.
Splat!
"My Ordinary Life 63" Ow...
"My Ordinary Life 63" Sheesh.
"My Ordinary Life 63"
If you'll take it off, tell me that sooner.
All right.
I'll take it right now.
Every day that passes by
is one I'll never get back.
But now, I can finally begin
my life as a normal high schooler!
Could you take it out right away, then?
--Stare...
--Hakase?
--That's... Don't tell me...
--Stare...
I took it.
Plop!
Ugh, geez...
Sheesh. When I said to take my key,
I didn't mean to take a picture of it!
Sorry, sorry.
So? Will you take off my key?
Well...
Kapow!
Enough with the silly gags!
Will you take it off or will you not take it off?
I'll take it, I'll take it.
I've taken more keys off than you can count.
Taking off your key is a super simple snap.
Coin, coin, coin, swish!
Coin, coin, you said!
Coin! S-S-S-Swish!
Hakase!
I have a question!
Can't breathe!
I'm laughing so hard I can't breathe!
Hakase, it seems like
I'm acting a little funny today.
Did you... You know?
Do anything? To me?
Actually, yesterday I gave you funny bones.
Shibibi! Shibibi! Shibibi! Shibibi!
H-Hey! Why did you give me
such a silly feature?!
Why did you have to give me that?!
I thought it'd be funny.
Thump!
Goal!
Dodododo!
Kiss!
Bang!
I'll die!
This funny business is going to kill me!
See? It's funny.
It's not funny at all!
Hakase, forget about my key for a minute.
Please, take that feature off of me.
Sure. One hundred yen.
Boom!
For some reason sometimes I get the urge
To follow the open sky and journey
Ride aboard a blimp and be taken where it goes
Cruising with the wind above the meadows
Soar above the clouds and far beyond
Because something there is waiting for me
La la la la la la la la la la la
La la la la la la la la la
La la la la la la la la
La la la la
La
"Word-Time"
This takes every last ounce of my strength.
I'm oil.
People often call me slippery.
But I'm oil, so you can't blame them.
The boss pours me all the time.
You're not the boss of me!
The next My Ordinary Life is Episode 16.
"Narration: Yoshiko Sakakibara"
Look forward to it!