Mai, let's walk home together.
Can we stop by the fire station?
Seriously? That's no place
for high school girls to hang out.
Oh, I've got it, Mai. Let's go
to Daiku Coffee on the way back.
The system is pretty weird at that place,
so it might be a little confusing for you at first.
Yoink.
I'll be there to show you the ropes though.
Uh, Mai?
That's...
Asymmetry.
Yeah, that's true, but it's a bit extreme!
Talk about making a fashion statement!
It's just a joke.
She really threw me a curve this time.
Mai must be completely out of her mind.
I don't know what to say anymore!
Good God...
The heavens are on Mai's side.
Greatest friendship
Super duper harmony
(na na na na na na na)
Hey! I'll say it
You are my best best friend
(bright) Every time I poke fun and tease you
(shine) You come and tease me back some more
(lan lan lan) There ain't
no better feeling in the world
(why) Even when bad things sometimes happen
(fine) I forget all of them around you
(lan lan lan) We'll forever let the good times roll
It's not a problem being with you
every hour of the day
As if we're twins, child-parent,
or a pair of cloned cells
Doesn't a friendship this good
make love not so needed anymore?
Wait hold on this and that
are totally totally different things
(fight) Even after we've had a fight
(down) Or when I feel down in the dumps
(shock) All the times I wanted to be alone
Before I know it there sitting beside me
my wonderful friend till the end
Why is it, I wanna be at your side?
Whenever we're together,
time flies 100 times faster
It's so fun with you,
I think it's almost too much fun
It's cuz you're such a good friend! Hey!
(na na na na na na na)
What's going on? Uh-oh we're synchronizing man!
It's always a wild time,
we make the people 'round us crazy
What time is it now? I think it's yodelayheehoo
What's that even mean?
SO-RE-DO-SHI-RA-
Unbelievably, how to put it, awesome!
No matter what happens
we are gonna be friends! Woohoo!
Greatest friendship
Super duper harmony
cha chara chara cha cha-n
"My Ordinary Life 68"
I wonder what I should put on today's menu...
Green onions are cheap today,
so maybe something with that.
Then again, Hakase kind of hates green onions...
Nano! Nano!
Nano!
Look, Nano! I caught a crow!
What in the world?!
What are you doing!
That's dangerous! You'll get pecked!
It's fine.
Give me a minute.
It's not here...
I might die here...
It's not here, either.
How did I lose my scarf?
Greetings. I'm Crow.
I'm very pleased to meet you.
Ah-choo!
I'm so impressed with how polite he is.
It's 'cuz he's a crow.
Your words honor me greatly.
Do you think he drinks strawberry juice?
I wonder if he would?
It'd be so cute if he did!
My goodness.
He's even killing insects for us!
It's nothing really. It's the least I could do.
What a nice crow.
Huh? What happened to your scarf, Sakamoto?
Without a scarf, no one knows what he's saying!
I'll speak with him.
I see. I see.
It seems that he wants my scarf.
I see.
It ain't your scarf!
Hakase... Did you actually put
Sakamoto's scarf on the crow?
My, what a dilemma.
But don't you think that's
a little cruel to Sakamoto?
I know, I'll make something!
That's a good idea.
I'm done!
Biscuit Number One!
That's totally not a scarf!
Excuse me, Hakase.
This Biscuit Number One, what is he capable of?
Good question, Crow.
He has a rocket punch.
Here we go!
Three, two!
Blast off! Fire!
Hakase, shouldn't you give
Sakamoto his s-scarf back soon?
Hold on.
We still have his left hand to fire!
Three, two!
Blast off! Fire!
"Shinonome Lab"
"Shinonome Lab" I'll kill 'em!
I'll kill 'em all!
"Shinonome Lab"
"Shinonome Lab" My...
What a fun day it has been.
My mischief has gone on for too long.
Please, give this scarf back to Sakamoto.
Though it was short, I enjoyed
being able to speak with you humans.
Crow...
Don't leave, Crow!
Hakase.
I hope someday, that we can meet again.
Until then, farewell.
See you again!
Crow!
Crow...
He took it with him!
"Love-Like"
This is impossible, Chief.
No, it'll be fine. Just leave it to me.
But...
What?
Don't you trust me?
No, that's not what I meant...
I've always completely trusted you, Chief.
Good. Then will you give me a hand?
But... Wait!
Well? Do you feel it?
What do you think?
"My Ordinary Life 69"
"Yield"
"Behind the Gym 1"
Yesterday, I dug holes behind
the gym and filled them with glue.
"Powerful Glue"
I'll use this letter as bait and lure her into my trap.
"Nano Shinonome"
Today is the day I capture Nano Shinonome.
She's here!
Good!
I had no idea that Makoto Sakurai
"My Ordinary Life 70"
was Ms. Sakurai's younger brother.
I could use him to get
information about Ms. Sakurai.
He...
He can play Go+Soccer?!
Interesting...
Hey, Sakurai.
Yes?
I don't suppose you have a boyfriend?
No future!
It's always like this!
I always screw up! I'm such a stupid man!
Um, I don't, but...
I don't, but... I don't, but...
S... S...
Sprouting!
Not sprouting! Not sprouting!
Um...
Sorry, sorry. Forget I ever said that.
Oh yeah! You know how to play Go+Soccer?
Yeah, I do.
Let me guess, Mr. Takasaki.
You like my sister, don't you?
D-D-D-D-Don't be stupid!
As a former player,
I'm just curious about you guys!
Mr. Takasaki? You played Go+Soccer?
Of course I did! You're looking at the MVP here!
Actually, our Go+Soccer club
doesn't have an adviser yet.
If you become our adviser,
I'll help you all I can with my sister.
Uh, I never said... I liked her.
If you won't do it, I'll tell everyone
in the school that you like her.
You!
How about it? Will you be our adviser?
Uh...
You won't do it?
Um... It's just...
Advising is so annoy--
Hey! Everyone listen up!
Gonna move!
Gotta chase him.
Mr. Takasaki!
Behind the gym, Nakanojou fell into a hole!
Eh?!
We need you to come right away!
Hey! Hear about Mr. Takasaki?!
Mr. Takasaki!
This is bad. Listen up...
Yes?
Nakanojou didn't fall in a hole!
Eh?!
Right, he might be hole-in-one!
Get this! All of his hair is missing!
Eh?!
Draw it in.
I'll give it a shot.
Eh?!
Wait!
Tell me what that's all about!
Hey!
Tea.
It's more important to stop students
from spilling their teacher's private life!
As a teacher, I can't... As a teacher!
Mr. Takasaki!
Yeah?!
I didn't say anything!
I'll be waiting for you to come and advise!
Good one, dude.
Annaka, let's go!
Okay!
It's time to hurry.
That's...
...my duty as a teacher!
It's this way!
This way?
Although I always thought it odd...
I do feel bad for cutting his hair.
Hmm...
I should probably help him.
"Behind the Gym 2"
He still doesn't know that I was the one who did it.
--What's this?
--Huh?
--What the heck? Where am I?
--Huh? Eh?
--Where am I? This is weird!
--Huh? Huh?
Huh?
--What the heck?
--Huh? Huh?
--I can't move.
--Um...
--What the...?
--My hair...
--Um...
--What? What? What?
Run away!
Help me!
My hair!
♪ Swim, swim! ♪
♪ Shark, shark, bite! ♪
♪ That's when you go like this! ♪
The Life of Chitchi!
"Daiku Bread"
"Behind the Gym 3"
What the heck?
Help me!
My hair!
--Huh?
--What the heck?
--Help me!
--What happened he--
--What the...?
--Help me!
--My hair.
--What, what?
--Help me!
--What the...? This is weird!
--Help me, please! Help!
--That's so dangerous.
--What the...?
--Help me!
--My hair.
I'm leaving!
"My Ordinary Life 71"
Today's the day...
I won't make a jab at her jokes!
It's Mai who's at fault in the first place.
She's like a machine,
always setting me up for the perfect jab!
At this rate, we'll be stuck in an infinite loop!
We're supposed to be girls.
Yes, more innocent and pure than flowers.
And yet...
We can't even carry a normal girly conversation.
Starting today, I won't make any more jabs.
My resolve is more firm than a diamond.
Ah. Good morning, Yuuko.
Oh, Mai. Good mor--
Double glasses!
It's intense! So intense today!
Why is she so intense today?!
But I will not lose!
We... We have to change!
Mai, Selamat pagi!
Good. Now's the time to break out the girly talk.
Hey, hey, Mai.
Did you see yesterday's Muscle Theater?
Wh... Wh-Wh-Which is it?!
Glasses... Glasses...
Oh gahhh!
W-What's with these high-paced jokes?!
It's like she's expecting me to make a jab!
No! Don't do it, Yuuko!
It's a trap!
What gives, Minakami?
You've got two glasses on.
Tanaka, you jerk!
You stole it from me! That was
my place to come in and make a jab!
Wait! No, no! I'm not doing it anymore!
I'm not making any more jabs!
Oh, yeah.
Isn't today's first period language?
That's right.
By the way, did you hear
that Ms. Nakamura fell over?
Really? Is she okay?
Oh, yeah.
Isn't today's first period language?
You just asked that a sec--
That was close!
Did she really just say the same thing twice?!
So scary! This girl is incredibly scary!
All right. Who's on day duty today?
Stand up.
Bow.
Take your sheet.
Let's get on with class today.
--Turn to page 82.
--What's "take your sheet"?
What the heck is "take your sheet"?!
What's worse, everyone ignored it!
So, who wants to read this section?
Me.
M-Mai?!
Sure, Minakami.
Okay.
--A peaceful shade enveloped the mountain.
--Sh-She's reading it, but...
--A sprinkle of light glimmered
--here and there around the village.
--It was my first time there,
--She's reading it, but...
--but somehow a feeling of nostalgia
--Reading, but... Reading, but...
--spread through my heart.
She memorized it!
It's true...
Jabs feel so...
...so...
...so darn good!
I'm sorry for raising my voice.
I'll go stand in the hall.
O-Okay.
Yes.
This is how it should be.
This is the path that I chose.
And...
This is the path that Mai chose, too.
Yuuko.
Actually, all this time...
Contacts.
You don't even need glasses!
"Kotatsu"
Hakase. Hakase.
Not here. Sleep in your bed or you'll catch a cold.
Hakase, you goof.
Just a little longer...
Huh? A little longer?
She tricked me!
In a desert with a red sinking sun
Is a big monster living peacefully
It wakes one morning to a distant caravan
Hearing their bells, it suddenly yells
I want to see the sea. I want to love people
Even monsters have hearts of their own.
It's time to leave the desert behind
For a place with love and sea
A new sun will blaze again
In a place with love and sea
"Word-Time"
Sakamoto? You should get in bed, too, Sakamoto.
Y-Yeah...
In the end, she had to be carried.
I'm three of spades!
In President, I'm the worst card,
but after a revolution I'm the best!
Be a man and aim for President!
The next My Ordinary Life is Episode 18.
"Narration: Kazuya Nakai"
Look forward to it!