Hellvetica Standard.
Glasses, glasses, glasses, glasses.
Glasses, glasses, glasses!
Glasses, glasses!
Glasses!
Glasses, glasses, glasses, glasses!
Glasses, glasses, glasses, glasses, glasses, glasses,
glasses, glasses, glasses, glasses, glasses!
Greatest friendship
Super duper harmony
(na na na na na na na)
Hey! I'll say it
You are my best best friend
(bright) Every time I poke fun and tease you
(shine) You come and tease me back some more
(lan lan lan) There ain't
no better feeling in the world
(why) Even when bad things sometimes happen
(fine) I forget all of them around you
(lan lan lan) We'll forever let the good times roll
It's not a problem being with you
every hour of the day
As if we're twins, child-parent,
or a pair of cloned cells
Doesn't a friendship this good
make love not so needed anymore?
Wait hold on this and that
are totally totally different things
(fight) Even after we've had a fight
(down) Or when I feel down in the dumps
(shock) All the times I wanted to be alone
Before I know it there sitting beside me
my wonderful friend till the end
Why is it, I wanna be at your side?
Whenever we're together,
time flies 100 times faster
It's so fun with you,
I think it's almost too much fun
It's cuz you're such a good friend! Hey!
(na na na na na na na)
What's going on? Uh-oh we're synchronizing man!
It's always a wild time,
we make the people 'round us crazy
What time is it now? I think it's yodelayheehoo
What's that even mean?
SO-RE-DO-SHI-RA-
Unbelievably, how to put it, awesome!
No matter what happens
we are gonna be friends! Woohoo!
Greatest friendship
Super duper harmony
cha chara chara cha cha-n
"My Ordinary Life 78"
Never before and never again
will anyone ever do what I'm about to do.
Domestic violence.
How was it?
How are we supposed to respond to that?
That's something you'd do.
Yeah, that is something she'd do.
Yeah, that was totally like you.
Then, this time I'll do something
totally unlike what I'd ever do.
Ugh!
I tripped and fell!
That's so like Fe to do...
That's so like her...
"Newbie 1"
Come get a daifuku! How about one?!
Sorry, but...
Would you mind wearing this instead?
Come get a daifuku!
How about one?!
Sorry, but could you please not say anything?
"Newbie 2"
Could you put on some clothes?
Are you pouting?!
"Newbie 3"
You're not pouting?
Then what's the matter?
Hey...
It's fine if you talk to me, you know!
"Love-Like"
"Please help me graduate from
Tokisadame High School."
"Please help the person above graduate."
"Please help the person to the right graduate..."
"Please help the person below graduate!! Good luck!"
"My Ordinary Life 79"
Here I go!
Yes!
You didn't jump over!
But look, the bar's still--
I'm saying you didn't jump over!
How many times will it take until you get it?!
It's getting late!
S-Sorry. I'll get it right this time.
I'll lower the bar for you this time.
Just take it nice and slow.
This time, jump exactly how I showed you.
All right.
In any case, I've gotta learn
how to clear the bar at least this high.
If I can't do that much...
...everyone will laugh at me!
How was it?!
You pumpkin head!
Why can't you jump like I told you?!
You screwing with me?!
Well, in my mind I'm doing
a perfect Fosbury flop.
Perfect Fosbury flop?
Your form is more like...
...a torpedo!
A human torpedo...
I never took it that far!
No, actually...
I think I...
I might have.
No, no, no way. You're kidding, right?
Is she oblivious?!
Sorry...
Well, I'll help you out until you're satisfied.
You're always showing me your homework.
Today's my turn to help you.
I'll stay here until you get it.
Don't try to hurry and rush it!
Jump like you're doing a bridge over it first.
Relax and take your time, Mio!
You've got this!
There's no one to hear the tale to pass it down.
It's not just now... I've always been awful at sports.
So it falls upon the wind, the wind trashing around.
Hey, Mio! Did you forget we're playing soccer?!
I'm just as athletic as anyone else.
So it falls upon the wind, the wind trashing around.
The names of the scattered stars are forgot.
But when you give me rules to follow,
I completely fall apart.
The names of the scattered stars are forgot.
Ukemi, ready!
Into obscurity they drown.
Begin!
Mio, reverse! Your ukemi's backwards!
Into obscurity they drown.
But...
If I don't do anything about it,
Into obscurity they drown.
Headlight. Taillight.
nothing will ever change!
I'll always stay the same!
Headlight. Taillight.
One, two...
The journey isn't over yet.
Mio, you're not supposed to do a propeller!
I don't care if I'm wasting my time.
The journey isn't over yet.
Headlight. Taillight.
I don't care if I never get it.
The journey isn't over yet.
Footsteps and tracks, together with the rain.
But...
There's just one... one thing I know I can do!
Footsteps and tracks, together with the rain.
One, two, three!
Fade, disappear, and vanish down the drain.
Let's try that again.
This is for Yuuko.
Fade, disappear, and vanish down the drain.
The songs being sung to praise the heroes
I'll take a short break over there.
All right.
The songs being sung to praise the heroes
Are so their deeds shan't wane.
It's for my own sake, too!
Headlight. Taillight.
I won't quit!
If I have to quit...
Headlight. Taillight.
The journey isn't over yet.
It'll be after I've given everything I've got!
Great effort will open new doors.
The journey isn't over yet.
Headlight. Taillight.
The future "Torpedo Leap" was made.
The Life of White Tiger.
It's like...
...all they do is sleep.
That one's sticking its butt at us.
Yeah it is.
They're so far away you can't see much.
And we came all this way. So lame!
But at least we got to see them.
I guess.
Woo-hoo!
"My Ordinary Life 80"
It's raining!
I need to get the laundry!
Where are you going?!
Yay!
It's too late now.
Just bring it in!
It's rain!
Hakase, Sakamoto. I'm home.
It's sure raining hard out there.
Did you bring in the laundry for me?
Sakamoto told me to bring it in!
It's true.
Sakamoto really told me to do it.
Did Sakamoto telling you
somehow knock all the laundry over?
No! Sakamoto told me to bring it in and...
...drop it everywhere.
I did not!
That was a shock. Trying to get me in trouble, Brat?
But you said to!
I never said to drop anything.
You did, too!
Did not.
Did, too!
Did not!
I did not!
Did, too!
Did not!
Gimme a break!
Eh?!
Nano...
Sakamoto can be the one
to take the blame then, okay?
Why me?
It's fine. Those clothes will go back
to normal once they're washed.
Ah! Oh yeah.
I guess that's true.
But my day won't recover that easily.
Both of you won't be getting any dinner.
Aww...
Dammit. Why did I get pulled into this?
It's all Sakamoto's fault, so he should be
the one to get punished, right?
All right.
I'll be taking Sakamoto then.
And only Hakase won't get any dinner.
No! Then I want to take
the blame and get punished!
I'm the one that knocked it over!
I'm the one who got it soaking wet!
Huh?!
Ta-dah!
Today, we're having omurice for dinner!
Wow!
Eggs were on sale today.
Huh? Am I allowed to eat today?
Oh yeah! I totally forgot about that...
Um... Then...
W-Well, you're allowed to eat this for today.
--Yay! Yay! Yay! Yay!
--So tomorrow you get nothing!
♪ Swim, swim! ♪
♪ Shark, shark bite! ♪
♪ That's when you go like this! ♪
Mio! Mai!
Selamat pagi!
Wasn't the clay self-portrait
homework a pain in the butt?
That homework was due today?!
Huh? Could it be that Miss Mio forgot to do it?
Gah! I swear it was due tomorrow!
Did you finish it, Mai?
Shoot...
Mai forgot, too? Wow.
When it rains, it pours, right?
It's not funny, all right?
This is a disaster, you know. A disaster.
"My Ordinary Life 81"
It really...
...started pouring.
"Shrine"
"Bushido Sixteen"
"Offering"
You fiends!
What the hell are you doing to my temple?!
You money thieves!
That was close!
"May Peace Prevail on Earth"
This is a curse!
You bring evil spirits!
Get out of here!
Get out of my temple!
"We should leave now."
Is what the girls thought while being
pelted by the late autumn rain.
"Takasaki"
"My Ordinary Life 82"
I'm begging you, President!
I'm about to have a match with
Mr. Takasaki, so could you referee?
Referee? You mean for Go+Soccer?
That's right.
If I win the match, he'll have to
become our adviser no matter what.
Trust me. I'll win!
But what am I supposed to do?
Don't worry. Use the Go+Soccer
beginner's guide I loaned you.
If you look at that, you'll be fine.
It's my own fault for not reading
the beginner's guide, but...
I don't even have the slightest
idea what these two are doing!
This is Go+Soccer?!
The beginner's guide wouldn't help you here.
Ah! Ogi!
These two are using forbidden techniques.
It's such high level play, it defies theory.
See how his arm is stretched straight out?
If that represents the leg of the Go table,
his opponent's stance is the stones.
It looks simple enough,
but the ball between his feet is the crux.
It's just my guess, but these two...
...are trying to become the sun.
Nothing he's saying makes any sense to me!
They're starting!
Oh no!
Beloved!
Ogi? What does that--
Quiet.
Can't you see?
This level of play is so intense...
...if either screws up, someone might die.
Just what... is really going on here?
It's been ages since I've seen such high level play.
No wonder the air feels so restless.
Oh no! This stance... It can't be!
He's doing it in a friendly match?!
Has he lost his mind?!
I can't just stand here and do nothing...
Father, the time has come to use it.
Justice is the answer to everything.
Shed thy light and become a star!
Ogi Forbidden Referee School! Secret move!
"Ogi"
"Ogi" Ogi Star!
This is it!
A final love!
You're pretty good.
Not bad yourself.
What in the world...
I made this club without thinking anything of it.
But this is...
...way crazier than I ever thought possible!
The wild horse (the wild horse)
Why does it run? (run)
Holding its head high, fluttering its tail
Muscles bulging on its chest (bulging on its chest)
Wherever it wants (wherever it wants)
wherever it wants (wherever it wants)
It runs (It runs)
Into the midst of a summer storm
Racing towards lightning (racing towards lighting)
The wild horse (the wild horse)
Wherever it wants, it runs
It runs
"Word-Time"
"Free for employees"
I break down when no one can see me.
Step and step on me, but I revive
like a phoenix! That's me, clay!
Here I am! Today, I fight with children
as I'm molded into shapes!
The next My Ordinary Life is Episode 20.
"Narration: Yuuji Mitsuya"
Come on, kids, bring it on!