"Spooky Face"
"Shinonome Lab"
"Shinonome Lab" A-A-A-Achoo!
A-A-A-Achoo!
It sure is getting cold lately.
Huh?
Wha--?
Sakamoto...
--H-H-Hey, wait!
--Sakamoto...
Wait, wait, wait! Would you guys cut it out?!
Just... what do you want from me?!
Greatest friendship
Super duper harmony
(na na na na na na na)
Hey! I'll say it
You are my best best friend
(bright) Every time I poke fun and tease you
(shine) You come and tease me back some more
(lan lan lan) There ain't
no better feeling in the world
(why) Even when bad things sometimes happen
(fine) I forget all of them around you
(lan lan lan) We'll forever let the good times roll
It's not a problem being with you
every hour of the day
As if we're twins, child-parent,
or a pair of cloned cells
Doesn't a friendship this good
make love not so needed anymore?
Wait hold on this and that
are totally totally different things
(fight) Even after we've had a fight
(down) Or when I feel down in the dumps
(shock) All the times I wanted to be alone
Before I know it there sitting beside me
my wonderful friend till the end
Why is it, I wanna be at your side?
Whenever we're together,
time flies 100 times faster
It's so fun with you,
I think it's almost too much fun
It's cuz you're such a good friend! Hey!
(na na na na na na na)
What's going on? Uh-oh we're synchronizing man!
It's always a wild time,
we make the people 'round us crazy
What time is it now? I think it's yodelayheehoo
What's that even mean?
SO-RE-DO-SHI-RA-
Unbelievably, how to put it, awesome!
No matter what happens
we are gonna be friends! Woohoo!
Greatest friendship
Super duper harmony
cha chara chara cha cha-n
Mai, you can apply the screentone.
As for Yuuko, you can use the pen to draw in
the page numbers and fill in the character's hair.
Okay.
Amazing!
Naganohara, you can even draw manga?
Well, it's nothing special.
She used to draw manga in secret
and never told anyone about it.
Who cares? That's in the past.
Is that true?
Well, yeah.
But the last time I sent one in,
it came back to me with a letter inside
saying they were hoping I would try again.
That made me think, maybe it's silly
that I keep drawing in secret from everyone.
They must think you have talent enough to make it!
I sincerely doubt that.
Do you mind if I take a look?
U-Um, Nano?
Ah... Sorry, sorry. It's fine
if you don't want to read it.
Nano?
S-Sorry. I think I need to go get some fresh air.
Are you okay? Want me to come?
No, no. You all came to give Naganohara
a hand with her manuscript.
I'll be back in a little while.
I kinda feel bad for poor Nano.
Oh, shoot! It's already this late?
Shucks. We don't have time to be goofing off.
Let's grind out as much as we can
before Nano gets back.
Tomorrow's the mail-in deadline.
Roger, roger!
You know, I'm pretty artistic myself.
This'll be a cinch.
All men to your battle stations!
Or something...
"My Ordinary Life 83"
Hey, Yuuko. We just started
and you're slacking already?
Here.
Oh, you're quick.
Gimme, gimme. Let's see...
I'll check it out.
I'll make you a slave.
Wha...?
Hey, Mai! What the heck did you draw?!
Priest Kuya.
That's not even the real problem here!
Why are you drawing things on your own?!
The blank space in the back was painful.
The heck?!
Just erase it all with the white-out.
Just stick to doing the screentone.
We don't need your graffiti.
Out of all the pain I've felt so far,
this is unofficially the worst.
I better fill in the hair.
"Here!! Kiss Thief"
Eh?
Um...
"Here!! Kiss Thief"
W-W-Wait! This, uh--! This--! Uh, um...
Oh, right.
If you see a mistake or something,
make sure to tell me right away.
Right away...
"Here!! Kiss Thief"
"All night long..."
"I'll close upon those teasing lips."
It's over! I've gotta do something to try and fix this!
Here.
Oh, you're done?
You know, I hope you didn't
draw anything weird this time.
I'll make you a grave.
Wha...?
"May God have mercy" A grave?!
What is this even?
A graveyard.
You idiot!
It's supposed to be a fancy palace in Daikanyama!
You can't be drawing like this!
Why do you keep doing it?!
Because there was space left over.
You're unbelievable!
I've had enough! Just erase it already!
You're only allowed to erase!
Only erase, you got it?!
All right.
I-I drew well for once!
I drew well, but this, it doesn't...
It looks nothing alike!
Will showing her just add fuel to the fire?
I'm done.
Did you erase it this time?
Sheesh. This time you better not
have done anything weird again.
Why?!
What's this?!
It's erased.
Do you want me to erase you?!
Why do you keep doing stuff like this?!
This manga... just isn't all that interesting.
Stop being so honest it hurts!
I'll give you some more paper,
so draw the grid lines like the other sheet.
All right.
Just the grid lines, got it?!
Helvetica Standard.
10 seconds.
20 seconds.
1, 2, 3, 4, 5,
6, 7, 8, 9, 10.
Time's up.
Th-This isn't going as planned!
He doesn't look anything close to how he should!
Who the heck is this guy?
If I show her this, it'll just make matters worse!
I'm done.
Okay.
You only drew the grid lines, right?
Long ago, there was a man and a woman.
The man ventured to the mountain
to gather firewood.
Private second class came from a peach.
What does that mean?!
Mai, please just read a book.
All right.
♪ Cha-cha-la-la! Cha!
Cha-cha-la-la! Cha! ♪
♪ Cha-cha-cha-cha, cha-la-la! ♪
Th-This...
...it's awful!
It's like the more I try to fix it,
the worse it becomes.
Not good, not good.
What should I do? What can I do?
Mai!
Leave it to me.
Y-You can actually fix it?
Can you draw it?
Mai!
That's right...
There's no way.
She can't really-- What?!
What?! Mai?!
She's good! So good it's crazy!
Maybe too good! But...
This...
It's too crazy to be good!
Let's go back... To that time...
Back to when I didn't know left from right.
Back to when everything was so fresh and new.
And then, let it be known.
The raw truth about me.
I'm so sorry!
Please, draw it over again!
But...
We don't have any more manuscript paper!
Huh? Huh?!
"Morals"
Uh, um...
You mustn't... run in the hall...
Sasahara!
"Word-Time"
Dammit, it won't come off.
They wanted nothing at all.
"My Ordinary Life 84"
Got you!
Naganohara?
What are you doing at a place like this?
No, no, no. Me, too.
Uh, right.
What are you doing?
Um, well... Nothing really.
Oh?
Uh, actually...
The competition is coming up,
but I just can't concentrate...
I'm sure that never happened to you
when you were in high school.
It's like, my armor feels so heavy these days...
She's not listening...
Shiitake Meditation is such a goofy manga!
This girl... She's totally useless outside of kendo.
Eh? What, what? Do you know a good story?
Just forget it.
By the way, aren't you going to
the national championship?
Oh, yeah.
Right? Mihoshi's been saying
you haven't come to the dojo...
I forgot I came to go shopping.
Huh? That's not...
Have my rice crackers.
Eh? Ehhh?
See ya!
What was that all about?
Hey, Sis!
What are you doing? Sitting there...
Just now, Naganohara passed by.
Really?! Even though tomorrow's
the national championship?
Seriously? It's tomorrow?!
Did she say anything?
Uh... Not really.
Oh. She left me these...
Want some?
Sure.
Wow. It's so red.
It sure is.
Spicy!
"Melon Bread"
"Expiration Date shown on bottom of bread."
"Expires"
"Love-Like"
Hey, hey, Mio.
Look at this.
What do you think? I bought this the other day
thinking it's about time for an image change.
Does it suit me?
Yeah. That's so you.
Are you ready?
"My Ordinary Life 85"
No, not yet!
Are you ready?
Okay, I'm ready!
All right! Then I'm coming to find you!
Hakase! Where could you be?
I'm ready!
"Daiku Eggs" Sakamoto spotted.
Beginner's luck is a hell of a thing.
I'm sorry.
I usually don't waste my time playing with you kids.
But, sometimes it's good just to break the boredom.
Right...
What are you doing?
Huh?
Hurry up and let's play some more!
--Shabadaba-doo!
--Right!
"Shinonome Lab" Hakase?
Where are you?
Hey, Brat!
Hakase?
I wonder where that brat is hiding.
She's not anywhere to be found.
Hmm...
No one will ever find me here.
Knowing that brat, she might be
hiding somewhere outside.
That's true. Isn't it about time we took a break?
Sure is. But you know what?
We might not even find her
for the rest of our lives.
Hakase?
Did you make this room yourself?
Yeah.
But why'd you come out of there anyway?
Doesn't that defeat the point of hide-and-seek?
Sheesh.
I was scared you might not ever be able to find me.
Well, that's true...
Hakase...
Did you... just blow your nose?
Yeah.
Geez, Hakase! Now I've got
even more laundry to do.
I guess that settles it!
This time I'll be it! Get ready, let's go again!
Then I can just wash it for you.
It'll probably get ruined so that's okay.
It won't get ruined, I promise...
No, no. I'm sure it'll get ruined somehow.
Eh? It'll be fine...
The Life of Pyon!
But then, what did you tell me?!
No, what I'm saying is...
I don't care what you're saying!
"My Ordinary Life 86"
You know, I'm glad you all came to help...
But guess what? You're the one
who spilled the ink everywhere.
And then we ran out of manuscript paper.
So I asked you to go out and buy
some more, but what did you say?
I asked you nicely, but what did you say?
So, let's decide who has to go buy it.
With a coin flip.
How about it?
You cheeky turd!
You're the one who knocked it over,
so you go get it!
I'm the one stuck with all the freaking work to do!
But whatever. In the end, you said
you'd go to the store to buy some.
But what did you say?!
Um, listen...
What did you say?!
Hey, hey.
How old do you think I look?
Who gives a damn?!
If you don't hurry up, the paper store will close!
Why are you asking me now?!
You look like your age!
But whatever. So, you finally
decided to get on your way.
So you put on your shoes and then...
It's so darn cold today!
Speaking of which, I have a bit of a cold.
Just suck it up and move your ass!
You're slower than molasses!
It's not even that cold today!
But whatever. So what did you buy
and come back with?
"Amazake"
What the hell is that?!
Um, so...
I asked you to go get manuscript paper!
Enough with the stupid jokes!
And what else did you show me?!
Here.
No, thank you!
I'm at the end of my patience here!
What am I supposed to do with you?!
And then you had the nerve to say to me...
I'm so sorry, calamari.
Calamari!
This isn't even funny anymore!
Where the hell did calamari come from?!
And yet I believed you. That you
actually went and got manuscript paper...
That it was all some hard-to-get joke!
But when I said to hurry and
bring out the paper, what did you say?
Mio, chill out. I'm sorry, calamari.
Calamari!
Are you saying sorry to me?!
--Um, I'm telling you...
--Or are you sorry to calamari?!
So I asked you one last time if you
actually got the manuscript paper!
And what did you say?!
I'm sorry, safari.
What the hell happened to calamari?!
Wait, who cares about calamari?!
Where's my manuscript paper!
And then?! What did you give me?!
Here.
Yeah, yeah. This is it.
Now, to finally wrap up and finish my novel.
You buffoon!
How long are you going to make a joke out of this?!
What do you want from me?!
And then you said...
The thing about the truth is...
it's not always true.
It is!
You're a lost cause, so I had to go ask Nano...
To please go buy some manuscript paper...
But then!
She's hooked!
She can't turn away!
Her happy squeals won't stop!
So then I gave up and went to ask Mai...
Mai, could I get you to go and buy some?
She already left!
She vanished without a sound!
She always goes at her own pace!
It's Mai's pace, so she goes at my pace!
But then you read the letter she left,
and what did you say?
"I went home"
It could be a prank from God.
"I went home" It's an evil trap.
This is all an evil trap!
It's been an evil trap since all of you came to help!
And what did you do next?!
I can't even start to understand!
I'm saying...
Stop! I don't want to hear your excuses!
You pickled pumpkin!
No, no, no. Hold on...
I don't want any more of your peanuts!
You...
You peanut head!
I'm telling you... This...
I don't want to hear it! You...
You... Huh?
"I-C Manga Manuscript Paper"
"Stationery Shop"
I-I'm sorry, calamari.
Let me feel that wonderful love once again
Ever since the day we pledged our lives
Even though we had such fond memories
We once looked upon the same flower
And said that it was beautiful
But our hearts no longer connect
Let me feel that wonderful love once again
Hello! I'm the pilot towards your dreams,
Manga Manuscript Paper.
Draw your heart out and achieve your dreams,
shooting me through the mail.
The next My Ordinary Life is Episode 21.
"Narration: Mami Koyama"
Walk-ins welcome, too.