Everything in this world
can be explained by science.
Our society often talks about
paranormal phenomenon.
Such dopey things cannot possibly exist.
It'd be wrong if they did.
In other words...
I refuse to believe in spirits!
"My Ordinary Life 93"
Greatest friendship
Super duper harmony
(na na na na na na na)
Hey! I'll say it
You are my best best friend
(bright) Every time I poke fun and tease you
(shine) You come and tease me back some more
(lan lan lan) There ain't
no better feeling in the world
(why) Even when bad things sometimes happen
(fine) I forget all of them around you
(lan lan lan) We'll forever let the good times roll
It's not a problem being with you
every hour of the day
As if we're twins, child-parent,
or a pair of cloned cells
Doesn't a friendship this good
make love not so needed anymore?
Wait hold on this and that
are totally totally different things
(fight) Even after we've had a fight
(down) Or when I feel down in the dumps
(shock) All the times I wanted to be alone
Before I know it there sitting beside me
my wonderful friend till the end
Why is it, I wanna be at your side?
Whenever we're together,
time flies 100 times faster
It's so fun with you,
I think it's almost too much fun
It's cuz you're such a good friend! Hey!
(na na na na na na na)
What's going on? Uh-oh we're synchronizing man!
It's always a wild time,
we make the people 'round us crazy
What time is it now? I think it's yodelayheehoo
What's that even mean?
SO-RE-DO-SHI-RA-
Unbelievably, how to put it, awesome!
No matter what happens
we are gonna be friends! Woohoo!
Greatest friendship
Super duper harmony
cha chara chara cha cha-n
I came to a local temple to ask for an exorcism.
So? What can I help you with?
I'll pretend like I'm possessed
by an evil spirit and point out the flaws.
Lately, it feels like something has been
strangling me by the throat.
My goodness.
Here. Use this.
Here it comes! He's going to recommend
some nonsense to ward away evil!
"Throat Drops"
It's made specifically for throat pain.
W-Well, I suppose that's quite logical.
Is my story not believable enough?
In any case, I have to make him believe.
Can't you see? It's not
just that my throat hurts, but...
It feels like someone's strangling me by the neck!
And that's when the strange voices
come out of my mouth!
Frankly, it's like I'm possessed!
It's that, isn't it?
Have you been reading too many weird books?
Maybe... Tone it down.
I never thought I'd be told
something like that... from an expert.
Actually, does this profession
even believe in spirits?
I came all the way to this temple though...
I'm not going to leave without giving it a shot!
Something evil is trying to choke me to death!
My...
I-I'm sorry.
He saw through it.
Of course he did. I can't expect to fool
an expert with such a lousy acting job.
I've got to sell it!
If he's going to believe me...
I've got to take it to the next level!
Wh-What the--?!
Stop! What do you think you're doing?!
What the hell's wrong with you?!
Y-You bastard!
Eeee-yah!
"Aikido"
You bastard!
My temple!
What are you doing in my temple?!
My hope for the future... is to become a scientist.
Sh-Shoot.
I lost control of myself.
Everything in this world can be explained by science.
I hope to spread that wisdom to the world.
And when the time comes,
impart this one message...
Are you okay?
G... Get out of my temple, you demon!
That is, there's a demon inside all of us, you see.
"My Ordinary Life 94"
Got you!
Who did that?!
It's been awhile, Mihoshi.
Hey, you! Naganohara!
I look away for a minute and
you're already a middle schooler.
That's because you've stopped coming to the dojo.
I haven't been training at college really either.
I skip it.
And yet you still won the national championship?
You dumb, gifted natural!
Going to the dojo?
Yeah, now that my club is over.
Will you come, Naganohara?
Hmm... I'm the kind of type that
gets worse the more that I train.
What the heck?
You dumb, gifted natural!
But I will admit she's good.
What I can't tolerate is that
she's so good without even training.
When she was in first year of middle school,
they say she got a point against the instructor.
Against the instructor!
I'm the same age now, and I can't even come close.
I go to the dojo after club,
and even give up my weekends to train!
Because the instructor says
great effort will open new doors.
Look! A black cat!
Hey, kitty...
Whenever I see her, it makes me tremble.
Ah, so cute!
I want to take a swing...
Just one swing...
If I do it now, even I can...
This is all I can do now, but one day, in a match...
And then against the instructor, too!
You dumb, gifted natural!
S-Sorry!
Instructor!
"Love-Like"
I'm freezing...
"Daifuku Fair"
"Daifuku"
Listen up. I'm counting on you.
"Control"
My father wants me to follow in his footsteps.
"Control" Take this balloon.
If a kid comes, give it away.
I'm not gonna do it. I'll find a way to escape!
This is ridiculous...
It's not even floating!
"Word-Time"
Everyone hopes to at least see a happy ending.
"Shinonome Lab"
"A Certain Magical Christmas"
What are you asking Santa for, Hakase?
I want, um...
Chocolate snacks, and colored pencils...
...a cake eraser, and um, um...
Ah! It's no fair if you ask for so much!
Then I'm going to ask for...
Two packs of eggs, and a gallon of milk...
...an Ivan Bilibin book, and--
I'm the one who asked for a lot first,
so Nano only gets one!
Nano? Um, um...
You can ask for a little of a lot, so...
I'll even give you this, too.
Helvetica Standard.
Hello!
Yes! It's Santa!
Merry Christmas--
"Yummy Melon Bread"
"Daifuku"
"Trap" "Daifuku"
I won't take part in this joke any longer!
I'll quickly take of this mask and...
Ow! Ow-ow-ow!
Trying to run, Tsuyoshi?
Father?!
This time, I added a little trap to the mask.
A trap?
On the inside of that mask...
Glue! Freshly applied!
Hot!
Crap! I dropped my fresh meat bun!
And I didn't even get to take one bite...
Just think, Weboshii...
If that meat bun was poisoned,
you might have died or something.
Consider it a good thing.
There's nothing good about it.
That was my favorite part about the walk home.
You know what they say... If you think positive,
luck will always come your way.
Take a look at that meat bun... and thank it.
"My Ordinary Life 95"
What's with this positive attitude?
I've decided to think positive from now on
no matter what happens in life.
See? If you just peel off the dirty parts, it's edible.
What happened to it being poisoned?
Like dis. Pull uff ta part dats dirty--
Hot!
Oh! My ice pop is safe!
See what I said? Positive thinking brings good luck.
It's positive thinking magic.
But my meat bun is out...
It's times like this you gotta stay positive.
If that meat bun was
actually poisoned, you'd be dead.
Is that your only variation?
Gah!
Even if I take off the bottom, don't forget
that your ice pop landed on top of it.
Come on, now. Think positive! Think positive!
Good God!
It probably melted from
the meat bun being all hot.
If I pretend my ice pop
was poisoned, it's not so bad...
You already munched on it...
What's up?
"Loser"
It looks like your luck ran out!
No! It's a message from God saying
if I ate another, I'd get a sick stomach.
Oh? You're unusually
stubborn today, even for you.
Besides if this was ice cream,
I wouldn't have a chance of saving it, but..
This ice will clean up since I can just brush it off.
As for that, I'm thankful.
You're still going to eat it?
Wait!
How does it look?
It looks soaking wet.
Hey, Fe. Be positive! Be positive!
Ehh! I give up!
"Sprint Towards Freedom"
If you're so opposed
to following in my footsteps...
I'll prepare a second trap,
a third, and so on until you do!
Father...
This is...
You...
...my...
It can't be!
...answer!
"School Counseling Office"
Tachibana... What are your plans for the future?
Um... I'm deciding between college
and becoming a professional chef.
Oh? A chef?
I...
I-I-I...
And marry him?!
Calm down, Tachibana.
"Shinonome Lab"
Tie it like this...
And we're done!
I'm home!
Ah! Nano! I'm going to take Sakamoto on a walk.
My friends are coming over to study.
Is that all right?
"My Ordinary Life 96"
Okay. I wanna play, too, so I'll be back soon.
See you later.
Hey, stop! What are you doing, Brat?!
I'll die! I'll die!
All right! You win! Make a wish! What do you want?!
Shark.
You're kidding me!
♪ Walking alone... and crying... ♪
I'm the one who wants to cry!
All right! Shark! I'll get you a shark!
I'll get you a stinking shark, so let me go!
Dogs...
It's dogs, so they might bite us...
Sakamoto... it's dogs.
We might get bitten...
Wh-Wh-What are you s-s-scared of dogs for?
They're on a leash, so there's no way they will.
We've got no choice but to run!
Okay! We'll run!
Sakamoto! We can't run!
Don't give up! Give up and we're doomed!
Tell their owner! Put 'em on a leash!
Geez!
We're doomed!
No, no! Wrack your brain!
Is there nothing?! Is there nothing?!
I found a gummi in my pocket.
Oh! Good one! We can run
while they're busy eating it!
I know! Make an invention to let us escape!
Oh yeah! I almost forgot!
Sakamoto!
What?!
I don't have tools to make anything!
Dammit!
Whatever! Boil me! Grill me!
Do whatever you want, you beasts!
Boil me...
Grill me...
Do whatever you want...
Meal...
I'll be eaten... I'll be eaten!
If I'm eaten, I might be eaten...
Hmm? Hakase?
What are you crying for? Are you lost?
It's Yuuko!
Eh? So this is the Hakase you were talking about.
Oh? Sakamoto's with you?
Let me pet him! Let me pet him!
No, Yuuko! Chase the dogs away!
Ooh! He's fluffier than I thought!
I get to pet him next!
I'm not kidding! Go chase the dogs away!
I know! You were bit so you want revenge?
No! It looks like they're going to bite me!
What's that? Are you afraid of dogs?
Who are you, Q-taro?
I'm not! It's a dog and they bite!
Just look at him. How could a dog that gentle bite?
He'll bite!
He won't bite.
Wanna bite on some gum?
He'll bite!
Just wait and see.
Gimme your paw.
Hey, Yuuko. You okay?
"Rattle"
They won't bite if you don't
go near them, so you'll be fine.
Yuuko was... Yuuko was...
Don't worry. She's just an idiot, okay?
All right...
Come on. Let's pick up Yuuko
and go together to Nano's place.
Oh? You know Nano?
Of course I--
Where did you go?!
You have to keep your dogs on a leash!
Did you play with them?
Are you crazy?! They're going to bite me!
"Choco" "Take a break" For you.
Shark Choco!
Thank you very much.
I got choco and got to see dogs.
What a nice walk, Sakamoto.
Hmph! You're still such a child
to be afraid of dogs.
More importantly, take this rope off me.
I got my choco, so okay.
Huh?
What's wrong?
Sakamoto, take it off.
It's tight.
If I could, I would!
I'll get Yuuko to pull it off.
Hey, Yuuko. Pull this.
Hey, Yuuko!
Hey, Yuuko! I said hey!
Hey... Isn't that...
Gah!
I'm home!
There's so many dogs...
You're covered in sweat!
Oh yeah! I got choco!
♪ Choco, choco, choco, choco, choco! ♪
--My goodness, Aioi and Naganohara
--♪ Shark choco! ♪
--♪ Choco, choco, shark, shark, shark choco! ♪
--sure must be running late...
"Heart"
I think they ran this way...
What the heck?
Buddy! Li'l-Buddy!
What happened here?
Gramps!
As people, we must always be there
to help each other, Takashi.
That same compassion lives in
the hearts of animals, too, Takashi.
The bond between humans and animals
is one to remember, Takashi.
Gramps...
I'm Kiyoshi.
Precious teachers, we're grateful to you
In your garden of learning we've grown for years
Reminiscing about those precious days,
how quickly they have passed
Alas, the day has come to part.
Alas, this means goodbye.
"Yummy Melon Bread"
I'm Melon Bread.
Fair humans... Whether or not
I should taste like melon or not
is a question that has been debated for eternity.
The next My Ordinary Life is Episode 23.
"Narration: Hidekatsu Shibata"
Look forward to it!