By the way, was Sasahara actually sleeping?
Yeah, he totally was.
His arms were crossed and he wasn't moving at all.
Misato, go back and wake him up.
Sasahara probably forgot
we're changing classrooms.
Wh-What's it matter? Just let him be.
Don't you feel bad?
He's your childhood friend. Go and wake him up.
Besides, Sasahara is probably all alone
in the classroom right now.
Eh?
Wh-What?
We'll go ahead without you.
Good luck!
W-Wait!
Sheesh! Why am I the one
who has to do something about him?
Just because we're childhood--
You should confess to Sasahara already.
Greatest friendship
Super duper harmony
(na na na na na na na)
Hey! I'll say it
You are my best best friend
(bright) Every time I poke fun and tease you
(shine) You come and tease me back some more
(lan lan lan) There ain't
no better feeling in the world
(why) Even when bad things sometimes happen
(fine) I forget all of them around you
(lan lan lan) We'll forever let the good times roll
It's not a problem being with you
every hour of the day
As if we're twins, child-parent,
or a pair of cloned cells
Doesn't a friendship this good
make love not so needed anymore?
Wait hold on this and that
are totally totally different things
(fight) Even after we've had a fight
(down) Or when I feel down in the dumps
(shock) All the times I wanted to be alone
Before I know it there sitting beside me
my wonderful friend till the end
Why is it, I wanna be at your side?
Whenever we're together,
time flies 100 times faster
It's so fun with you,
I think it's almost too much fun
It's cuz you're such a good friend! Hey!
(na na na na na na na)
What's going on? Uh-oh we're synchronizing man!
It's always a wild time,
we make the people 'round us crazy
What time is it now? I think it's yodelayheehoo
What's that even mean?
SO-RE-DO-SHI-RA-
Unbelievably, how to put it, awesome!
No matter what happens
we are gonna be friends! Woohoo!
Greatest friendship
Super duper harmony
cha chara chara cha cha-n
Sasahara!
We're moving classrooms
so what are you sleeping for?
Misato Tachibana.
G-Go and get your textbook for class.
I see...
I only intended to rest my eyes a moment.
I must have been lulled to sleep.
You better hurry it up, okay?!
If we're both late to class,
people will misunderstand!
Misunderstand?
About what?
Shut up!
"My Ordinary Life 106"
N-No! I mean...
What I mean is, what was it doing there?
It's your fault for being so slow!
Misato Tachibana.
There's blood on your hand.
Wh-What are you being nice for?
You should be angry that I broke your glasses.
Why?
It doesn't hurt when my glasses are broken.
But it hurts your hand, I'm sure.
What's that?
Of course it does.
Are you trying to sound cool?
Fortunately, one of the lenses is still intact.
It's a fragile survivor of war.
Speaking of a fragile survivor...
Speaking of fragile...
I'll guide you.
Misato Tachibana.
I know!
I know what I did was bad... I know it's my fault!
"As soon as they begin walking..."
You know what I'm saying?
That's totally not cool at--
So...
I know, right? But then--
Ugh! They're staring!
I'm dying! I'm dying!
So embarrassed I'm dying!
But, it's my fault I broke his glasses.
I've got to act as Sasahara's eyes for now.
It's fine. It's fine.
If I tell people his glasses are broke,
they'll see I'm just doing a good deed.
That's right! I'm just being a nice volunteer
by being his eyes for the whole day!
Misato Tachibana.
Y-Yes?!
Before we go to the classroom,
I'd like to use the toilet.
Th-The toilet?!
You mean, the men's toilet?!
Naturally.
An obstacle has appeared!
But, I'm the one whose fault this is...
What doesn't kill you makes you stronger...
All right! I'm coming, too!
Why?
Because your glasses are broken!
And?
Sheesh, are you clueless?!
You can't see at all, so I'm saying
I'll be your eyes for the rest of the day!
Oh.
These are fake.
Don't misunderstand, all right?!
There happened to be a bug on your right arm!
I was only trying to slowly crush it with mine, okay?!
What beautiful weather today.
"Shinonome Lab"
"Nap" "Shinonome Lab"
"Curry" U-Um!
"Curry"
There's this spicy curry restaurant in Kamakura!
Y-Yes?
Ms. Sakurai, which level of spicy do you eat?!
U-Um...
Only zero...
M-Me, too!
"My Ordinary Life 107"
Um, Naganohara?
Class is about to start...
Wait, Mio! The Language Lab isn't that way!
Language Lab...
And, hey, besides! It's like baseball,
you never know what's gonna happen!
That's what makes life fun!
You never know what's gonna happen.
That's baseball.
We still don't know if that person
is his girlfriend, you know?
Right, Nano?
Eh? Ah, yeah! That's right!
Sasahara is...
He's...
Anyways, let's head back, Mio.
Mio!
Naganohara!
Nano, get to Language Lab
and make an excuse for us!
Okay!
Mio, wait!
Mio! You'll crash!
Mio!
M-Mio!
M-Mio?!
Mio!
--Say cheese!
--Mio!
Mio!
This is my stop.
M-Mio!
Mio!
Mio! Mio!
--Ma fell in the river!
--Mio!
Mio! Mio! Mio! Mio! Mio! Mio! Mio! Mio!
Dammit!
Ch-Chan Mio!
Ch-Chan Mio?!
Thank you...
Mio!
Mio, are you okay?!
I think...
I'm whipped.
Mio...
Where is he?!
This way!
M-Ma!
Osamu?
Thank goodness! Are you okay?!
You all right?
Yeah, I think so.
Because this person saved me.
Y-You two!
Ah!
From that time!
I hope you two know that interfering
with police work is a criminal offense!
You two?! Even me?!
Normally, I'd try to get a hold of your school, but...
Given the circumstances, I'll overlook it this once.
Really?
There you are. There you are.
I've finally tracked you down, Braid Girl.
After seeing you shadow box...
...something sparked in my head.
What do you say?
With boxing... You can take the world by storm.
--He snatched my purse!
--Don't think bad of me!
I've gotta go!
Come to the station later!
You'll get commendation for your help!
Hey, lady... Will you take this?
Sure...
Osamu, you don't mind right?
Of course not!
When you're ready, please make a trip to the gym.
I'll talk to you then when you come.
Ah, your English textbook
got lost during all of that!
Mio?
Rejected before I even confessed...
Saved a kid while sprinting at full speed...
Got an award... Got a kite...
Got scouted by a boxer...
It's true. You never know what's gonna happen.
It's exactly how you said.
Eh?
You never know what's gonna happen.
That's why it's interesting.
That's baseball. Right?
Eh? What do you mean?
See what I mean?
"Word-Time"
I just realized that daydreaming is totally free.
Damn... I completely lost track of her.
"My Ordinary Life 108"
I was right on her mark at school, but...
The moment I took my eyes off her,
she suddenly disappeared.
What a remarkable advanced feature.
It only makes me want to know
your secrets more, Nano Shinonome!
Well, I've come this far.
Perhaps I should look for her house.
Hmm... It may be dangerous to probe too deeply.
I'll continue tailing her tomorrow
and back out for today--
"Shinonome Lab"
It's completely in the open!
I stumbled across her house. This is my first lucky
break since beginning my mission to capture her.
No, this is more than mere luck.
It's what you'd call... Um, uh, um...
Whatever!
"Shinonome"
What's with this rising tension?!
I want to sneak right in and take a look at the lab!
I want to see the person who made her!
I want to steal her blueprints!
This excitement is causing a stampede in my heart!
Calm down, the cowboy inside me, Bill Watts!
If this is the house of her creator,
there's no knowing what traps there may be.
I must restrain myself to be safe.
Right. Today, I'll just have a peek--
Can I help you?
Guinea!
Shoot! I was spotted by a surveillance robot!
He looks cheaply built, but he's probably made
with the same advanced technology as Nano!
If I'm a threat, who knows what he'll do to me?!
For now, I need to appear innocent.
Ms. Nakamura?
Guinea!
"School Counseling Office"
Last week, I heard your goat
carried a hurt old lady to the hospital.
Indeed.
Is that why you come to school
on a goat, for situations like that?
Don't be ridiculous.
Riding your goat is ridiculous.
Here you go.
I let down my guard and it cost me.
And though I've infiltrated her house,
I mustn't forget I'm in hostile territory.
Make no mistake, I'm surrounded by traps.
For example, this tea. I'm certain
it contains some drug to erase my memory.
And this room, too. It must be under surveillance.
Wh-Wh-What's that?!
Something about it is all wrong!
It's sitting there so randomly, I'm almost positive
it's watching over my each and every move.
If I do something wrong... it'll get me!
Wh-What's wrong?
Oh, sorry! It's nothing.
I drank it...
--Um, was it too hot?
--How foolish of me!
I've got nothing to lose!
I'll come straight out and say it.
Eh? O-Okay.
I came here because I want
to know everything about you!
Eh?
Eh?!
I want you to show me your true self!
--Eh?!
--No?
Um! Everyone's free
to make their own decisions, but...
Two girls dating isn't so normal, and I think,
probably for me, that normal is best...
Y-You dummy! No!
You're so wrong!
What are you thinking? That's so embarrassing!
Ah, I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
What I meant by knowing everything about you is--
Nano?
--Hakase!
--Eh?!
--Nano...
--Is this the one she calls Hakase?
--We ran out of snacks.
--No, no, I must've misheard something.
--You'll have to wait for tomorrow.
--Eh?
--This child can't be the one
--who created Nano Shinonome.
--Eh?
--Who's this person?
--Could she be one of her relatives?
--It's Ms. Nakamura from school.
--Her younger sister?
--Ah!
--It's Ms. Nakamura from school.
Which means, the child is a robot.
Hello, I'm Hakase.
I created Nano.
Shoulder block!
--H-Hakase! Why did you say that?!
--Created? This child created Nano?
--It's just my introduction.
Hey!
Do something about this!
That brat screwed with me again!
Ho... Ho...
Homunculus!
The surveillance robot! The daruma weapon!
The child Hakase! Nano Shinonome! Homunculus!
I admit it was stupid to come into this house
completely unprepared and unarmed, but...
I never thought it'd be this dangerous!
--I've gotta find a chance to escape from here
--Hakase, how did you tie this knot?
--and reformulate my plans!
--Tighty-tight knot.
--Not again, Brat!
However...
Knowing that thing will attack
makes me so scared I'm afraid to move!
If I suddenly say something like I have to go home...
This leaves just one option...
I need to use the toilet. Is that all right?
Y-Yeah.
I'll show you--
No, thanks!
If you tell me where it is, I can go alone.
You completely fell for it, Nano Shinonome.
My escape tactic has worked.
I knew it would. She believed I'd do
exactly what I said I'd do.
Yes... Her weakness is that she trusts people.
The next time I come back to this place,
I'll be turning the tables on you.
Just you wait.
As long as you still have that weak point,
I'll come back as much as it takes!
Oh... Were you leaving?
Ah!
Shoot!
Uh, well... I was asked to
take care of the grass outside...
Wha--?!
Uh, don't move an inch!
Crap! They're onto me!
They're all going to find out
I was trying to sneak away and escape!
Dammit! What is this stuff?!
My body! My freedom!
This way!
Huh? The toilet's not that way...
Ack! What in the world?!
Oh!
Hakase! Doesn't this glue come off with water?!
--If they capture me here, it's all over for me.
--What?!
--Water! Water!
--All my hopes! All my dreams!
--Huh? What?!
--Crap! I've got to get out of here somehow!
--I can't hear you!
--You bastards from the Shinonome Lab!
--Hurry up and take this off me!
--Nano! I want snacks!
--Water! Water!
--Someone help me...
--What do you want me to do?
--Nano!
--Anyone!
--Bring water!
--Somebody help me!
"No Eternal Life No Killing"
"My Ordinary Life 109"
Oh, I actually have that one.
Really? Could I borrow it?
Sure. I'll bring it next time.
You never know what's
gonna happen. That's baseball...
Is that all she said?
Yeah. And then she laughed and acted all happy.
Do you think she's just pretending?
She was kinda rejected by
the guy she's liked for so long...
She doesn't not look like she's not happy.
Wait, which was that?
Yuuko, did you forget your homework?
No! You're wrong!
Uh, but you're right,
I did forget my homework.
Which is it?
The answer... is after the commercials!
Huh?
That's so funny, Aioi!
Right, Minakami?
Left-hand rule?
Rap?
Naganohara. There's something else I need to ask.
S-Sure.
What?
Aioi, is there anything you know?
Some way to cheer up Naganohara.
I wonder why they all left.
And I was hoping to grab a bite
with Yuuko and the others, too...
Whoa!
What are you doing?!
Congratulations!
Take a spin.
What's going on? That's Yuuko, right?
Yuuko? Who might that be?
It's totally obvious.
I can even see Nano's key.
Th-This isn't anything robotic!
Anyways, everyone who comes
through here has to do the lottery.
Come on. Hurry, hurry.
What?
I don't get what this is all about.
I just turn it, right?
Congratulations!
What? You're so loud...
Here's your special prize.
What's this all about?
Just take it already!
Eh?
I keep telling you that these
little jokes of yours are so annoy--
Great, now go on your way.
Thank you.
Bonus prize.
Freshly carved.
Thanks...
I heard once that Sasahara said
something a while back...
That our ordinary lives that pass by day by day...
...actually may be a series of wonderful miracles.
I think... No, I know...
That that's true.
"Friends for life coupon"
"Aioi" "Shinonome" "Minakami"
All right! Let's go home and draw manga!
Let's search for tomorrow in this huge world
Now is the time, so let's all journey together
Towards tomorrow's endless possibilities
Finding all of our hopes and our dreams
Let's search for tomorrow
Search for tomorrow
In this huge world
"Love-Like"
Sheesh. It's your fault we got lost out here.
Sorry. I'll look up the way on my mobile phone.
What, do you think you're British?
Just call it a cell phone.
Ah!
Why are you watching TV on there?!
Misato Tachibana should watch TV on hers, too.
Mine doesn't have TV!
I'm Nano's Key!
Sometimes I spin, sometimes I don't...
Sometimes I get pulled out! That's my daily life!
The next My Ordinary Life is the last!
"Narration: Keiko Yokozawa"