"Scorching"
"Sold Out"
Man, it's so hot.
Too hot!
Tanaka, all you've been saying
is "It's hot" for a while now.
It's hot enough already, so if you
say it's hot, it feels even hotter.
So no more saying it's hot.
Okay, okay.
Man, it's scorching.
This summer sure is scorching.
You know?
Man, it's so scorching.
Why's it so scorching?! Scorching!
It's so scorching!
I may just have to punch him...
It's scorching! So scorching!
It really is scorching!
I realized just this very moment
I think I might have fallen in love
24 hours a day of you you you
I can't get you out of my head!
Something (something) feels different now
With you (together) it's awkward conversation
Is it (mutual love) no it's one-sided love
Uh-oh I think our eyes just met!
What is this anxious nervous feeling?
My train of thought is tangled with confusion...
This kind of thing is a first for me
Could it be a fever and I'm sick?
With a sudden twist it's awakened love
There's a fire in my cheeks and my face is all red
Th-Th-This can't be real, my hands are trembling
Is this what people mean when they talk about "love"?
I-I-I'm stuttering non-stop talking to you
Awkward silence and then mumble-mumble-mo
I wanna (I wanna) know how you feel about me
O-O-O-One one-sided love
First love! Every day on the path to school
Sparkle-sparkle dazzling I DO fall in love!
It's like I'm flying through the sky
O-O-O-One one-sided love
Shiny!
Today, anything and everything is sparkling!
The air, the people, and...
...even the classroom!
That's because...
Today, I actually completed my homework!
I've gotta show this off to Mio.
What? Whaaat...?
Wh-Wh-What?
"My Ordinary Life 48"
Wh-Wh-What?!
No, no, no! It can't be!
The one time I actually did my homework?!
Why? Why, why?!
Why isn't it here?!
Well, I guess it's fine if I copy it.
Hey, Mio!
Wait...
Wait a sec... Wait!
Our homework... was a printout!
What's wrong, Yuuko?
You're noisy this morning.
The homework...
I forgot it...
Can the aliens please come invade now?
You forgot your homework again?
Don't make fun of me! I did it, but I forgot it!
I'm not making fun of you.
It's the language printout, right?
Maybe you jammed it
inside a book or something.
Did you look for it?
I just searched for it a minute ago.
It's definitely not--
"Geography"
"Neighborhood Association"
"Daifuku Fair"
My God!
What the hell is a Daifuku Fair?!
What's that... stupid fair...
W-Well...
Maybe they left a printout
you can use in the front desk.
You're kidding! You really found one?!
"Daifuku Fair"
Dammit!
Dammit, dammit! Son of a dammit!
You're going to get it?
You won't make it in time!
Even so, I must go!
Hey, class is about to start.
Get to your seats.
"Idiom"
Roll, roll, roll, roll, roll...
Spin, spin, spin, spin, spin...
Rush and you'll spin your wheels.
"My Ordinary Life 49"
"Go+Soccer Club"
He made me stand outside again...
Why is it that every time
I forget my homework?
I even did it today, but then I forgot it...
God, you cruel fool!
"Shinonome Lab"
"Business Card" "Shinonome Lab"
"Business Card" Sakamoto.
Here's my business card.
"Hakase"
What's this about? What do I say?
What's this about?
"Hakase"
What do I say?!
"Vending Machine"
"Sports Cider" "H Cider" "Apple" "Black"
Sorry!
What's the matter, Misato Tachibana?
Wh-What?
New drinks came out, so I was
just pondering which one to get.
I see.
Then, this...
I'm not going along with what you say.
...one is rather awful.
So I recommend the one next to it.
Sorry to bother you.
I-It's not like I bought it
because you suggested it!
When I heard there were stalls in
"My Ordinary Life 50"
the neighborhood, I went to check it out.
But what I really came for
was the shooting game.
I've only ever seen it on TV,
so I'm really excited to play.
But all I brought is 500 yen...
Will it be enough?
Hello. One go is 500 yen.
Lucky! I have exactly enough!
I wish I had enough for yakisoba, too,
but this is what I came for.
It's all just eggplant and caramel...
Um...
Don't you have anything else?
Anything else? What's that?
It's all brand name goods here.
Well, I did already pay.
I can't leave without something.
Missy, you shouldn't aim for
the big prize right away.
It's not that easy to knock over.
Big prize?
Why not aim for something easier to get?
Easier to get?
The only other choice is caramel though.
"Daiku Caramel"
So close!
That caramel is totally stuck in place!
A little bit more and you had it!
You're pretty good at this, Missy.
Don't tell me you're a trained gunman?
Just kidding!
This eggplant isn't budging an inch!
What's the matter? Making such a pitiful face.
You're thinking I might be cheating you?
My stall is too cheap for such tricks.
But my spirit and honesty are authentic!
No way... There's totally
something going on here.
"Knock Over and Win" "500 yen"
What's that?!
What?! Look! Look, what is that?!
A nail! I see a nail! A nail!
This is totally a fraud!
Hey! Why aren't you saying anything?!
You're not allowed to do stuff like that!
You were talking so much just a minute ago!
At this rate, I bet even
the caramel is rigged, too!
You're just pretending to sleep!
I've still got a bullet left,
but what's the point of shooting?!
"Shooting Game"
Don't come back.
What the heck...?
Things that are cool!
"Aioi"
Mio!
Here it comes!
"Aioi"
Nice catch!
Oh! Super Ball!
Things that are cool!
Damn! So close!
Wow!
Oh! Slip stream!
Thanks!
I haven't been to
an amusement park in forever!
Isn't it great to come?
I want a drink so lend me my wallet.
Oh, that's right.
I forgot you had me hold onto it.
Sorry about that.
If I keep it, I'll probably lose it.
That's true.
What?
Wh-What?
Wh-Wh-What?
What? Wh-Wh-What?
Wh-What?!
I-It should be right here...
I think I dropped your wallet.
"My Ordinary Life 51"
H-Hey!
If we go to the Lost and Found,
it might be there!
How much was in it?
Four thousand, sixteen yen.
That's so precise...
"Lost And Found"
Um, we're looking for a brown
wallet with snakeskin inside.
There's one just like it.
Whew! Aren't you glad we found it?
I know! I thought it was gone for good!
This is an announcement
regarding a lost child.
A girl with denim shorts,
a tucked denim shirt...
...and wearing a denim hat,
has been found looking for her mother.
If you know this child, please come
to the lost child station immediately.
I'm so terrified of haunted houses!
It's coming!
I'm taking it!
"Phantom Left Hook"
"Coffee Shop" "Daiku Cafe"
Three lattes. Will this be for carryout?
Uh...
Um!
I'd like this, this, and this, too, please.
"Izumi"
Um, sorry. Could you please tell me the name?
It's Sakurai.
Um, that's not what I meant.
Oh, I'm so sorry.
It's Izumi. Izumi Sakurai.
No, I mean, I wasn't asking
the name of yourself personally.
You know, people often say
I have two last names.
Um... By name, I meant the name of the item.
The name of the item?
Sorry, but I don't really know it...
No, um... I'm very sorry.
"Restaurant House"
"Japanese Food Fair"
Whew. That was delicious.
"Chopstick Holder"
"Chopstick Holder" Yum, yum!
Now all that's left is for
our dessert to be served!
Yeah.
I'm doing one, too.
I'm done!
Me, too.
Wow! Cool!
Good one, Mai!
How's yours, Yuuko? Done?
Crane?
“Shinonome Lab”
Nano! Look, look!
"My Ordinary Life 52" Ta-dah!
"My Ordinary Life 52"
I put one on me, too!
Now that we match, we're like a pair!
I guess we are.
I'm going to be Nano all day,
so don't call me Hakase, okay?
All right, Nano.
That was fast!
Hakase, did you quit already?
Nano! You just called me Hakase!
Um, well that's because you took off the key...
I'm just taking a break right now!
I'm still being Nano all day!
All right.
Hakase, I mean...
Nano, do you want to play a game?
Sure! What kind?
You can be me and I can be you.
We'll switch roles!
For sure!
Okay, Hakase. I mean...
Nano has to wear the key, then.
Okay!
And since I'm being Hakase,
let's take the key off my back.
Not a chance.
Hey, hey! What game should we play?
Cards or something?
"Yummy Snack" "SnaQ"
Ah, these snacks are tasty.
I was saving those snacks for later!
But now...
...I am...
...Hakase, so...
That doesn't make any sense!
I can be Nano, but if Nano is me and
eats my snacks, Nano should just stay Nano!
Then since I'll be remaining as Nano...
...I'll be leaving to buy the meal for tonight.
“Shinonome Lab” I'm coming, too!
“Shinonome Lab”
We're not buying any snacks.
I want to buy shark chocolate and apple juice!
“Shinonome Lab” No way.
“Shinonome Lab” Let's buy some!
“Shinonome Lab” No.
--Hey. Don't forget my food again.
--Shark chocolate and apple juice!
It's another peaceful day at
the Shinonome household.
"A Daiku Burger in every city!" "Delicious!"
"Lunch Game"
The first one to use an English word loses.
Okay.
You just used English.
I'm safe because you didn't say start.
Should I speak a bunch of
English before we start?
You know a bunch of English?
Okay.
"Word-Time"
Carbonation makes drinks fizzy
which really seems to wake you up.
"Unintended"
I fell asleep.
Oh?
The sleeping beauty wakes without a kiss.
Why?
Wh-Why what?
Wake in the morning, teeth get a brushing
Before you know it, it's ten at night
Another day was full of laughter
Another day filled with joy
Goofing with friends and acting so silly
Making a ruckus and then I see
A glimpse from you and then our eyes meet
Coincidence, or not?
I won't ever admit it's first love
That's not something I would say
Hey, I'll see you again tomorrow too.
When I close my eyes I see
My vision sparkling, filled with you
Wasn't it so much fun today?
Ah, I think I'm in love
I'm so happy I'm so happy
Nice to meet you, awakening love
I'll see you again tomorrow too
Good night
I'll see you again soon in my dreams
Welcome home, Master!
It's Cider-meow!
There's a magic spell sealed in
my bubbles to make me tasty-meow!
"Narration: Satomi Koorogi"
The next My Ordinary Life is Episode 13.
Look forward to it!