"Shinonome Lab"
I'm starving.
That brat...
Doesn't she have anything better to do?
Well, if that's all it is,
I might as well fall for the trap.
The bait's worth it.
--I got you! I got you!
--Dammit.
I got the short end of the stick.
Ah!
This was going to be the side dish for lunch.
Now we've got nothing.
Sakamoto...
It's your fault, too.
Nuh-uh! Sakamoto said he wanted to eat it.
--I did not!
--Good morning!
--Where'd you get that idea, Brat?
Well, you ate it, didn't you?
It's so hot today.
It sure is.
Let's get ice cream on the way home.
Yeah, let's!
Hey, Brat.
Don't you think she wants to go to school?
Don't leave me!
What's wrong all of a sudden?
Nano's going to leave me...
What? Who said that I'm going away?
Sakamoto.
That's not even close to what I said!
Nano? Are you going somewhere?
I was planning to go shopping before lunch.
Since our side dish is gone,
we'll need something else.
I want to go shopping, too!
I'm not buying anything else.
I wanna buy shark chocolate!
Not happening.
Buy it!
--Shark chocolate!
--I said I'm not buying it.
Buy it! Buy it!
I will not.
Sakamoto wants you to, too!
I never said that!
I realized just this very moment
I think I might have fallen in love
24 hours a day of you you you
I can't get you out of my head!
Something (something) feels different now
With you (together) it's awkward conversation
Is it (mutual love) no it's one-sided love
Uh-oh I think our eyes just met!
What is this anxious nervous feeling?
My train of thought is tangled with confusion...
This kind of thing is a first for me
Could it be a fever and I'm sick?
With a sudden twist it's awakened love
There's a fire in my cheeks and my face is all red
Th-Th-This can't be real, my hands are trembling
Is this what people mean when they talk about "love"?
I-I-I'm stuttering non-stop talking to you
Awkward silence and then mumble-mumble-mo
I wanna (I wanna) know how you feel about me
O-O-O-One one-sided love
First love! Every day on the path to school
Sparkle-sparkle dazzling I DO fall in love!
It's like I'm flying through the sky
O-O-O-One one-sided love
Mio...
Good morning...
What's wrong, Yuuko? You look awful!
Now mention you it, felt awful since morning.
Wait a sec. You can't even form
a complete sentence.
Do you have a fever, too?
Why didn't you stay home today?
No way...
Remember?
I told you before... I was gonna show you my magic.
"My Ordinary Life 53" You know?
"My Ordinary Life 53"
What are you talking about?
That's the first I've heard of it.
Hey! Just forget about your magic, okay?
But I practiced it so much...
Once you witness my magic,
you'll be so shocked.
Just wait and see.
To be honest, I'm shocked already.
Why don't you take a se--!
Yuuko...
Your props...
...are migrating out of your bag!
For now, let's pretend that I didn't see it.
After all, she dragged herself here to show me.
That Yuuko... What kind of trick
was she planning to pull?
Dove!
D-D-D-Dove on the head!
The props are on the loose!
It flew away!
Tissue...
All right. You ready?
I'm going to start.
O-Okay...
Ugh, what am I doing?
I just hid it without thinking.
"Agriculture"
"Agriculture" Um...
Here we go.
First off...
She must be incredibly sick to not notice
the missing dove or wand.
I'll pass a cigarette through this 100 yen coin.
There's a hole in it!
There's already a hole in it!
Everything's Ace of hearts!
Just now...
Didn't something fly... from her mouth?
You...
What kind of trick were you planning?
Yuuko!
Yuuko...
For now...
...you should just sleep.
"My Ordinary Life 54"
I'm heading over to the supermarket now.
Okay! I'm coming, too!
You were bad, so I'm not getting you anything.
That's too bad. Poor Sakamoto.
She's talking to you.
All right. Shall we go?
What are you buying, Nano?
Hmm. Maybe fish again, I think.
I wonder what I should buy...
Eh? I said nothing for you today.
Then I won't get a snack.
Anything other than snacks, either.
But now I don't know what else I can buy.
You're really set on getting something.
"Shark Castella"
Nano! It's a shark castella!
It's a food stall!
It looks yummy, so let's get some.
Did you forget already?
I said nothing for you today.
But Sakamoto wants one for a snack...
Sakamoto was bad, too, so he gets nothing.
But I was really going to give it to you...
I messed up.
No means no.
If I spoil her here, she'll just do it again.
Come on, Hakase. We're leaving.
Buy it! Buy it! Buy it! Buy it!
--I need to stand firm!
--Buy it! Buy it! Buy it! Buy it!
Buy it--
But I don't know...
Buy it! Buy it! Buy it! Buy it!
I can't give in!
--Should I?
--Buy it! Buy it! Buy it! Buy it!
--No, no, I can't!
--What if just a little?
--Buy it! Buy it! Buy it! Buy it!
--No! No!
--But maybe...
--Buy it! Buy it! Buy it! Buy it!
--No, no!
--Buy it! Buy it! Buy...
--But...
Tasty!
What? So you bought it in the end?
Sorry... I lost.
This brat always throws a tantrum
and gets what she wants.
I need to give her a talk.
Hey, Brat.
Have you ever once practiced self-control?
I have!
No, you haven't!
It's another peaceful day
at the Shinonome household.
"80 Point Mongolian"
That's amazing! Eighty points!
I knew you could do it!
Yeah!
So what is it? What's your
secret to get a good score?
No way, man! You really think I've got a secret?
Oh, just spill it. Come on and tell me your secret.
--Eighty points, yeah! Eighty points!
--Ow! Stop! That hurts!
Quit it!
"Secret"
"Secret" Ouch...
Should I tell you the secret to get 80 points?
No, it's fine. I got 96 points anyway.
Eighty points.
It's all about having endless discipline and...
...having heart.
Shut up.
"A Trivial Miracle"
Aioi.
Uugh...
Eh...?
Eeh...?
Woo-hoo!
"Reality"
Dad? I came over to make you some dinner!
Mom's still on her vacation, right?
Oh? That helps.
Hello!
Hello there, Mii.
Good. I'll play with my grandson all day today,
and forget about the cruel reality.
Mii. What do you want to play today?
Hey, hey. Where's your official seal?
Hey, hey. Where is it? Where are you hiding it?
Hey, hey. Tell me!
Is it in this book shelf?
Hey, hey. Where's your seal?
--This...
--Where is it? Where? Where?
--...is even worse than reality.
--Bring out the seal!
Helvetica Standard.
You're late!
Did you forget when we were meeting?!
Sorry, sorry!
I thought I boarded the right
bus...
But instead I rode the waves of life.
Let's take this all the way to Okachimachi.
"My Ordinary Life 55"
Nano...
Hey, Nano. Nano...
What is it, Hakase?
I think I kinda gotta go potty...
Will you come with me?
Hey, let's go.
Hey. Hey, let's go.
Hey, Nano! Hey...
Hey...
Hakase, you're wrong.
About what?
Borscht is a food, silly.
What? That's not it...
Let's go potty.
Hey, Nano. Nano! Hey...
Just go!
Wait. Don't tell me...
It's okay. I only have to a little.
For now, just hurry up and go to the toilet.
Okay.
Sleep.
Just go!
Sakamoto is considerate
and doesn't speak aloud.
Sheesh. Can you believe this?
Brats these days...
She's not going anywhere in
the dark during a storm like this.
She's a brat.
But maybe...
I could go with her this one time and
make her finally appreciate me for once.
Hey, Brat.
She's not budging so I'll take you there.
Sakamoto is small and weak-looking,
so there's no point.
Don't you think she wants to go to school?
Huh?
Hakase? You got in bed with me?
Nano... Let's go potty together.
Well, I don't really have to go, but...
It's a little scary, so let's go together.
Oh...
Geez. You should have woken me then.
I tried to a lot!
The walls keep banging.
Is somebody at the door?
I think it's the chimney making a racket.
Can you believe all this rain?
Nano? What's wrong?
Hey, Nano?
Hey, hey!
Hakase! Hakase!
It's lightning!
I'm here, so there's nothing to worry about.
Hurry up so we can get back under the covers.
Okay.
It's kinda scary going alone...
But together it's not so scary.
You're right.
Nano...
Do you want to go to school?
Huh?
No... I'll stay here at home.
But Sakamoto said you wanted to go to school!
Hmm...
I suppose so...
Things that are cool!
Eighty points!
Shut up.
"Word-Time"
One month goes by fast,
but Sunday seems so far away.
"Pumped"
Next stop is 80 points.
Eighty points. The doors on the right will open.
Shut up.
Want me to sing a song from the '80s?
One of the top 80's?
Shut up.
Eighty points! Hurrah!
Eighty points! Hurrah! Eighty points! Hurrah!
Eighty points!
Go back to Eden!
"Eden"
Hey! Quiet down there.
I'm announcing the average score.
This time it's 92.
Yuuko...
Don't!
Please...
...don't...
"Great Luck"
Hey! What the heck was that for, Brat?!
Ah! What in the world are you doing?
Will you please stop playing around
and help me with laundry?
You can go to school starting tomorrow.
Eh?
Is this for real?!
Yup.
Wh-Why?!
Why the change of heart?
I'm generous to a fault.
Woo-hoo!
Now I can eat all the snacks I want
for lunch and not get yelled at.
But, Hakase...
I can't wear a backpack with this.
It's high school.
But, Hakase, if you don't take off the key, I can't--
It's Nano's school uniform.
Hakase, I love you!
Nano, Nano, Nano, Nano, Nano, Nano!
Hakase, Hakase, Hakase, Hakase, Hakase, Hakase!
Hakase, Hakase, Hakase, Hakase, Hakase!
Nano!
Hakase!
Nano, Nano!
Hakase, Hakase!
Nano!
Hakase!
Wake in the morning, teeth get a brushing
Before you know it, it's ten at night
Another day was full of laughter
Another day filled with joy
Goofing with friends and acting so silly
Making a ruckus and then I see
A glimpse from you and then our eyes meet
Coincidence, or not?
I won't ever admit it's first love
That's not something I would say
Hey, I'll see you again tomorrow too.
When I close my eyes I see
My vision sparkling, filled with you
Wasn't it so much fun today?
Ah, I think I'm in love
I'm so happy I'm so happy
Nice to meet you, awakening love
I'll see you again tomorrow too
Good night
I'll see you again soon in my dreams
I'm the national flag!
I'm sometimes called a flag or banner,
but both of them are correct.
"Don't worry about the little things"
were my dad's last words...
"Narration: Megumi Ogata"
The next My Ordinary Life is Episode 14.
Look forward to it!