Okay! Class is over for today.
The days are shorter now, so make sure
to head home before it gets too dark.
--Let's go out and play, man!
--What you wanna do?
Well, people often say plasma is the answer.
Nano!
Yes?!
Let's walk home together!
Want to drop by the station for a bite?
Huh?
What do you say?
U-Uh, um...
Hey, Mio. You'll come, too, ri--
Huh? She already went home?
So, Nano...
Huh?
I left without saying a word...
That was a mean thing to do to Aioi.
If only I had introduced myself like a normal girl.
"Nano Shinonome"
M-M-My name is Nano Shinonome!
"Nano Shinonome" U-Um!
"Nano Shinonome"
You see, um, about this key on my back...
Greatest friendship
Super duper harmony
(na na na na na na na)
Hey! I'll say it
You are my best best friend
(bright) Every time I poke fun and tease you
(shine) You come and tease me back some more
(lan lan lan) There ain't
no better feeling in the world
(why) Even when bad things sometimes happen
(fine) I forget all of them around you
(lan lan lan) We'll forever let the good times roll
It's not a problem being with you
every hour of the day
As if we're twins, child-parent,
or a pair of cloned cells
Doesn't a friendship this good
make love not so needed anymore?
Wait hold on this and that
are totally totally different things
(fight) Even after we've had a fight
(down) Or when I feel down in the dumps
(shock) All the times I wanted to be alone
Before I know it there sitting beside me
my wonderful friend till the end
Why is it, I wanna be at your side?
Whenever we're together,
time flies 100 times faster
It's so fun with you,
I think it's almost too much fun
It's cuz you're such a good friend! Hey!
(na na na na na na na)
What's going on? Uh-oh we're synchronizing man!
It's always a wild time,
we make the people 'round us crazy
What time is it now? I think it's yodelayheehoo
What's that even mean?
SO-RE-DO-SHI-RA-
Unbelievably, how to put it, awesome!
No matter what happens
we are gonna be friends! Woohoo!
Greatest friendship
Super duper harmony
cha chara chara cha cha-n
The local coffee shop was remodeled,
so I went to check it out.
Um...
May I take your order?
One espresso... T please.
"My Ordinary Life 64"
U-Um...
You would like a tall espresso, then?
T-Tall?!
Tall?!
T means tall?!
Well, I was thinking of getting a T espresso...
But, yeah...
Espresso T in small, please.
Uh...
You want to order a short espresso?
Um... I'll take a small short!
That'll be fine!
O-Okay.
So an espresso then...
Um...
It comes in either hot or cold.
Hot, please!
Ah, um...
Hot it is, then.
As for the size...
We have solo and doppio.
D-D-D-D-D-Doppio?!
Doppio?! Doppio?! Why is it called a doppio?!
Doppio?! Doppio?! What in the world is "doppio"?!
"Today's Special"
O-Oh yeah. That's right, I forgot...
I think I'm just going to have today's special.
Um...
Today's special is our espresso...
Fine... I'll take it.
Okay, then...
Solo or...
...doppio for your order?
...doppio... doppio...
Th--
That's right...
Th-Then...
Please just make it however you like.
All right.
Thanks for waiting. Here's your espresso.
It's so tiny!
So bitter!
Thank you for coming!
Well, you know what?
I think I'll just stick to the vending machine.
For my grandson Mii's birthday present,
"Catch"
I bought him a baseball glove.
Gramps! I'm gonna throw it!
Whoa there, Mii. It won't reach
if you throw from that far away.
Grandkids are so cute when
they get so excited like this.
Here it comes!
Oh well.
Throw it as hard as you can!
Good. Today I'll show him
how cool a grandpa I can--
Sinker...
"Agonizing Hot Chicken Bar" "Tico Mart"
U-Um...
Yes?
I'll take one Agonizing Super Hot
Chef's Fanciful Chicken Bar please.
Excuse me? People actually buy those?
"Tico Mart"
What's wrong, Kojiro?
Oh yeah.
If I don't hurry, the post office is gonna clo--
Mio!
Y-Yuuko? What's up?
Do you have to ask?
You went missing as soon as homeroom was over.
Oh. Yeah, that.
It's not too late!
--Naw, I have something to do...
--Let's go home together!
Eh? What, what?
Ah, well, it's hard to explain.
Huh? What, are you too cool to tell me?
No, it's like... you know.
Come on, come on!
Could I interrupt?
"My Ordinary Life 65"
S...
Sorry!
Hey, Yuuko! What are you doing?!
I apologized on reflex.
You surprised me, too.
I wasn't expecting an apology.
Sorry...
Is there something we can help you with?
Actually, some people have been using
fake bills in vending machines.
I was wondering if you've seen
anyone suspicious or anything.
Have you at all, Mio?
I don't really come through this area much.
An eyewitness reported seeing a person
with a beige, red striped tote bag...
It can't be, right?
What?! Why is she reacting so bizarre?!
Does she have some?! Does she have fake bills?!
No, no... There's no way that's possible.
Quit joking around, Mio--
Eh?!
Why is she putting her hands out for handcuffs?!
Hey now. Do you really have fake bills?
Don't be ridiculous...
She's just being prepared in case
a volleyball comes flying in.
Right, Mio?
Whatever...
Just to be sure, I'd like to see
inside both of your bags.
Sure, no problem!
You, too, Mio--
She dished it out! She dished out a fake bill!
It's over!
I can't believe she really had one!
Please, let me go with this.
Please, let me go with this!
That's one fake bill. Where are the rest?
It's not a fake bill! It's a real bribe!
What are you talking about?!
Show me the bag!
Why are you fighting?!
It's a relative's!
This bag is a relative's!
"You fool." "Senpai." You fool.
One, two!
Three, four!
Five!
Six?!
Passion...
Kyuu...
Fever?
Fool... fool... fool... fool...
What? What's this?!
An accident?!
Oh, Kojiro. There you are.
You walk like you were just born.
Mio!
Aren't you going to eat?
It's going to get cold!
Hey, Mio!
Answer me!
The Life of Kojiro!
What are you eat--
Okay! Class is over for today.
As for the mid-term exam, I wrote what material
it covers on the wall, so make sure to take a look.
Goodbye!
Nano always books it out of here as fast as possible.
Yeah...
Goodbye!
Goodbye.
"Word-Time" Goodbye.
When I don't know something,
--I just pretend that I do.
--Goodbye!
--Goodbye.
♪ Cha-cha-la-la! Cha!
Cha-cha-la-la! Cha! ♪
♪ Cha-cha-cha-cha. Cha-la-la! ♪
Ah...
Yuuko. Can I borrow your eraser?
Aye, aye.
Which hand?
Uh...
Mai, lend me your eraser.
--Wow!
--All right.
Here.
Character eraser?
"My Ordinary Life 66"
Eh? This won't erase anything,
it'll just smear it around.
Yuuko. Lend me your eraser.
Mai doesn't have one either?
You guys are hopeless.
Here. Which hand?
This one.
Whoa! No, no, no, no, no!
The rules say one at a time, so that doesn't count.
Who decided that rule?
Let's start with Mai.
Go on, go on. Look as much as you like.
Hot! Hot! Hot!
No, no! Offensive attacks aren't allowed!
That's one strike for Mai.
What's one strike?
One penalty.
What happens when you get one penalty?
You've gotta treat me to 23 juices!
You're still hung up on that?
Ah!
Here, Yuuko. Baby Star.
Kan-ji-zai-bo-sa-gyo-jin-han-
nya-ha-ra-mi-ta-ji-sho-kei-go...
Whoa! Scary! That was too close for comfort!
It's not sho-kei-go, but sho-ken-go.
I was hoping that worked.
That's two strikes for you.
Rock-paper-scissors!
Silly! I'm not going to play with the real hand.
This one.
Shoot! I fell for the trap!
Hand it over, Yuuko. Eraser.
Fine, fine, fine, fine...
Here. You win.
Character eraser surfboard lock!
Thank you for coming!
Character erasers are useless.
So true.
It's Nano!
It really is!
I'm pretty sure Nano is a robot.
Would you cut that out?
Nano doesn't like it.
What? Why doesn't she like it?!
Robots are sweet!
Eh?
"Love-Like"
Hey...
Wanna just run for it?
"The Truth After 15 Years"
Dad...
Hey, Dad!
You really want me to wear this
around town? It's embarrassing!
Embarrassing?
Is that it?!
You spineless, mugwort dumpling!
"Max Height 4.0 M"
"My Ordinary Life 67"
"My Ordinary Life 67" Um...
Shinonome. Shinonome...
Ah! Here it is!
"Shinonome Lab" "Shinonome Lab"?
Wow! It's a laboratory!
That's so cool!
Excuse me?!
Is anyone home?!
Huh? Is everyone gone?
Yes! Be right there!
Sorry to keep--
Eh?!
Wh-Wh-What should I do?!
What is Aioi doing at our house?!
--If she meets Hakase, --Hello!
--she'll find out that I'm a robot for sure!
--Hello!
--Hi there!
--she'll find out that I'm a robot for sure!
--What happened to Nano?
--What should I do?!
--Nano's right over there.
--Ah, wait.
--Are you one of Nano's friends?!
--What if she just came to give me
--Yeah, I am.
--a printout from school?
--Yay! Come inside!
--Is that why she came to my door?
--Excuse me.
Come in, come in!
--Don't mind if I do...
--You fool!
Ohhh!
It's too late now since she's already inside.
I'll find out what she wants
before Hakase opens her big mouth.
Ugh.
I'm starv--
What? Who said that?
Our cat Sakamoto can talk.
Hakase!
Really?!
O-Of course that's not true!
S-Sakamoto! Say "meow"
for me, please! Say "meow!"
Huh? Why do I have to--
Say "meow," Sakamoto!
M-Meow...
See?! He's just a typical cat.
O-Okay.
Sakamoto, we have a guest today,
so you'll have to play outside, okay?
What'd you say?
Scary!
Meow...
I never introduced myself yet.
I'm Yuuko Aioi.
Are you Nano's little sister?
No, I'm Hakase.
I built Nano.
Built her?!
Awesome! You're tiny, but so awesome!
I'm Hakase after all.
Y-Y-You've got it wrong, Aioi!
This girl is a relative with two working parents!
They don't come home until late,
so I watch her until then!
Right? Isn't that right? Right?
What are you saying?
Y-You fool!
Eh?!
Sorry. I'll go prepare some more tea.
Ah. Wait a second, Nano.
Push here for tea.
Ah! Eh?!
Gah!
There you go!
Sweet! Sweet!
And this one's a gun!
Cool! That's so cool!
It's over...
And now for the cool word showdown!
Yay!
Starting with the unworthy Yuuko!
Hey... Tell me you're joking!
Wake up! I said wake up!
Oh! So cool!
Next up, Hakase!
Okay!
Rhinoceros Beetle!
Cool!
I wonder what Aioi actually came here for?
It's riding on top!
I give up! I give up!
You're so small!
It's so big!
Okay. I'm going home.
She came for nothing?!
Thanks for having me over.
I hope I didn't stay too long.
No.
U-Um, Aioi?
Yeah?
I was actually just practicing some magic tricks!
I'm not really a robot or anything--
Yeah, I got it.
You're not a robot, I know.
There we go.
Nano is just Nano.
That's all that matters.
That's what I came to tell you today.
I almost forgot.
See you tomorrow!
Y-Yeah.
Aioi!
Um...
If you want to come again...
Yeah! I'll come for sure!
Really?! Yay!
How about we draw next?
Yeah! We can draw sharks!
Sharks are so cool!
They're cool! I love sharks!
You like sharks, Hakase?
--I love sharks! They're the coolest!
--That's neat! Sharks!
Me shark!
Do more! Do more!
Shark attack!
Again! Again!
I'm hungry shark!
--Do the shark, Yuuko!
--Hakase! Me, too!
Me shark!
So cool!
Let's all sing together, everyone's hearts as one
In both sad times and bitter times
Let's all sing together, with great, loud voices
Without feeling embarrassed, let's sing
A song that will inspire your heart
A song that will definitely reach you
Sparkle across the world, my song
Sparkle across the world, my message of love
Ah!
It's Sakamoto!
See you later!
See ya.
Well, whatever...
I like to think I'm a plus screw.
It gives me a positive vibe.
It's best to look on the plus side in life.
The next My Ordinary Life is Episode 17.
"Narration: TARAKO"
Look forward to it!