"My Ordinary Life 72"
It's true! Daiku Coffee got a huge remodel.
Really?
Here it is.
You're right. It's more like a café now.
Welcome!
I've already been here once,
so you can go ahead and order first.
What, really? Then...
White chocolate mocha prappuccino grande.
Eh?!
Oh, but I also want caramel sauce and hazelnut syrup
with chocolate chip extra whip
and one espresso shot.
Just die!
Hey! Where are you going, Yuuko?!
Greatest friendship
Super duper harmony
(na na na na na na na)
Hey! I'll say it
You are my best best friend
(bright) Every time I poke fun and tease you
(shine) You come and tease me back some more
(lan lan lan) There ain't
no better feeling in the world
(why) Even when bad things sometimes happen
(fine) I forget all of them around you
(lan lan lan) We'll forever let the good times roll
It's not a problem being with you
every hour of the day
As if we're twins, child-parent,
or a pair of cloned cells
Doesn't a friendship this good
make love not so needed anymore?
Wait hold on this and that
are totally totally different things
(fight) Even after we've had a fight
(down) Or when I feel down in the dumps
(shock) All the times I wanted to be alone
Before I know it there sitting beside me
my wonderful friend till the end
Why is it, I wanna be at your side?
Whenever we're together,
time flies 100 times faster
It's so fun with you,
I think it's almost too much fun
It's cuz you're such a good friend! Hey!
(na na na na na na na)
What's going on? Uh-oh we're synchronizing man!
It's always a wild time,
we make the people 'round us crazy
What time is it now? I think it's yodelayheehoo
What's that even mean?
SO-RE-DO-SHI-RA-
Unbelievably, how to put it, awesome!
No matter what happens
we are gonna be friends! Woohoo!
Greatest friendship
Super duper harmony
cha chara chara cha cha-n
"Ms. Nakamura"
The sleeping pill was
ineffective on Nano Shinonome.
But I have the answer.
Now with double the oxidizing strength
and built in anesthetic, it's Mr. Oxidation Plus!
I'll get Nano Shinonome to drink this
and capture her once and for all.
When she's mine, where should I start?
I'll could do this and that to her...
"Science Room ♪2"
"Earth's Magnetic Field"
"Geomagnetic Reversal"
Mustard?
--Custard?
--Wh-What should I do?!
--That's not it.
--Mustard?
--Wh-What should I do?!
--I said no!
Hmm. I guess we're using compasses today.
Did you get your compass, Nano?
Y-Yes!
Everybody!
I'm told class is self-study now.
Oh! Woo-hoo!
I wonder if Ms. Nakamura collapsed again?
She sure falls over a lot, that Ms. Nakamura.
"My Ordinary life 73"
Sasahara! You're supposed to be cleaning the room!
I did clean my assigned area though.
You left behind a huge pile of dust!
Did I now?
Go back and finish cleaning up!
Actually, how did you know
I was up here on the roof?
Are you stupid?!
I just happened to come up here
to enjoy the nice weather, okay?
I see.
Sorry to trouble you.
I'm glad you checked my area for me.
Don't take it the wrong way!
I wasn't doing it for you, all right?!
Wow.
"Crane Game"
"Tokisadame"
"My Ordinary Life 74"
My day off.
I'm meeting with Mai in the neighboring city.
She said there would be free candy,
so I couldn't resist.
Do you want some bread?
No, I'm fine. I ate just before I left.
Aren't dogs like...
...against the rules?
Oof.
I'm quite all right.
Oh! We're almost to my stop,
so I better stand up and get ready!
--In just a moment, Tokisadametonyamachi.
--Nice timing, announcer!
Tokisadametonyamachi. Tokisadametonyamachi.
--Good. Let's get out of here.
--Doors will open on the right.
"Tokisadametonyamachi"
Goodbye, my friends of the train.
"step step step"
It's okay. It's okay. This is where I say goodbye.
Stay cool! Stay cool! I can't lose my composure now!
S-Sorry! I was in a bit of a hurry, and--
Argh! Sheesh!
It's okay! I'll never come back here again!
It's one city over.
There's nobody that knows me here.
Don't worry! Don't worry!
Is it just me...
...or am I being followed?
"click-clack click-clack click-clack"
It's gotta be my imagination!
I'm just being overly nervous today.
Wasn't the Daiku Burger supposed
to be right outside the station?
Where is it?
According to the map Mai gave me...
"Daiku Burger" "Here"
This map is so whacked...
I should just ask someone.
"Daiku Burger" "Here" All right!
Um, excuse me? Do you know where Daiku Burger--
H-Hey! Why are you following me?!
You can't do that! It's, like, against copyright law!
Daiku Burger is right around the corner.
I'm meeting someone there, too,
so I'll show you the way.
Welcome!
Sorry, Sis. Club ran long today.
You're late!
So she wasn't lying after all.
Thank you for waiting.
I guess Mai hasn't got here yet.
Sheesh.
What an unlucky day.
I've never been so embarrassed in my life.
Oh well. It's one city over.
Yeah. If I think about it, this is like
a rehearsal for real life.
That's right!
If I was able to conquer this embarrassment,
there isn't anything I can't conquer!
Yuuko.
Sorry for the wait.
Mai!
Is that... what I think it is?
Trick or treat.
At this rate, I have no choice.
If it's for candy, I'll go!
Trick or treat.
Halloween was last week...
The Life of Crow!
"If you have to pass by a menacing crow
for whatever reason..."
"...make sure to maintain eye contact at all times."
"Shinonome Lab"
"Sleep" "Shinonome Lab"
I'm not tired enough to sleep.
They say to count sheep jumping over fences.
It'll help you fall asleep.
Okay. I'll try it.
One sheep jumps over...
She fell asleep at one!
Hakase, wow!
I'll try, too!
One sheep--
That sheep...
It never made it over...
"Volunteer Spirit"
I'm all done.
Thanks. You're good at this, Sis.
Yup.
Hey. Does Sasahara teach you how
to do things like this?
Wh-Why do you think I go to him
to teach me everything?!
Because you get along.
Not at all, no! Not at all!
When I say not at all, I mean not at all!
Calm down, Sis.
But didn't you iron his handkerchief the other day?
Th-That was just some garbage
I picked up on the road.
Eh? But you did it because it was Sasahara's.
I-I'm telling you that's not how it is.
I just wanted to work out my arm
and I saw the iron sitting there,
but the handkerchief just happened to be under it.
Like that...
It happened like that, okay?
Ugh. So easy to read...
But, Sis, when you were ironing,
you looked so happy about it.
D-Don't be ridiculous!
Th-That's because...
That's because the Earth must
have entered the Photon Belt!
Get this, yesterday...
What, what?
I went and talked to Oono!
Really? That's awesome!
Two hours by train.
One hour by bus.
I left the hustle of the city behind.
And came... to the remote countryside of S Town.
All these years, I never thought
I'd be able to find it in my life.
But unable to give up looking,
I continued to search for that one book.
It changed my gray, sullen childhood days.
That fantasy which brought color into my heart...
In this library...
It's in here.
At this age, I can read it once more.
I thank the one who was
kind enough to donate this book.
I finally take it in hand.
"Colors of Autumn"
While suppressing my racing heart...
I...
...slowly pull back the cover.
"Love-Like"
"Name" "Hiroshi Honda"
Okay! Time's almost up,
so make sure you've written your name!
Ten, nine,
eight, sev--
...ven...
Six...
Five...
Four...
Three...
Two...
One...
Zero!
Okay! Pass your papers up from the back!
"My Ordinary Life 75"
Halloween is over already...
This coffee isn't very coffee-coffee.
Not very "coffee-coffee"?
What's that?
I can't really explain it myself,
but it doesn't taste very coffee-coffee!
Here, you try it. Come on.
Sheesh. What's "coffee-coffee" anyways?
It's not coffee-coffee at all...
Hop!
Wah!
"My Ordinary Life 76"
Everyone! I finally completed my project!
I present, Biscuit Number Two!
I'm Biscuit ♪2.
Ah... The one from before.
Such a weak reaction.
Hey! I want you to look at him!
But I saw the one already.
One and Two are totally different!
This one's way, way cooler!
Right...
My name is Biscuit Number Two.
I'm a biscuit robot
made by Hakase Shinonome.
As my name implies,
I need biscuits to operate.
Biscuits are like my fuel.
Hakase! I need a biscuit at once!
Eh? But this is the last one I've got...
Eh?
Biscuit Number Two's specialty is speed reading!
Go ahead.
I'm finished.
Done.
Why aren't you surprised?
Well, I can read pretty fast, too.
Then how come you always read so slow?!
Because that way seems... a lot more
like what a normal person would do.
Yawn...
What's wrong, Biscuit Number Two?
All the tiny letters in this book
are making me sleepy.
That's so normal of you.
Why aren't you calling me amazing?!
Can't you see how amazing I am?!
Oh my. I didn't know that made you angry.
I'm not angry...
Hakase, you've been amazing from the start.
Oh yeah. I guess I was wrong, then.
I don't know if you'd consider that wrong, but...
Hey, hey! How awesome am I then?
Um... As awesome as the Chichibu Mountains.
Uh, I don't know what that means.
Then-- Hmm. You're as great as the Nullarbor Plains.
What? I wanna be bigger than that!
How about a whale?
Oh, maybe that!
Whales are so big, right?
They're so big!
"Word-Time"
Never say something is good enough.
Never say this is good enough.
That's good enough.
"Konsuke"
What are you gonna do?
I'm thinking backgammon.
What about you?
I'm doing a quiz.
Everyone loves a nice, peaceful quiz.
Getting a chunk of money for amusing
the princess sure is a fun little game.
I couldn't take it if we never
got to do things like this.
I'm with you there.
You saw me place the ball in the cup, however...
Actually, it's in this one right here.
Well done, 66!
I never knew you had so much talent!
To be honest, I wanted to be
the royal magician someday.
You've got it in the bag, man!
Hope so!
Oh! I'm getting pumped up!
I'll take that chunk of change!
Hey! It's time.
"My Ordinary Life 77"
Silence!
"Otsuki"
Now, we will progress in the order you drew.
Whoever drew one, step forward.
That would be me.
Ooh! Number 66 right off the bat.
He'll win the cash for sure.
Royal magician, eh?
Make your dreams come true, 66.
--Amazing!
--He's so fast!
Now, which cup do you think the ball is under?
I just wanted to be the royal--
Next.
Whoever drew two, step forward.
The time has come...
Soon, the whole world shall know my name.
I'll turn this plight into a plus.
Hey. Who's that?
It's Funny Four.
With his humor, he'll be able to do it.
Four here. Allow me to entertain you.
Next.
--I can't believe even Four was done in...
--Who drew three? Step forward!
Hey, you all right?
I-It's me...
A-Aren't you doing a quiz?
It's over...
Do I have any choice? Doing quizzes
is the only talent that I've got...
I've gotta make sure the princess
gets it right no matter what!
Relax. I just can't let her fail...
As long as I give her a nice, simple one.
S-Six here.
I'd like to give you a quiz!
E-Even though it's not a cake,
what kind of food do you make in a pan?
U-Uh, it's multiple choice!
One is frying pan, two is pancake!
So, which is it?!
H-He said it!
Ah!
I don't know.
Y-You are correct!
My whole life, I regret nothing...
Except this!
It's over...
Even the quiz master is done for...
Next.
S-Seven!
I'll recite everywhere the Olympics
have taken place! First is--
We will always remember your courage, Seven...
What's wrong?
Is there no one here
who can entertain the princess?
Wh-What to do...
And here I thought I had
a chance being a cheerleader...
What about me?! I was going to
split chopsticks with my butt!
I was going to put on a show!
I thought I could shred some cabbage!
All of us... are doomed.
Hey now.
Did you forget I was here?
You're...
His harlequin antics make him
the best clown in town.
There's no harlequin funnier than him.
Harlequeen Thirteen!
I'll lift up this dreadful atmosphere
and give everyone a show to remember.
Wait, Thirteen!
Don't do it! It's too dangerous!
Tsk, tsk, tsk.
Did you think I was going to dance
Swan Lake or something?
Just wait and see.
I'll show you what a real harlequin--
...can do!
Harlequeen Thirteen!
Huh?!
Why me, too?!
"Otsuki" Next, number five.
Don't make us wait forever! Hurry!
Who is it?
Number five!
Who's that?!
Isn't it you?
No! That's just my hat number!
Who is it?
No!
H-Hey.
Aren't you number 5?
He's screwed...
Come on, five! Hurry and get up over here!
What's your problem?!
Eh?!
I knew it!
Next.
I don't care who. Just do it.
What can we even do?
This is...
...it's useless!
At this rate, I could have a thousand lives
and it wouldn't be enough.
I've had enough of this stupid game.
I'm not doing it anymore!
I'll go stand in the hall!
One day, my papa and I had a talk
About the joy of living
And all about sadness
Green green
Little birds want to sing in the blue sky
Atop the hill la la the green is growing
Then my papa said, pulling me into his arms
When you're sad and times are tough
La la la you shouldn't cry
Green green
A soft breeze blows in the blue sky
Atop the hill la la the green is swaying
The green is spreading
For when you want sweet, I'm a caramel sauce
hazelnut syrup chocolate chip extra whip,
with one extra espresso shot white
chocolate mocha prappuccino grande.
The next My Ordinary Life is Episode 19.
"Narration: Rikako Aikawa"
Look forward to it!