All right!
Is everyone ready?
Rock! Paper! Scissors!
"Glico" Aww!
"Glico" Good! I get to start.
Pi-n-e-ap-pl-e.
Rock! Paper! Scissors!
Sweet!
Here I come!
Wait a second!
Only one step at a time!
I know already!
G-li-co...
...'s toy-pr-ize!
You!
Hmm? What?
You can't just add whatever you want!
Huh? But Glico always throws in a prize.
Right? Mai?
Fifty-fifty.
Fine. I'll let it slide.
But if you're doing that,
I'm adding in my own rules, too.
Rock-paper-scissors!
Okay! Mai gets to go next!
Chi-yo-ta...
Ni-ke-ra-ha-to-ho-ra-su-te-no-ha-te...
...ki-ra-to-na-ri-ha-shi-te-to...
The Incantation of Resurrection.
I realized just this very moment
I think I might have fallen in love
24 hours a day of you you you
I can't get you out of my head!
Something (something) feels different now
With you (together) it's awkward conversation
Is it (mutual love) no it's one-sided love
Uh-oh I think our eyes just met!
What is this anxious nervous feeling?
My train of thought is tangled with confusion...
This kind of thing is a first for me
Could it be a fever and I'm sick?
With a sudden twist it's awakened love
There's a fire in my cheeks and my face is all red
Th-Th-This can't be real, my hands are trembling
Is this what people mean when they talk about "love"?
I-I-I'm stuttering non-stop talking to you
Awkward silence and then mumble-mumble-mo
I wanna (I wanna) know how you feel about me
O-O-O-One one-sided love
First love! Every day on the path to school
Sparkle-sparkle dazzling I DO fall in love!
It's like I'm flying through the sky
O-O-O-One one-sided love
It's not moving...
Jeez, mom!
I told you to wake me up at 7!
Mom!
"Mio. Went with the neighborhood association
to play sepak takraw. Mom."
Sepak...
"My Ordinary Life 5"
Sepak takraw...
Just great!
Of all days to be on morning duty!
You had one job, alarm clock!
Why'd you have to run out of batteries today?!
If you're going to conk out,
warn me about it beforehand!
You cretin!
Anyways, if I run my fastest lap time ever...
...I think I can make it.
But, wait. Just now...
I saw something crazy!
Is it just me, or...
It's coming!
Wh-What? What?! Who is this sprinter?!
Why... are they... chasing me?!
They passed me!
This is it.
Um, excuse me?
Did you drop this wooden fish?
Was it a gold wooden fish?
I'm done for...
I have to...
I'm so sorry!
Sometimes I'm a bear...
And other times, I'm...
Be-ar...
But! My true identity is...
S-Sorry!
Yoink!
Surprise!
The correct answer is, your sister!
You didn't know it was me
because I borrowed your uniform!
Ah! That was fun--
What a commendable corkscrew this morning.
Wow! It truly was marvelous!
I went through all sorts of trouble for this!
I even stopped your alarm clock!
So you're the culprit!
Whoa, whoa. Don't be so angry.
Here! I'll treat you to some ramen with this!
But that's my moola!
Chi-yo-ta...
"Incantation" Chi-yo-ta...
Ni-ke-ra-ha-to-ho-ra-su-te-no-ha-te...
...ki-ra-to-na-ri-ha-shi-te-to...
"Please enter the Incantation of Resurrection."
"Incantation is incorrect."
"My Ordinary Life 6"
Shark...
Shark!
I'm home!
Hmm? What are you doing, Hakase?
Nano! That cloud looks sharky!
Really? Which one?
Ah! You're right.
So cool...
Yeah it is.
Oh, I know!
Look what I bought, Hakase!
Milk...
Is it 4.5%? 4.5%?!
--Yes, it's extra thick.
--Is it milk? 4.5%? Milk? 4.5%?
--But why do you suddenly want to drink milk?
Eheh...
That's because...
I've got a roll cake.
Eh?
Hey! Why did you add that feature?!
Because it's a roll cake.
That doesn't make sense!
Nano! 4.5% milk!
This isn't about the milk!
Why do I have to walk around
with a roll cake in my arm?!
So cold and yummy!
That's not the issue here!
Sheesh! What if someone
from outside saw this?
Rolly-rolly-roll! Rolly-rolly-roll!
Hakase...
What?
Um, could I please have some, too?
All right.
Wait just a second.
Here you go.
Thank you.
Um...
Some roll cake as well?
Huh?
I know! You can have a sweet bun!
Eh?!
Help yourself!
It went back in!
Sorry! I pushed it by accident.
Wh-Why did you do this to me?!
Do you know what would happen if
that popped out when I was outside?!
What would happen?
Probably...
Command Sambomaster was awesome!
Yeah it was!
I'll add a feature to let you play music!
That's not what I meant!
Why is adding more features
your answer to everything?!
Please at least listen to me...
One big gulp!
Geez...
What is it?
Sweet bun...
Not for you! You already
had yourself a roll cake!
Eh?!
Huh? Hakase?
That's fine! I can still eat my layer cake!
Huh? Huh?!
N-Not again! Where will it
come from?! Above? Below?!
Ah...
Uh...
Ah! Shock!
Why can't you just put all the food
in the fridge from the start?!
No!
Eh?!
"Shinonome Lab"
"Shinonome Lab" Eh...?
First comes rock, then your hand delivers...
What's it gonna be, no cheats!
Rock-paper-scissors!
Ugh...
I'm so tired...
Mio!
What? What's with that smile?
Lend me your notebook!
Did you really forget to do
your homework again?
And I am extremely ashamed of it...
Geez. You'll be in trouble again
when the test comes around.
I know, I know! It'll just be this once!
This will be the last time. Please! Okay?
Yuuko. That's what you said
the last time around.
A samurai never goes back on their word!
I'm telling you that you already did.
Eh? R-Really?
Sheesh. Fine...
"Go+Soccer club!!"
This is the last time. For real, okay?
I got it!
Mio, you're such a savior!
Yuuko! That thing you said came up!
I'll bring it back as soon as I'm done.
'Kay.
Really? Show me, show me!
Hmm? I feel like I'm forgetting something.
Last night, after finishing my homework...
After finishing my homework...
I won't...
I randomly drew...
...let you...
The picture I randomly drew!
--I forgot to erase it!
--I won't let you do this.
I totally forgot!
"My Ordinary Life 7"
Uh! Um...
Yeah, yeah!
You see!
Yuuko!
Sorry, sorry! I forgot to do my homework, too!
What a shame! What a shame!
So gimme back my notebook, okay?
Sorry!
What?
I told you, there's no point in looking at it.
You stinker...
You think I'd fall for that?
I promise I'll get the next one for you.
See ya!
Sorry to keep you waiting!
This is bad...
This is real bad...
If anyone sees it,
they'll never look at me the same!
And it had to be Yuuko to see it, of all people!
Her speed at spreading rumors...
...breaks the sound barrier!
Yuuko!
Th-That's my language notebook.
This one's for math.
Huh? But look...
Math is written right here.
"Math"
"Daily Diary"
E-Eh? I-It's...
It's wrong!
I-It hurts! My stomach hurts!
Uh, okay.
Gah!
I'll be done in a jiffy.
Just wait a sec.
It's over...
If she sees it now...
My high school life... is over.
Yuuko!
That notebook!
I'll buy it for 1000 yen!
Why are you running?!
Yuuko!
You've got it wrong!
That notebook! That notebook...
It's gonna explode!
It's impossible.
Yuuko runs too fast to catch up.
It's over... My life is over!
Thank you for everything, my life...
"Entrance Ceremony"
It was good while it lasted.
Sure, some bad things happened, too.
"Sasahara"
But overall, it was a wonderful life.
But it's over now!
My life has come to an end...
--It's over, along with the manly buffet.
--Manly... buffet.
It's over.
There's...
...no...
...way...
...I'd...
...let that happen!
My life force...
...is a raging fire!
"Nata de coco"
But in the end... I couldn't reach her.
Yuuko!
When in the halls...
...no running!
Eh?!
A-Are you all right?
Here.
Pass your notebooks up from the back.
Say your name if you forgot your homework.
For a second, I was worried what would happen.
But all's well that ends well.
My daily life will go on as normal, safe and...
Ah!
Huh?
I never erased it!
Yo.
What's the matter, Naganohara?
"Goals: Sweat and live the spring of youth. 1-Q"
Teacher!
My homework...
I forgot it!
"Cleanup" There we go.
Hakase.
Would you mind cleaning up
your things in the room?
Huh? Uh, um...
"Science" Huh? Uh, um...
Hmm?
I don't think I'm ready for this.
I'll go and play.
Um...
"Student Guidance"
But then I went and told him everything.
Um, excuse me?
Could I stop you for a second, Annaka?
Yes?
Uh, well.
It's just one little thing.
I was thinking,
isn't your ribbon a little too big?
Bunny ears! See?
"Sweet Bun"
Sweet buns are tasty, too.
They sure are.
"Tico Mart"
"Tico Mart" Welcome!
"Sold out."
"Classic Sweet Buns. 3 piece. 150 yen."
"Sweet Buns. 55 count. Godly quantity."
"Sweet Buns. Economy Pack."
"My Ordinary Life 8"
Sasahara.
Do you even care about being a member
of the culture festival committee?
Are you going to take this seriously or not?
I am always serious.
As the president of the drama club,
I'm always doing my part.
Did you not know this, Misato Tachibana?
How am I supposed to know?!
--Sweet...
--Listen to me!
We're supposed to be deciding
the program for the culture festival!
This has nothing to do with the drama club!
They changed the brands?
Why did I have to end up
paired with this guy?
This is delicious.
What's more, the kendo
tournament is coming up soon.
Geez. I should have never volunteered
to be a committee member.
Hey, you! Who said you could read manga?!
If we can't think of any ideas,
we won't be able to go home!
Sorry. It's the latest release.
Don't you have at least one good idea?
Was my Wine Tasting Championship a bad idea?
Of course it was!
Denied, I say! Denied! Totally denied!
Hey, Sasahara...
What the heck do you think you're doing?!
Sorry. I'm fresh out of ideas.
My remote control won't connect...
Hey! Where are you going, Sasahara?!
For a brief visit to the restroom.
Sheesh.
Today she's in a particularly bad mood.
I, for one, thought the Wine Tasting
Championship was a stellar idea.
Even so, she has yet to suggest
a single idea of her own.
Yet if I bring this up, I would
be lucky to escape with my life.
Which means if I'm ever to go home,
any ideas must come from me.
But can I reduce my thinking
to a mere commoner level?
I suppose I have no choice but to try.
I-It's not like you mean anything to me!
Wake in the morning, teeth get a brushing
Before you know it, it's ten at night
Another day was full of laughter
Another day filled with joy
Goofing with friends and acting so silly
Making a ruckus and then I see
A glimpse from you and then our eyes meet
Coincidence, or not?
I won't ever admit it's first love
That's not something I would say
Hey, I'll see you again tomorrow too.
When I close my eyes I see
My vision sparkling, filled with you
Wasn't it so much fun today?
Ah, I think I'm in love
I'm so happy I'm so happy
Nice to meet you, awakening love
I'll see you again tomorrow too
Good night
I'll see you again soon in my dreams
"Word-Time"
The purity of Asia.
This is a sweet bun.
As they are rare in Kansai,
many people don't know whether
to call them "amashoku" or "kanshoku."
The next My Ordinary Life is Episode 3.
"Narration: Masako Ikeda"
Look forward to it!