"My Ordinary Life 87"
Finally, lunch time!
I can't believe what I just witnessed.
It's a miracle! A miracle!
I didn't have to stand in the hall
for forgetting Takasaki's homework!
Must be my lucky day.
Just do your homework.
Since I'm on a lucky streak,
treat me to some juice, Mio.
Aioi. We need to talk about today's homework.
Come to the Faculty Room.
Okay.
Maybe I should treat her for once.
Greatest friendship
Super duper harmony
(na na na na na na na)
Hey! I'll say it
You are my best best friend
(bright) Every time I poke fun and tease you
(shine) You come and tease me back some more
(lan lan lan) There ain't
no better feeling in the world
(why) Even when bad things sometimes happen
(fine) I forget all of them around you
(lan lan lan) We'll forever let the good times roll
It's not a problem being with you
every hour of the day
As if we're twins, child-parent,
or a pair of cloned cells
Doesn't a friendship this good
make love not so needed anymore?
Wait hold on this and that
are totally totally different things
(fight) Even after we've had a fight
(down) Or when I feel down in the dumps
(shock) All the times I wanted to be alone
Before I know it there sitting beside me
my wonderful friend till the end
Why is it, I wanna be at your side?
Whenever we're together,
time flies 100 times faster
It's so fun with you,
I think it's almost too much fun
It's cuz you're such a good friend! Hey!
(na na na na na na na)
What's going on? Uh-oh we're synchronizing man!
It's always a wild time,
we make the people 'round us crazy
What time is it now? I think it's yodelayheehoo
What's that even mean?
SO-RE-DO-SHI-RA-
Unbelievably, how to put it, awesome!
No matter what happens
we are gonna be friends! Woohoo!
Greatest friendship
Super duper harmony
cha chara chara cha cha-n
Hey! I'm over here!
Ah... Sorry, I kept you waiting.
It's okay. Actually, I only just got here, too.
--That's a relief.
--Did Sis invite her friends over again?
--There's somewhere I'd like to go together.
"My Ordinary Life 88"
Hey, hey.
How are things progressing?
Hmm?
What things?
You know what I mean. Sheesh...
Misato and Sasahara's love boat.
Gah!
Why is he the one I've gotta get married to?!
Eh? I never said that!
What's wrong with having
a daughter and one son?!
I got it, I got it! Your adult plans
for a happy life are very admirable!
Adult...
What about you, Weboshii?
Huh? Me?
Forget about me.
Eh? Tell us!
There's someone, right? Someone you like!
Come on! Come on and say it already!
Fe, stop it!
I give up! I give up! Have mercy!
I'm not stopping until you say it!
All right! All right! I'll tell you!
If you don't, I'll tickle you to death!
I said I'd tell you!
Eh? Sorry... I was having way too much fun.
So? Who is it? Who is he? This guy that you like...
Hmm... I wouldn't say that I like him yet, but...
I actually don't even know his name.
He's the guy with the mohawk.
Ah...
That guy...
What? You two know him?
Of course we know him.
He's pretty famous in our school... with that hair.
Weboshii, why are you
interested in him of all people?
Hmm... I guess...
He's so punk.
Honor students just don't
draw you in like that bad guy vibe.
He's totally bad. I mean, he's even got a mohawk.
But, just the other day...
I heard that delinquent talking so politely.
Yeah, right!
You've gotta be kidding! He's got a mohawk!
No, no. That same guy... was watering the plants.
Yeah? So unexpected!
Oh, and then... He put one of those
Yakult-looking things in, too.
Oh?! You'd never think it with him!
His head's like a pineapple.
They say a good man is full of pineapple juice!
But with that kindness, he scores a lot of points.
I think I'd prefer a nice guy, too.
What about you, Fe? Anyone you like?
What, me? I--
Sasahara, too.
Kojiro.
Sasahara was outside feeding
his goat some grass in the rain.
I get it, I get it!
Yeah, yeah! That sort of kindness!
Huh?! I never said I liked it or anything...
Yeah, yeah!
So, what about you Fe?
Eh? What about me?
Is there somebody that you like?
Um... There's no one
I'm interested in right now, but...
I'm not interested in weirdos like you two are.
Helvetica Standard.
Begin!
Seiya!
Soiya!
One point!
"Love-Like"
Ow! Ow-ow-ow...
Hold on.
Here.
Thank you.
Huh?
Come on. Give me your hand.
Eh? Um, uh...
It's finally my day off but I sleep, eat, and
take care of the plants like I would any other day.
It's peaceful enough.
I guess I should be happy for that.
I wonder if anything interesting
will happen for a change?
Hello.
"My Ordinary Life 89"
Casual clothes?
Ms. Sakurai's casual clothes...
Are you out shopping as well, Mr. Takasaki?
Her hair's tied!
And on the weekend, too!
I feel like I've inched closer to her private life!
I can't believe... what a blessing this is!
Um, sorry? Are you in pain?
Ah! Sorry! I was just feeling overwhelmed.
Ah! Are you out shopping, too?
Y-Yes!
Green onions were cheap today so I bought plenty.
Green onions, eh?
If you ever need bamboo sprouts,
just say the word and I'll give you some.
Hmm? Bamboo sprouts?
--You see, I have a little garden of sorts...
--But, hmm. The thing is...
Wow! You do? That's wonderful!
Meeting like this on the weekend is like...
...doesn't it feel like fate?
That we're tied together by fate...
Has this coincidence created a moment?
To be honest, I'm surprised with myself.
I've never felt like this before.
I wish I was a green onion.
Um, are you all right? You don't look so well...
Shall we sit down somewhere?
S-Sorry! I'm completely fine!
I'd never think of doing such a ridiculous--
Shall we sit down somewhere?
A ridiculous...
This is so good... I can't get enough.
I know! M-Ms. Sakurai! There's a park
that way, so how about there?!
Uh, sure!
"Huge Sale"
Well, well... I can't believe
this is actually happening.
Ah!
Is this... Could it be... considered a date?!
Aioi!
M-Ms. Sakurai! Let's go the other way!
What is Aioi doing here? If she sees us together...
Hey! What are you two doing over there?
You idiot! This is... uh, you know, that...
Hello!
Geez! I had no idea you two were going out!
You moron! Don't tease your teachers!
Eh? What's the big deal? You both look so happy!
You turd...
"Next day"
Ms. Sakurai. Good morning.
"Notice Board"
"Ms. Sakurai | Mr. Takasaki"
It's the two lovers!
Hot, hot!
Whoo-whoo!
You morons! Enough with the teasing!
Sheesh, those rascals.
I'm sorry about that.
I hope that didn't trouble you.
N-No... But...
I kinda... liked it.
Good enough!
I'm such a huge idiot!
Like it would ever work out that good!
We've gotta leave quick!
What a surprise.
Shoot!
What are you doing, Mr. Takasaki?
Huh?! What a coincidence, Ms. Sakurai!
And Aioi! Look who it is!
On closer look, yeah! Almost missed you!
Hmm? Aioi? You're Aioi, right?
Aioi as in Aioi, right?
Well, I've got that thing to do,
so I'll be heading out and on my way.
I guess...
...I'll buy green onions and go home.
"Shinonome Lab"
Sorry for calling you out like this.
"Ah, This Is Youth"
Did you sleep last night?
Yeah, but while sleeping I saw a strange dream.
A strange dream?
Well, um... We were kissing right here.
Shall I make your dream a reality?
--Ah!
--Eh?
Hakase! H-How about we get you some snacks?!
Do you really love me like that?
Save your questions for after.
Ah! Yah... Mmm!
After one month of investigation,
I've determined she visits the supermarket
in this shopping district every Saturday.
"My Ordinary Life 90"
It's nearing the time she usually arrives.
When she finishes shopping,
I'll trail her from behind.
Once we get to a place out of sight,
I'll try this Mr. Short Circuit once again
and use it to snatch her away.
A perfect plan.
Today's the day I pry you open, Nano Shinonome!
"2 Hours Later"
Huh?!
"Farm-Fresh - Fresh Vegetables"
"Super Discount"
Why haven't you come, Shinonome?
"Farm-Fresh - Fresh Vegetables"
"Super Discount"
Could it be that she doesn't come
to the supermarket every week?
No. I've waited this long...
If I leave now and somehow miss her--
Hmm?
Ah. I knew it was you, Ms. Nakamura.
Hello there.
It's him! The language sideburns guy!
H-Hello.
I hardly recognized you without your lab coat.
It's really a nuisance meeting sideburns here.
If you don't need anything, get lost.
If Shinonome slips by while he's bugging me...
This outfit of yours kinda
makes you look like a young man.
It's rather cute.
No... It's not really...
It's so far off from your usual lab coat
it makes you seem innocent... cute even.
Today, I'll have to retreat!
Huh? Ms. Nakamura?
Um...
Have you given any thought to what
you want to do in the future, Minakami?
I have.
Eh?
You want to find a job?
Uh, um...
Pursue higher education?
Uh...
Um...
I see...
"My Ordinary Life 91"
Did you find it yet?
It's not here... The wood cube.
But how could something stored
in the safe just disappear?
If you can find it, a whole wad of cash is yours.
I'd be pretty content with that.
The Officer said we recovered one already.
Just one left, huh? Guess we should get looking.
If I can come up with it, I might be able
to get in the King's good graces--
H-Hey... What?
That's...
Give me back my wood cube.
Hey, hey. What are you on about, little girl?
How did you manage to get here?
Are you a stowaway or something?
If so, your punishment will be brutal.
You'll get at least ten years locked up in jail.
Or come with me...
...and have some tea.
Just kidding.
22!
You bastard! Who do you think--
Wait. Wait, wait, wait.
I'm fine, I just let down my guard.
I've got this under control.
Sheesh. You sure pack
a powerful punch for such a tiny girl.
Say, I think your little playtime is over--
You okay?!
It's no use. He's dead.
You freak!
The stowaway is after the wood cube!
Go around behind her! We'll overwhelm her!
Hmm...
Quiet, everyone.
There's no reason to panic.
Officer!
"Fey Kingdom Officer
Alias: Tenacious Negotiator"
Please allow me to handle this.
In this situation... only the Officer
may be able to do something.
Coming all by herself to take the wood cube...
She's undoubtedly a spy from somewhere.
This immense strength of hers... If we could tame her,
she would be a great asset to our kingdom.
Fortunately, I have the other wood cube right here.
If this is what she wants,
we can negotiate and strike a promising deal.
I have here the wood cube you are after.
What do you say? How about we make a trade?
Ouch!
Officer!
No use! He's dead!
This is bad!
That bastard! She demolished the officer!
You monster! Don't think
you'll escape from here alive!
"Hell Encyclopedia"
"Himalaya Dolphin"
This is bad! This is bad!
This is incredibly, awfully bad.
"Fey Kingdom ♪71
"Fey Kingdom ♪71 Alias: Scholar"
What's wrong, Scholar?
What is it that's so bad?
You have no idea how bad this is!
She just put the wood cube in her hair!
Another one is right on the side of her head!
It's the other wood cube!
She's managed to obtain both the wood cubes!
But even with both of them, as long as she
doesn't know how to summon the ancient weapon...
Right! We have a chance!
Shut up, okay?!
Here in the Hell Encyclopedia,
it says that whoever possesses both cubes
is bestowed with the power of the ancient weapon!
In other words...
Whoever has both cubes is bestowed
with the power of the ancient weapon!
What was that?!
Say it again!
Scholar, repeat that again!
In other--
There's no time for that!
If we fight her, it won't be the end of us,
it'll be the end of the world!
We're doomed...
We're doomed!
Don't back down!
"Fey Kingdom Captain"
"Alias: None really"
Nothing is ever born from fear.
"Fey Kingdom Captain"
"Alias: None really"
Nothing at all!
Captain!
Listen up. Attacking her head-on
will guarantee your destruction.
There's no chance to win.
However! The enemy is just one lone girl!
We have the number advantage!
In that case, we must rush in and
snatch the wood cube from her together!
I'll take the vanguard!
Press the attack!
Captain!
Don't worry about me! Go!
B-But...
You piddling fool!
I don't remember raising you so weak!
It's over...
The Officer was done in...
The Captain can't move...
There's no hope for us...
One...
One for all...
And all for one!
Captain!
It's been 12 years since I joined this squad...
Twelve long years of memories...
To end like this...
To end by this monster...
In a place like this...
I will not let it happen!
We're doomed!
No! I don't want to die!
I'm going to wash my face.
"Word-Time"
"Surprise Box" "Don't be scared"
It's so obvious!
Good grief.
Well, I'm bored as it is.
Might as well play with the brat.
Making something a waste of time is a
special talent indeed.
"My Ordinary Life 92"
Oh? Bed head? It's so cute on you.
It's rather cute.
Geez! What the hell am I doing?!
"Sunday Night"
I'm all done. That was such a wonderful bath--
"The Truth About Santa"
The color of flowers (the color of flowers)
the shade of cloud (the shade of cloud)
Those nostalgic (nostalgic) memories
Seen through (seen through)
the window of our past
Time to leave the nest
(time to leave the nest) today we part
Alas, goodbye goodbye sensei
Alas, goodbye goodbye my friends
It's for a beautiful tomorrow
"Ms. Sakurai | Mr. Takasaki"
I'm a Love Umbrella. I bet you
haven't drawn one of me in ages.
Write your name on the right,
and on the left... No one to write?
For a sad soul like you,
"Narration: Sumi Shimamoto"
the next My Ordinary Life is Episode 22.
Look forward to it!