Good morning!
First one here!
"First One Legit"
Stag beetle.
What are you doing, Aioi?
Wh-Why are you here so early in the morning?!
I'm on morning duty today.
Oh, yeah. Come and help me take out the garbage.
Mr. Takasaki! You won't tell
anybody about this, will you?!
I wonder about that...
You're killing me!
Safe by a hair!
Greatest friendship
Super duper harmony
(na na na na na na na)
Hey! I'll say it
You are my best best friend
(bright) Every time I poke fun and tease you
(shine) You come and tease me back some more
(lan lan lan) There ain't
no better feeling in the world
(why) Even when bad things sometimes happen
(fine) I forget all of them around you
(lan lan lan) We'll forever let the good times roll
It's not a problem being with you
every hour of the day
As if we're twins, child-parent,
or a pair of cloned cells
Doesn't a friendship this good
make love not so needed anymore?
Wait hold on this and that
are totally totally different things
(fight) Even after we've had a fight
(down) Or when I feel down in the dumps
(shock) All the times I wanted to be alone
Before I know it there sitting beside me
my wonderful friend till the end
Why is it, I wanna be at your side?
Whenever we're together,
time flies 100 times faster
It's so fun with you,
I think it's almost too much fun
It's cuz you're such a good friend! Hey!
(na na na na na na na)
What's going on? Uh-oh we're synchronizing man!
It's always a wild time,
we make the people 'round us crazy
What time is it now? I think it's yodelayheehoo
What's that even mean?
SO-RE-DO-SHI-RA-
Unbelievably, how to put it, awesome!
No matter what happens
we are gonna be friends! Woohoo!
Greatest friendship
Super duper harmony
cha chara chara cha cha-n
"My Ordinary Life 97"
"My Ordinary Life 97" Mio?
Yeah?
I tried making some jam yesterday.
Want to have a taste?
Why? What's gotten into you all of a sudden?
It's because I used all your marmalade the other day.
Ah. Yeah you did.
But for you to make jam? Did you
finally decide to show off your girly side?
Don't you tease me.
Try to guess what flavor jam I made.
Yeah, yeah. Let me give it a taste.
Nasty!
Nasty, nasty, nasty, nasty, nasty!
It's so nasty, it doesn't make sense!
Here, Mio. Drink some Russian tea.
Hot!
Hot, hot!
It's hot, but even worse, it's nasty!
Nasty, nasty, nasty, nasty, nasty!
--Here, Mio. Eat some jam to cool your mouth.
--Nasty, nasty, nasty, nasty, nasty!
Nasty!
Nasty, nasty, nasty, nasty, nasty!
Water!
Water, water, water!
Water, water, water! Water, water, water!
Water!
"Water outage"
Splat!
Milk!
"Extra Thick" Milk! Milk!
Milk, milk!
Oh, Mio. I put the extra jam in there.
Splat!
"Extra Thick"
What is this... This unparalleled nastiness?!
How is it so nasty? Nasty! Nasty! Nasty!
Nasty! Nasty! Nasty! Nasty!
Nasty! Nasty! Nasty!
"Entrance Ceremony"
"Middle School Graduation"
"Hair tie (wood)"
"Daifuku Dude"
Hey, Mio. Are you okay?
Okay?! You're asking if I'm okay?!
You've gotta be kidding me!
It's so nasty, I had my life flash before my eyes!
I knew it'd be bad, but I didn't think
it'd have that much an effect...
Why are you making stuff you knew would be bad?!
I just thought it would be kinda interesting.
Ugh, you stupid sister!
But whatever. You haven't answered yet.
What kind of jam do you think it is?
Like I know?!
I bet you made it out of rotten fish or something!
So close!
The answer is...
Dried fish jam.
Dried fish!
This was my first and my last...
...dried fish anniversary.
"Accident"
Mako?
Dad's going to be late today, so we're
getting take-out. Is there anything that you want?
He leaves everything just laying around.
Sheesh. He never listens when I tell him to clean.
Will he not do anything unless I get mad at him?
"Movie Edition"
"Helvetica Standard"
"Vinyl"
"My Ordinary Life 98" "Vinyl"
"You won't believe it inside!!"
"Thump Thump Thump Thump"
Th-Th-Th-This...
C-C-Could it be...?
Hey! What the heck are you doing?!
You scared me!
I told you not to come in!
If you come in again, you'll pay for it!
You'll really pay for it!
I'm sorry...
"Censored"
That's right...
I need to set him straight!
Hey!
I already told you not to come barging in!
Eh? I'm sorry...
Who gave you permission to clean my room?
That's only because you won't clean it yourself!
It's fine! Everything has its place!
Just stay outta my room!
Mako!
Why do you keep invading my room?!
As...
As your sister, I think you're
too young to have things like this!
"As your sister, I think you're too young
to be looking at lewd things like this!!!"
Y...
"As your sister, I think you're too young
to be looking at lewd things like this!!!"
Y-Y-You...
"As your sister, I think you're too young
to be looking at lewd things like this!!!"
Th-Th-That's...
Th...
Tha--
Y-You... Huh?!
Huh?! What's that? I don't know
what you're talking about!
That's not even mine!
But I found this hidden in your room.
Huh?! I've never seen that in my life!
Who decided this was my room anyways?!
I'm not the only one that uses it!
I still think you're too young
to have things like this!
Huh?! I don't even know what you're talking about!
You're not making any sense!
Then I'm throwing it out!
Eh?!
Uh...
That's my club president's!
Eh?!
I can't believe you'd throw
something of his away!
I'm sorry...
But I looked inside it a bit...
In a way, it's amazing, but it's also so...
You shouldn't be looking at things like this.
You'll become a delinquent...
I get it, I won't look! I won't,
so stay out of my room!
Geez! This is the worst...
What does Mr. Takasaki see in that--
Mako, are you mad at me?
At least knock before you come in!
But I was worried you might be angry with me...
I'm not mad!
See? I knew you'd be mad...
I'm not mad! I'm not, so get out of my room!
If you don't knock again, you'll pay!
You'll totally pay for it!
Man, I wish I had my own place...
Ugh... I think I screwed up today...
Though now his room's a bit tidied up...
At least that book didn't belong to Mako...
But at school, everyone's been acting up lately.
No, it's not the school.
It's me who needs to shape up.
I'm the guidance counselor.
Oh? I almost forgot.
Mako? What do you want for take-out?
How many times do I have to tell you?!
"Career and Future Aspirations"
"Class: 1-Q" "Name: Yuuko Aioi"
"Current Interests: Global warming.
Aging populayshon and low birth rate."
"Plans for the Future:"
Um, it's about your plans for the future...
It could be any dreams or goals
that you have. Are there any?
Uh, yes...
Um...
Uh, I want to be on TV at least once before I die!
U-Uh, that's not exactly what I mean, but...
I'm sorry. I think I worded that wrong.
Is there any sort of work or career
that you hope to get into?
U-Um... Maybe...
Yeah...
Um, uh...
I want to become a nice teacher like you!
Become... like me?
Uh, um...
Helvetica Standard.
The sash we all made... together!
It's all up to you, Nakamura!
Our last...
...relay... of college!
Disqualified. Tokisadame College
has been disqualified.
Nano, Nano!
Yes? What do you need?
We ran into Hakase when coming to visit your place.
But then we were attacked by dogs.
That sounds horrible.
Make sure to tell Hakase
that we'll come by again soon.
All right.
"My Ordinary Life 99"
Mr. Takasaki! Please become our adviser!
I said that I'm not gonna do it!
Come on! You even gave me your word before!
Eh? When did I ever say that?!
Gah! You fraud!
Don't you remember your promise to
become our adviser if I beat you in a match?!
Back then?
No! That ended in a draw due to an injury!
Eh?
Geez... I'll tell everyone
what you think about my sister.
Where's the club room at?
This way!
Yes! Go+Soccer is finally on a roll!
Yes!
President!
"President"
S-Sorry! Didn't mean to barge in!
Uh, anyways... I brought a teacher
who'll be our new adviser!
H-Hey, wait! Why are you running away?!
"--er Club" Mr. Takasaki!
They both ran away.
And we were just about to go and recruit...
Without Sakurai, there's no one
to explain what our club does.
Whatever. I guess it's still my club in the end.
"My Ordinary Life 100"
Man, I'm getting nervous!
Why the heck are you getting nervous?
Because, you're going to confess aren't you?
To that guy, Nakanojou...
Yeah. He's the spirit of punk in this peaceful school.
That mohawk is irresistible.
I don't know about irresistible,
but it sure is unique.
Mr. Takasaki! Wait a minute!
Come on, Mr. Takasaki.
Why are you running away?
That was a sweet game of Go+Soccer.
My first in a long time.
There's nobody that's more fit
to advise us than you.
Sorry. I... You know... have things...
That's... It's... for me...
Well, it's like... I...
But you even came to our club room!
I've no choice...
Mr. Takasaki.
Look at this... and see if you can still say that!
You! This...
That's right. It's a photo of my sister
from when she was in high school.
So, Mr. Takasaki? What will you do?
I'll trade it to you to become our adviser.
I want it!
I want it so bad I can taste it!
But if I do, I feel like I'll lose
something important inside of me.
Sakurai...
Yes?
I'm sorry, but...
I just can't...
...pass this up.
What the hell am I doing?!
Woo-hoo! So you'll be our adviser, right?!
I'm the worst!
This is not what a teacher should do!
But...
Before I'm a teacher, I'm one hungry wolf.
Sacrifices... must be made.
Listen up, Sakurai! If we're doing this,
we're going to the top!
Do you understand?!
Yes!
Yeah! It's Go+Soccer club's time to shine!
Starting tomorrow we're going full steam ahead!
Yeah!
Is this it?
Really? Is that true?
Hey, hey!
Yes?
Is there a Nakanojou here?
Y-Yeah.
Nakanojou!
Nakanojou, someone's here!
Yes? What is it?
Eh?
He lost his charm...
"Love-Like"
Dad, can you go and look for me?
Okay. All right.
How is it?!
Which is that?
"Wet Paint"
"Store"
The train is temporarily delayed.
"Someone Save Me"
"Shinonome Lab"
Minakami? Is something wrong?
I came to play.
"My Ordinary Life 101"
Wow! I'm sorry! You didn't
have to bring so many snacks!
Oh!
It's the girl who made her dogs try to bite me!
Eh?
I know it was her for sure!
Well, I'll go start making the tea.
What did you come for?
For you.
What's that?
Yamantaka.
Don't want it.
But it's cool.
That's not cool at all.
This one's interesting.
What's that?
Thirty-six room apartment.
That's not interesting at all.
No bath, toilet, or windows.
That's not interesting.
What are you drawing?
I'm not telling you.
"Memo"
Here.
Blue Shark.
That's so cool!
For you.
Yay!
Hey, hey! Draw another shark!
Okay.
Draw one that's smiling!
Can I trade you for mine?
Okay.
Sorry to keep you wait--
Huh?
"Went home - Minakami"
Hakase? Did Minakami go home?
Yeah. But she said she'll come back
another day to draw some more.
Is that so?
--I wonder what she came for...
--Bubbles!
I never realized
How blue the sky is
Holding hands and walking
Looking up at the sky together
It really is so blue
The sky taught me
To have an open heart
To never let go the hands of my friends
I never realized
How blue the sky is
I wonder why it makes me sad
Looking up at the sky alone
That very blue sky
The sky let me hear
The song of the clouds, rivaling the winds
So that even alone, I won't want to cry.
"Word-Time"
So amazing.
I'm a graduation photo!
When people say you looked so cute, it makes you
think, "What, am I not cute now?" wouldn't you say?
The next My Ordinary Life is Episode 24.
"Narration: Yui Horie"