Nano Shinonome...
Sleep medicine, Mr. Short Circuit, a pit trap...
"Nano Shinonome Research--"
Seeing how she's avoided every single trap of mine,
she must be more advanced than I thought.
I want her!
My attempts to capture her have managed
"Ms. Nakamura 2"
to avoid drawing suspicion in school, however...
If this keeps up...
Could that be?
Wait! Wait up!
Wait! Wait for me!
Wh-Whoa!
Time to eat!
Call for your father first!
Eh?
Hey, Sis, where's the remote?
It was under the kettle yesterday.
That's not him...
Hey! Who's that over there?!
What are you doing?!
A thief?!
Not good!
What? A woman?
Greatest friendship
Super duper harmony
(na na na na na na na)
Hey! I'll say it
You are my best best friend
(bright) Every time I poke fun and tease you
(shine) You come and tease me back some more
(lan lan lan) There ain't
no better feeling in the world
(why) Even when bad things sometimes happen
(fine) I forget all of them around you
(lan lan lan) We'll forever let the good times roll
It's not a problem being with you
every hour of the day
As if we're twins, child-parent,
or a pair of cloned cells
Doesn't a friendship this good
make love not so needed anymore?
Wait hold on this and that
are totally totally different things
(fight) Even after we've had a fight
(down) Or when I feel down in the dumps
(shock) All the times I wanted to be alone
Before I know it there sitting beside me
my wonderful friend till the end
Why is it, I wanna be at your side?
Whenever we're together,
time flies 100 times faster
It's so fun with you,
I think it's almost too much fun
It's cuz you're such a good friend! Hey!
(na na na na na na na)
What's going on? Uh-oh we're synchronizing man!
It's always a wild time,
we make the people 'round us crazy
What time is it now? I think it's yodelayheehoo
What's that even mean?
SO-RE-DO-SHI-RA-
Unbelievably, how to put it, awesome!
No matter what happens
we are gonna be friends! Woohoo!
Greatest friendship
Super duper harmony
cha chara chara cha cha-n
Nano...
"Tofu"
Th-Thanks.
That looks heavy.
Not really. Thanks for the help.
Are you okay by yourself?
"My Ordinary Life 102"
Mio! Mio! Big news!
I'm writing a report. Tell me later.
It can't wait for that! I saw it!
I really saw it!
Saw what?
Just now, Sasahara and Nano were walking together!
Yeah?
Huh?
What gives? I thought she'd
react a lot more than that...
So?
Uh...
O-Oh!
And then, they were being all friendly and talking.
Yeah?
Well, that sort of thing is normal.
Eh?
We're humans. Of course we talk to each other.
And? Is that it?
Uh, yeah...
That's it.
You know, I've gotta finish
this report before next class.
So yeah, I'm trying to concentrate here.
Uh, okay. Sorry.
Well, shucks. That's no fun.
And?
Huh?
So? And then? What?
Meaning what?
I'm asking you what they were
being friendly and talking about.
Hello?
Earth to Yuuko.
Uh, um...
Sasahara said those books looked really heavy.
And?
Uh...
That's all.
Sheesh, Yuuko!
You're such a huge idiot!
I knew you were an idiot before,
but I never thought you were this stupid!
Saying "Mio! Big news," and stuff!
You're such an idiot,
it's like a miracle how stupid you are.
You're a miracle idiot. Get it?
I never told you that Sasahara and Nano...
...were also kissing.
Y-Y-You're kidding...
Starting with a greeting kiss, they intimately
walked to the cafeteria to get bread together.
After they both bought their bread
and had a lovely conversation...
Sasahara then...
Sasahara then what?
He suddenly took off his clothes.
Took off his clothes?!
Saying "Delicious!",
Sasahara decided to make his move.
Together they...
Together they?
In the courtyard...
In the courtyard?!
--Wah!
--Gah!
I forgot! I forgot! I've gotta do that report, too!
Crap!
We've got to think of our own subject for this?!
In the courtyard...
In the courtyard!
What's this? What made you
decide to get yakisoba bread?
Because! I like it!
But you always get yakisoba bread.
Should I call you the Yakisoba Princess?
Th-Then... What did you buy, Koujirou?
Me?
I bought a sweet roll.
Th-Then Koujirou is...
What's wrong?
It's none of your business! Hmph!
Then I should call Koujirou...
...the Sweet Roll Prince!
Delicious!
Then Koujirou is...
What's wrong?
It's none of your business! Hmph!
Then I should call Koujirou...
...the Silky Skin Beauty!
Let's eat in the courtyard.
Splendid idea.
And then I heard the teacher ate a wild whale.
Are you sure about that?
It's the truth!
But, if that's the case, they went out
of the 200 mile exclusive fishing zone.
There's nothing to worry about.
That teacher is an Eskimo!
Nano...
Hmm?
There's yakisoba bread...
Eh?
...on your cheek.
It was... a gentle moment carried
by the soft spring breeze.
Ours alone...
That gentle... moment.
"rendezvous--"
Rendezvous!
I can't do it! I can't do it!
How can I write a report like this?!
This isn't going anywhere!
--Yuuko!
--Ahh!
I was just about to think of a topic!
What happened in the courtyard?!
What did they do?!
Ahh! Geez, just shut up!
Um... Umm!
Addis Ababa!
That settles it! Off to the courtyard!
To that Eden of obscenity!
Thank you very much.
It was no big deal.
Farewell.
Huh? What's wrong, Naganohara?
Nano...
Yes?
I heard you were eating yakisoba bread
with Sasahara in the courtyard.
Sasahara?
Oh, you mean him?
He just helped me pick up a book.
That's all?
Yes, that's all.
For real? What about the yakisoba bread?
Huh? What are you talking about?
"Helvetica Standard"
Eh? Come on, tell me! Who do you like, Yumi?
Eh? I don't know if I should...
I won't tell anybody!
If I do, I'll give you a million yen.
Really?
You better not tell anyone.
Yeah, yeah!
It's Takashi.
Hey, everyone, listen! Yumi said she likes Takashi!
"Undress"
I see...
"My Ordinary Life 103"
Yah!
Head!
Thank you for today.
Here.
"Knight"
You dumb, gifted natural!
It's so rare for you to come to the dojo.
The competition is coming up, so it's nice getting
lessons outside of school from the instructor.
Besides, Naganohara was there, too, which helps out.
Though she never comes these days.
What? Really?
She says she gets worse the more she trains.
That girl is a monster.
Yeah?
So, who do you normally get lessons from?
The instructor and...
Oh. Also, Sasahara has been
coming pretty often lately.
Yeah?
S-Sasahara?!
Why does he come to the dojo?!
Why? He came to our dojo all throughout
middle school, so who cares if he comes?
Well, I guess that's true, but...
Why didn't you know that?
Don't you talk to him in school?
You're in his club, right?
I'm not. He's been in drama club since his first year.
Hmm?
Eh?!
Drama club?!
Why isn't he in the kendo club?!
How am I supposed to know?!
If you take kendo away from Sasahara,
all that's left is a guy with a funny face!
You say that because you've
only ever seen him at the dojo.
What do you mean?
You see, Sasahara's acting in the high school
--drama club is like nothing you've ever seen.
--Actually, this is grape juice.
I can just imagine it now...
Right?
But why haven't you invited him
to the kendo club? It's such a waste!
Huh? Why do I have to be the one to invite him?
What he wants to do is up to him.
Because with Sasahara, you could
go to the national tournament!
I don't know what he's thinking.
He joined the drama club without saying a word.
He's an idiot, that idiot. That huge idiot!
B-But, well... If you're going
to bug me about asking him...
Maybe I'll invite him after all...
She's...
...so easy to see through.
So?
Eh?
When does Sasahara come?
Ah. He comes like once every three days,
so he'll probably be there tomorrow.
Yeah?
Not that I really care...
Hey, Sis.
What?
You should confess to Sasahara already.
I don't want to hear it from a middle schooler!
I'm going home!
Sis...
You're so transparent...
"Love-Like"
So cold!
Cold attack!
See you!
"Leap"
I see...
"Shinonome Lab"
"My Ordinary Life 104"
That was yummy!
Thanks for the meal!
Hakase!
You need to eat your green onions!
I think it's a bit too soon
to eat green onions for me.
What is that supposed to mean?
Anyways, you have to eat everything on your plate.
But green onions are bitter and that's so weird.
If you don't eat everything,
you get no snacks tomorrow.
See? You should learn from Sakamoto.
He never leaves any--
Sorry. I don't have the strength...
Sakamoto! What's the matter?
A-Are you all right?
It's nothing. Just a little cold.
I'll be fine if I sleep.
But you haven't eaten anything at all.
You need to eat something.
No, that's okay.
Will you at least drink milk?
No...
Well, this is a problem...
Is there anything you think you can eat?
No...
I don't want anything right now.
But...
Sakamoto wants to eat green onions.
Trying to kill me?!
Achoo!
Is there anything that you want?
No...
Well, for now, I'll just set this milk right here.
If you want some food, tell me. I'll go and buy it.
Okay.
Huh?!
Achoo!
I think I have a cough, too,
so I want to eat chocolate.
Hakase needs to eat her onions.
Why does Sakamoto get something but not me?!
Because Sakamoto has a cold.
But I'm coughing over here, too!
But you're full of energy.
Because I have a cold and want chocolate!
I have a cold, too, you know!
If you have a cold, you need to take some medicine.
Will you drink medicine?
I've had enough!
Ah, Hakase!
Sheesh, Hakase.
Leave me alone!
You hate me so that's why you're
making me eat green onions!
You like Sakamoto more because
you're not making him eat any onions!
No, that's not it at all.
Cats aren't supposed to eat onions.
I don't know anything about that!
Sheesh...
You're so hopeless.
Actually, I like Hakase the most.
Really?
Yes!
Then, then, can I eat chocolate?
Lemme see...
You can if you eat your onions.
Eh?! Why?!
I thought you said you liked me most!
Then now I like Sakamoto the most.
Which is it for real?
I like both of you!
What the heck?!
Sakamoto, what the heck?!
Achoo!
"Hypnotism"
"Word-Time"
Which floor?
Oh... Seventh floor, please.
Thanks.
The thing is, I don't remember
feeling embarrassed this year.
"School Counseling Office"
Um...
Naganohara's hopes for the future...
"Current Interests:"
"Plans for the Future: Manga Artist"
"Manga Artist"
"Manga Artist" Manga Artist.
Y-Yeah.
You're very good at drawing, Naganohara.
Eh?
No...
Chase your dreams. I'll be cheering for you.
Good luck!
"Melon"
Um, Yuuko wanted melon juice and...
What do I want to get?
I'm kinda broke this month.
I'll get the usual banana juice instead of splurging.
Wh-Whoa, whoa...
Ah...
Sorry--
"My Ordinary Life 105"
S-S-S-S--
S-S-- It's Sasahara!
What's wrong?
You look like a deer in the headlights.
S-Sorry!
Um, uh... What to do? I gotta talk about something.
Uh, um...
It's such nice weather today.
What the heck am I saying?!
Gah! The whole sky is cloudy!
That was deep.
Yeah...
By the way, does this coin belong to you?
Y-Yeah.
I see.
I'm very sorry.
Eh?
Y-Yeah...
You know, maybe this was supposed to happen.
Eh?
Well, the thing is, I forgot
to bring my wallet today.
I passed right in front of the vending machine
as my throat became parched.
And there, I picked up a coin.
The heavens... must love me.
In other words, this beverage is like
holy water from the heavens.
Um...
"Coin Return"
This vending machine...
...it's quite the swindler.
Y-Yeah!
I can't believe this vending machine
has managed to best me.
That's such an admirable feat in this day and age.
I like it!
You deserve that coin!
S-Sasahara?
Shh.
I don't know why, but...
I feel like I've grown just
a little closer to Sasahara.
Mio! My melon juice!
"Knight"
I wonder if she was trying to tell me something?
Naganohara is so strong, she's practically unrivaled.
Knight...
Knight, huh?
"Knight" Knight, huh?
"Knight" Speaking of knights...
You should confess already.
Sis, the bath is open.
I wonder if Sasahara is looking at the moon, too.
Sasahara! You're pretty good!
You should come and train with me again!
Okay.
All right!
I'll teach you my secret move next time!
Sis!
Look, look, look!
Sisters!
Eh?
Geez, don't just invite yourself in.
What were you daydreaming about?
Sh-Shut up! It doesn't matter!
Is that blush? Is that blush?
I'm not blushing!
Just leave me alone!
Long ago, the Icarus of Greece
Using bird feathers hardened with wax
Took them in both hands and flew into the air
Higher than the clouds and even farther yet
Bringing nothing but courage
The hills drifted out of sight
Ocean spread far down below
Flapping both wings in his arms
Aiming, soaring towards the sun
Bringing nothing but courage
We must all try to live strong
We always run out of money
whenever you don't have exact change.
That is our, the vending machine's, law.
The next My Ordinary Life is Episode 25.
"Narration: Ichiro Nagai"
Look forward to it!