"Birthday"
"Birthday" Hey, hey.
"Birthday" Hmm?
Let's celebrate Nano's birthday!
Oh, good idea! When is it?
Today.
As in now?!
Man, you've gotta tell us these things in advance!
Sorry!
Eh? Hmm...
What to do...
I don't have anything for it.
Well, I don't even know if today
is Nano's birthday anyway.
You didn't ask her?!
That's right!
What the heck?!
It's a surprise!
Hakase, too.
We should celebrate Hakase's birthday together.
Oh! I like it!
Two birds with one stone! Let's do it!
But well,
--surprises are fun for both
--Cool, right? It'll be nice!
--the person and the people doing it.
--Nice, Yuuko. Nice, nice.
All right, I know! Let's all go and buy
a cake right after school!
All right! Are you cool with it, Mai?
I forgot my purse.
O-Oh well.
Fine, Yuuko and I can pay.
I forgot my wallet, too.
Mio, please!
Well, I never paid you back for
your money I lost at the amusement park.
I guess I can cover for you two today.
Then I'll go tell Nano we're
going to celebrate her birthday!
What happened to the surprise?!
Sheesh. You're such an idiot, Yuuko.
A-At least I didn't get rejected by Sasahara.
Wow!
I-I didn't get rejected!
But you ran away crying.
That's... Besides, their arms were just locked.
It doesn't mean they're going out or anything.
There's no confirmation from the person himself!
So I haven't been rejected at all yet!
I'm not about to give up without even trying!
I'm still in love with him!
So you'll just have to deal with it!
"Shinonome Lab"
Good!
"My Ordinary Life 110"
I'm all set and ready to go.
"My Ordinary Life 110" Hakase!
I'll be on my way!
Nano!
Yoink!
Wh-What's this about, Hakase?!
I made a little guy so I'm taking the big one off.
Hakase? What do you mean by little guy?
The little guy is, um...
--Um, uh...
--Are you saying with that,
--my back could actually be smooth?
--Um, uh...
It could.
But the little guy is even better than that... Um...
Uh, um...
Nano?
Yes?!
I lost it.
Nano! Are you okay?!
What's with this ruckus so early in the morning?
You brat! What kind of trap
did you set for me now?!
Ah! Sakamoto broke the little guy!
Eh?!
Eh? Uh, no wait!
No... Um...
Ah! Sakamoto made Nano cry!
No, no, no! It's your fault
for leaving it on the ground!
I'm leaving for school...
Eh? Um, uh, um...
Nano!
Don't forget this.
Nano...
I can make another one easy.
Can you finish it before I get back?
It's not hard for me to make.
Hakase!
I'm leaving for school!
Okay!
I'll be back later!
"Shinonome Lab"
"Shinonome Lab" See you later!
"Shinonome Lab" See you later...
"Principal"
"Principal & Vice Principal"
Huh? How weird is that...
Vice Principal!
This is the statue that used to be here
when I was the principal of the school.
That's odd... Isn't this where your statue
is supposed to be, Principal Shinonome?
Good grief. Students these days are pulling pranks
with the strangest sense of humor...
Or maybe it's just...
I wonder if some of them are my supporters?
Vice Principal!
We're done with the delivery!
This is where you wanted the statue, right?
U-Uh, um...
I don't know what you're...
Vice Principal... What are you...
Sh-Sheesh.
The pranks kids are pulling these days...
They're so involved, you know?
S-Sorry.
Please take this statue away, too.
"Daiku Delivery"
Eh? You want us to take this tiny one back?
Tiny?!
All right!
We'll take this ugly statue right away!
Ugly?!
Hey! We're loading up this pathetic one, too!
It's okay, Vice Principal. Don't let it get to you.
Put it right next to the crappy one
already in the truck!
What was that?!
"Go+Soccer 8"
"Go+Soccer Club"
Huh? It's already open...
Oh, wow. You're here already, Sekiguchi?
I even wanted to get here first
so I flew in on the blackbird.
What? Did you come for morning practice?
Um...
Uh, um...
Yeah.
What? Really?
Ugh. Figures that I'd have to
"My Ordinary Life 111"
buy both of your lunches, too.
"My Ordinary Life 111" Sorry!
Well, you don't have your wallet
so there wasn't much choice.
Yeah, that's our Mio!
What a saint!
A-Are you okay?
Geez. Would you stop slapping me so hard?
Sorry, sorry!
Wh-Whoa...
Ah, sorry Mai.
It's okay.
Oh. By the way, Yuuko. Did you ask Nano
if we could stop by today?
Whoa! I totally forgot!
All right! I'll go tell her
we're celebrating her birthday!
Gah!
You can't go do that!
Only ask her if today is okay!
I know that already!
I don't believe you!
Geez, I'll go do it!
I said I would go!
No, let me go!
I wanna go!
I'll do it!
I'm going.
Wait, Mai! Mai!
A moment, please! Just a moment, please!
Fine. I'm going to go find Nano!
Time for action!
"Sweets" Ow!
"Sweets" Whoa!
"Sweets" S-Sorry!
"Sweets" Don't worry about it.
Go!
I'm really so sorry! I'm very sorry...
Geez...
Ah!
I didn't want black coffee...
S-Sorry!
It's okay. It's fine.
I'm sorry for getting in the way.
I'm very sorry!
"Free can if you win!!" "Winner"
A-Aioi! Please behave in the hallway!
A-A-Achoo!
Rainbow.
Achoo!
Oh! Found it!
Ow-ow-ow...
Aioi!
Are you all right?
Oh! I was looking for you, Nano!
You were?
Yeah! Actually--
No! This is...
Hey! Are you okay?!
Did that hurt at all?
No, I'm fine...
Oh, phew. Thank goodness.
Um, this isn't what you think it is...
How should I put it--
Hey, hey! More importantly,
can we come over today?
S-Sure.
Oh, that's right!
It's a surprise so I can't say anything else.
Huh? Um...
We'll see you later, okay?
O-Okay.
I'll buy enough for Aioi and the others, too.
♪ First comes rock, then your hand delivers... ♪
♪ What's it gonna be, no cheats!
Rock-paper-scissors! ♪
What the heck?
"My Ordinary Life 112"
This kabocha squash!
It's hard!
"Rice Balls"
Sheesh, that brat. Why is she always--
Taisho!
Is that you, Taisho?
N-Nakamura!
I've been looking for you, Taisho!
I'm so glad you're all--
Why are you running away?
Did you forget who I am?!
I'm running because I didn't forget!
Taisho, time for dinner.
Here.
What's wrong, Taisho?
Aren't you hungry?
What's wrong, Taisho?!
Time for a bath.
Taisho!
"Robot Research" "Cat Life"
Shoot.
I need to hurry or I'll be late.
Taisho. I'll see you later.
Whoa! Wh-Whoa...
Shoot.
Taisho!
Where'd you go, Taisho?!
Taisho?!
Please, just leave already!
Huh? Ms. Nakamura?
Hello!
Shinonome?
Oh, good! Do something!
What's the matter?
--Are you searching for something you lost?
--She's been drawn like a robot to a flame.
Though, actually... I can meet
Shinonome at school any time.
Right now...
Taisho's my priority.
Sorry, Shinonome.
Have you seen a black cat?
Huh? Do you mean that you have
a black cat at your house, too?
W-Well, yeah.
It ran away though.
I have a black cat at my house, too.
I see...
Would you like me to help search for him?
Sure. Sorry to bother you.
It's okay.
What are you, an idiot?!
Oh, that's right, Ms. Nakamura.
What's the name of your cat? What do you call it?
It's Taisho.
That's an interesting name.
The cat we keep at my house is called Sakamoto.
That's a weird name.
That's true. It really is a weird name.
Is he cute?
Taisho. Is he cute?
Wh-What are you talking about?
You...
Well, it's not like Nakamura
treated me like that on purpose...
Though, if her blunders
"Memories of Nakamura's constant blunders"
don't stop, I'll never survive.
No, hold on a second...
"Memories of that brat's constant pranks"
Isn't now essentially the same as before?
The scale of pain... It's bad either way!
Oh, it's already this late?
Sorry, Ms. Nakamura.
I need to be heading home soon
since this won't stay fresh...
Oh, I see.
When you find him, do you mind
if I come and see Taisho?
Oh, sure!
Come whenever! Come tomorrow!
Well then, I'll see you later.
Yeah!
Dammit! No matter who I go with, it's all the same!
"My Ordinary Life 113"
Hakase! Sakamoto!
I'm home!
Nano!
"Peace" It's a little guy!
Did you finish it, Hakase?!
Sakamoto stepped on it again!
Sakamoto...
Yoink!
Eh? Huh?
You're fine with taking it off?
I'll make one really quick!
Hakase!
But it sure is easy for you to pull the key off.
It never comes off for me
no matter how hard I try.
About that... You can't take it off yourself,
but other people can do it no problem.
I see...
But guess what? Anyone can
put it in, including you.
What kind of feature is that?
Oh. By the way, Hakase...
What kind of features does the little guy have?
Without this, your thumb
won't be able to fly anymore...
That again? Such a silly feature...
I wonder if that's Aioi and the rest?
Eh?!
Yuuko!
Yay! It's Yuuko!
Oh, yeah!
I need to hide this key somewhere...
Now I look exactly the same as a normal person.
I wonder if this means I'll get along
with everyone better now?
If we can all go places like normal... Have fun
like normal... Spend my days like normal...
Hey, hey! More importantly,
can we come over today?
Because it's so cute.
Nano is just Nano.
That's all that matters.
That's what I came to tell you today.
I almost forgot.
Nano!
Hey, you.
Shh!
Quietly!
This is the important part!
I know, I know!
One, two!
Nano!
Ta-da!
Happy birthday!
We bought a cake for you!
Aioi!
Birthday? Huh? How?
It was a surprise! A surprise!
Cake! I wanna eat cake!
--Cake, cake, cake, cake, cake, cake,
--Wait! Hakase, would you cut that out?
--cake, cake, cake, cake, cake!
--Ah. No, Hakase!
--Hey, now, Hakase.
--cake, cake, cake, cake, cake!
Darn it!
The cake!
Wh-What now? Um, um...
I brought one extra.
Mai!
What the heck?!
Yay!
Eh? Do it again!
--This time it's Mio's turn!
--Do it again!
I wonder how they all knew it was today...
That it's my birthday...
"Nano's Birthday"
Nano!
I made another little guy!
Hakase...
It's true, this key has always been inconvenient.
Sometimes I really wanted to take it out.
But now, I...
I'm fine with it now!
Huh?
What this little guy does... is when Nano gets happy,
it spins your key around and around in a circle!
What's the point of that?!
Oh, that's right...
Hakase. Could I have you carry
this cake to the other room?
Wow! Another cake!
I'll be right in with the tea.
All right!
Cake, cake, cake, cake!
Hakase?!
Cake...
What the heck are you two doing?!
Are you all right, Aioi?
Nano! Get me something to wipe it with!
Right!
I'll put the candles on.
No fair! I want to do it!
Mai! Can't you lend us a hand or something?
Something to wipe! Something to wipe!
Mai!
U-Um, um!
Put this in the cake!
Another candle...
No! You've gotta help us out here!
Mai! Stop! Stop!
Um, uh!
Put this in the cake!
Thank you...
The mountains glow ablaze lit by the white light
You're leaving on a journey
to the far skies and beyond
Your heart trembling at the endless skies that await
Fly free like a bird, and don't look back
Tuck your courage in your wings
and ride the winds of hope
Under this great sky, make your dreams come true.
"Motivation"
A-Achoo!
What's wrong, Mio?
I totally can't stop sneezing.
What are you talking about?
All it takes is motivation to stop sneezing.
How are you supposed to stop sneezing
before you find the motivation?
Hmm...
You've just gotta stop it!
It's no use.
There's an idiot among us.