"Wonderful Science"
"History of Information [Absurd Edition]"
"Thermodynamics [Katsuwo Umino]"
"Electromagnetism" "Robotic Engineering"
"Cat Life"
"Sakamoto Pharmaceutical"
I realized just this very moment
I think I might have fallen in love
24 hours a day of you you you
I can't get you out of my head!
Something (something) feels different now
With you (together) it's awkward conversation
Is it (mutual love) no it's one-sided love
Uh-oh I think our eyes just met!
What is this anxious nervous feeling?
My train of thought is tangled with confusion...
This kind of thing is a first for me
Could it be a fever and I'm sick?
With a sudden twist it's awakened love
There's a fire in my cheeks and my face is all red
Th-Th-This can't be real, my hands are trembling
Is this what people mean when they talk about "love"?
I-I-I'm stuttering non-stop talking to you
Awkward silence and then mumble-mumble-mo
I wanna (I wanna) know how you feel about me
O-O-O-One one-sided love
First love! Every day on the path to school
Sparkle-sparkle dazzling I DO fall in love!
It's like I'm flying through the sky
O-O-O-One one-sided love
Hey, hey, Mio.
What?
I've always wondered about something.
Why do you always wear that same hair tie?
Oh, this?
Mmm... Just because.
What do you mean, "Just because"?
"Just because" means just because.
Yeah?
Ah! Erm... Uh...
I forgot to bring my math notebook.
Huh? We had math today?
We do! We even had homework, right?
I'll go back and fetch it.
Go ahead without me!
Well, I didn't do the homework
so it's the same either way.
Ah! Hey, Mai!
Selamat pagi!
"Mouth" "Nose" "Eyes"
"My Ordinary Life 9"
It's here, it's here!
It's finally here, Miss Mai!
Is this the delayed greeting
we've all been waiting for?!
She's taking it to another level!
A mountainous level!
In fact, the mountain has come!
Is it true that you're actually a mountain?
Well, she's definitely not a mountain.
I get it.
--I know already.
--So I was watching TV in my room last night.
--Why you're angry at me.
--Yeah? And then?
--It's because I went through your lunch yesterday
and took all the broccoli.
And so...
I went and bought some broccoli!
After I ate it all, I found out you liked broccoli.
That's why I felt really bad about what I did!
That's why... this is for you!
My old man went and took all the wheat.
It wasn't the broccoli.
It's not the cauliflower either.
I've done so many things, I don't even know
which one she's mad at me for.
Ugh...
Though, I do have a hunch.
I can't let her stay mad at me forever.
I'll just have to suck it up and apologize.
Mai!
Sorry for eating your main course!
"Sale!" "30% off retail" "Ground Pork"
Sorry for taking your apple bunny!
Sorry for eating your rice!
Sorry for skipping the black soybeans!
What is it?!
Why are you so angry at me?!
I just don't know anymore!
It's not because of yesterday's lunch?
Ah! Maybe it's from earlier back?
That thing you had on your desk...
Is it because I broke your
Buddha statue's neck?
Or that I took it home without telling you?
Was it because I secretly gave it a burial?!
"Sorry Mai~"
Or because I felt bad and left
an offering on your desk?!
Or because I changed my mind
and tossed it in the incinerator?!
Mai! Help me out here!
Wha--
Oh, geez!
You were just listening to music?
No wonder you didn't hear me.
Here I was blabbering
to myself this whole time!
That was close.
I almost spilled the beans there.
That last part.
Eh?
That last part...
It's news to me.
Gah!
"Tanaka"
Um, Tanaka?
Hmm?
Sorry! Do you have a moment?
Um, uh...
Th-That haircut is, um...
Isn't it a little extreme?
Ma'am...
Yes?!
Wanna eat a pancake?
"My Ordinary Life 10"
"Break the formula into two."
Aw, shoot!
I totally forgot to do the worksheet!
I only have five more minutes until math starts.
But I already asked to see
Mio's just yesterday.
I'm begging you!
I can't ask her again!
That leaves... just one option.
Hey, Mai?
I'm totally ashamed.
Get this... I completely forgot
to do the math homework.
Um... If you don't mind,
could I please take a look at yours?
Sure.
Wow, thanks! You're the best!
Just one sec. I'll have it copied in a flash!
This sucks! I'm so late!
"Pitter-patter"
This sucks! This sucks!
You idiot! Don't make such
a racket in the morning, Masao!
This sucks! I'm so frickin' late!
And I was just laid off!
That's weird...
Um, Mai?
I'm pretty sure this wasn't our homework...
I'll buy you some juice!
Here.
Thanks!
I'm so late for school!
My dad just got laid off!
It sucks for both of us!
You've got bigger problems than that!
Hey! Masao's in trouble here!
What's gonna happen to Masao?!
No...
Wait!
I've got bigger problems than that!
I almost got carried away there!
Dish out the homework, Mai!
I'll even treat you to one of
the snacks by the station!
Here.
Th-Thanks!
Yeah, yeah! That's what I'm talking about.
I knew you had it. Break it out faster
next time, Mai. You stinker!
It's time to slay this homework!
This homework of mine...
When's it even from?
"Word-Time"
I want to go to New Orleans.
"Quadrilateral ABCD contained in a circle where"
"Calculate the Area S of Quadrilateral ABCD"
Does anyone know the answer?
Not a single person?
Akagi's classes aren't even fair.
You end up like this if you forget homework
and get yelled at for answering wrong.
By the way, any lack of enthusiasm
will be reflected in your report cards.
So that's how it is.
I will not be broken by his threats!
"My Ordinary Life 11"
Hmm. What to do...
Today's the 23rd,
so let's go with the 23rd seat...
Now!
Nakanojou!
Oh, he's absent?
What?!
A-Arm cramp!
--Why did it have to cramp up now?!
--Let's see...
--It's May, so how about seat number 5?
--Not good. At this rate,
--he might actually see me!
--They just answered.
--I've gotta hide in his blind spot.
--How about someone who hasn't answered yet?
--His blind spot! His--
"Gurgle~"
--What? What was that sound?
--Chair! Pretend my chair made that sound!
Hey! I think someone's phone rang!
Vibrate only!
Maybe the phone wants to answer.
A smartphone!
Suddenly everybody learned
how to smile! You know?
Uh, so for this problem...
Aioi.
First comes rock, then your hand delivers...
What's it gonna be, no cheats!
Rock-paper-scissors!
Blast off! Shapapapapa! Bam!
Shabobo...?
Um...
"My Ordinary Life 12"
I already bought sugar and milk...
--So I'm not forgetting anything, am I?
--The eggs sure were cheap today.
I bought two extra packs.
--Shoot!
--What a deal.
There was a special on eggs today?
What to do? Can I make it in time?
Should I hurry back to the store?
Hmm?
A black kitty!
C-Cute!
Wait. We can't be keeping a cat...
I'm busy caring for Hakase already.
I'm sorry.
I'm home...
Welcome back.
What? That cat!
I caught him!
You can't just bring cats home.
Eh?
But it's so cute...
Mmm, well that's true...
N-No! I didn't mean that!
What? You don't think he's cute?
No, I do, but...
He's cute, but...
Um, it's tough work caring for a living animal.
Can you even handle it, Hakase?
I can!
I'm not going to help at all, you know.
You'll even have to clean their potty.
You're not going to help with anything?
Fine! Then I won't let you touch it!
What?!
Th-That's...
No! What I'm saying is...
Hakase! Hakase! He's napping on my lap!
I get to pet him!
He's so fluffy!
No fair, Hakase! Let me, too!
His tummy's fluffy-fluffy!
His side's so fluffy-fluffy!
His right hand's fluffy-fluffy!
His left hand's fluffy-fluffy, too!
His tail's so fluffy-fluffy!
His tail's not as fluffy as behind his ear.
Huh? But touching his tail feels even softer.
His tail isn't fluffy at all!
What?!
What's the matter?
Do you think he's hurt somewhere?
Eureka!
Hold on a second.
Hakase?
Nano! Nano! Nano!
I invented a scarf for him to talk!
Hakase! That's amazing! And fast!
Let's try putting it on Sakamoto.
Sakamoto?
Is that what the cat's name is?
Yup! Because that's what was on the box.
That's so... simple.
Okay! All done!
Will he actually talk?
He'll talk.
Here it comes...
I don't care who you are--that much
petting is overboard.
Stare...
Besides, it's common sense that
cat's meow when they're hungry.
Sorry. I didn't know...
And my name?
You took it straight from a box? That's pathetic.
I'm sorry...
See? That's what I told you.
But!
How old are you anyway?
I'm eight.
One year old.
In human years, I'd be twenty.
Call me "Mr. Sakamoto," ya hear?
"That accent..."
"That accent..." "Ya hear"?
I do appreciate the free meals
coming my way, but...
You better respect the fact
that I'm the oldest one here.
And another thing I want you to know...
Just because I'm a cat doesn't mean
you can pet me indiscriminately.
To be fair, it's not that I dislike being pet...
But see? Even cats have their limits...
I'll go put him back where you found him.
Okay.
Please forgive me.
"Straw"
"4.5% Milk"
Here you go.
Are you sure?
You're giving me food even after
letting me be late on rent?
It's fine, really!
We're all here for each other.
If you ever need anything else, let me know.
Seriously?
Well, in that case...
A little money, please?
Don't think you can be a greedy goblin
just because I'm nice.
I'm sorry.
"Straw 2"
V-Vice Principal...
This is...
Don't misunderstand me, Principal.
Peek inside its stomach.
If I win...
"My Ordinary Life 13"
I don't owe you a snack
from in front of the station.
"My Ordinary Life 13" All right?
Yeah.
Sweet! I've got this!
One win, one juice.
Ready? Go!
Mai! That was totally a false start.
Right, Mio?
Hmm... It might have been a bit early.
Just a hair.
See? So let's start over again.
Get in position.
Ready?
Go!
Mai wins!
Whew, I wasn't ready for that.
I think I underestimated you.
Well, that'll do for a nice little warm-up.
Come on! Let's go again!
I think I'm still a bit weary!
I pulled an all-nighter!
But now, my body and spirit are ready to go!
It's time I got serious.
Think you can handle it?
Shoot! I wasn't paying attention!
Bummer!
That's three in a row you caught me off guard.
Surprise, surprise.
Yuuko. Isn't that enough?
Wait.
Just you wait.
Hmm, hmm. Yes, yes.
I see, I see. I've got it.
Your beginner's luck has come to an end, Mai.
--Ready...
--Bring it on!
Chest!
Well, isn't this interesting.
What do you call this?
Yuuko...
Arm wrestling, was it?
Mio, if you will.
Hold onto it for me, will you?
This is about to get real.
Would you cut it out already?!
It's because you're not even trying!
I can't try for real if you don't!
Come at me with all you've got this time!
I'm gonna unleash my secret moves!
Earth Destroyer!
Shooting Star!
Death!
Da!
Argh!
Death!
Drr!
Dah!
Why?
Why is it?
I don't get it anymore...
It's only arm wrestling...
Why are you so damn good at it?
You made me forget I had to pee.
I'll be right back.
I knew something was wrong from the start...
Yuuko.
One snack from the station.
And 23 juices.
Wake in the morning, teeth get a brushing
Before you know it, it's ten at night
Another day was full of laughter
Another day filled with joy
Goofing with friends and acting so silly
Making a ruckus and then I see
A glimpse from you and then our eyes meet
Coincidence, or not?
I won't ever admit it's first love
That's not something I would say
Hey, I'll see you again tomorrow too.
When I close my eyes I see
My vision sparkling, filled with you
Wasn't it so much fun today?
Ah, I think I'm in love
I'm so happy I'm so happy
Nice to meet you, awakening love
I'll see you again tomorrow too
Good night
I'll see you again soon in my dreams
My stupid arm cramps and then I get
yelled at for not doing my homework.
Today's the worst.
More importantly, Mai!
What happens to Masao?!
Tell me already!
Fine, I get it. I'll throw in another juice.
Here.
Yoink.
I don't know what to think.
What's nattokinase anyways? Is it
supposed to be some sort of joke?
Does kinase mean anything?
Is it some sort of instrument?
The next My Ordinary Life is Episode 4.
"Narration: Hiroshi Masuoka"
Look forward to it!