"Principal's Office"
Lately, the mood in the school
"My Ordinary Life 14"
"Principal's Office"
Lately, the mood in the school
"My Ordinary Life 14"
"Principal's Office"
has turned quite disorderly.
As the guidance counselor, I'd like for you to
become a little more strict with the students.
Okay.
I-I'll do my best!
I realized just this very moment
I think I might have fallen in love
24 hours a day of you you you
I can't get you out of my head!
Something (something) feels different now
With you (together) it's awkward conversation
Is it (mutual love) no it's one-sided love
Uh-oh I think our eyes just met!
What is this anxious nervous feeling?
My train of thought is tangled with confusion...
This kind of thing is a first for me
Could it be a fever and I'm sick?
With a sudden twist it's awakened love
There's a fire in my cheeks and my face is all red
Th-Th-This can't be real, my hands are trembling
Is this what people mean when they talk about "love"?
I-I-I'm stuttering non-stop talking to you
Awkward silence and then mumble-mumble-mo
I wanna (I wanna) know how you feel about me
O-O-O-One one-sided love
First love! Every day on the path to school
Sparkle-sparkle dazzling I DO fall in love!
It's like I'm flying through the sky
O-O-O-One one-sided love
That's right! l became a guidance counselor
so I could begin to change myself.
It's about time I turn things around.
Dear me! Oh my goodness, dear me!
This is it! I can't back down!
E-Excuse me?
What can I do for you, Miss?
Sorry, you see... It's just that...
I was just thinking it might be
a little rude to eat while walking...
My apologies. I missed breakfast this morning.
My stomach was absolutely
grumbling with hunger.
I shall put it away. Forgive me.
S-Sorry! It's okay, as long as you understand.
Thank goodness!
All I had to do was say something.
Send message...
The meal was delicious!
I'll give you delicious!
Shouting in the halls?! How about
you remember you're still at school!
U-Um, I don't think you're
supposed to bring that to school...
Misato? We're leaving.
Ah, okay!
Sasahara, I need to talk to you
during lunch break.
You better be in the classroom.
He was right. The school
may be a little disorderly...
My apologies.
I'm sure Misato Tachibana
had no ill intentions either.
Forgive us.
Um, sure. I'm very sorry.
U-Um!
What might that be?
That fluffy thing on your neck.
Oh, this?
Yes, it looks so cute.
The lives that we live are a succession
of miracles day after day.
So to speak.
That's all there is to it.
Uh, so that fluffy thing is what exactly?
Nice try.
Farewell, Miss. I shall see you in class.
Thank you very much.
Wanna stop by on the way?
Yeah, it sounds fun!
"The Sciences"
"Guidance Counselor"
Um, excuse me? Nakanojou?
Yes? What is it?
No, um... You see...
I was just thinking that hair style
might be a little too much for school...
Uh... No, I... Just a bit? Really only a little...
Um, sorry. You must not have heard me so--
The sides!
The sides just won't grow out!
"Go+Soccer Club 1"
Da... ru... ma... -san... doll...
...fell over!
Everyone went home already.
"Please take 1000 steps forward."
"My Ordinary Life 15"
Nano? What are those?
They're plums.
I was thinking of making some
pickled plums at home this year.
Pickled plums. So sour...
Plums are very healthy for you.
And putting one in a rice ball
keeps the rice from going bad.
"Potato Chips" "Lightly Salted"
Nano!
No.
I haven't said anything yet!
We bought plenty of snacks
for you the other day.
There's no point in buying more
until you finish what you already--
Geez, Hakase...
You can't. Remember,
we came to shop for the cat...
Sakamoto.
Right. I promised Sakamoto
I'd bring back some food for him.
So, snacks...
It's huge.
E-Excuse me?
Yes? What can I help you with?
Um, this... What is it?
Oh, that's a snowman.
It just came in today. It's all yours if you like.
I see...
Snack?
Um, I think it might be shaved ice.
It's cold.
And cheap!
Buying it?
Huh? No, I was just looking...
Check out the snowman.
I wish I could have that...
Hey, lady.
Um, yes?
If you're not getting that, give it to me.
I'm buying it!
Ahh!
Nano gets to buy what she wants,
but Hakase isn't allowed!
No, this is just...
If Nano can buy what she wants,
then why can't Hakase, too?!
I want! I want! I want it!
Fine, but only just one.
Really?!
I love Nano.
So that's why you bought that thing?
Yes. It's cute, cold, and feels good.
Hakase, I'm all done.
Okay!
Nano, more!
Okay, okay.
You two are unbelievable.
So? Where's my food at?
Ah!
Shaved ice...
I've been given the cold shoulder...
Not cool.
First comes rock, then your hand delivers...
What's it gonna be, no cheats!
Rock-paper-scissors!
Going up...
The screw!
"My Ordinary Life 16"
"Mid-term" "Phys. Ed." "English"
Nono...
"Now recruiting!! Jazz Karate!!"
Okay! Test time is over!
Oh my god!
That was a wig.
"Word-Time"
If you ask yourself what other people are after,
there are so many people
that you'll never find the answer.
Instead, ask yourself what you're after.
That's a much easier question.
Then, all you can do is pray to a god.
Well then.
For that god, whoever you are,
we're all counting on you.
"Go+Soccer Club 2"
Da... ru... ma... -san...
Da... ru... ma...
- san...
...doll fell over!
Can we stop this already?
"Parrot"
Ugh, I've got to stand outside again.
Huh?
I'm very used to this body now.
"My Ordinary Life 17"
--I'm drooling just looking at these.
--Fuzzy Wuzzy was a bear.
Fuzzy Wuzzy had no hair.
--What's this?
--Fuzzy Wuzzy wasn't fuzzy, was he?
--Oh, Sakamoto! They're pickled plums.
No, you can't! They're not ready yet!
I'll play with Sakamoto using this!
Ah. That's a foxtail.
Sakamoto! Sakamoto...
You brat! I told you to call me "mister"!
Ah, that's right. I'm sorry, Sakamoto.
You trying to fool with me?
Oops. I didn't mean it. Sorry, Sakamoto.
You're doing it on purpose!
I'm off to go shopping!
See you later!
Sheesh. You guys really are an ignorant bunch.
Sorry, Sakamoto. I didn't do it on purpose.
It's not Sakamoto, remember?
Okay, Sakamoto. I'll give you some gum.
How many times do I have to tell you?!
In the first place, who in their
right mind gives gum to a ca--AAH!
Cut it out already.
I'm sorry.
Listen here. Like I said before,
I'm much older than you.
You need to respect your elders and...
...say mister when you, um...
That uh... Basically, um...
You gotta, that thing... I mean, you see...
You gotta, when... you...
Ah!
What?!
Can I go potty?
Yeah! Go ahead!
Potty!
She took it with her?
As I thought, those two kids are
the only ones living in this house.
I see...
Now it makes sense why they're so ignorant.
On the other hand, that makes me
the oldest in the house.
So be it. I might as well step in
and be their father figure.
Sheesh. What a crazy house
I've landed myself in.
Oh man, this thing is sick!
What are you doing, Sakamoto?
Crap! If she finds out I was playing with
an eraser, I'll get no respect as a parent!
No respect...
I think I fell asleep.
Cats sure like to sleep.
That's the way things are.
The way things are?
Yeah. The way things are.
You gotta get a grip on the basics.
F-First, you need to learn how
to respect... your elders!
Crap! This is too much fun!
Sakamoto! Do it again! Again!
Sakamoto!
--Y-You've got it wrong! I just...
--Sakamoto! Come back! Sakamoto!
--Hey! I told you to call me "mister"!
I'm home!
Home run!
"Nakanojou"
Mom!
"My Ordinary Life 18"
Daruma-san doll... fell over!
Daruma-san doll...
Is Mai setting me up for some obscure joke?
I think I better call her out on it.
Hey, Mai. Don't judge a book by its cover.
Yuuko. Don't ever make a joke like that again.
When you make a joke that good,
it makes my jokes seem like nothing.
It's that, you know? Sometimes words
just pour out of my mouth.
You make it hard to understand, so I couldn't
tell if you were setting me up or not.
But you know, it's just
in my nature to crack a joke!
Hard to understand?
Are you saying that for real?
I thought, being you...
Being you, you might actually understand.
Wow, I'm so flattered you think that of me.
It's nice knowing someone
believes in me like that.
Believes?
Yeah...
We're not just friends anymore. There's
no reason for us to be talking about this.
Huh?
Best friends shouldn't need
words to communicate.
Mai...
Silly, Mai! It's totally fine
for best friends to talk!
Mai...?
It's a problem that you're so touchy.
Uh, err... Um...
Sorry.
Stop it...
When you do that, I can't help it...
Huh?
I can't help... but like you even more.
S-So what's wrong with liking me?
Right? Best friends! Yeah? Best friends!
It's not like that...
Eh?
We're both girls, but it makes me
think of you differently...
Sorry.
It's hard to explain.
Uh, um...
Wh-Wh-Wha?!
Something's going on with her today!
She's talking way more than usual!
And she wanted to stop and sit down here!
Was it... all so she could tell me this?
But why? Since when?
How long has she felt like this?
Uh, um... H-Hey, M-Mai?
U-Um, I don't know what to say!
Th-This is kinda confusing for me!
Aren't we a little too young for that?
W-We're still only high schoolers!
It was just a joke.
That was super, ultra-great, delicious,
and wonderfully hard to understand!
Geez!
Quit with the act!
I totally believed you there!
I see...
Eh?
You're usually a lot smarter than that.
I thought you would get it.
W-Well, I might have got it a little.
You liar.
No way. It's not that I'm lying about it.
My brain was still processing.
It was just about to hit me.
I knew something was odd
about that entire conversation.
You said you totally believed it.
Huh?
I hate being lied to more than anything else.
Sorry.
That was another joke.
I don't even know what's what anymore!
You don't? So you didn't get the other joke?
I don't know? When was it?
The one part about you being smart.
You should have caught that one.
Was that it?!
At least that's one joke
easy enough to understand.
Wake in the morning, teeth get a brushing
Before you know it, it's ten at night
Another day was full of laughter
Another day filled with joy
Goofing with friends and acting so silly
Making a ruckus and then I see
A glimpse from you and then our eyes meet
Coincidence, or not?
I won't ever admit it's first love
That's not something I would say
Hey, I'll see you again tomorrow too.
When I close my eyes I see
My vision sparkling, filled with you
Wasn't it so much fun today?
Ah, I think I'm in love
I'm so happy I'm so happy
Nice to meet you, awakening love
I'll see you again tomorrow too
Good night
I'll see you again soon in my dreams
I'm 40 years old now!
Me, the apartment complex.
You can just call me Land Lady.
Doesn't that make me sound a little bit sexy?
"Narration: Noriko Ohara"
The next My Ordinary Life is Episode 5.
Look forward to it!