"Shinonome Lab"
"Shinonome Lab" Nano!
"Shinonome Lab" Nano?
Nano!
Yes?
Nano! Nano!
Nano?
Yes, yes?
"Meow"
Nano!
Hmm?
Look, look!
It's me-ow!
Meow!
Sakamoto! Look, look!
It's me-ow!
Hakase...
I think that's...
...so cute!
Meow?
Meow!
It's me-ow!
So cute!
It's me-ow! Meow!
It's me-ow!
So cute!
It's me-ow! Meow!
It's another peaceful day
at the Shinonome household.
I realized just this very moment
I think I might have fallen in love
24 hours a day of you you you
I can't get you out of my head!
Something (something) feels different now
With you (together) it's awkward conversation
Is it (mutual love) no it's one-sided love
Uh-oh I think our eyes just met!
What is this anxious nervous feeling?
My train of thought is tangled with confusion...
This kind of thing is a first for me
Could it be a fever and I'm sick?
With a sudden twist it's awakened love
There's a fire in my cheeks and my face is all red
Th-Th-This can't be real, my hands are trembling
Is this what people mean when they talk about "love"?
I-I-I'm stuttering non-stop talking to you
Awkward silence and then mumble-mumble-mo
I wanna (I wanna) know how you feel about me
O-O-O-One one-sided love
First love! Every day on the path to school
Sparkle-sparkle dazzling I DO fall in love!
It's like I'm flying through the sky
O-O-O-One one-sided love
Why is the Earth round?
Why do rockets fly?
Why do magnets repel and attract?
Everything in this world
can be explained by science.
"Grave"
Our society often talks about the afterlife,
ghosts, and paranormal phenomenon.
"Grave"
Such dopey things cannot possibly exist.
It'd be wrong if they did.
"Mount Osore" In other words...
I refuse to believe in mediums!
"My Ordinary Life 19"
On one of my days off,
I climbed eight hours up Mount Osore.
As I approached the summit,
my heart began to race.
Was there really a medium up here?
If so, then where?
Does one live way up here all by themselves?
Or perhaps...
"Medium"
"Medium" I found her!
G-Good.
I'll have her channel a spirit.
Excuse me.
Yes?
Um, I want to speak with Soap.
Uh, sure.
Hello. This is Soap.
Ah-- Ah-- Mic test. Mic test.
Three. Mic test-test-test.
Three-three-three-three.
What the--? What is this outrageous sensation?
Could it be? Was there someone
actually called Soap?
Test-test-test. Three, three.
So-- Ah-- S-Soap. I'm Soap.
No... I can't falter now.
Besides...
If I just question her,
she'll contradict herself somehow.
I have a question.
What is Soap's blood type?
Who knows?
Let's try with someone easier to understand.
Excuse me.
Nobunaga... I want to speak
with Oda Nobunaga.
Give me a break.
She's refusing me without even trying?
No... I'm dealing with an elderly woman here.
She could be overexerting herself.
I'll have to attack from another angle.
"Medium"
Excuse me.
I'll go home.
I don't have it in me to criticize others.
Realizing that alone makes this trip worth it.
Um, mister?
Hmm?
That'll be 5,000 yen.
"Daruma-Otoshi"
"Tokisadame Bypass Open"
"Tokisadame Newspaper"
"100 Points"
"Sneeze"
Seriously?!
Boys are so...
"My Ordinary Life 20"
"2nd period" "Self-Study"
You ready?
"Integrated Japanese"
Rock-paper-scissors!
W-W-Wow!
You're doing it wrong, Mai!
I just explained it to you!
When you win, you need to hit me!
How cruel. You're killing me.
In a way, this hurts more than getting hit.
Listen, like I said before...
If you lose, you guard. Win, and you strike.
Not yet! Why the heck did you hit me?!
Because I won.
Don't hit me now! That was before!
Hit in that instant! Live in the moment!
That's the way we humans are supposed to live!
First comes rock, then your hand delivers...
What's it gonna be, no cheats!
Rock-paper-scissors!
It's Nano-meow!
Whatever. Let's do it again from the start.
Rock-paper-scissors!
She doesn't even care!
I'm a clown! I feel like such a clown!
She's totally killing my vibe...
Um, Mai?
Found it.
Mai...
H-How did you get that?
I carved it.
Thank god! I thought it
reincarnated for a second...
I'll put this right here.
She looks... so happy.
Well, who cares about that? Let's play.
Okay? Rock-paper-scissors.
M-Mai...
That's... cheating!
You're kidding me...
So destructive!
For crying out loud, Mai!
None of that! None! No cheating!
And no more hitting me with Buddha!
Are you ready?
First comes rock...
Rock-paper-scissors.
Mai...
Yeah, yeah! That's it, Mai!
I knew you could do it!
Great! Let's do it again!
Um, first comes--
Roooooock...
"Integrated Japanese"
God is dead!
"God is dead."
Hey! Why did you hit me?!
You even did it right before!
Well, I just...
I don't want to play.
Huh?
Can I see your Buddha?
Sure.
"Shinonome Lab"
I'm going to the library to return some books!
Take care of the house while I'm gone!
Okay!
"My Ordinary Life 21"
"No snacking on Ice Cream & Juice!"
Why does Nano's daruma only have one eye?
I know! If I fix it and give it
another eye, maybe she'll praise me!
"No snacking on Ice Cream & Juice!"
She might even say I can
eat all the snacks I want!
I think I messed up a bit...
It's not mine either... What should I do?
What if she gets mad at me?
No more snacks for Hakase!
Um, like this... and this...
What are you doing?
Sakamoto! What do I do?
Look...
What the-- What the heck did you do?!
Isn't that her favorite?
But it didn't have both eyes...
Hmm.
Hmm, hmm.
Don't worry.
Just do exactly as I say.
I'm home!
Good luck.
Sakamoto!
Huh? Are you going somewhere, Sakamoto?
Hakase, I'm back!
I was busy picking out new books to borrow.
What are you doing?
Wha-- Hakase?!
What happened to your stomach?!
Ehe... Heheh... Ehehe...
Don't "ehehe" me!
I'm giving birth!
Dah!
No, no, no. There's no way that could happen.
I'm giving birth!
--Um, is this some sort of game?
--I'm giving birth! I'm giving birth!
No! I'm having your baby brother!
Baby brother.
Uguu... Uguu...
Th-This could be bad.
"Shinonome Lab"
Helvetica Standard.
"Kokkuri-san"
Mio, Mio!
What?
Let's play Kokkuri-san.
Huh? What's that?
Oh? You don't know about it, Mio?
Not a clue.
Okay. I'll explain the gist of it.
First you draw a shrine gate in the middle.
Then you write "Yes" and "No"
on some paper with the alphabet.
Okay.
In some regions you're supposed
to draw fried tofu on the paper, but...
Let's just keep it simple for now.
Sure.
Then, you open up a window facing north
so Kokkuri-san can get in.
Right.
Then you take a 10 yen coin
and set it right over the gate.
With both your fingers touching it,
you're supposed to ask a question.
About their secrets, who they like,
or an answer to their problems.
Yeah.
And then, even though you don't move it,
Kokkuri-san answers by sliding the coin around.
Really?
Isn't that cool? But there's things you can't do.
First, you can't do it alone
or screw around while playing.
If you do, you'll get possessed by a spirit.
Oh?
And if you stop halfway,
you might get possessed, so watch out!
I see.
That's how you play. It's kinda spooky isn't it?
So, what do you say we try it?
No, thanks.
Huh...?
"My Ordinary Life 22"
Um, that wraps it up for class today.
We'll be having a quiz tomorrow,
so don't forget to study.
Eh? Push it back! Push it back!
You won't do any good
no matter when we take it.
"Quiz" "English" Probably.
"Quiz" "English" Miss Sakurai?
What can I do for you, Aioi?
I just wanted to ask you something.
Sure!
Um, it's about the test we had before.
"Replace the Japanese word with English"
What's this supposed to be?
Oh, that should be "Fly."
No, not the answer.
This monster you could kill with
a vanish spell... Did you draw him?
I did.
I thought it'd make the test
a little easier with pictures.
You sure draw funny pictures.
Sorry. I'm terrible at drawing,
so it's probably hard to understand.
I know! What if I draw you
the pictures for our next test?
I'll draw something really cool!
Sure!
Hey, Mio!
Get this! My picture's
gonna be on our next test!
Really? Why?
The teacher said she'd let me do it.
I bet if you draw one now,
we might even have room for yours.
What's the point if I don't know for sure?
Huh? You're not drawing anything?
No, I don't think so. I'll pass.
I've got to return this anyway.
Oh, really?
All right! Lemme doodle a cool-looking guy.
Du-doodle-du, doodle-du-du...
Du-du-du-du-doodle-du...
What do you think about this?
Wow! He's so cool!
You're so good at drawing, Aioi! I'm impressed!
Well, I'm not that good.
Shoot, maybe I am.
By the way, his name is George Samidare.
Wow! He's getting cooler by the minute!
You call that cool?!
Hold on, you guys.
Usually when you think of cool...
"So edgy" Something like this!
Wow, amazing!
It's looks just like a manga!
Do you draw your own manga, Naganohara?
Well, uh... Just a little.
Amazing! You should show me sometime!
I don't know about that...
No? You won't?
I'd really like to see it.
Eh? Uh, but...
Hand it over!
My version is way cooler.
"So edgy"
You copied me!
I did not.
You sure did!
A copy is like paying homage.
So now you admit it!
Wow! So cool!
Will anything impress you?!
Then how about some of this?
--Glasses!
--Part of the face.
--Girls of all types can't resist
the smart and cool image!
Oh. Glasses, is it?
Are his eyes bad?
He should have worn contacts.
These two don't understand anything!
Then how about I do this?
They're hanging under his ears!
And you totally copied me!
Tsk-tsk-tsk. They're sunglasses.
Wow! So cool!
You're so biased!
How about this?!
A butler! He'll welcome you home
and serve you tea!
Your wish is his command!
The magic of Darjeeling Tea can be yours!
Glasses again? Sorry, I just don't get it.
You should have taken the hint about contacts.
Mio, you're so out of the loop.
You know, being cool is all about...
Scribble, scribble, scribble, scribble...
Like this.
It's floating!
Wait! Hold on a second!
He's actually driving?!
Wow! He's so fast and cool!
You've gotta be kidding me!
Being cool is all about...
Really...
If you think about it, really...
Being cool is all about...!
Something like this!
Yo.
Oops...
Just kidding!
Ahaha! I kid!
"Class 1-Q podium"
"Mio Naganohara" "Shipwrecked"
"Word-Time"
I drew this listening to jazz.
"The next day"
Good morning.
Good morning, Ma'am.
Who you calling "Ma'am"?!
I'm handing out the morning quiz,
so pass it behind you.
Oh well.
I hoped to keep it a secret that I drew,
but then I had to go sketch that...
"Quiz"
"Quiz" Then again...
I guess I should be thankful that's
all I drew considering how crazy I went.
Let's just call it a lucky escape.
Though I'm sure I'll get teased
by Yuuko for a couple of days.
No, no... It's okay! I need to be positive!
"Quiz"
"Describe the picture with a word"
No, no... It's okay! I need to be positive!
Yo.
"Poisonous snakes need not rush."
Hurry up, Miss Mio.
Um...
Begin!
Miss Mio!
Wake in the morning, teeth get a brushing
Before you know it, it's ten at night
Another day was full of laughter
Another day filled with joy
Goofing with friends and acting so silly
Making a ruckus and then I see
A glimpse from you and then our eyes meet
Coincidence, or not?
I won't ever admit it's first love
That's not something I would say
Hey, I'll see you again tomorrow too.
When I close my eyes I see
My vision sparkling, filled with you
Wasn't it so much fun today?
Ah, I think I'm in love
I'm so happy I'm so happy
Nice to meet you, awakening love
I'll see you again tomorrow too
Good night
I'll see you again soon in my dreams
Zoom! Yoink!
Bang-bang!
Yo! Nice to meet you.
I'm Onomatopoeia.
"Cock-a-doodle-doo"
just feels so good to say.
Is it actually English?
"Narration: Rikiya Koyama"
The next My Ordinary Life is Episode 6.
Look forward to it!