"Twice-cooked pork"
Thanks for waiting.
I can't really make anything other than this.
Here.
Wow, awesome! Twice-cooked pork!
I was getting hungry so this is great!
It's got my secret flavoring in it, too.
Can you tell what it is?
It must be pretty authentic
if it's got secret flavoring.
Thanks for the meal!
Hmm. I can't taste anything but miso.
It's like she didn't even try to make it subtle.
No... So much for secret flavoring.
It's so strong, it gets worse with every bite.
This isn't authentic...
It's the opposite!
I realized just this very moment
I think I might have fallen in love
24 hours a day of you you you
I can't get you out of my head!
Something (something) feels different now
With you (together) it's awkward conversation
Is it (mutual love) no it's one-sided love
Uh-oh I think our eyes just met!
What is this anxious nervous feeling?
My train of thought is tangled with confusion...
This kind of thing is a first for me
Could it be a fever and I'm sick?
With a sudden twist it's awakened love
There's a fire in my cheeks and my face is all red
Th-Th-This can't be real, my hands are trembling
Is this what people mean when they talk about "love"?
I-I-I'm stuttering non-stop talking to you
Awkward silence and then mumble-mumble-mo
I wanna (I wanna) know how you feel about me
O-O-O-One one-sided love
First love! Every day on the path to school
Sparkle-sparkle dazzling I DO fall in love!
It's like I'm flying through the sky
O-O-O-One one-sided love
"My Ordinary Life 23"
This came out pretty good!
Mio! Mio!
"Handsome, right?"
The heck is this?
A kappa?
Why'd she show me a kappa?
And what's this about handsome?
Though...
It might be a good idea to draw
a fantasy story for my next one.
Daidarabotchi and Kappa... or something.
Kappa, hmm... He'd be the bottom.
Kappa. Kappa, eh?
Kappa. Kappa-pa.
Pa... Pa... Parasite.
Whatever. Might as well turn
this into picture shiritori.
Yuuko.
Cool, thanks.
Parashite?
Is that what a parashite looks like?
Does this arrow mean what I think?
She's challenging me to
a game of picture shiritori!
That's totally fine by me.
Hmm, parashite. Te... te... Got it.
It's huge!
And a tengu? Maybe I confused her
by writing "parasite" in English.
Whatever. Tengu it is.
Tengu. Gu... gu... gu... gu.
Gah! You've gotta be kidding me!
Tengo!
What the hell is a tengo?! A tengo?!
No! It has to be on purpose!
No high schooler could make
a mistake that terrible.
I mean, she drew a tengu and
wrote the letters as extra.
I don't get it...
This really bugs me, but it's too late now...
I'll just stick with "Go."
Here.
"Draw smaller!!"
What's with this casual Goku?
Eh? Huh? Goku?
Wasn't the last picture I drew a tengu?
Well, I guess I can see why
you'd mistake "Gu" for "Go."
I'll harass a juice out of her later.
Well then... "U," is it?
U... U... Got it!
"Draw smaller!!"
"I suuuuck at drawing!!"
Eel? No... Rabbit?
It's a cow?!
This cow looks like bull crap!
Here.
Ooh! She wrote shita for "tongue"?
Then... It's "Ta," right?
Ta... Ta... Taxi, yeah.
Here.
Wh-Wh-What the heck?!
This isn't a taxi!
It's taxyyyy!
Well, I'll just draw whatever now.
"Shisu"
Oh! She's on top of the industry jargon!
It's really heating up now!
Yeah, yeah, yeah...
Shoot! I'll lose if I go with this!
"Superman"
No... Wait! If I just fix it with this...
Here.
"Supermans"
Eh?
"Superman"
"Go+Soccer Club"
"Go+Soccer Club 3"
Ugh... I'm so bored.
I'm bored, Sekiguchi.
I know, Sekiguchi! Let's play Ready-Set-Go!
We'll start with me.
Ready, set, go!
Two!
Sekiguchi...
It's boring, so play a game with me.
President...
Sekiguchi...
"My Ordinary Life 24"
Forget your homework...
Forced to stand out in the hall.
Mogami River.
Yuuko.
Why do I have to stand in the hallway
just for forgetting my homework?
I'm stuck in the hall.
What to do to pass the time?
Mogami River.
Yuuko.
Wh-Whoa! Guys...
Deer! Deer!
Wh-What's the Principal doing to the deer?!
P-Principal! D-Deer!
Principal!
G-Guys! The Principal! In trouble!
What's that?! A deer biscuit?!
G-Guys! The Principal! A-A deer...
He's getting up...
He climbed it...!
He jumped...!
And fell straight down...!
He's climbing again...?!
He climbed down...!
A-A stalemate?!
Principal!
Principal...!
G-Guys! Death! The Principal! Death!
H-He stood up!
Eh?!
Wha--? Uh, eh...
Ehh?!
G-Guys! Get this!
Uh... Um...
P-Pr...
Pr...
The hallway is perfectly normal!
These words came straight from her heart.
Not to cover for the Principal, and not even
because it would be a pain to explain.
No, that is not why.
It was perhaps, to give respect to those
brave fighters who fought for their lives.
Early summer rain,
pours down and speeds the waters.
Mogami River.
What's it even mean?
"10-yen Soccer"
Sweet! Let's do this!
Mio can be the referee.
You don't need a ref in 10-yen soccer.
Tsk, tsk, tsk.
You're missing the point.
It's all about the mood!
Game time! Kick-off!
Whatever.
Bring it on!
Okay...
First comes rock, then your hand delivers...
What's it gonna be, no cheats!
Rock-paper-scissors!
Sa...
Chomp!
Sarang hae yo!
[Korean for "I love you!"]
"Shinonome Lab"
"My Ordinary Life 25"
What should I do?
There's a cockroach...
...under this cup!
I must... I must proceed carefully.
This evil incarnate must never
torment this household again.
I need a plan... A master plan!
Insect spray!
"Rorin" Insect spray!
That won't work.
It won't kill instantly,
so it might even be able to run away.
But even worse...
I don't want to see it squirming!
I know! What about dish soap?!
"Papa" "Lemon"
If I spread it on the table
and trap its movement,
I could go straight for the finishing blow!
I-It's jumping!
Cornered creatures fight for their lives!
It might even leap up in desperation!
What if... it gets on me?!
No! What if gets on my face?!
No... Wait!
What if it jumps in my mouth?!
If that thing... gets in my mouth!
It'll be rock and roll!
It's the final gig. It's show time!
There's only two outcomes
once I pull away this cup...
Kill or be killed.
I...
"Trash" I...
"Trash" I might just have to...
What are you doing?
S-Sakamoto!
Please help me!
U-Underneath this cup is a co... a co...
What?
Let me guess--a cockroach?
You're so hopeless.
All right. Leave it to me.
You're a savior!
Hey.
Yes?
What are you doing?
I'll get it, so lift up the cup.
Yes?
Uh, like I was saying...
Lift up the cup. I can't get it if you don't.
Hey!
Wh-What are you saying?!
I can't break the seal of this evil incarnate!
It's Pandora's Box!
To open it is to kill or be killed!
What the heck? How can I do
anything if you don't lift it?
Lift it yourself!
As if I could!
Wh-What to do...
Sakamoto already ran off...
Nano!
What do we have for snacks?
Good timing!
Hakase seems to be fine with bugs, so maybe...
Hakase! Inside this cup is a cockroach!
I-I'd be so grateful if you dealt with it for me!
Sure!
R-R-R-Rock and Roll!
S-Sorry. Then, please...
Okay!
I'll get the bugger in one hit!
Head!
I missed.
A-And here I am, genuinely in distress.
And yet, she... And yet, she...!
Geez! I hate you, Hakase!
T-Tears?
N-No, I'm just kidding!
You really believe that?
There's no way I could ever hate you!
Hakase... I love you!
Nano!
Oh, silly Hakase!
It's time for rock and roll!
"Counting to 10"
Hey, it's hot so can I get out?
Huh? But you only just came in.
But now I'm too hot.
Well, you can get out once you count to ten.
Twenty times log square root of ten!
Huh?
That's ten, so can I get out?
Uh, uh...
One... Two... Like that, okay?
Aww...
"Go+Soccer Club 4"
What the heck? I can't believe
everyone left for cram school.
Aren't you bored, too, Sekiguchi?
Huh? Aren't you supposed
to be at cram school, too?
Seriously?!
"My Ordinary Life 26"
Yum!
Yuuko? How's the curry coming?
Good! It'll be done in a sec.
I'm practically starving over here.
Yeah, me, too.
How about you, Mai?
I sense a big one.
Oh!
Can't wait for the feast.
Sweet! It's looking good...
Oof!
The wait is over!
Scrumptious super curry has arrived!
The final form of taste!
It'll take a little longer over here.
I should have prepped
before we started the curry.
Oh well. The meal's not done until it's done.
Shoot! We should have
brought some mayonnaise!
It tastes so good together with curry.
M-Mayo... Ma...
Yuuko, what do you think?
Just kidding!
Uh, no... It's not...
Th-This isn't what you think...
L-Look! We still have jelly noodles!
J-Jelly noodles, see...?
Your blood...
Mi-Mio?!
Your blood!
What color is your blood?!
I'm so sorry, Mai!
We don't have rice and curry for lunch anymore!
Mai?
We do have jelly noodles though...
Mai!
Release...
Well then...
Here's our one serving of jelly noodles.
We only have one?!
I was thinking of passing it around to eat.
But, Mio and I are the ones who screwed up.
So Mai gets to go first.
Rock-paper-scissors!
--Yes!
--Gah!
You better not try to eat it all in one bite!
Don't be ridiculous.
I'd never do something that evil.
Well, I guess I'll dig in first.
I kinda choked...
"Grumble"
I know! Let's play cards!
Or not!
At this rate, our whole trip
will be down the drain.
At least we could play cards
and make it a happy ending!
I got it!
Yeah? What?
I almost forgot.
In times like this, adults like to drink.
Y-Yeah they do.
Isn't that right, Mai?
Actually, I brought some of my own, too.
S-Seriously? Mio?
You bet I'm serious.
Rebel! We have a rebel here!
"Vinegar" Ta-da!
I-I don't care anymore!
Don't do it, Mio! You'll die!
Mai still has some left!
This... It's cider.
"Mogami River"
"Cider" This... It's cider.
Wake in the morning, teeth get a brushing
Before you know it, it's ten at night
Another day was full of laughter
Another day filled with joy
Goofing with friends and acting so silly
Making a ruckus and then I see
A glimpse from you and then our eyes meet
Coincidence, or not?
I won't ever admit it's first love
That's not something I would say
Hey, I'll see you again tomorrow too.
When I close my eyes I see
My vision sparkling, filled with you
Wasn't it so much fun today?
Ah, I think I'm in love
I'm so happy I'm so happy
Nice to meet you, awakening love
I'll see you again tomorrow too
Good night
I'll see you again soon in my dreams
"Word-Time"
Out from the bath, have some milk.
Pretend that you're drunk.
I'm Peso!
Ten-yen here!
I'm Wado-kaichin.
No, no! Don't judge people by their worth!
"Narration: Fumihiko Tachiki"
The next My Ordinary Life is Episode 7.
Look forward to it!