"Language"
All right! With that, test time is over.
Yay!
Oh? What a celebration.
It just shows how hard they
must have worked to pass this test.
How touching it is.
That test was as hard as
rock-paper-scissors!
What kind of rock-paper-scissors is that?!
It's a dream! This is like a dream!
It's over! It's all over now!
My parents are sending
each one of us a bag of rice!
Hail the rice vendor!
We're getting married!
Wow!
Come on! Everyone help! Ready, set!
What are you doing to me?!
I realized just this very moment
I think I might have fallen in love
24 hours a day of you you you
I can't get you out of my head!
Something (something) feels different now
With you (together) it's awkward conversation
Is it (mutual love) no it's one-sided love
Uh-oh I think our eyes just met!
What is this anxious nervous feeling?
My train of thought is tangled with confusion...
This kind of thing is a first for me
Could it be a fever and I'm sick?
With a sudden twist it's awakened love
There's a fire in my cheeks and my face is all red
Th-Th-This can't be real, my hands are trembling
Is this what people mean when they talk about "love"?
I-I-I'm stuttering non-stop talking to you
Awkward silence and then mumble-mumble-mo
I wanna (I wanna) know how you feel about me
O-O-O-One one-sided love
First love! Every day on the path to school
Sparkle-sparkle dazzling I DO fall in love!
It's like I'm flying through the sky
O-O-O-One one-sided love
Oh, Mio.
Morning.
"My Ordinary Life 35" Morning.
"My Ordinary Life 35"
Eh?! No, no, no, no!
Hey, hey, hey, hey!
Eh? Wha-- Not even a "What's with that outfit?"
Sheesh. Are you still mad at me?
For putting that chess piece
in your mont blanc...
"Knight"
For putting that chess piece
in your mont blanc...
Well, it's not like I couldn't eat it
anymore, so it wasn't that bad.
Said... no one ever!
I was looking forward so much to
that mont blanc! And then that? Why?!
I don't get it! Why stick a knight in my food?!
I dunno. It seemed like a cool idea.
Head!
As usual, she can't take a joke.
"Meat Miso" Stupid sister.
"Meat Miso"
They only make ten of those mont blanc a day.
She has no idea and yet always
pulls pranks like this.
My sister is in college, for crying out loud.
She needs to understand when enough is enough.
Though in today's case, I actually feel generous
enough to overlook my sister's terrible crime.
"Kimuchi Ramen"
That's because I secretly hid in the fridge one
of five special shortcakes made every day, so--
What?!
"King"
Checkmate!
Habu! Habu! Habu! Habu!
Strawberry!
The one thing I've been looking forward to
since last night! My one in five!
My... My...!
"Tofu"
Strawberry!
My strawberry!
Where's the sweet that's
supposed to go right here?!
Namu... [Sanskrit for adoration]
Stomach!
You stupid sister!
A cake without strawberries
is no better than bread!
It's just a sweet-tasting bread now!
♪ Happy birthday to me... ♪
♪ Happy birthday to Yoshino... ♪
"King"
♪ Happy birthday to me... ♪
"King" "Happy Birthday!!!"
Sis...
Mio.
It's not your birthday today!
"Faculty Room"
"Quiz" "Faculty Room"
"Udon & Soba Restaurant"
"My Ordinary Life 36"
I've always wanted to come try this place.
You said you saw it in a magazine?
Yeah, yeah. I even got a coupon for it.
You don't have to show it now.
I'm having Herring Soba.
Oh? Even in this heat?
--You connoisseur...
--Without the herring.
That's just regular soba!
What about you, Mio?
I think I'll stick with Zaru Soba.
That's so safe. Totally something
an amateur would pick.
That's fine with me. What about you?
I think the Summer Veggie Tempura Special.
A daring rice choice at a soba restaurant. Yeah?
That sounds cool.
Doesn't it?
It's a seasonal item, too.
If I miss it now,
who knows when it'll come again?
Once every year, right?
No, no, no. You've gotta dream
bigger than that, Mio.
What matters most is this moment. Now!
Oh, really?
Well, you're still too young to understand.
Yeah, yeah.
Excuse me!
May I take your order?
One Herring Soba, one Zaru Soba, and...
One Summer Veggie Tempura Special...
Herring Soba, Zaru Soba, and
Summer Veggie Tempura Special, correct?
Please wait while I put in the order.
I heard they make the soba noodles
by hand at this place.
Now that's what I call authentic.
I wonder what this buckwheat dumpling is?
They take the soba flour
and make it all squishy.
Wow, really?
Thank you for waiting.
This is the Herring Soba...
...and the Zaru Soba.
I don't care if you go ahead and eat without me.
Sorry.
Before it gets cold.
But it's cold to begin with.
It must be because mine's
on the seasonal menu.
They're taking extra time to make it delicious!
Yours is sure taking long, Yuuko.
Maybe frying the tempura is holding it back.
They're probably out picking
my fresh summer veggies!
Shoot! Well, no wonder it's taking so long.
I guess you can even order food
other than meals here.
Really?
Me?
Guess not.
That's a bummer.
Goddamn!
Y-Yuuko! Calm down!
Like I can! This is insanely slow!
I don't care if this place is famous!
Even if they capture the flavor,
they can't capture my heart!
You're not making any sense!
I'm gonna give them hell!
Thank you for waiting.
Do you know how long I've wait--
Thanks.
You can read a magazine
or something. I'll be done soon.
Things that are cool!
A child chess player!
"My Ordinary Life 37"
My repellent and vapor should work okay.
I thought they'd be gone by now.
They won't leave in
the late night, Mogami River.
Even a bug has a life to live.
I'll return to my peaceful sleep.
I've got you now!
Yay!
Chest!
I have taken a precious life.
I hit! And I hit!
Every year it's always the same!
I just don't know what to do anymore!
Mom! This house... It's no good!
We'll just have to move!
Idiot! Do you know what time it is?!
Be quiet and sleep!
Helvetica Standard.
Try saying "chirashizushi."
Tsurasuzusu.
No!
Chi-ra-shi-zu-shi!
Try!
Tsu-ra-su-zu-su.
No, no!
Chi.
Chi...
Ra.
Ra...
Shi.
Shi...
Zu.
Shi.
Yes!
Chirashizushi.
Try!
Tsurasuzusu.
"Refrain"
"No Fan Voice"
"Shinonome Lab"
"My Ordinary Life 38"
Sakamoto! Look, look!
"Winner"
My winner is on the bottom!
Hmm?
What do you mean by "hmm"?!
You shouldn't be eating those things.
What do you mean by "those things"?!
You won't have room to eat your supper.
Omurice!
Who gets that excited over
a popsicle stick winner?
You're such a child.
It's not just a regular winner!
It's super rare to be written on the bottom!
It's the same whether
it's on the top or bottom.
You'd find out after a bite or two anyways.
Sheesh. You kids are so easy to please.
You get all excited over nothing.
Wha-- It's a crab!
It's super rare to see something like this!
I think I'll save the best for last!
Thanks for the meal.
Hmm? You've barely touched
your meal, Hakase.
Don't tell me you ate
more snacks after lunch?
Sorry...
My goodness! Just how many
snacks did you eat?!
All of them...
All of them?! You ate
a whole month worth of snacks?!
I'm not impressed!
My goodness...
It's 'cuz Sakamoto told me to!
Sakamoto!
Sakamoto said food spoils fast in summer.
That has nothing to do with this.
Snacks go to a different stomach!
You sound like a middle-age woman!
Sakamoto!
Why do you believe her?
I'm completely innocent! This is so
black-and-white, and I'm white!
But you're black.
You are.
Gah! I was born this way!
Enough. There's no point in arguing anymore.
So instead, Hakase won't be
getting her strawberry juice.
I won't eat anymore snacks!
I said no.
I'll give you the winning popsicle stick!
I don't want it.
I'll eat all my vegetables!
You better!
I'll take off your key...
Eh?!
"Strawberry"
I-I'll let it slide this once.
Next time, you'll get no snacks for a month.
Okay!
Then...
It's like, if I give it to her now,
nothing will come of it!
You'll get the strawberry juice
after you take out the key.
Then turn your back.
Okay!
"Loser Gah!
Your right hand is a loser.
How do you come up with these ideas?!
I'm not impressed!
You need to stop doing things like that.
So please at least think about
the consequences of your--
You're not listening!
"A Trivial Miracle"
Rock-paper-scissors!
Mine!
"Word-Time"
If you look hard enough,
you can find anything.
Oh, Mio!
It's good you're here.
What is it, Sis?
Something urgent came up for me.
It'd be great if you could take my place
helping the neighborhood association.
Eh? You should be asking Mom, not me.
She's busy doing sepak takraw
with some friends.
Besides, you'll get 10,000 yen for helping.
I'm counting on you!
"Daifuku Fair"
I guess I could use the money.
I'm not doing anything anyhow.
Might as well go.
Think I should try a mohawk fade with a wig?
"My Ordinary Life 39"
Check it out! That's so cute.
I-I was tricked!
This stinks! What the heck? What am I doing?
Why do I have to put up with this?
--Plump and white! Delicious! Come and get 'em!
--This was the association's big plan?
To sell daifuku with just
two people on the street?
This is embarrassing!
This is way too embarrassing!
Everyone's staring at me like I'm an idiot!
It's my job to draw people in with this
Daifuku-Dude costume, their mascot character!
But there's no eyes and not even
a mouth! Just a big, white face!
How is this even a Daifuku-Dude?
It's just a giant daifuku!
But wait... This Daifuku Fair...
...isn't even a fair!
Sorry--
This is totally out.
Hey, what's that? It's disgusting!
Take this!
Stop it! It hurts, so cut it out!
Q-Quit it! Th-The bottom has no padding!
It's not padded! Hey! Stop it!
Get lost!
She's mad! Let's go!
What a freak!
Give me a break...
Gah! Yuuko!
Stop tarnishing the daifuku image.
I can't watch this anymore.
Hurry up and take this off.
Useless part-timers...
Don't just stand there.
Go and work behind the counter.
Got it?
Yeah.
This is all for 10,000 yen.
I've gotta hang in there.
♪ Tokachi! Azuki beans! ♪
I want to leave.
♪ Wasanbon sugar! ♪
I miss my home...
Will these even sell?
They are lined up pretty nice.
Excuse me.
How much for one?
A customer!
Um...
I wonder what they sell for...
Sorry. How much were these daifuku--
What's wrong with wasanbon sugar?
I won't run! A strawberry can't run away!
Uh, um...
You can have it for free.
Cool! Lucky!
Wake in the morning, teeth get a brushing
Before you know it, it's ten at night
Another day was full of laughter
Another day filled with joy
Goofing with friends and acting so silly
Making a ruckus and then I see
A glimpse from you and then our eyes meet
Coincidence, or not?
I won't ever admit it's first love
That's not something I would say
Hey, I'll see you again tomorrow too.
When I close my eyes I see
My vision sparkling, filled with you
Wasn't it so much fun today?
Ah, I think I'm in love
I'm so happy I'm so happy
Nice to meet you, awakening love
I'll see you again tomorrow too
Good night
I'll see you again soon in my dreams
"Mosquito"
It's another peaceful day
at the Shinonome household.
Greetings! I'm the King!
Think of chess, you think Habu!
Think of Habu, you think mongoose!
Now I'm dying to go on a trip to Okinawa!
It'll be all right!
"Narration: Aya Hirano"
The next My Ordinary Life is Episode 10.
Look forward to it!