At last, the decennial combat
festival known as the
"Grand Fighting Tournament" has
reached its exciting conclusion!
Could a Human bring home the gold
for the first time in 150 years?!
If I win this thing now...
We... Luvellia-senpai and I...
Somewhere out there, in a faraway land...
A martial arts competition to decide the strongest
man on the planet was underway.
To the victor of said competition
goes fame and glory.
In turn, he will become the object
of international intrigue.
Your new champion is...
The representative of the
Yakeppachi Warriors Guild:
Peter Grill!
Indeed.
Peter Grill knew not of what
the future had in store...
Nor the terror that lay ahead...
Episode 1: Peter Grill and the Ogre Sisters
Yo, Peter!
What happened to meetin' up at the bar?!
Gotta hurry...
I can't wait to celebrate with her...!
Senpai...
Senpai!
Oh, it's you, Mimi.
Major congrats on your win!
As a fellow guild member,
I couldn't be more proud!
Huh, looks like I'm the
first one to show up...
Hm? What do you mean?
Well, y'see...
Now that you're officially the
strongest man on the planet,
I've got a favor to ask...
Not sure what you're gettin' at...
But since I'm in a good mood,
go ahead and lay it on me!
Aw, thanks! Much appreciation!
So, I was thinking...
Hm...?
Lemme get your junk spunk!
Are you CRAZY?! What are you talking about?!
Oopsie... Did I say something
I wasn't supposed to...?
For us Ogres, producing strong
offspring is a pretty big deal...
And in terms of breeding partners,
a champion like you...
Ogre-based logic isn't gonna fly around here!
I'm sorry!
I forgot the Human Realm has
rules for this sorta stuff...
Jeez...
-Y'see, it hasn't been very
long since I moved here...
-She's not a bad kid.
-Y'see, it hasn't been very long since I moved here...
But the weirdest crap comes flyin'
outta her mouth sometimes...
'Kay! I understand now, Senpai!
Would you...
-Please consider having sex with me?!
-You obviously don't understand a damn thing!
Enough of your foolishness!
B-Big Sis?!
Oh, Lisa!
Talk some sense into her, would you?!
Mimi, I insist you cease
this behavior immediately.
-For I shall be the one to
partake in this man's loins!
-You, too...?!
-For I shall be the one to partake in this man's loins!
A close call, indeed.
At this precise moment,
countless nations are beginning
the race to obtain your sperm.
As an Ogre of the fairer sex,
I cannot allow such a thing to happen!
History has proven time and again...
The blood of the most powerful
warriors belongs to OGRES!
Unbelievable...
Come along, Peter Grill...
You get the picture, so
no puttin' up a fight!
Seriously?!
This can't be happening!
What...? What is it?
I refuse to be your studhorse!
Peter Grill!
On my pride as an Ogre...
I shall NEVER let you slip through my grasp!
...yeah!
Forget them... There's
no time to waste, Peter!
Go... Quickly!
Take your place by her side...!
Luvellia-senpai!
Hello, Peter-kun.
I've been waiting for you.
I finally did it.
And now... Now we're home free!
Indeed.
He may be stubborn,
but with such an impressive
victory under your belt,
my father HAS to give us his blessing.
Once we're married...
All that's left is to have a child
and carry on the family name.
Uh... Just checking, but...
Could you remind me how babies are made?
Not this again...
Despite what you think, I'm
not COMPLETELY oblivious.
Pay attention. I won't spare you the details:
When two people who love
each other pray to the heavens,
the stork carries their
child to a cabbage patch.
It's the miracle of life!
So innocent...!
I can't help but feel
that's the REAL miracle...
It's been two years since
Senpai and I started dating.
Thanks to the Guildmaster's overprotective
personality and brainwashing methods,
the most we've ever done is hold hands!
If we get married like this, I'm screwed...
Come on!
Why don't we say a prayer
together, Peter-kun?
Sure...
What a day...
I'm glad I won the tournament,
but now I've got all sorts of problems...
Goof juice...!
There's no use dwelling on it...
Ta-da! Guess who?!
Make a woman outta me, Senpai!
Go away!
-Wait, Senpai! Please open
the door! C'mon, Senpai!
-Have these Ogres no sense of decency?!
-Wait, Senpai! Please open the door! C'mon, Senpai!
It seems the two of us are finally alone...
Open up, Peter Grill!
What EXACTLY are you dissatisfied with?!
Is this about money?! How
much do we gotta pay?!
Shut up and take a hike!
What's all the ruckus...?
No way...
This dude's kickin' out a
couple of naked girls...
Are you serious?!
What an asshole...
Goddammit!
Breathe...
At this rate, you're gonna
fall into their trap...
I'm happily engaged to Luvellia-senpai...
We are well aware, Peter Grill,
of the fact that your relationship with Luvellia...
...has never gone beyond
holding hands, for example...
Us, on the other hand...
H-hold on...
We can entertain you in ways she
couldn't even begin to imagine...
Knock it off!
What kind of scumbag do you take me for?!
Senpai and I made a
commitment to one another!
Betraying her trust...
It's absolutely unforgiveable!
That's right...
And no Ogre on this planet
can convince me otherwise!
Did you... say something just now?
C-crap... This feeling...
There's someone I care about deeply...!
And yet...
I...
I...!
WHAT HAVE I DONE?!
How could I be so weak...?!
Why...
Why...?!
WHY COULDN'T I KEEP IT IN MY PANTS?!
Peter-kun, are you awake?
I know that voice...!
Oh no...
Dear Sir Peter Grill,
Word on the street is you won the tournament
and got engaged to Luvellia-san.
Episode 2: Peter Grill and
the Future Father-in-Law
Betcha feel like the luckiest
guy alive right now, eh?