Peter-kun...
At long last, I understand
where babies come from.
Luvellia-senpai...
I'm glad to hear you've finally
taken my explanation to heart.
Now, if we're to have a child...
Let us embark upon this journey together...
Peter-kun.
Luvellia-senpai...
You're dead meat...
A-a ghost...?!
Kanzen seijin ni nante nare yashinai
Nanben shippai shite naori mo shinai
Doushiyoumonai shi datte datte muri datta shi
Konna hazu janai tte genjitsutouhi
Mata shinitakunaru konna jibun, iya
Fusagikonde uso o tsuite kizutsuita tte naite
Maigo no kanjou dakishimete nemuttemo
Koukai zenzen zenzen zenzen kienai!
Hitorikiri de kubi shimeai
Kanzen seijin ni nante nare yashinai
itsumo risou ni zasetsu shite
Jibun semeru pose dake totte oyasui
menzai nigirishimete amaeteru
Nanben shippai shite naori mo shinai
Hansei bakari de kawarenakute
Kokorogoroshi yarisugosu owaranai
zange to yuuutsu no yoru
Kanzen na jibun ga dokonimo inai
Saitei na jibun shika mitsukaranai
Wait... you're a thief, aren't you?!
Episode 3: Peter Grill and
Relationships with Elves
Don't put up a fight, you bastard!
C'mere! There's nowhere to run!
What are you doing, you cretin?!
Everything would be fine
if you had stayed asleep!
Why, you...!
Good ol' Peter sure is rowdy tonight...
He drinkin' in his room or somethin'?
Yo, knock-knock!
What're you fussin' around
in the dark for...?
Huh?
A-A girl...?
Release me, you imbecile!
No need to worry!
I'll take this whole thing to the grave.
"Tim Robinson withdraws coolly."
N-No, this isn't what it looks like!
Wait a minute, Tim-kun!
Let me explain...!
Tim-kun...!
Cheatin' on her, eh?
The dude's got balls of steel...
Tim-kun...!
Given the situation,
I suppose I'll have to do
this the old-fashioned way...
My name is Vegan Eldoriel.
I have traveled here as the designated
goodwill ambassador from the land of my brethren.
Elf...
Demi-human...
Female...
Not sure why...
But I've got a VERY bad feeling about this...
Don't tell me she's got the same idea
as those crazy Ogre sisters...!
As for the reason I've traveled here today...
I have come to acquire the
nectar of your nethers!
Goddammit!
At this point I'm afraid to ask...
But why ME, exactly...?
A good question, indeed!
Why would us members of the proud Elven race
require the seed of an inferior Human such as yourself?
The answer, of course, is none other than to save
our beloved village from total annihilation!
A humiliating subject though it may be,
our nation has continually failed to yield sufficient
results at the Grand Fighting Tournament,
an event that celebrates combat prowess!
We're the object of ridicule amongst neighboring
countries who terrorize us with acts of aggression,
and our international reputation
is slowly deteriorating...
Despite taking various countermeasures,
Elves are a physically weak species.
History proves that we aren't
suited for military conquest.
Therein lies MY role!
The Council has chosen to adopt a
resolution stating that we shall aim
to obtain an optimal genetic
specimen from an outside source!
And as the designated goodwill ambassador,
I have been tasked with the responsibility
of bringing back your juices!
Now, with that being said, Peter Grill...
Y-You are welcome to play with me...
As much as you'd like.
Why are these demi-human types completely
incapable of considering MY point of view?!
Is breeding the only thing they care about?!
Look, to be honest with you...
I don't necessarily mind being
approached by cute girls.
Of course not! I mean, who would?!
However...!
I'm sorry.
While I appreciate the offer,
I must respectfully decline!
What...?!
Impossible!
Are you saying a plebeian Human
like you would let the chance
to mate with a member of the
noble Elven race such as I go to waste?!
The superiority complex
is strong with this one...
Pretty typical comin' from an Elf...
Then I shall squeeze every
last drop out of you by force!
Not happening! Just take a look for yourself!
H-How dare you?!
It can't be...
Does my sublime body not arouse
that ugly meatstick of yours?!
How come?!
Why don't you have an erection?!
As long as my heart belongs to another,
the blood in my veins shall refrain
from flowing to my spongy tissues!
No way...
Impotent moron!
How am I supposed to fulfill my
duties as an ambassador now?!
In that case...
You've left me no choice but
to utilize my secret weapon!
Huh?
H-hold on!
What are you doing?!
Go!
Wh-What's with this light...?!
A magic spell?!
The hell'd you do to my crotch?!
It's far too late for
apologies, you imbecile!
The curse I placed upon you is a powerful
type of forbidden sorcery
that's been carefully sealed
away in my homeland for generations!
F-forbidden sorcery?!
Peter Grill.
Allow me to share with you a prediction:
Tomorrow night,
you shall appear before me and drop to your knees,
pleading for mercy in a pitiful voice!
"Please, I'll do anything for
you to sample my man goo!
I'm begging you, please let me bang you!"
That was oddly specific, don't you think?!
Until we meet again...
Fare thee well!
H-Hey, wait!
Well, the light died out...
My junk looks normal, too...
And besides, I've never heard of a spell used
to mess with a man's dangly bits...
That's just silly.
She's bluffing, that's all!
Now then, it's time to get
ready for today's hunt.
I'm itchin' for some action!
According to the villagers,
the creature supposedly emerges around dusk...
Isn't that right?
Lady Luvellia.
Nighttime is nearly upon us.
We'll be in grave danger should the sun set
before we're able to locate the creature's lair.
Perhaps we ought to wait for the
combat unit to arrive and try again
What's wrong?!
L-Lady Luvellia!
The ground...!
Th-This is...!
Peter-san!
Terrible news!
It's Lady Luvellia...!
If you're looking for Senpai,
she should've already left for the hot
springs area as part of the vanguard.
I'm headed out now, myself.
I just received word from our messenger that
she's been ambushed by the creature...
Based on our intel, this is
the creature who attacked her:
The Great Worm Goblin!
Huh?
Oh, my mistake.
Here it is!
S-Seriously...?!
They say it wreaks havoc across the village at sunset,
devouring the men and defiling the women!
Luvellia-senpai...!
Oh, Senpai!
Accursed demon...!
Lady Luvellia, it's too risky!
I shall act as a shield.
Escape while the creature is distracted!
I am a knight...
I cannot in good conscience surrender now!
Let go, you fiend!
Lady Luvellia...!
It's no use...
We can't win!
Save me...
Peter-kun!
Hajimari wa tada no koigokoro
Kizukeba yuiitsumuni no yoridokoro
Onaji toki kizami toshi o torou yo
Korekara wa onegai sa
Stay with me, stay with me
So long time tonari ni ite eikyuu ni
Tatakai no hibi ni tsukaretemo
Ikari no ame ni furaretemo
Nureteshimau naraba mayowazu
Ore ga kawari ni anata no kasa to naru
Samukunai yo tonari ni iru
Tada soredake de
Kimi wa boku no yoridokoro sa
Sono egao ni mata iyasareru
Sekaijuu sagashitemo
Kawari nante inai
Kimi wa boku no yoridokoro sa
Soko ni iru dake de mata mitasareru
Donna ni kizutsuitemo
Kono mi sasage mamoru kara
Dear Sir Peter Grill,
Rumor has it, you set out on a
dangerous hunting mission...
Betcha no monster can hold a candle
to the strongest warrior alive!
Episode 4: Peter Grill and Bathing Etiquette