[theme music playing]
LOVE
YAGAMI
[Soichiro] Light, Ryuzaki has decided
that he'd like you to help
with the investigation.
If you're still interested, then you need
to come here right away.
-[Light] Okay, Dad.
-[Ryuk crunching]
All along I've been trying to find a way
to get involved in the investigation.
But I never thought
they would actually approach me.
Now I'll have access
to classified information about the case,
which means I can learn more
about this other Kira.
I need to figure out
what this impostor is all about
before someone else
on the Task Force beats me to it.
-[L] Thank you, Light.
-Not at all.
After all, I want to catch Kira
as much as you do, Ryuga.
I'll have to ask that you call me
"Ryuzaki" here.
Huh?
I'm Matsui.
I'm Aihara.
And I'm Asahi.
Yes, of course.
Then, perhaps I should call myself
"Light Asahi?"
[L] Yes, please do.
To keep things simple from this point on,
I'll call you "Light."
Okay, let's get down to work.
You can start by looking over
all the information we've collected.
I'd also like you to examine these videos.
They were sent to the TV station
but were never aired.
For security reasons,
you're not permitted to take notes,
and all materials must remain here.
I understand.
We will begin now.
[beeping]
Light...
THE PREVIOUS NIGHT
Well then, we need to ask Light Yagami
to assist us.
However, we cannot tell him
that we're considering the possibility
of a second Kira.
Are you serious? But wouldn't that make
working together a bit difficult?
He's right. Why even bother asking him
to work with us?
[L] Well, I didn't mean indefinitely.
I'm curious to see what his impression
of these tapes will be
prior to knowing ours.
COPY 1
Light's deductive reasoning
is really quite incredible.
He may suspect that these tapes
are the work of a second Kira,
an impostor or copycat
imitating the original.
But the basis for the second Kira theory
is that the victims
of these recent killings
were minor criminals who don't fit
the normal profile.
Without hearing our explanation,
how will Light ever know that?
[L] Yes, but there's more to it than that.
The suspect that we've been pursuing
up until now
has needed both a name and a face
to kill his victims.
But there's something different
happening here.
Recall that Mr. Ukita was killed
the moment he arrived at the station,
and this Kira demanded only
that I appear on TV
but made no request for my name.
This implies that the second Kira
only needs to see a person's face
to kill them.
So, I'll ask Light to look over
all of our information
as well as our video evidence.
If he comes to the conclusion
that there could be a second suspect
then he'd be almost completely cleared
of suspicion in this case.
[Soichiro]
But how will that prove anything?
Logically, if he's really Kira,
he'll want me dead,
seeing as I'm the one leading
the investigation against him right now.
And the ways things are going,
if I comply
with this new subject's demands
and appear on TV in three days,
there's a very good chance I will die.
I can't see the real Kira jeopardizing
such an easy opportunity to get rid of me.
Okay, but are you suggesting
that if my son does not come
to the same conclusion,
there's an even greater chance
that he is guilty?
No. In that case, there will still only be
a five-percent chance.
We'll inform him that we are investigating
the possibility of a copycat
and have him cooperate with us as planned.
[sighs]
[Kira] Now that you've seen
proof of my powers,
you should have no trouble
believing that I am Kira.
-On the designated...
-[Light] This video is so mediocre,
it's making me sick to my stomach.
I don't know,
maybe it's because I'm the real one.
But this is a complete disgrace
to everything Kira stands for.
Something's not right here.
Seems unusual that no one bothered
to explain this video to me.
It's not like them.
Well, in any case,
I'd be stupid to comment on it.
It's probably best if I say nothing.
If I just leave it alone, L dies.
So, what do you make of this, Light?
Have you come to any conclusions?
Hmm?
Damn, it's a test!
It's hard to say for sure
but there might be another person
out there with Kira's power.
With Kira's power?
But what do you mean by that, Light?
At the very least, I'd say this tape
was not created by the Kira
we're familiar with.
It's extremely out of character for him
to use these kinds of victims
for his killings.
And since we've established
that he needs a name and face to kill,
it makes you wonder how he was able
to kill that detective
and those two officers right outside
the television station like that.
It's the same.
That's almost exactly how L...
I mean, Ryuzaki said it.
That was incredible, Light.
Now, any doubts about you
should be resolved.
I think you're exactly right about that.
We also believe that this is the work
of a second Kira.
[Light] I knew it.
So you knew about this all along, Ryuga...
Sorry, Ryuzaki?
Which means this was
just another one of your tests?
It wasn't my intention to test you.
The truth is, if I was the only one
who thought there was a second Kira,
it wouldn't be too convincing.
But the fact that we both came
to the same conclusion
makes the theory
that much more believable.
As expected, you did not disappoint us.
You've been a great help.
It's decided then.
First, we must focus on stopping
this copycat.
From what we've seen,
he sympathizes with the real Kira
but clearly lacks his sophistication.
I think he might even be willing
to obey the original.
[L] If so, we could lure him into a trap
by sending our own message
from the real Kira.
I guess I shouldn't be surprised.
You literally took the words
right out of my mouth.
[L] Oh, and Light...
I would like you to play the part
of the real Kira.
Huh? Me as Kira?
[L] Yes, you're the only one
I can think of
who'd be able
to pull something like this off.
At any rate, we don't have time to waste.
Do you think you could script
a message from Kira
in time for it to be aired
on this evening's national news?
[Ryuk chuckles]
[Light] Damn him.
He must have been planning this
from the beginning.
It's the only reason I'm here.
[Light] Ryuzaki, does this look okay?
I think I managed to make it believable.
I think you've done
an excellent job with this.
However, if we don't omit the part
that says, "You're free to kill L,"
then I'm gonna end up dead.
[chuckles]
Uh, sorry. I guess I got carried away
playing the part.
I figured if I was him,
I'd probably demand that you be killed.
I was improvising.
Feel free to change it
to whatever you like.
Sounds good.
[L] Okay, Aihara, the script is ready.
I'll leave it to you.
[Aihara] All right.
And now, a shocking announcement.
In response to the frightening Kira video
aired on Sakura TV only a few days ago,
an anonymous individual has contacted us
claiming to be the real Kira.
In short, he has demanded of this network,
as well as several others,
that we air the message
you are now about to see.
I would also like to mention that the NPA
has granted us permission
to air this video.
Is this the real Kira?
No one knows for sure.
But we can only hope this video
will provide us
with some much-needed answers.
[distorted voice] I am Kira.
It worked! I knew he'd answer me.
[distorted voice] The true Kira.
The one who was broadcast on Sakura TV
several days ago is a pretender.
A fake.
The purpose of this message is
to communicate my will to this impostor
I have chosen to be lenient with him
for the time being,
only because I believe he wishes
to cooperate with me
in the creation of a new world.
But I want to make it absolutely clear
that the taking of innocent lives
is against my will.
If this person claiming to be me
is truly sympathetic to my cause
and wishes to be of some help,
I ask two things of him:
That he refrain from killing aimlessly
and that he agree to abide
by my basic principles.
[Misa] Yay! Now where is that camcorder?
What are you planning to do?
[Misa] Uh, hello!
Do you really need to ask?
I'm going to reply to him, of course.
SEVERAL DAYS LATER
[Watari] Ryuzaki, we have a reply
from the second Kira.
-What?
-Really?
I'll be bringing over the envelope
and tape that we received,
but in the meantime, I'm streaming a copy
of the video so you can view on your end.
[Second Kira]
Kira, thank you for your reply.
Please do not worry.
I will follow orders and do as you say.
-Wow!
-It worked!
[Light] "I will do as you say," huh?
This guy's gonna be no help at all.
If this fake had any idea
what my wishes were,
he'd insist that L appear on TV
and then kill him anyway.
How could you fall
for something like this?
Damn it!
[Second Kira] I really want to meet you.
-I don't think you have the eyes.
-[Light gasps]
[Second Kira] You don't have to worry.
I would never try to kill you.
That's a promise.
[Light] What the hell is he thinking?
Talking about Shinigami eyes
in a public message like this?
What's this "having the eyes"
supposed to mean?
-Is it a code?
-[L] Yeah.
[Second Kira]
Please tell me how I can meet you
without the police knowing.
You'll think of something.
And when we meet,
we can confirm our identities
by showing our Shinigami to each other.
-[L gasps]
-Shinigami?
[Light] He's a liability.
If I don't do something
about him quickly...
-[L screams]
-What?
[L continues screaming and panting]
[groans]
Ryuzaki!
-Are you all right?
-Shh...
Shinigami?
Am I supposed to believe that?
That Shinigami actually exist?
Shi-- Shinigami?
Am I supposed to believe that?
That Shinigami actually exist?
That's impossible...
Obviously they don't exist.
Yes, that's right, Ryuzaki.
Listen to yourself.
Of course Shinigami don't exist.
[nervous groan]
You're probably right,
but I remember that Kira
had those prisoners write something
suggesting the existence of Shinigami.
So, based on that fact,
perhaps we're dealing
with the same person after all.
That would definitely explain
why we're hearing the same words.
I don't think so, because...
if this was the same person,
it's highly unlikely he would have
responded to our video in the first place.
[Light] And why would he agree
to let L live
after going to all the trouble
of getting him to appear on TV?
The real Kira wants him dead,
so it doesn't make sense.
[Aizawa] Then maybe
there's some other connection
between the real one and this new guy.
They could've already met
and decided to use the word "Shinigami"
as a way to confuse us.
[L] No, I'd say that's unlikely.
Hmm?
[L] It's as Light says.
If the two Kiras were connected,
I don't think the impostor
would be so willing
to give up on his plan to kill me.
All of this suggests to me
that the copycat has his own agenda
and is acting independently of the first.
I believe his actual motivation
is to meet the original.
I think you're right.
He's acting out of an interest in Kira.
The word "Shinigami" could very well be
some reference to their killing power.
Saying we can confirm our identities
by showing our "Shinigami" to each other
probably means that they can confirm
their identities
by somehow demonstrating
their ability to kill.
Yes, that's it.
[L] Based on their messages,
we can assume that the word "Shinigami"
must hold some other meaning
that only the real Kira
and the second Kira are aware of.
Now, we just need to convince this copycat
to tell us what that is.
[Light] So, will you respond
and force him to be more specific?
We have to be careful how we handle this.
We can't make it too obvious
that we're asking.
Otherwise, he'll realize we're not Kira.
[L] No, from now on, it's best
that we leave it up to the two Kiras.
-Huh?
-What do you mean?
[L] I imagine that the second Kira
is probably quite satisfied
with the current situation,
now that he's received
a televised response.
He sent a message to get Kira's attention,
and as far as he knows, he now has it.
Also, there's that word he used,
one that only the two of them
would understand.
We'll arrange to have this reply
broadcast today
on Sakura's six o'clock news.
Naturally, this will be
of interest to Kira,
and he'll be following this exchange
between the copycat
and the one we have invented.
Now, if I were Kira himself,
my priority would be
to prevent this impostor from coming
into contact with the police.
This is good for us, because it means
that the real Kira may feel pressured
to respond this time.
Okay. But let's say
that he doesn't respond.
Then what do we do?
[L] Yes, I've been thinking
about what the second Kira might do
if he gets no response.
For one, he might reveal more information
that he knows Kira wants kept secret.
To pressure him into a meeting.
Of course, that would make Kira nervous.
It could be interesting.
And what would be more interesting
is if Kira sends a message of his own
to prevent this from happening.
Ideally, this could provide us
with the physical evidence we'll need
to build a case against him.
[L] In the meantime,
let's gather all the information we can
on this copycat.
[camera clicking]
[photographer] Oh, that's good.
Yes! Beautiful.
Just like that. Perfect!
I'm telling you,
these are gonna knock 'em dead.
-You look like a little angel, Misa.
-[giggles]
[Misa sighs] Oh, I'm so tired.
That shoot went on forever.
Modeling takes a lot of energy.
[Misa] Hey, Rem.
Huh?
Can I ask you something?
What is it?
Each Shinigami has to have
one Death Note of their own.
For a Shinigami to give a notebook
to a human, he needs to have two.
Ryuk could give a Death Note to Kira,
because he somehow found a way
to sneak an extra one
passed the Shinigami King.
Right.
What about you?
The Shinigami King isn't someone
who is easily fooled.
It doesn't happen often.
Oh! Then how did I get mine?
Let's just say it has
a lot to do with the fact
that I'm one of the few
in the Shinigami Realm
who knows how to kill another of my kind.
That's how I ended up with two.
Oh, I think I get it.
You killed a Shinigami and then
you gave his notebook to me, right?
It's not like that.
I wasn't the one who killed him.
I just happened to be around when he died.
It was coincidence, really.
So, how do you kill a Shinigami?
I have to know.
-Well?
-Never repeat this to anyone.
I learned the only way
to kill a Shinigami...
is to make them fall in love
with a human.
What a beautiful way to kill.
[bones creaking]
[Rem] There once was
a Shinigami named Gelus,
who spent all of his time
watching over a certain human girl.
Gelus wanted nothing more
than to look at her
as she went about her daily life.
[Rem] It's today, isn't it?
Her last day alive?
[Gelus] She looks so full of life.
I wonder, why today?
It's...
[sniffs] It's just not fair.
[Rem] I also wanted to find out
how she was going to die,
so I stayed and watched with him.
It was nighttime
and she was walking alone.
No one else was around.
And then it happened.
A man suddenly appeared
and blocked her path.
He was clearly infatuated with the girl.
I love you more than anyone else
in the world!
I'm always watching you!
I want to protect you forever!
[Rem] She'd never seen the man before,
and, of course, turned him down.
[laughing manically]
[sobbing]
Then, if I can't have you...
I'll kill us both!
[screaming]
Wait. Stop it!
What are you doing?
[Gelus sobbing]
Without even thinking, Gelus did something
that we Shinigami must never do.
[man screaming and gasping for air]
[choking]
[Rem] Gelus used his Death Note
to kill the man instantly,
and, therefore, saved the girl's life.
It was the wrong thing to do.
Shinigami exist only to shorten
and take human lives.
We aren't permitted to undo
that which has been fated.
[Gelus sobbing and groaning]
[exhales]
At that moment,
Gelus became something
which was neither sand nor rust
and disappeared forever.
He died.
The only reminder of his existence
was his Death Note left behind.
The rest of his lifespan
was added to hers.
So, not only had he saved her life,
he'd accidentally extended it
well beyond its natural end.
So, if he'd never fallen in love
with this girl,
he'd probably still be alive today,
wouldn't he?
That's right.
Hmm...
[Misa] I had no idea.
All this time, I thought it was luck.
But it was a Shinigami
who saved my life that day.
Yes.
Gelus loved you enough to die for you.
So that Death Note is now yours to keep.
Hmm.
I see.
For a Shinigami to die,
they have to love a human enough
that they'd prevent their death
from happening.
So, what about you, Rem?
You're not in love with me, are you?
Be honest.
Just forget it.
You really think
you can kill me that easily?
Oops. You saw through that?
[giggles]
I'm so glad.
At least now I have something interesting
to tell Kira.
But I wonder...
Does he know how to K-I-L-L a Shinigami?
I asked him on TV to find a way
for us to meet each other,
but he hasn't replied to me yet.
What's taking him so long?
Maybe I should just send him
another message.
[Light] This isn't good.
I can't allow this Second Kira
to act on his own for much longer.
He's careless, so it's only
a matter of time before he slips up.
And when he does,
the police will be waiting.
With him in custody, they could find out
about the Death Note.
[waiter] Something to start?
[Misa] Hmm, a strawberry sundae, please.
Of course. Be right back.
[sighs] What should I do?
How can I contact the Second Kira
without L noticing anything?
-Here you go. Enjoy.
-Mmm!
I can't wait to meet Kira!
I wonder...
What kind of person are you, impostor?
What kind of person are you, Kira?
Mmm. [giggles]
TO BE CONTINUED
[theme music playing]