[theme music plays]
CONFESSION
[Yagami] Light, there's another message
from the Second Kira.
It was sent to Sakura TV
and we intercepted it.
I'm told it's a video
and a journal this time.
Anyway, I figured I should tell you.
A journal?
What is that idiot up to now?
Why can't he just wait?
He wanted the journal shown on TV?
Yes. This is it.
Hmm...
2006?
These entries are from last year.
Please take a look at the entry
he made on the 30th.
[Light] "Confirmed our Shinigami
at the Tokyo Dome."
This is probably supposed to mean
that he's going to do it on May 30th.
If these were aired on TV,
his intentions would be obvious
to anyone who sees it.
[cackles]
[Light] Besides, he can't see my Shinigami
unless he touches my Death Note.
How's he planning to do that?
22nd - My friend and I showed off
our notebooks in Aoyama.
[Misa] Hey, Rem.
[Rem] Hmm?
[Misa] I forget,
why can't I see my own lifespan
even though I have Shinigami eyes?
MISA AMANE
Do you think you could tell me again?
Humans with Shinigami eyes
only need to know
the lifespan of their victims.
And just as we can't see
the lifespan of others of our kind,
humans who possess a Death Note
cannot see each other's lifespan
-even with the eyes.
-[Misa sighs]
"May 22nd,
my friend and I showed off
our notebooks in Aoyama."
If by "notebooks" he is referring to
our Death Notes,
that's something
that could only be understood by me.
And as for the police,
they'll be distracted by May 30th entry.
"We confirmed our Shinigami
at the baseball game at the Tokyo Dome."
It must have been intended for them.
I'm almost positive
that the real message from this diary
is the one regarding Aoyama.
But if that's the case…
What do you think?
Is it real?
I have to be careful not to say too much.
Better to wait
and hear his opinion first.
At this point in time,
all I can say for sure is
he must be stupid.
Yeah, I agree.
I mean, it's completely obvious he wants
to meet Kira at the home game.
Doesn't he understand what would happen
if we aired this message?
It would create an immediate panic
and the game would have to be canceled.
To be honest, it's so stupid.
[chewing] Mmm.
I'm not even sure
how to deal
with this whole situation anymore.
If we make the diary public,
then we'll be forced to make
some kind of televised announcement
cancelling the game on the 30th.
But if we don't broadcast it,
we can be sure
the Second Kira won't do anything.
Won't cancelling the game make him angry?
There's no telling what he'll do.
Frankly, that's not a big concern.
From what we have witnessed
it's safe to say
the Second Kira admires the real one.
He gave his word to the Kira we invented
that he'd refrain from killing aimlessly.
I'm inclined to believe that.
I say we make it public
and we air an announcement
canceling the game.
At the same time, we'll announce
that on May 30th
we're gonna set up checkpoints
on all roads leading to the Tokyo Dome.
And finally,
we'll send a response
from our invented Kira,
something like "I understand,
and I agree to meet you there."
Ryuzaki, you don't honestly expect
him to go there
if we set up checkpoints
around the Dome, do you?
I don't think that Kira
would even consider it,
but it's possible the other one might.
It all depends on how stupid he really is.
However, assuming he is not
actually the idiot we think he is,
there could be another message
hidden in this diary,
one that's not so obvious.
If there's a message here
written in some code
that only people with this Shinigami power
can understand,
there would be no way for me
to decipher it.
Still, it would only make sense
for us to look into all of the places
that were mentioned in the journal.
Uh, 22nd,
he's meeting a friend in Aoyama.
The 24th,
meeting another friend in Shibuya.
We have to be prepared for the possibility
that all of our efforts will be fruitless.
Let's keep an eye out
for people with notebooks in Aoyama,
and people in clothing stores in Shibuya.
It's as I thought.
If this phony Kira skips up
and gets apprehended,
at the very least
I have to obtain his notebook.
And in the worst-case scenario,
I may end up
having to kill everyone there.
All we can do
is place more surveillance cameras
in Aoyama and Shibuya
in the hopes that we might
capture something.
We should also arrange to have
undercover officers
in both locations on these dates.
I should probably go
to Aoyama and Shibuya
since I blend in with the crowd there,
you know.
[Light] I'll go too.
But Light…
I'll be all right. Don't worry.
Aoyama and Shibuya are places
I'd go anyway.
Not to mention, out of all of us
I'd probably look the most natural
hanging out with Matsui there.
Besides,
the Second Kira would be there
looking for Kira, not for the police.
[Light] Okay, we will talk
more about our trips tomorrow.
[Matsui] Sounds good, Light.
See you tomorrow.
Careful getting home
-[phone ringing]
-[Matsui] Huh?
It never fails.
The second I'm out the door,
my phone starts ringing.
Yes?
[Ryuzaki] It's Ryuzaki.
When you two are working together,
I want you to keep a close eye on Light
the entire time.
And please keep this between you and me.
Uh... sure.
Yeah, I understand.
[sighs]
I guess he still plans
to investigate Light
until the probability that he's Kira
reaches zero.
[Light] I'm home.
Hello, dear. You're back quite late today.
[Light] Yeah.
I'm supposed to keep the fact
that I'm helping
with the Kira investigation a secret.
It's because I was hanging out
with my girlfriend.
Your...
[Sayu squeals] What?
Light, you have a girlfriend now?
What's her name?
It's not that surprising.
I'm 18 and I'm in university now.
Of course I have a girlfriend.
You should look for a boyfriend, Sayu.
Huh? A boyfriend?
What's that supposed to mean?
Light, aren't you going
to have any dinner?
[Light] Actually, I’m still full
from room service at the hotel.
[squeals] I can't believe
you just said that to mum.
So what's this about a hotel?
Sound pretty suspicious.
Okay, Ryuk.
We need to have a little talk.
Oh… Should have known
And I'd appreciate an answer
if you could.
If two Shinigami happen to meet
in the human world,
-are they allowed to speak to each other?
-Hard to say.
As long as I'm attached to a human,
I'd say it's against the rules,
unless I have their permission first.
But there's no laws against it either,
so I guess it's possible
that another Shinigami might talk to me.
So does that mean if this fake Kira's
Shinigami were to see you,
there's a chance he might mention the fact
that you’re with me
and reveal that I'm Kira?
[Ryuk] They probably wouldn't,
but it depends on their personality.
And if this kind of situation did arise,
I can assume that you'll act
the way you normally do?
[Ryuk] Yeah.
Even if I see another human
with a Shinigami,
I'm not gonna tell you.
Well, I definitely think
you've got the right approach.
[Ryuk] Uh… Thanks.
Huh?
There's no way.
Did he really think this far ahead?
What is it?
[Light] Aoyama is a big area.
I was searching
for possible meeting places
when I stumbled upon this...
On the 22nd,
there's a big event going on at the club
in Aoyama called the Note Blue
Aoyama, Blue Mountain.
"Note" and "blue." It's a code.
[Ryuk] Well, well, if you ask me,
that's pretty elaborate.
He might be smarter than I thought...
which means I will have to be
that much more careful from now on.
In any case, this Note Blue place
is definitely worth checking out.
What's the point in going there,
if you don't want him
to find out that you're Kira?
You really think it's worth the risk?
[Matsui] Uh… Excuse me. Light?
So, what's going on here?
Oh, these are some of my friends
from school.
[Matsui] Nice to meet you.
[Light] This is my cousin Taro.
It's his first time ever in Tokyo
and he wants to see Aoyama and Roppongi,
so I figured the least we could do
is show him a good time.
I'm counting on you guys.
Oh, yeah. He also told me
he is looking for a girlfriend.
So, does anyone want to volunteer?
-[laughter]
-Hey, I never said that!
I'm impressed, Light.
I doubt that anyone would ever suspect
that there was a police detective
hanging around with these students.
With all of us walking together like this,
even if Ryuk is seen,
no one would be able to tell
which one of us he's following.
It's also a good defense
against L's surveillance cameras.
Not such a bad way to investigate, really.
I just have to stay relaxed
and keep an eye on the entrance
of the Note Blue when it opens.
Found you!
"Moon" Yagami, is it?
You’re the only one
whose lifespan I can't see.
LIGHT YAGAMI
He's Kira! I can't believe it.
I never thought it would be
this easy to find him.
All right, Rem. Time to go.
Huh? You finally found him
and now you just want to leave?
[girl] Well, I can't go up to him
and say "Hi, Kira.
Nice to meet you.
I'm the one who sent you the messages"
with all these people around.
I know his name now,
so I can easily find out all about him.
After all, it's such a unique name.
Yagami, Light - Birthdate: Feb 28, 1989
Height: 179cm - Weight: 54kg
BLOOD TYPE: A
[Misa] Oh, it's written as "moon,"
but read as "Light."
Light Yagami.
Oh, he sure is amazing.
Look at all this stuff.
He won the national tennis championship
when he was in his second
and third years of junior high.
He gave an address
as the freshman representative
at this year's entrance ceremony
at To-oh University.
I can't find a picture of him,
but there won't be anyone else
with the name like Light Yagami.
Who would have ever thought
that Kira would be so young and handsome.
Everything about him
is better than I imagined.
I can't believe how easy it was
to purchase this information.
The world sure is a scary place.
I even know his home address now!
[Aizawa] So we were there both days.
In Aoyama on the 22nd
and in Shibuya on the 24th.
And we observed nothing of significance
on either occasion.
That leaves us with only
the Dome on the 30th.
[Light] I didn't notice anyone
who looked suspicious at the Note Blue.
Was he serious about the Dome?
[beeping]
[Watari] Ryuzaki, apparently Sakura TV
has just received another message
from the Second Kira.
It was postmarked on the 23rd.
[Second Kira] I am happy to say
that I have found Kira.
To all of the people
at the television station
and the police department,
I want to thank you very much.
[Light] Huh?
I-- I-- Impossible!
Where? In Aoyama?
His Shinigami...
It must have seen Ryuk
and picked me out of the crowd.
No… No, there's no way he could have known
who Ryuk was attached to.
I checked repeatedly
that no one was following me.
If this is true,
the only possible event
that would correspond with this tape
being mailed on the 23rd,
is the entry regarding Aoyama on 22nd.
The only ones from the task force
who went to Aoyama
are Matsuda and Light Yagami.
Is Light really Kira after all?
Still, there's no proof
it even happened in Aoyama.
This is a disaster if he found him.
Yeah.
It most likely means that the two Kiras
are now cooperating with each other
At this point I don't think
we should jump to any conclusions.
The Second Kira is only saying
that he found him, nothing more.
He may not have made contact yet.
[Yagami] Hmm...
Now that's it come to this...
[slurps]
...we have no choice
but to communicate as the police
directly with the Second Kira.
You want to send a message?
Yes.
The police need to reach out
to the copycat and offer him a deal.
We need to negotiate with him
to see if we can get Kira's real name.
[chuckles]
That's the last thing
you wanted to hear, right?
[Light] This isn't good.
I have no idea
how the Fake Kira will react to this,
but I have no means of stopping the police
from sending this message.
[man on TV]
If Kira doesn't yet know your name,
it may not be too late for you,
provided you're willing to cooperate.
Whatever you do, you must not
approach Kira out of curiosity.
Make no mistake.
Kira will kill you if you contact him.
You will used and disposed of.
Consider your own life for a moment.
Yours, like every other life,
has an intrinsic value.
Now is your chance
to right past wrongs
by sharing what you know about Kira.
Only you can help us
bring his reign of terror to an end.
Where are you going?
To introduce myself.
[rings the doorbell]
[Rem] So, this is what you meant.
Oh, could that be your father?
Coming.
Welcome ho--
Hi.
Hello and good evening.
My name is Misa Amane.
I just came by to give Light
an important notebook
he left at school earlier today.
C-- Could you wait here for a second?
[Sayu calls out] Light!
Notebook? Could it be...?
[door closes]
[Misa] Um... Pleased to meet you.
I am Misa Amane.
I thought you might get worried
if you saw the message on TV.
I just couldn't take it anymore,
so I brought this... notebook.
[trembling breath]
A Death Note…
A Shinigami!
She's the Fake Kira.
-Huh?
-[Light] Please, come in.
[Misa] Uh, you're sure it's okay?
Thanks.
[Light] Mom, she came all this way
to return my notebook to me.
Could you make us some tea?
Sure, I don't see why not.
-[Sayu] Huh?
-[Light] Hm?
I already told you about her.
[Sachiko and Sayu] Huh?
[Light] Have a seat.
Oh... Um... thank you.
How did you find me?
Oh… I knew it.
You never made the Shinigami eye deal.
When you have the Shinigami eyes,
like I do,
you can see most people's
name and lifespan just by looking at them.
However, you can't see the lifespan
of any person who possesses a Death Note.
No kidding.
I have to admit, even I wasn't aware
of that little detail.
Well, now you've managed to find me.
But you were careless.
What if you'd been caught by the police?
Then they'd know everything about Kira.
It's all right.
Because the police didn't catch me.
And if I do as you say from now on,
they will never be able to.
So we're safe.
After all, don't you need
someone to see L's name?
If you want, I could be your eyes.
So…
[Light] Yeah?
So what?
Would you please make me your girlfriend?
Huh?
Girlfriend?
Yes.
[Ryuk chuckles]
If she finds out I'm manipulating her
and gets hurt,
she'll probably kill me.
But still...
Impossible.
The day you and I were in Aoyama,
there were three times the usual number
of surveillance cameras around.
Anyone who was in Aoyama on the 22nd
would've definitely been caught on camera.
That includes me.
If you and I were seen together,
it wouldn't look very good.
In fact, even being here together
right now
is a problem.
I wish you'd understand that.
But look.
These are pictures of me
when I went to Aoyama that day.
Well, I'm sure no one
would recognize her from this.
And what about your fingerprints?
All those tapes you sent
to the TV station.
They all had
the same fingerprints on them.
Yeah, but those aren't my fingerprints.
It's not like I do these things
without thinking about them first.
Up until recently
I lived in the Kansai region.
And I had this friend
who was into the occult.
I suggested that we distribute
this fake poltergeist video
I had made
to a bunch of different TV shows,
sort of as a prank.
And she agreed to help me with it.
I had her take care of
all of the dubbing
so my fingerprints
wouldn't be on the tapes.
Then I took them from her,
added the Kira graphic
and recorded the message
with that voice effect.
And this friend you made the tapes with,
where is she now?
Why you're doing this to me?
If you want me to kill her,
just say so and I'll kill her!
If you really still can't trust me...
then here, I'll even let you
hold on to my Death Note.
But you'll just be holding it.
So, I'd still be the rightful owner of it
and that means
I get to keep my Shinigami eyes.
Isn't that right, Rem?
Yes, that's right.
Now, there's no way
I could possibly kill you.
And if I become a burden to you
then you can just kill me, okay?
Why would she go this far?
But you might have removed
several pages from your Death Note.
You could be hiding them somewhere,
for all I know.
Why are you so suspicious of me?
I already told you!
I don't care, even if all you do
is use me.
Believe me.
[Light] How can you say that?
Oh...
Exactly one year ago,
my parents were killed in a robbery.
I was home with them at the time.
It happened right in front of me.
I wanted that man
to pay for what he did.
But the trial dragged on forever.
Opinions started surfacing
that he was being falsely accused.
Then it happened.
Kira punished him
for what he did to my parents.
And that's why Kira means everything.
Kira means everything to me.
All I...
All I wanted was the chance
to meet you one day.
So, I could thank you for what you did.
[Misa sobs]
So, all these irrational moves
they're just he means for her
to meet Kira.
Still, she got around surveillance cameras
with ease
and managed not to leave her fingerprints
on the evidence.
She's not as stupid as I thought.
And she has promised
to obey me from now on.
Huh?
[breath trembling]
I understand.
I can't be your boyfriend, but...
I can act like it.
The lengths you went to meet me,
to be of help to me,
those eyes of yours
that you sacrificed half your life to get,
will become my weapon.
Thank you so much.
I'll try my hardest to make you love me.
I promise.
TO BE CONTINUED
[theme music plays]