[theme music playing]
DECISION
DEATH NOTE
I hereby relinquish ownership
of this Death Note
Take care of her.
You gave your word.
[whimpers quietly]
[moans]
[Misa] Mr. Stalker.
Hello, Mister.
Where are you right now?
Do-- do you think we could stop this game?
-[Matsuda] Huh?
-[Aizawa] "Stalker?"
Where did she get that?
What's with the new attitude
all of a sudden?
Just as I thought.
As long as I still have Ryuk's notebook,
even though I gave up Rem's,
all awareness I have of Rem still remains.
Rem.
The only reason I have to go through
all this trouble
is because you brought another Death Note
to the human world.
Is this really what you want, Light?
Yeah.
Okay. I never thought
the Death Note I gave you
would end up buried and abandoned.
Listen, Ryuk,
for the time being
I'm just hiding it, but...
it stays mine.
Until the next time
you hear me say the following words:
get rid of it.
When I say that,
regardless of the context,
assume that I want to relinquish
ownership of this Death Note.
Got it.
Mr. Stalker, this is illegal.
You have to stop.
Okay. Come on, please.
She's been acting like this
ever since she regained consciousness.
[Matsuda] Seriously.
Does she think she can get out of this
just by playing dumb?
[Misa] Okay. How about this?
You could at least take off my blindfold,
don't you think?
It would be nice to see
what you look like.
Matsuda, call Mogi for me.
Huh?
Just a second.
[phone keys beep]
Here.
Mr. Mogi, when you apprehended Misa Amane,
you made it clear
that she was a suspect. Am I correct?
Yes. Like you told me.
First, I blindfolded her
and covered her mouth.
I... told her we knew
she was the Second Kira.
I made sure that she heard me.
She didn't struggle when I
put the blindfold and handcuffs on her.
It was like... she accepted it.
What if I give you an autograph
or shake your hand?
I know! I can give you
a kiss on the cheek if you want.
Oh, come on. I won't run away. I promise.
We've already made
so much progress with her.
I actually thought she'd crack.
Why is she suddenly talking
about a stalker?
-[L] [modified voice] Misa Amane.
-[Misa] Huh?
What's that, Mr. Stalker?
Are you planning to release me?
[L] [modified voice] Before you
passed out, you barely spoke.
And you even asked me to kill you.
And now you're claiming ignorance?
Hm? I don't understand.
I mean, you're the one who knocked me out
and brought me here, remember?
Wait?
I get it. This is some kind of Misa Amane
interrogation fantasy, right?
Do you know why I'm detaining you here?
You must have some idea.
[Misa] What do you mean?
Because I'm a celebrity, obviously.
But you’re definitely the first stalker
who's ever gone this far.
And you're starting to scare me.
Hey, Amane, no one is buying this!
So, cut it out!
Oh. This is scary. What's going on?
I can't stand it anymore!
Please, let me go!
You have to me go!
Oh, I need to go to the bathroom.
I have to go to the bathroom again! Okay?
[L] [modified voice]
It's only been four minutes
since you last went to the bathroom.
I'm afraid, you'll have to hold it.
You have to!
It's the only time you'll untie me
and let me move!
Plus, you'll be able to watch.
Isn't that what you want, isn't it?
You pervert!
I'm a... pervert?
Amane, let's get back to the conversation
we were having
before you lost consciousness.
First of all,
do you know who Light Yagami is?
And if so, why did you approach him?
Huh?
What do you mean?
How can I not know my own boyfriend?
[L] She was so tight-lipped
about it earlier,
but now she's openly admitting
he's her boyfriend?
Where is this coming from?
-[phone ringing]
-[L] Huh?
Good timing. It's Light.
Please, turn the video and audio off.
-[Yagami] Yes.
-[phone ringing]
[L] Yes. Yes, I understand.
We will be expecting you in room K2801.
Are you saying my son's coming here?
[footsteps]
Ryuzaki, like I said over the phone,
I could be Kira.
[gasps]
No, Light!
What are you talking about?
Why would you even say
something like that? Why?
[L] There's no real proof
that Light Yagami is Kira,
why come here to announce
that you could be Kira?
It's an act.
There's no "could be" about it.
You are Kira.
What do you hope
to accomplish by this?
Look, Dad, if Ryuzaki is L,
then it's safe to say
that he is the world's best detective.
And right now, he seems pretty sure
that I'm Kira.
We know L's never been wrong before.
Wha-- What are you saying, Light?
Stop this!
[Light] What about that FBI agent,
Raye Penber?
It was me he was investigating
immediately before he died.
And I was in Aoyama on May 22nd.
Also, I'm the first person
in the Kanto region
that Misa, the alleged
Second Kira, approached.
It's all been me.
If I were in L's place, even I
would have come to the same conclusion.
You see, subconsciously I might be Kira.
If that were the case,
I could be him and not even know it.
No, Light.
[L] I see.
So, you're not conscious of it, huh?
I... I'm not sure of anything anymore.
I'd never kill someone, but...
unconsciously, who knows
what I'm capable of?
Another me could be killing people
as I sleep.
I'm afraid that's not possible.
Huh? Not possible? What do you mean?
Well, I never mentioned this to you,
but at one point I had hidden
surveillance cameras
installed in your room for five days.
Cameras?
Yes.
Every single night you slept normally.
Criminals, whose names were broadcast,
were still dying,
even though you would have had no way
of knowing about them.
But this didn't prove your innocence
to me.
All it proved was
that if you were Kira,
no amount of camera surveillance
would reveal that fact.
Wouldn't reveal that fact, huh?
I... don't know. It could be true.
I have to admit,
I've found myself thinking that…
some criminals deserve to die.
If I can think like Kira,
than how can I be sure
that I'm not actually him.
Hold on, Light!
I feel exactly the same way.
I've found myself thinking before
that some people would be better off dead.
But still, that doesn't mean
we're gonna go out and kill people.
Isn't that right?
Besides, criminals were still being killed
even while you had no knowledge of them.
I mean, the surveillance cameras
proved it, didn't they?
Well, no.
Because we were
short of investigators then,
we only watched him while he was at home.
Truth is, we weren't able to watch him
every hour of the day.
It's possible he could've found some way
to kill those criminals
while he wasn't at home.
[L] This was premeditated.
It's no accident you chose to do this now.
Well, what if we incarcerate
you for a while?
Imprison you, like we did Amane.
If criminals whose names were made public,
keep dying,
then it would lead us to think
that you're innocent, right?
Is that how you imagined it?
[Yagami grunts]
[L] Honestly, I don't like the way
that this is going at all.
But what choice do I have?
Let's do it.
[gasps]
I need you to fully restrain Light Yagami
and place him in solitary confinement.
What? You can't!
You want us to confine him? Seriously?
[L] If we're gonna do this,
it has to happen immediately.
From this point on you can't be allowed
to go anywhere where I can't see you.
This is crazy!
There's no way my son could be Kira.
My son is not capable of...
[Light] It's okay, Dad.
Stop this, Light.
Listen.
Something has to be done about this.
As long as I'm having these doubts,
I can't work with you to catch Kira.
But Ryuzaki,
promise me this.
Until you can say
with absolute certainty that I'm not Kira,
you cannot set me free,
no matter what I might say,
or what condition I might be in.
You have my word.
Mr. Yagami, can you come up with some
sort of excuse for Light’s absence,
something to tell your family?
And... please, do it now.
But... this is all so sudden.
What should I say?
And I see no reason
why he should be in prison.
-Let it go, Dad.
-Huh?
If I don't do this,
I won't be able to live with myself.
But son, do you really... mean that?
Yeah.
I believe that by giving up
my very freedom,
I'll defeat this fear
that Kira lurks within me.
[L] Aizawa, please, take him away.
Right.
[prison gates slam]
FIRST DAY IN PRISON
Next, I just have to
get rid of the notebook.
So, I guess apples
are out of the question?
Ryuzaki.
I'd like to request that you take me
off this investigation.
-Chief!
-But why?
I've thought about this and the fact is
that we're holding my son, Light,
as a prime suspect.
Given that, it's not appropriate for me
to be here.
When we spoke earlier,
my feelings got in the way.
It's impossible for me to be objective
in this situation.
I agree with you.
We can't let personal feelings
get in the way.
And in truth... if...
if the task force concludes
that my son is Kira,
I don't know what I'd be capable of.
[L] Yes, I'll agree with you there.
To be honest,
I wondered what you might do.
I believe you'd kill your son
and then yourself.
I'd also agree that it's best
that we don't have you
working here for now.
Ryuzaki!
I will ask that you confine me as well.
At the moment, I'm calm,
but to be honest, I'm not sure
how much more of this I can take.
I thought you might say that,
so I spoke with Watari.
He's made arrangements.
[Matsuda and Aizawa] Huh?
Mm-hm. But your confinement
will be different.
You will keep your cell phone turned on
and maintain regular contact
with family and friends.
You won't tell Light about this.
If he does call you at some point,
he must be made to believe
that you're still at headquarters.
While you are in confinement,
we'll be giving you
continuous updates on the investigation.
so you'll know what's happening.
So, how does that sound to you?
I'm grateful.
Thank you.
THIRD DAY IN PRISON
[Misa] Hey, Mister,
I really wanna take a bath.
I'm pretty sure you already know
where I live, don't you?
Could you bring me some clean clothes?
I didn't think this could get
any more bizarre.
I feel so sorry for the Chief right now.
Ryuzaki, talk to me.
What's happening?
Have any new criminals been identified?
Anyone that Kira would be
likely to target?
If so, has he killed any of them?
In fact, quite a few criminals' names
have been broadcast recently.
But since you've been detained
we haven't had one report
of a criminal being killed by Kira.
Wait, no one's been killed?
Really?
[L] Yes.
I see.
So, it's only a matter of time
before I'm convicted as Kira.
What I wouldn't give for an apple...
[L] What's going on here?
I thought the murders would continue
even after Light was confined.
Instead...
they've stopped completely.
Light asked to be confined
in the first place.
If this continues,
it will only strengthen
the argument that he is Kira.
The only question left
will be whether or not
he was conscious of being Kira.
Does he really think that's gonna work?
That he will be let off the hook,
if he can just prove
he wasn't conscious of being Kira?
It's not like Light Yagami.
No, it's not like Kira.
FIFTH DAY IN PRISON
I can't take this anymore.
If I don't get an apple soon,
I don't know...
In the end, I just have
to get through this.
No matter what.
You know what, Mr. Stalker,
your video won't sell if it's just me
sitting here the whole time.
[L] Mr. Yagami looks pretty bad.
I think he's taking this harder
than Light or Misa.
[Matsuda] What do you expect?
It's been five days
since Light was put in prison.
And look, not a single criminal
whose name has been broadcast was killed.
In these situations
I think the parents must suffer
a lot more than the accused.
[Aizawa] No kidding.
Especially now that we're seeing proof
that Light is Kira.
Mr. Yagami.
What is it? Is it good news?
Is it bad news?
[Matsuda and Aizawa groan]
No. I wanted to tell you
not to worry so much.
It doesn't matter how much time
you devote to worrying about this.
The outcome will be the same.
This could go on for quite some time.
Perhaps you should rest
in a more comfortable place.
Impossible!
What makes you think I care where I am?
It won't change anything.
With the state I'm in now,
this is the best place for me.
And no matter what the results,
when I leave here
it's going to be with my son.
I understand.
SEVENTH DAY IN PRISON
Light, you've only been here
for one week,
but I'm sure it can't be easy.
Are you feeling all right?
[Light] Now, that I've come this far,
I think it's about time.
Yeah, I know I must look
pretty bad in here,
but this useless pride...
I suppose I'll have to...
get rid of it.
Huh?
-[grunts]
-[chains jangling]
Got it.
Later.
[gasps]
Hm?
[Light] Why am I doing this?
I don't belong here.
Ryuzaki.
I realize that I was the one
pushing for confinement
and that I asked you to put me in here.
But I just realized something important.
This whole thing is completely pointless.
-Huh?
-[Light] Because I'm not Kira!
You have to get me out of here!
Hmm...
[L] I can't do that.
I promised you that no matter
what you said, I wouldn't let you out
until I was convinced
that you're not Kira.
Please, L. I wasn’t thinking clearly.
Do you really think
that a serial killer like Kira
could commit those crimes
without being aware of them?
If I have no memory of his crimes,
I'm not him!
I have never been able
to accept this idea
that Kira has been acting
without self-awareness all this time.
But that doesn't change that fact
that all the evidence
points to you being Kira.
Since we imprisoned you,
Kira hasn't committed a single murder.
Listen, just hear me out.
I swear to you, I am not lying.
You have to believe me.
I'm not Kira!
I must have been framed!
That's the only explanation for this.
[L] What's wrong with you, Light Yagami?
What you're saying is completely absurd.
But, for some reason,
it feels believable to me.
[Light] You have to let me out!
We're wasting time!
[L] We can't let you out yet.
[Light] Damn.
Why is this happening?
What the hell is going on?
This isn't like Light at all.
He's contradicting himself.
It doesn't make any sense to me.
We can't release him
now that the murders have stopped.
It doesn't matter what he says.
I mean, even I know that much.
Anyway, I don't care what anyone says,
as far as I'm concerned,
we have all the proof we need.
Light Yagami is Kira
and that's the end of it.
[Matsuda panting]
FIFTEENTH DAY IN PRISON
What's going on?
I just heard two weeks’ worth of criminals
were just murdered all at once!
It happened yesterday!
Yeah, Kira is back.
KIRA STRIKES AGAIN
So, did you guys already tell the Chief?
No, not yet.
Guess what, Chief?
Kira has started killing again!
What?
It looks like Kira was only resting.
But now he has started
punishing criminals again!
[Yagami] Is that true, Matsuda?
Then that means my son...
I shouldn't be happy
that people have been killed but...
at least Light's name
will finally be cleared.
Wait, knowing Ryuzaki,
this won't be enough to clear him.
[Matsuda and Aizawa] Hm?
Well, he's in the gray.
Did you hear what he just said, Chief?
[Yagami] Yeah, it's a hell of a lot better
than being completely guilty.
Thank God.
[Matsuda] I'm sure as grays go,
he's a shade closer to being cleared.
-Let's tell Light!
-[L] Matsuda!
I mean, please don't, Mr. Matsuda.
"Matsuda"?
We shouldn't tell him about this.
But... But why not?
Hello, Light.
[Light] What is it, Ryuzaki?
You've been in here just over two weeks
and not a single new criminal
has been punished.
Now, why make this harder
than it has to be?
Are you ready to confess?
[Light] Don't be ridiculous.
I'm telling you, you're wrong.
I understand why you feel that way.
But even if the evidence does point to me,
I swear to you this is a set up!
I'm not Kira!
Zoom in on me, if you want.
Go ahead, look at my eyes!
You tell me,
do these look like the eyes
of someone who's lying?
[L] Amane, are you ready to tell me
who Kira is or not?
What? That again?
I wish I knew but I don't.
Because, if I did,
I'd thank him for punishing
the burglar who killed my parents.
To me, Kira is a hero.
Hm...
I don't understand what's going on here.
TO BE CONTINUED
[theme song playing]