[theme song playing]
[Light] The human whose name
is written in this notebook...
shall die…
-[Takuo laughs] Woo!
-[Lady] Help me!
[Light] Now… what will happen?
TAKUO SHIBUIMARU
ACCIDENTAL DEATH
The Death Note...
It's for real!
[screams]
Any human who's used a Death Note
can neither go to heaven nor hell
for eternity.
[Light] I want the world to know
of my existence.
That there's someone passing
righteous judgement on the wicked!
And I…
I will become the God of this New World!
CONFRONTATION
[teacher] He found himself overwhelmed
with happiness and satisfaction...
[girl] I have no idea what he was thinking
coming to my house,
but I am so through with him.
[boy] Seriously? So, what happened
with your dad after that?
[teacher] Alright then.
-Yagami?
-Huh?
Please recite this line for us.
[Light] Sure.
"Having finally made his dream a reality,
he was overwhelmed.
Both by the magnitude of his achievement,
and by the joy and happiness
that it brought him."
That was very well done,
but I'm not surprised, of course.
Absolutely flawless. Very good.
Well then,
we'll leave it at that for today.
-[chairs scraping]
-[footsteps receding]
[bell ringing]
-[students chatter]
-[Ryuk] I thought it'd never end.
How do you do this every day?
It's so boring here.
Hey, where're you going?
Hey, Light! Are you listening to me?
[quietly] Don't talk to me.
Unlike you, people can still hear me
when I talk out loud.
Heh, well aren't you boring.
Hey, what's up, Light?
-We were just going to head down to the--
-Sorry, I'm a little busy today.
You don't have anything to do.
Aren't you just going to go home
and hang out in your room, as usual?
What are you talking about?
Of course, I have something to do.
Yes, something very important.
[news reporter] There was more violence
across the city today. Another stabbing.
This time at a restaurant in the heart
of the Kabuki-cho district of Shinjuku.
[chomping]
Mm. Hey, Light.
[swallows] I'm talking to you.
[Light] What is it?
[Ryuk] Why are you working so hard?
[Light] I can't afford to waste any time.
I have a very small window
to write names in this notebook.
I only have from when I get
home from school until I go to bed.
I still need to sleep,
so I can maintain my average
Obviously, I can't be sleeping in class.
Plus, there's all the studying at home
and at cram school.
I can't let myself get too tired.
It will start to affect my health
and my mental performance.
If I'm serious
about trying to create an ideal world
that's free from evil
then I need to make the most of my time.
[Sayu] Huh? Weird.
Hey, Light, what's going on?
Why is your door locked?
[Light] It's Sayu.
What is it?
[Sayu] Can you help me with my homework?
Uh, yeah. Okay.
We're doing quadratic equations in math.
Sorry to interrupt.
I know you're studying right now,
but I'm like the only person in my class
who doesn't get this stuff.
Thanks so much!
No problem.
I'd be careful if I were you.
If anyone else touches that notebook
you've got hidden in the drawer right now,
they'll be able to see me too.
Huh?
He waits till now to mention
that important detail?
Damn Shinigami.
What's wrong? Are you alright?
[Light] Hm? It's nothing.
So, what exactly don't you understand?
What are you stuck on?
[Sayu] Um… well…
I think all of it.
[delegate 1] There have been 52 deaths
that we're aware of,
and that's just in the past week.
[delegate 2] Every single one of them
involved a heart attack.
[delegate 1] They were all criminals
who were either being held in prison
or who were wanted by police
for outstanding crimes.
And I think it's safe to say
there are other criminals
whose deaths are unaccounted for.
In which case the death toll
could be well over 100.
Uh… morning, Chief.
They started the meeting without you.
That's fine. I had to take an urgent call
from headquarters.
At any rate, these were criminals
who were probably
facing execution sooner or later.
Perhaps we shouldn't be--
Why should it matter
if it's a criminal or someone innocent?
Last time I checked,
murder was still murder!
It's still too early
to consider these a homicide.
Then how did all these people have
heart attacks at the exact same time?
That's not coincidence, it's murder!
You think it's possible
to simultaneously kill all these people
in different locations?
We're treating this as
an elaborate murder plot
that's been carried out by
a large organization.
If it is a large organization,
I'm sure I'm not alone
in suspecting the FBI or CIA.
[delegate] I dare you to say that again!
Now, now, this is not the time
to be joking around!
We need to confirm that these
are indeed homicides and not coincidences!
How? Autopsy results show
that in all of these cases, the victims
died of a sudden heart attack.
Investigating a series of heart attacks
is pointless.
I don't see what else we can learn.
Absolutely.
If these people had been shot or stabbed,
at least we'd have something to go on.
If that's the case, it looks as if
we'll have no choice but to bring in L.
[delegates muttering]
Uh, Chief. What's this "L"
they're talking about?
Right, I forgot that it's your first time
at this conference.
We don't know L's real name
or whereabouts.
In fact, we still don't even know
what he looks like.
However, he's managed to solve every case
he's ever taken on.
And he's tackled some of the greatest
mysteries this world has ever known.
He hides in the shadows,
but he's the best of the best.
A last resort. Our trump card.
[delegate] But I've heard this "L"
is extremely arrogant
I understand he'll only take on cases
that he's personally interested in.
That's exactly right!
Besides, we don't even know
how to contact him!
[Watari] L is already on the move.
[Watari] Gentlemen, L has already begun
his investigation into these incidents.
[delegate] Watari?
Huh? Who's that?
That man's the only known person
who can contact L.
Nobody knows his true identity either.
-[murmuring]
-[Watari] Please be silent.
L would now like to address the delegates.
[L, voice altered via voice distorter]
Greetings to all of you at the ICPO.
I am L.
[Ryuk] What are we doing here anyway?
I don't understand why we're
sneaking around this dump. Tell me.
Isn't it obvious? You told me that anyone
who touches the Death Note
will be able to see you.
I can't afford to carry something
this dangerous with me anymore.
Up until now,
I thought that if my family
ever saw the notebook,
I can tell them I was keeping records
of various criminals
in preparation
for becoming a detective one day.
But I'm walking a very fine line
right now.
I don't want to think about it,
but if I make one mistake,
I might end up killing my own family.
[L] The difficulty of this case lies
on its unprecedented scope.
And make no mistake.
We are witnessing an atrocious act
of mass murder,
one that is unforgivable.
This case cannot be solved
without the full cooperation of the ICPO.
That is all of the police organizations
you represent throughout the world.
You need to make the decision to fully
support the investigation at this meeting.
Also...
I require additional cooperation
from Japan's National Police Agency.
Huh?
What? Why Japan in particular?
[L] Whether the guilty party
is an individual or a group,
there's a strong possibility
that they are Japanese.
And even if they are not,
we can be sure they're hiding in Japan.
What is all this based on?
[L] Why Japan, you ask?
I think I will be able to provide you
with proof of that
after I directly confront the culprit.
A direct confrontation?
[L] At any rate, I would like to set up
the investigation headquarters in Japan.
Hmm...
That was easier to make
than I thought it'd be.
Huh?
Does that mean
you were able to hide the notebook?
Yeah. I hid it right here in this drawer.
But it doesn't seem to be
particularly well hidden.
You left the key in the lock.
[Light] And that's the whole point.
I intentionally left the key
in the most noticeable place
I could think of.
Isn't that just a regular diary?
[Light] That's what it is.
I'm guessing that once most people
find the diary inside my desk,
that'll probably satisfy their curiosity.
But... the real key...
is this.
Just an everyday item you'd expect
to find lying around on my desk.
A regular ball-point pen,
and all I need is this part.
[Ryuk] So that's the key?
Yeah. If you look closely,
you'll find that there's a small hole
underneath the drawer.
Then you just insert this...
[Ryuk] Aha. A fake bottom.
The diary will distract most people,
so I doubt anyone will find it.
-[Light] But that's not all.
-Oh?
Even if someone figures out
that there's a fake base,
I've set things up
so that there's no way they could
get their hands on the notebook.
You see,
once the ink reservoir is inserted,
it acts as an insulator,
preventing the flow of electricity
around this circuit.
When the fake base of the drawer's
put back,
this piece of rubber
also prevents the flow of electricity.
However, if someone were to try
and force the bottom of the drawer open,
the circuit would connect
and now would ignite the gasoline
contained in this thin plastic casing,
instantly setting the notebook on fire.
The way I’ve got it set up,
all the evidence
would be completely destroyed.
If I'm ever questioned,
I'll just say
that I was hiding the real diary
because I didn't want anyone to see it.
It sounds like a pretty believable excuse.
I mean... it is my diary after all.
I've heard of humans finding Death Notes
in the past
and typically,
the biggest problem they had
is finding a good place to hide it.
But you, Light, you're probably the first
to have given it this much thought.
Though, it's a pretty risky setup
from the look of it.
If you make even the slightest mistake,
you could be badly burned.
Risky?
You say
the strangest thing sometimes, Ryuk.
This whole thing has been a risk
since the very beginning,
from the moment I obtained the Death Note.
I'm sorry, but compared to that,
this doesn't even qualify as a risk to me.
In fact, it actually protects me.
It all comes down to a choice:
would I prefer to be executed
or deal with a little house fire?
[announcer] Last night
in the West Tokyo penitentiary,
Naoki Koro Kitayama, originally sentenced
to 15 years for armed robbery,
was reported to have died
of a sudden heart attack at the age of 32.
This is just the most recent death
in a steadily growing number
of cases involving inmates
dying of heart attacks.
[student 1] This is unbelievable.
Criminals are dropping like flies lately.
[student 2] It's a little scary,
but at the same time, it's kinda cool.
[student 1] Just make sure
you don't do anything bad.
[student 3] I wouldn't be surprised
if the police were behind this.
[student 2] No way.
The police don't have that kind of power.
-Don't you know about him?
-[student 3] Hmm? About who?
[student 1] Kira. You know, Kira.
[student 4] I wonder
who's gonna be killed next.
KIRA, KILL EVERYONE
SEND MESSAGE?
SEND
[computer chimes]
NAME: ROCOCO
KIRA, KILL EVERYONE - NAME: MISERY
-[Light] Ryuk, you should check this out.
-[Ryuk] Huh?
Websites like this
are popping up everywhere lately.
[Ryuk] "The Legend of Kira the Savior."
Huh. Sounds pretty cool.
Is this about you?
Yeah. I think
they've taken the name "Kira"
from the English word "killer."
Can't say I'm too happy about that, but...
it looks like that's the name
they've decided to give me.
When I search the word Kira, I'm pulling
up tons of sites just like this one.
The media hasn't picked up on it.
They're still calling this
"a succession of unexplained deaths
among the world's
most hardened criminals."
But…
the people of the world can already sense
that there's something happening.
They know there's someone out there
passing righteous judgment.
Oh?
[Light] Human beings are like that, Ryuk.
Huh.
Although this would probably
never happen in school,
let's say that students
were asked to discuss
whether bad people deserve to die.
Well, you can bet that everyone would
give the politically correct answer.
It's just wrong to kill people.
[Light] That's what they're bound to say.
Of course, that's the correct response
to give, right?
Humans will always try
to maintain appearances
when they're in public.
That's just how we are.
But this is how they really feel.
Most are too afraid to support me
as they’re worried about
what others will think.
Many would rather deny my existence.
But on the Internet,
where you can remain anonymous,
support for Kira is growing.
Maybe people are afraid
to say it out loud,
but they all understand what's happening.
Someone's making the bad guys
disappear one by one.
Those who have done no wrong
are cheering for Kira in their hearts
because they have nothing to fear,
while those who have done wrong
are on the run.
They're forced to hide
from an unknown enemy.
This is how it should be.
It's perfect.
Everything is going just like I planned.
THE PROGRAM IS INTERRUPTED
FOR A SPECIAL BROADCAST
We'd like to apologize
for the interruption.
As of now we're bringing you
a live worldwide broadcast
from Interpol's ICPO.
Hm? What's this?
Interpol?
[announcer]
We now take you live to the ICPO.
I head up
an International Police Task Force
which includes all member nations.
I am Lind L. Tailor,
otherwise known as L.
What? Who is this guy?
[Soichiro] So this is how it all begins.
[Matsuda] But, sir, I don't get it.
He's never actually
shown his face before, right?
Why would he choose to do it now?
-It must mean L's serious about this.
-Hm.
L, we've followed every single one
of your orders.
Now, it's time for you to prove
what you said to the ICPO.
Criminals around the world
are being murdered by a serial killer.
I consider this crime to be the most
atrocious act of murder in history.
I will not rest
until the person or persons responsible
are brought to justice.
Kira, I will hunt you down.
I will find you.
He seems certain he'll catch you.
Hm. That fool.
He'll never find me.
He'll have to get this first.
And as long as the police don't find it,
there won't be any evidence
to convict me,
which means that catching me
will be absolutely impossible.
[sighs]
I anticipated that the police
would get involved
and that something like this might happen.
Kira, I've got a pretty good idea
what your motivation might be,
and I can guess what you hope to achieve.
However,
what you're doing right now is evil.
You think… I'm evil?
I am justice!
I protect the innocent
and those who fear evil!
I'm the one who will become the god
of a new world that everyone desires!
All those who would oppose that god,
they are the ones who are truly evil!
I guess you're just too stupid, L.
Well, too bad.
This could've been a lot more interesting
if you'd only been a bit smarter.
[pen scratching]
[chuckles]
[Light laughs]
I'll show the world what happens
when you cross me.
The entire world is watching… L.
Five more seconds.
Four.
Three.
Two.
One.
[groans]
[laughs maniacally]
What's wrong?
You got nothing else to say?
[L] [through distorter]
[gasps] I had to test this, just in case,
but I-- I never thought
it would actually happen.
Kira…
it seems you can kill people
without having to be there in person.
I wouldn't have believed it
if I hadn't just witnessed it.
Listen to me, Kira.
If you did, indeed, kill Lind L. Tailor,
the man who you just saw
die on television,
I should tell you that he was an inmate
whose execution was scheduled for today.
That was not me.
[Light] What?
[L] The police arrested him
in absolute secrecy,
so you wouldn't have heard about him
on TV or through the internet.
It appears that not even you
have access to information
about these types of criminals.
[cackles]
He got you there.
[L] But I assure you, L is real.
I do exist.
Now…
try to kill me!
[Light] You… you bastard.
-[L] What's wrong? Hurry up.
-[man 1] What the hell is going on?
-[L] Come on, right now. Kill me!
-[man 1] He's really taking this too far.
[man 2] Are you trying
to kill yourself, L?
-[bystander 1] What's going on?
-[bystander 2] Look,
-it's Kira versus L!
-[L] Come on. What are you waiting for?
[bystander 3]
A live broadcast of a killing?
[L] You better do it.
Come on, Kira, kill me.
-[bystander 4] Amazing!
-[bystander 5] Do it, Kira!
-[bystander 6] Someone, stop this!
-[L] What's the matter? Can't you do it?
[Light exhales shakily]
[L] Well Kira, it seems that you
can't kill me after all.
[cackles]
[in normal voice]
So, there are some people you can't kill.
You've given me a useful hint.
[distorted] Let me return the favor.
I'll tell you something
that I think you'll find interesting.
Although this was announced
as a worldwide broadcast,
the truth is,
we are only broadcasting
in the Kanto region of Japan.
[Light gasps]
I had planned to broadcast this message
around the world until we found you,
but it looks like that won't be necessary.
I now know where you are.
[cackles]
This L guy is pretty good.
[L] The police treated your first killing
as an unrelated incident,
but in actuality,
the first of your victims
was a suspect in Sinjuku.
Of all the criminals that have recently
died of heart attacks,
this one's crime was, by far,
the least serious.
Furthermore, his crime was
only ever reported inside Japan.
[in normal voice] I used that information
to deduce this much.
[distorted] You are in Japan
and your first victim was little more
than an experiment,
which means you haven't been killing
for very long.
[Light gasps]
[L] We decided to broadcast in Kanto first
because of its large population,
and, luckily, we found you.
To be completely honest with you,
I never expected that things
would go this well…
but it won't be too long now
before I'll be able to sentence you
to death.
L has…
certainly lived up to his reputation.
Mhmm. He proved that Kira exists,
that the deaths were murders,
and that he is here in Japan.
Naturally, I am very interested to know
how you're able to commit these murders
without being present…
but I don't mind waiting
a little bit longer.
[in normal voice]
You can answer all of my questions
when I catch you…
[distorted] Let's meet again soon, Kira.
[Light exhales]
Really?
He's gonna sentence me to death?
Sounds interesting.
I accept your challenge, L.
Each of them has to hunt down the other
without knowing the other's name or face.
And the first one
whose identity is revealed will die.
Humans are...
so much fun.
L...
Kira...
[L and Kira] I will hunt you down
wherever you're hiding
and I will eliminate you!
-I am...
[L and Kira] ... justice!
TO BE CONTINUED
[theme song playing]