[theme music playing]
REVIVAL
Ryuzaki, please,
let me go and make the arrest.
I'd like to come with you, Chief,
if that's all right.
I understand, but remember this is Kira.
Be sure to take every precaution
when you approach him,
and don't allow him to see your face.
Watari, if Higuchi tries anything
or makes any sudden moves…
[Watari] Understood. I will shoot
to stop him, not to kill.
Aizawa, do you have a helmet
or something to hide your face with?
I do.
Good. Then cover me.
Yes, sir. You can count on me, Chief.
[quick footsteps]
[Yagami] Higuchi, put your hands
above your head
and get out of the car.
[Yagami] We've apprehended him.
Mogi, I want you to put a headset on him
as planned.
[Mogi] Roger.
[L] Higuchi,
how are you able to kill people?
Tell me!
[grunts]
If you're not going to talk,
I'll use whatever means necessary
to get it out of you.
[sighs]
The notebook.
[L] Notebook?
You probably won't believe me,
but I've got a special notebook.
If I write someone's name in it
while thinking of their face,
that person dies.
A notebook…
Mr. Yagami.
[Yagami] Yeah, I found it.
It was in one of the compartments
of Higuchi's bag.
He has written a lot of names in it,
but there doesn't seem to be
anything else unusual about it. Huh?
[Yagami screams]
[L] What is it, Mr. Yagami?
[Yagami] It's a monster!
[L] Please calm down.
Don't panic; remember,
you're not really armed
to defend yourself.
Oh… oh right, of course.
[Mogi] Chief, hang in there.
Are you all right?
Mogi, can't you see that thing over there?
Chief, I think you must be getting tired.
[Yagami screaming]
Mogi, what's wrong?
[Yagami] That… that thing.
It seems that only people
who have touched the notebook can…
can see this… this monster.
[L] Please bring the notebook
over to the helicopter.
[Yagami] Uh… o-okay.
What in the world are you planning to do,
Light Yagami?
Once you take hold of that notebook again,
all the memories of the Death Note
and what you did when it was yours
will return at once.
However…
[Mogi] Here it is, Ryuzaki.
Hmm...
It really is… a Shinigami.
They really… do… exist.
[L] Light Yagami…
This is how Kira killed.
No, the second Kira.
[L's thoughts echoing]
Ryuzaki, come on, let me see it!
[L] The Second Kira…
Two books!
There have to be two notebooks.
Possibly more.
This isn't over yet.
[Light screaming]
[echoing voices and sounds]
[Light panting]
Um... Are you okay, Light?
I suppose seeing that monster
would surprise anyone.
[Light] Ryuzaki…
What is it?
[Light] I wanna check this out.
I'm going to try comparing the names
written in this notebook
with the names of the victims.
Hmm? Oh, right.
Yeah, that sounds like a good idea.
I've won.
Exactly as planned.
I hereby forfeit
ownership of this notebook.
Now, that means ownership
has transferred back to you, right?
[Rem] Yes, I already told you.
[Light] Next, pass it on to Ryuk.
Hm?
[sighs] Very well. Here.
Now that notebook's ownership
has transferred from you to Ryuk.
Okay, Ryuk, take the notebook
and drop it on the ground,
so it's in the human world again.
Huh?
Well, okay.
Now the ownership goes back to me.
Wow, hang on!
It’s just gone around in a circle!
Nothing's changed, right?
Maybe at first glance,
but there will be a time
when I'll benefit from this.
Now, as for this notebook,
the one I first received,
I’m gonna give it back to you, Ryuk.
Then you hand it over to Rem.
[Ryuk] Huh?
[Ryuk] Here.
Rem, I want you to give the notebook
to someone with status
who lusts for power and money.
They'll end up using the notebook
to satisfy that urge.
If you do that,
I can guarantee that Misa will be
released from her confinement soon.
And if I'm wrong, and it looks like
she won’t be released for years,
then you can kill me.
Does that sound fair to you?
Light Yagami, just what are you thinking?
Look, this is all to save Misa.
You're gonna have to trust me on this.
All right.
If it means that Misa will be saved,
I'll do as you ask.
[Light] After this, I'll go and demand
to be confined like Misa,
and have them put me
under 24-hour surveillance as well.
While I'm locked up,
I'll relinquish ownership of the notebook
to you.
That'll mean I'll lose
all my memories of the Death Note.
During this time the killings of criminals
will start again.
KIRA RETURNS
Once that happens,
Ryuzaki will be put in a position
where he has to release us.
And, after I've lost all my memories,
chances are
I'll wanna help catch Kira myself.
That's just the way I am.
So, then you'll try and catch the guy
who Rem gives the notebook to
and steal it before L gets to it!
[Light] Right.
Once that's done,
I'll kill the new owner of the notebook.
But there's still one problem remaining.
[Rem] If you don't have full ownership,
your memories will only return for as long
as you're in contact with the notebook.
As soon as you let go of it,
your memories will disappear again.
[Light] That means I've gotta kill Higuchi
without letting go of this notebook.
If I manage to do that,
ownership will transfer back to me
and my memories won't disappear.
Hmm...
I just have to pull this four times
in less than a second.
Got it.
Just as I expected:
I'm wearing this watch.
Old habits die hard.
[loud heartbeat]
Mr. Yagami,
please take Higuchi to the car.
[Yagami] Uh, right. Of course.
[loud heartbeat]
KYOSUKE HIGUCHI
[panting]
-[Light] You know, about this notebook…
-Huh?
[Light] I wonder what we would find
if we put it through forensic analysis.
[L] That doesn't sound like you,
Light.
We both know this thing is beyond science.
[chuckles]
Yeah, you're right. Hmm…
[footsteps echoing]
This has gotta be
the longest 40 seconds of my life.
[loud ticking]
Ooh...
[Higuchi grunting]
[Yagami] Higuchi.
Ryuzaki, Higuchi is…
What the hell?! What's happening?
[Yagami] Hey, Higuchi!
[Light] Dad, what are you doing?
We can't lose him!
If Higuchi dies on us now--
[Yagami] It's impossible!
The… but… [sighs]
There's nothing I can do.
He's already…
[Light] Yes. He's already dead.
And you're next,
Ryuzaki.
[Aizawa] "How to use it."
It says, "The human whose name
is written in this notebook…
shall die.
"This note will not take effect
unless the writer has the person's face
in their mind
when writing his or her name.
Therefore, people sharing the same name
will not be affected.
[Light typing]
[Aizawa] If the cause of death is written
40 seconds of writing the person’s name,
it will happen.
If the cause of death is not specified,
the person will simply die
of a heart attack.
After writing the cause of death,
details of the death should be written
in the next six minutes and 40 seconds."
As well, the back cover has some more
instructions on how to use it.
There are two more rules.
One of them is,
"If you make this note unusable
by tearing it up or burning it,
all the humans
who have touched the note till then
-will die."
-What?
Is that really true, Aizawa?
-[Aizawa] Yeah, that’s what it says.
-[Light] That's right.
-[Matsuda] No way! That sucks!
-[Light] With a rule like that in place...
-[Matsuda] Why didn't you tell me
before I touched it?
-... the notebook's safety is guaranteed.
[Aizawa] How was I supposed to know?
[Light] Which means my memories
of it will remain.
[Ryuk] Rem, there's no way
the old man back home
will get mad at us
if we write fake rules in here, is there?
[Rem] No. There are no rules
against doing so.
Fine then, Light, I'll do it.
But you owe me an apple for this.
[cackles]
Oh man, maybe I shouldn't have
let my curiosity about seeing a Shinigami
get the better of me.
Maybe, but then you would be
the only one in the investigation
who didn't know what we were dealing with.
Is that what you want?
Uh, no, of course not.
I wanna be on the same page
as everyone else on the Task Force, Chief.
And then… [sighs] there's this last rule.
According to these instructions
in the back of the notebook,
"If the person using the note
fails to consecutively write
names of people
to be killed
within thirteen days of each other,
then the user will die."
[Matsuda gasps] Wait a second.
If that's true,
then it means Light and Misa-Misa
are completely clear, doesn't it?
[Aizawa] Yeah, now that you mention it,
that's right.
Light and Misa were detained
for more than 50 days
and are still under surveillance.
If either of them had been Kira,
there's no way
they would still be alive by now.
Wow, that’s great news, isn't it, Chief?
[Yagami] Yeah.
Rem, was it?
That's your name, isn't it?
The white thing over there?
Ryuzaki, isn't it a bit rude to go around
calling someone a "white thing"?
[Rem] What do you want?
[L] There's more than one notebook
in the human world, isn't there?
[Rem] Who knows.
There may be and there may not be.
If there are other notebooks either here
or in your world,
would they all have the same rules
as this one?
You're wasting your time, Ryuzaki.
You'll never get Rem
to admit these rules are fake.
[Rem] Yes, they are all the same.
There are many notebooks
in the Shinigami Realm,
but they all have the same rules.
Even the rules
for when humans obtain them.
Ryuzaki!
[Aizawa] Misa Amane and Light have both
been cleared of suspicion.
They shouldn’t be under surveillance
any longer.
[Matsuda] That's right,
it's crystal clear!
I suppose you're right…
[L] I understand.
[L] Please, except my apologies
for all the trouble.
[Matsuda and Aizawa sigh]
Thank goodness.
Yeah, but…
We still can’t say we’ve solved the case
until we’ve figured out everything.
Would it be all right
if I kept investigating with you,
without the handcuffs on?
Yes.
[Light] And just like that,
Misa and I are proven innocent.
A notebook of death filled with rules
written by a Shinigami.
He has no choice but to believe it.
He just lost his edge
thanks to the fake rules I created.
Listen Ryuzaki:
no matter what the world,
the god of that world creates the rules.
In truth, you've already been defeated
by the rules I created.
And as punishment
for defying the god of the New World,
you will die.
Oh, Light!
Be sure to text me every day, okay?
[Matsuda crying]
[Matsuda] After all this time,
we're saying goodbye to Misa-Misa.
Knock it off, Matsuda!
Let's leave them alone.
[Matsuda] Goodbye Misa-Misa!
[Aizawa] Enough!
[Light] Good,
there are surveillance cameras,
but they won't be able to pick out
my face or mouth at this angle.
Misa, I'm gonna tell you
about a special place.
I need you to go there
and dig something up,
but you have to make sure
that no one is watching.
Light! Your memory must have returned!
Don't worry, I can do this.
I won't let you down.
[gasps]
[Misa] Light, I remember!
I remember everything that happened
when I had this notebook.
You buried this one,
so I could come here
and regain my memories.
Huh?
FOR MISA, LIGHT YAGAMI
[Light's voice] "Dear Misa,
by the time you read this letter,
you should've remembered everything."
Oh, a letter from Light!
[Light] Do you remember
my friend at To-Oh University?
He went by the name "Hideki Ryuga."
I want you to write his real name
in the notebook
and kill him.
Then burn this letter right away.
Take a number of pages from the notebook,
and rebury it where you found it.
The next time that we see each other,
casually touch me
with a piece of the notebook.
If you do this for me,
I promise I will love you...
-for the rest of my life.
-[Misa] …for the rest of my life! Yay!
[Misa] Now I see.
This was all part of Light's plan!
He wanted me to get this notebook,
regain all my memories,
and then kill Hideki Ryuga.
Kill Ryuzaki.
One of Light's biggest obstacles
will be gone,
and I'll be helpful to him at last!
Oh, but Light, it's no good!
I don’t remember his name anymore!
I was seeing dozens-- no,
no, no hundreds of names and lifespans
every day!
Oh! I can't remember it no matter what!
Oh, I'm such an idiot!
[Misa] Huh?
I finally return to the human world!
Huh? Ryuk!
[Misa] Oh, it's been so long!
Oh, I'm so glad to see you.
-How are you doing?
-Sorry, uh.
Ugh!
I'm a guy, I get a little shy,
some… times.
[giggles]
[Misa] Oh yeah, I almost forgot.
Here!
Light told me to bring one for you.
Is it really that good?
[Ryuk] Oh yeah. Human apples are--
what's the word-- juicy, I think.
They're great, anyway.
[mumbles] Why don't you try this?
Huh?
[Ryuk gulps]
An apple from the Shinigami world.
Uhh… Ew, it doesn't look very good.
Come on, one bite won't kill ya.
Mmm…
By the way, before I forget,
I want you to make the eye deal with me.
[Misa biting apple]
Peh! Peh! It's sand! Bleh.
Ugh!
A deal, huh?
Mmhmm.
You understand what that means?
You already made the same deal with Rem
once before.
Are you sure
you really want me
to cut your lifespan in half,
for the second time?
Uh... I know, but what choice do I have?
You see, I've forgotten a name
that I absolutely have to remember.
Light will be so mad at me
if I let him down.
Heh, well it's fine with me.
[Matsuda] Hey, it's Misa-Misa.
The poor girl.
As long as we're stuck in here,
we can't turn our cellphones on,
so she has to come all the way out here
just to hang out with Light.
Light, would you hurry up and go see her?
Don't you know,
you should never keep a woman waiting.
Okay.
Huh?
Ryuk.
Why is he attached to Misa?
Huh?
[Rem] Misa's lifespan!
It's been halved again!
No! Did she make the eye deal with Ryuk?
Hey, Light.
It's been a while, Ryuk.
[Ryuk cackles]
Light, I'm so sorry!
I don't remember Hideki Ryuga's real name!
I tried, but I totally forgot!
Oh, I see.
Well, that's too bad.
But I did the eye deal with Ryuk,
so I can try again!
So, everything's going according to plan…
You idiot!
If you do that,
then your lifespan will--
Mmm… no, it's all right.
I just want to be of use to you, Light.
Misa, all I want is
to enjoy a long life with you
in an ideal world.
That's how I feel.
Light, I'm so happy.
[Light] Let's create a New World together.
It'll be a place with no crime,
where only kind people live.
-Okay?
-[Misa] Yeah.
TO BE CONTINUED
[theme song playing]