[theme song playing]
[alarm blaring]
[Matsuda] What is this?
[Watari grunts]
[groaning]
Everyone. Shiniga--
[heartbeat]
RENEWAL
[L] Now, try to kill me!
[L] Although this was announced
as a worldwide broadcast,
the truth is, we are only broadcasting
in the Kanto region of Japan.
In actuality, the first of your victims
was a suspect in Shinjuku.
Furthermore, his crime
was only ever reported inside of Japan.
[reporter] The suspect is now dead!
I used that information
to deduce this much:
You are in Japan,
and your first victim
was little more than an experiment,
which means that you haven’t been killing
for very long.
KIRA TASK FORCE HEADQUARTERS
Kira has found a way to obtain information
from the task force headquarters.
There are 141 people in the police force
who have access to classified information
regarding the investigation.
I’m sure that somewhere in this list
of police officers,
and the people closest to them…
we will find our suspect
SOICHIRO YAGAMI (48) DOB 7/12/59
DETECTIVE SUPERINTENDENT,
FBI INVESTIGATION OF THOSE INVOLVED
WITH THE JAPANESE POLICE
On December 14,
twelve FBI investigators enter Japan.
Here we are on December 19th.
Using prison inmates,
Kira conducts experiments,
manipulating his victims' actions
before they die.
He needed to know
how much control
he had over his victims
before he could use it
against the 12 agents.
I suspect Kira had to be one of the people
being investigated by the FBI,
between the 14th and the 19th of December.
-In fact, I have no doubt.
-[man groans]
[grunts]
AN IMPORTANT WITNESS
NAOMI MISORA
Raye Penber's fiancée?
Naomi Misora.
So, it's her.
She was working under me.
I guess she must have come to Japan
with her fiancée.
I heard she was seen with Penber.
It's possible
that she may have found a lead.
If that's the case,
did Kira manage to get to her first?
LIGHT YAGAMI
[L] Everyone, at this point
I'd like to focus our investigation
on only those people
who Raye Penber was tailing.
There are two groups.
Deputy Director Kitamura,
as well as Detective Superintendent Yagami
and their families.
At this stage, I'd like to place wiretaps
and surveillance cameras
in both households.
That's my son you're talking about.
Are you honestly telling me
that you suspect him?
I do suspect him.
CONTACT WITH LIGHT YAGAMI
I want to tell you I'm L.
[L] Relax, Light.
While it's true that Kira hates losing,
it's also true that most people
would rather win than lose.
It's human nature.
Look at that. He's going for the win.
I suspect that you, Light Yagami,
are in fact Kira.
[chuckles] You think I'm Kira?
Ryuga,
what would it take to get you
to believe that I'm not Kira?
Please, isn't there something?
If you are not Kira,
that truth will be revealed.
Just let things run their course.
KIRA MURDERS
USING A TELEVISION STATION
MESSAGE FROM KIRA
4 VIDEOS
[director] Our audience rating
should go up 60,
no, more like 70 percent
after this!
[newscaster] It contained a prediction
of two deaths, proving that he is Kira.
We understand that the 2nd tape contains
a message to all people of the world.
[Kira] I am Kira.
The news anchor, Mr. Kazuhiko Hibima,
will die of a heart attack
at exactly six o'clock.
Stop this broadcast!
We can't let him finish!
You idiots!
-[heart beating loudly]
-[groans]
[Matsuda] Ukita!
You told us that Kira
couldn't kill without a name!
[L] But from what we've just seen,
I'd say it's not entirely impossible
that Kira can kill with only a face.
This is the police!
Stop this broadcast now!
[L] There's a strong possibility
that this Kira is a fake.
No, we should think of him
more as a Second Kira.
Mr. Yagami.
I'd like your permission to ask your son
to cooperate with us
in this investigation.
LIGHT YAGAMI IS SUMMONED
TO TASK FORCE HEADQUARTERS
At the very least, I'd say
this isn't the Kira we are familiar with.
That's almost exactly
how L, I mean Ryuzaki, said it.
[Kira] When we meet,
we can confirm our identities
by showing our Shinigami to each other.
[screaming]
[L] If there's a message here
written in some code that only people
who have this Shinigami power
can understand,
there'd be no way for me to decipher it.
Still, it would only make sense for us
to look into all of the places
that were mentioned in the journal.
When you two are working together,
I want you to keep a close eye on Light
the entire time.
It's only a slim chance,
but if Light is Kira,
then there's still a possibility
that the Second Kira
may try to contact him somehow.
Also, Mr. Yagami, please ask Mr. Mogi
to start following Light,
so we can keep tabs
on what he's doing.
MISA AMANE ARRESTED UNDER SUSPICION
OF BEING THE SECOND KIRA
Light! There you are!
Hi there. I'm Light's girlfriend.
Misa Amane. Nice to meet you.
-I'm Hideki Ryuga.
-Huh?
Hideki Ryuga?
[L] I'm not exactly sure
how you will take this,
but regarding Misa Amane,
there's something you should know.
We've taken her into custody
under suspicion of being the Second Kira.
We gathered physical evidence
from the envelopes
sent by the Second Kira.
In particular, hairs and fibers
caught in the masking tape
used to seal them.
They matched what we found in Misa's room.
MISA AMANE'S CONFINEMENT
[Yagami] Ryuzaki!
What's the meaning of this?
Now, hurry up and kill me!
If you wanted to, you could kill me
right, now, couldn't you?
[L] Does that mean
you admit to being the Second Kira?
-Is this the reason you wish to die?
-[Misa] No!
[Misa] I don't know anything
about the Second Kira!
LIGHT YAGAMI IS CONFINED
AT HIS OWN REQUEST
Ryuzaki, like I said over the phone,
I could be Kira.
[L] Why come here to announce
that you could be Kira?
It's an act.
There's no "could be" about it.
You are Kira.
[L] Light, are you feeling okay?
Yeah. I know I must look
pretty bad in here,
with this useless pride...
I suppose I'll have to...
get rid of it!
Ryuzaki!
I realize I was the one
pushing for confinement,
and that I asked you to put me in here,
But this whole thing
is completely pointless!
I'm not Kira!
You have to get me out of here!
I just heard.
Two weeks’ worth of criminals
were just murdered all at once!
It happened yesterday!
KIRA RETURNS
I don't understand what's going on here.
TWO PEOPLE RELEASED
I-- I'm not sure how much more of this
the three of them can take.
Ryuzaki, you have no reason
to keep Light locked up anymore!
It's already been fifty days.
I'm going to kill you here
and then kill myself.
What? What are you talking about, Dad?
-That's crazy!
-Don't say that.
[Yagami] It's too late.
Please, stop, Dad. I'm not Kira!
Light, my son...
-From one murderer to another...
-No, Dad!
I'll see you in Hell.
No! Stop it!
[gunshot]
[cawing]
[L] It was
a convincing performance.
As we discussed,
I will end their confinement immediately.
LIGHT YAGAMI IS SUMMONED AGAIN
TO HELP WITH THE INVESTIGATION
As for you part in this agreement, Light,
you and I will be together 24-7.
And that's how it will be
until we have brought Kira to justice.
[grunting]
[Misa gasping]
YOTSUBA
[Light] Their deaths have all worked
in Yotsuba's favor.
Looking back,
there've been 13 similar deaths
in the past three months.
INVESTIGATION AND INFILTRATION
OF YOTSUBA
[L] Is Kira someone from Yotsuba?
Or is Kira simply using Yotsuba?
I haven't figured that out yet,
but we'll proceed under the assumption
that this is Kira's doing.
We will focus on Yotsuba.
Please be sure not to act impulsively,
out of panic or haste,
and don't take matters
into your own hands.
My name is Taro Matsui.
I'm an agent with Yoshida Productions!
Would you be interested
in using Misa Amane
as your new spokesperson?
Ryuzaki, are you watching this?
The eight men who came here
were having a meeting to decide
-who'd they get Kira to kill for them.
-[L] If Matsuda dies,
our suspicions about the Yotsuba group
would be confirmed.
[Matsuda] Do you think there’s anything
I can do to save myself?
[L] Matsuda, you idiot.
KYOSUKE HIGUCHI CONFIRMED AS KIRA
Good luck, Misa-Misa!
I'll be here ready to celebrate
when they decide to hire you!
It's always been my dream
to become Kira's wife.
-I know he'll need me by his side.
-Huh?
And you know why?
Because I'm the Second Kira.
[laughs]
Well, since I happen to be Kira,
does that mean you'll marry me, Misa?
So, based on what he said,
Higuchi is Kira!
THE PLAN TO CAPTURE HIGUCHI
IS SET IN MOTION
-[Matsuda] So, what are you gonna do?
-[L] I'm going to trick Higuchi
-using Sakura TV.
-Like a hidden camera show!
Higuchi, we've got a problem.
Turn on the television.
Hm?
[man 1] So, you're saying
one of those people is Kira, right?
[man 2]Yes. I've got a lot of evidence
to prove it, too. [yelps]
[Higuchi] It-- It's him!
Why is he still alive?
[tires screeching]
I see Higuchi. I'm in pursuit.
We're heading after him!
[siren wailing]
You in the red car.
Pull over to the side of the road. Now!
[Higuchi] Rem. Let's make the deal.
A deal?
You were speeding.
License, please!
Yeah, no problem.
[officer 1] Hey!
[officer 2] Higuchi ditched the cop
He's driving away!
This is traffic control.
-[heartbeat]
-[groans]
Everyone! It's too dangerous
to allow further action by Higuchi!
Let's bring him in!
I believe he has the same powers
as the Second Kira,
He is able to kill
just by looking at someone's face.
Please, keep this in mind
when you move in to arrest him.
-[tires screeching]
-[grunting]
Stop right there!
[tires screeching]
Stay back!
Stay back or I'll shoot!
-I swear! [yells]
-[gunshot]
HIGUCHI'S CAPTURE
[L] Higuchi, how were you able
to kill people?
You probably won't believe me,
but I've got a special notebook.
If I write someone's name in it
while thinking of their face,
that person dies.
[Yagami] It was in one of the compartments
of Higuchi's bag.
[Yagami screaming]
[L] What' is it, Mr. Yagami?
[Yagami] It's a monster!
A Shinigami…
There have to be two notebooks!
Possibly more!
This isn't over yet.
THE DEATH NOTE AND AN INQUIRY
INTO ITS RULES
[Aizawa] "How to use it..."
It says: "The human whose name is written
in this notebook,
shall die."
And then, there's this last rule...
According to this,
"If the person using the note
fails to consecutively write names
of people to be killed,
-within 13 days of each other..."
-[L] ...within 13 days of each other,
then the user will die."
Light Yagami and Misa Amane
are both still alive.
Thirteen days.
That's the only problem.
The following is the record,
which contains everything
I have investigated on the Kira Incident.
The fact that now you are reading
this message,
means I am no longer alive at this moment.
I hereby leave this record
as my firm achievement.
That is all.
[continuous beep]
[Matsuda] It's been ten days
since Ryuzaki's funeral.
It looks like we
are not gonna die after all.
We know Watari's true identity now,
but we never found out
anything about who Ryuzaki really was.
Yeah, that's true.
Who could have guessed that Watari
was actually a famous inventor.
The paper says he founded orphanages
around the world
using the fortune
he inherited from his patents.
[Matsuda] He was a fine man. A hero!
But it doesn't help us now.
We can't continue investigating
using this place as our base
with L and Watari gone.
This is tough.
[Yagami] Hmm. Light, how's it going?
I should be able to transfer the system
and most of the information
out of here by tonight.
It's weird, though.
I almost feel as if I'm stealing.
I've created a voice filter
identical to the one Ryuzaki used.
We can use it
to make the police think he is still alive
and give them orders
like we've doing so far, but…
Who's going to take the place of L?
Where he will work from?
And what do we do with the notebook?
Come on.
What are you talking about, Light?
You're the only one
who can take on the role of L.
[Light] Hm.
[Light] I don't know.
Ryuzaki was killed by Kira
because he challenged him.
That's not something I'm eager to do.
Besides, I would be fooling
the people of the world.
I can understand how you feel,
but you're really the only one of us
who can do this.
That's right.
Even Ryuzaki said so himself.
You would be capable of succeeding L.
[Light] Just as I thought.
It's too simple.
It's no fun without Ryuzaki here.
[Light] I understand.
All right. I'll do it.
But... I won't be like Ryuzaki.
I won't take big risks
like challenging Kira directly
to gather clues.
It's just not me.
Yeah, it's probably better
if we play it safe.
Ryuzaki may have been
a little too confrontational.
[Light] In that case…
I'll be able to do the same sort of work,
using both this computer and my own.
In fact,
it'll be possible for me to act as L
in the comfort of my own room.
I can be Watari as well.
But it'll be difficult to pull off
with Mum and Sayu around.
Things would be easier
if I could rent a one-bedroom apartment.
Well, considering your age,
it certainly wouldn't look odd to anyone
if I let you move out on your own.
Hey, yeah! And then we'll be able
to use Light's new apartment
as our taskforce headquarters.
-That's a great idea!
-[Yagami] Hm.
All that's left to figure out now
is what to do with the notebook.
[Light] It's really not that difficult.
There's five of us here.
And we know none of us
will ever use the notebook.
We'll just have one of us take it
and hide it somewhere
where no one else can ever get to it.
Please, Chief, it's gotta be you.
Yeah, Chief! We can count on you!
You're a pillar of justice, after all.
[nervous laughter]
You want me to...
All right.
We'll avenge Ryuzaki together!
Yeah. Kira's still out there somewhere.
We'll catch him. That's a promise.
-Mm-hmm.
[Matsuda] Well then, why don't we
have a little party
to celebrate Light becoming
L number two?
[Aizawa] Quit fooling around.
Now's not the time for stuff like that.
[Yagami] Let's take it easy.
[Misa] Light!
This is our first date in forever.
Can't you enjoy yourself a little more?
[Light] Misa…
-Let's move in together.
-[Misa gasps]
You mean it?
[Light] Yeah. I've already rented a place.
[gasps]
[screams] Yay! Victory is mine!
Misa wins!
-[Ryuk] Victory?
-[Misa] Over Kiyomi and Mari and Yuri.
But it's all right, now. Don't worry.
I knew you were
just using those other girls to trick L.
You don't have any reason
to see them anymore, right?
[Light] Right...
Hey. Now that L's dead,
does that mean
you've finally settled the score with him?
[Light] Yeah.
So, in that case, I guess things
are gonna get pretty boring from now on.
[Light] That's not true, Ryuk.
From this moment on...
I'll show you the creation
of the new world.
Huh?
[lightning crackles]
[thunder rumbling]
[inaudible]
[gasps, groans]
-[cat meows loudly]
-[tires screeching]
[crashing]
Daddy!
-[thud]
-[glass breaking]
[child] Daddy?
This will be the rebirth of Yotsuba.
Yeah. It's a new start.
-Huh?
-[man groans]
Namikawa? What's wrong?
Huh? That's impossible!
-[loud heartbeat]
-[groans]
[man] In April 2012, Light Yagami, age 23,
joined Japan's National Police Agency.
In the summer of 2012,
Kira's killings increased
at an unprecedented rate.
Numerous people around the world
were terrified of Kira,
and yet, there were just as many
cheering him on.
Gradually, their private thoughts
became public opinion,
and soon, certain nations
began to accept Kira's judgement.
The world was heading into a dark age
in which Kira's will was the only law.
[beeping]
-[birds chirping]
-[children playing]
[man] What is it, Roger?
It's L.
He's dead.
TO BE CONTINUED
[theme music playing]