[theme music playing]
Greetings to all of you at the ICPO.
I am L.
Whether the guilty party
is an individual or a group,
there's a strong possibility
that they are Japanese.
Kira, I've got a pretty good idea
what your motivation might be,
and I can guess what you hope to achieve.
However…
what you're doing right now is evil.
[Light] You… you bastard.
[L] Now… try to kill me!
-I am justice!
-What the hell is going on?
I protect the innocent
and those who fear evil!
I'm the one who will become the god
of a new world that everyone desires!
L…
Kira…
[Kira and Light] I will hunt you down
wherever you're hiding,
and I will eliminate you!
I am…
[Kira and L] … justice!
DEALINGS
[car horns honking]
SERIAL MURDER
SPECIAL INVESTIGATIONS HQ
[Yagami] All right. Let's start
with the tip line reports.
[detective 1] Yes, sir.
Up to this point, we've received
3029 responses about the murders
via telephone and e-mail.
Most of these have been curious citizens
and prank calls,
but there are 14 people who claimed
to either know Kira or who have seen him.
All 14 accounts were followed up on
and carefully documented.
However, nobody could provide
any information
that wasn't already publicly available.
And lastly, this week
there were additional 21 people
who called in claiming to be Kira.
[indistinct chatter]
Hm… [clears throat]
[detective 1] We didn't want
to rule anything out.
So, we followed standard procedure
and created files for all 21 of them.
[Yagami] Uh huh. All right.
On to the victim reports.
[detective 2] Yes, sir.
Upon further investigation,
we have confirmed that information
of the heart attack victims
was in fact publicly available in Japan
immediately prior to their deaths.
Also,
concerning L's request that we investigate
the time of death for each victim,
we found that all of them occurred
between the hours of 4 p.m. and 2 a.m.
on weekdays, local time,
with 68 percent of them
occurring between 8 p.m. and 12 a.m.
Weekends and holidays appeared
to be the exception to this rule
as the times of deaths vary
much more widely than during the week.
[L through voice modifier]
That information
is extremely relevant for us.
It suggests that,
given the times of death,
our suspect could very well be a student.
Hmm?
[L] Based on the fact
that Kira is only killing criminals,
I think it's safe to assume
that he is driven
by a very idealistic notion of justice.
It's highly possible he may even aspire
to be some sort of godlike figure.
We're dealing with an individual
who has a very childish concept
of right and wrong.
[muttering]
[L] Of course,
this is mere speculation at this point,
but still, I recommend you re-examine
any assumptions you've made
as to whether or not our suspect
could be a student.
We must consider every possibility.
I believe that's the shortest route
to finding and arresting Kira.
Please, continue with your report.
Hm. All right.
Does anyone else have
something they'd like to add?
Um, yes sir.
[Yagami] What is it, Matsuda?
Um… well, I'm not saying this
to support Kira
or to condone the murders, but…
in the last few days throughout the world,
but especially here in Japan,
we've observed the dramatic decrease
in the number of violent crimes committed.
[muttering]
[Yagami] Well, I suppose it makes sense.
We've suspected
something like that would happen.
Anything else?
No.
[unsettling music playing]
[Yagami] Well, that about sums up
our report for today. L?
[L] Thank you, everyone.
I feel we're one step closer
to finding Kira.
Before I go, I'm afraid I have
one additional request to make.
This is directed
to the teams investigating the victims,
TV news, and internet.
I would like you to go back
and take a closer look at the exact way
in which the victims' identities
were made public.
Be as thorough as possible.
[L] In particular,
I want to know if photos of the victims
were made available to the public
in Japan.
[through voice modifier]
I leave it to you.
[groaning]
-[Matsuda] Chief!
-Hm?
You look like you could use one of these.
Sleepy much?
Ah. Thank you. That'll do the trick.
I feel all these late nights
are starting to take their toll.
[Yagami gulps] Ah.
About what I said earlier at our meeting…
Well, now that I think about it, um,
I'm sure everyone already knew that.
I wanted to apologize.
What on earth are you talking about?
Nobody said it'll be easy
to speak the truth,
but it has to be done.
Especially when it is something
that isn't easy to say.
Huh?
Having said that,
if you'd gone on to say
that we should commend Kira
for doing such a great job
of reducing violent crime,
then yes, I might have
had a little problem with that.
[Matsuda] Oh, no. No, I wouldn't.
That would never happen!
[Yagami laughing] Just kidding.
[Sayu] I knew I can count on you, Light.
Hey, so do you think you're ready
to try a few on your own now?
Huh?
Yeah. I guess so.
[doorbell rings]
Oh, sounds like Dad's home.
-[Sachiko] Welcome home, dear.
-[Yagami] Thank you.
He's home really early today.
Hey, why don't you at least
try the last problem by yourself?
[Sayu] I will, but maybe after dinner.
Yeah, right.
Helping your sister with her homework?
You sure are relaxed.
Of course.
If the police try to come after me,
I'm pretty confident I've got something
that'll give me the advantage.
Hey, glad you could join us for dinner.
You hungry, Dad?
Yeah. It's been a long day.
[chopsticks clattering]
So, Light, tell me.
How are your studies going?
Hm? Everything's okay, I guess.
Whatever. He's at the top of his class.
My big brother is a genius!
That's my son!
We're all proud of you, Light.
[Light] Is everything okay, Dad?
You look tired.
[Yagami] Yeah.
I'm not able to say too much about it,
but this case I'm working on now
is really tough.
[Ryuk] I see.
-Well, well. Daddy's a policeman.
-[keyboard clacking]
And that must be the reason
why you're so confident?
That's right. It's easy for me to hack
into Dad's computer.
We're on a home network,
so I can copy the files I need
without leaving a trace.
This way, I can keep track
of their investigation.
Here we go.
Well, isn't that interesting?
Looks like the police are already
beginning to suspect a student.
[Ryuk cackles]
I guess that means you're in trouble.
Hm…
If the cause of death is written within
40 seconds of writing the person's name,
it will happen.
If the cause of death is not specified,
the person will simply
die of a heart attack.
After writing the cause of death,
details of the death should be written
in the next six minutes and 40 seconds.
That sound right to you, Ryuk?
So, what's your point?
In other words, if I write
heart attacks as the cause of death,
then I should be able to write down
all the details including
time of death afterward, shouldn't I?
Looks like I will be able to provide you
with more entertainment now.
[tense music playing]
[inmate grunts]
[panting]
-[grunting]
-[chuckles]
[grunts]
Inmate 148, what's wrong?
Snap out of it!
[grunting, gasping]
[inmates] Huh?
TASK FORCE HEADQUARTERS
[Yagami] What?
I-- I don't believe this.
Another 23 victims yesterday?
Are these confirmed?
[detective] Yes.
The day before there were
another 23 victims.
He's killing one off,
every hour on the hour.
Considering that this new pattern
has been going on for two weekdays…
It does punch some holes in the theory
that our suspect is a student.
Maybe not.
Anybody can skip two days of school.
[L] You're missing the point.
-Huh?
[L] It does appear less likely now
that Kira is a student,
but that's not the message he's sending
by doing this.
Ask yourselves, why every hour?
And why are all these victims in prisons
where they are sure to be
discovered immediately?
Why not other criminals like before?
I believe Kira is telling us
that not only can he kill from a distance,
but he can also
determine the time of death.
[muttering]
[L] But something's not right.
As soon as we began to suspect
that Kira might be a student,
the pacing of the killings changed.
As if to contradict that theory.
Coincidence?
No.
Too convenient.
This can only mean that Kira
has access to police information.
It's obvious now.
This is a direct challenge to me.
[Light] I'd say L is probably
starting to sweat a little by now.
What'll really make his job difficult
is that I've deliberately left
about 50 criminals alive
for times like this.
Oh?
If L is as good as they say,
by now, he should be starting to suspect
someone with connections to the police.
[L] So, Kira has found a way
to obtain information
from the Task Force headquarters.
This is one fact that cannot be ignored.
But what does he get out of all this?
What is he hoping to achieve in the end?
There's one thing I don't get.
Showing them
you have connections to the police,
makes it easier for them to find you
than when they
just suspected you a student.
Well, my real agenda is…
to get close to L,
so I can eliminate him.
How are you gonna do that?
You still don't understand human beings.
In this world, there are very few people
who actually trust each other.
And it's no different for the police,
you know.
What's especially important
is that L and the investigators
don't trust each other at all.
Think about it.
Could you trust someone
whose name and face you don't even know?
When L discovers that I'm somehow
getting confidential information,
he'll be obligated
to start investigating the police
to find the source of the leak.
When that happens,
it'll only be a matter of time
before the police start resenting L.
On the surface it will appear
that L and the investigation team
are working together to try to catch me.
But in reality,
L will investigate the police,
and they will be investigating L.
I'm not the one who is going to find L.
I can let the police do that for me.
And when they do,
that's when I'll eliminate him.
TASK FORCE HEADQUARTERS
[Yagami] What's this about?
LETTER OF RESIGNATION
[detective 1] With all due respect, Chief,
we're resigning.
[muttering]
[detective 1] We demand that you assign us
to a different case.
Otherwise, you can have our badges
right here and now.
Why? You're good cops!
Isn't it clear?
It's because we value our lives, sir.
[detective 2] If what L says is true,
Kira has some ESP-like power
that somehow allows him to kill people
indirectly from anywhere.
[detective 3] Well, if I were Kira, sir,
I'd probably wanna try and get rid
of the people who are trying to catch me.
Let's face it, he knows he will be
sentenced to death if he's caught.
[detective 1] We all sat here and watched
when L decided to pull that media stunt
and challenge Kira to kill him.
Well, it was all very impressive
at the time,
but then again,
L never had to show his face
or reveal his name for that matter.
I'm sure you recall L's last request?
He asked that we take a closer look
at how these victims' identities
were made public
and specifically, to determine
whether photos of the victims
were available to the public
prior to their deaths.
Well, it turns out he was right!
Every single one of those victims'
names and photos
were broadcast to the Japanese public,
and then they died!
Unlike someone we know,
we're out there investigating this case
wearing police IDs
with our names and photos on them!
Anybody with a computer
can find out who we are!
We don't hide our faces!
We're out in the open!
Sir, the truth is,
we could be killed by Kira at any time.
For these reasons,
we refuse to continue working this case.
Excuse us, Chief.
Hey, stop! All of you,
hold it right there!
[door closes]
Huh?
In order to solve this problem,
we must establish the concept
that X squared equals large X.
Now pay attention
because this is important.
Before we tackle
more complex quadratic equations,
we have to start thinking
of large X's value
as simply the multiple of two integers.
Now, let's apply this concept
to our first problem.
[Watari] We brought the FBI to Japan
four days ago.
They are fully operational.
As requested, they're now
gathering intel on the police.
-[L] And this is the complete list?
-[Watari] Yes.
There are 141 people in the police force
who have access to classified information
regarding the investigation.
I am sure that somewhere in this list
of the police officers
and the people closest to them,
we will find our suspect.
SOICHIRO YAGAMI
DETECTIVE SUPERINTENDENT
NPA HEAD OF SPECIAL INVESTIGATIONS
SERIAL MURDER CASE
[Ryuk] Light, you got a second?
I've already told you, Ryuk.
You can't talk to me in public.
How many times do I have to tell you?
In that case, I'll talk, you just listen.
If you don't want to hear me,
you can plug your ears or something.
First of all,
I don't have anything against you.
I actually think the notebook
couldn't have been picked up
by a better person.
I'm here 'cause I have to stick around
till the Death Note is finished,
or I see you die, whichever comes first.
But make no mistake, Light,
I'm not on your side or L's side.
[Light] Yeah. Well,
I knew that much already.
You'll never hear me say anything
about whether what you're doing
is right or wrong.
I'm not here to support you
or give you my opinion.
I'm just a spectator,
but as your roommate,
I might have a few things to say
now and then.
What's this about, Ryuk?
Why are you
telling me all this stuff now, anyway?
It's really not like you.
It's just that I'm no ally of yours,
or Kira's, if you prefer.
The only reason I'm going to tell you this
is because, personally,
it is starting to creep me out.
[Light] Get to the point already.
[chuckles]
You are being followed by another human.
He's watching you right now.
It's really starting to get on my nerves.
I realize there's no way he can see me,
but because I'm always following
behind you wherever you go,
I feel like I'm constantly being watched.
[Light] That's a problem.
I'll have to get rid of him
as soon as possible.
Who would be following me?
[door squeaks]
Does this mean L is already starting
to suspect the police?
If he's gonna investigate the police,
he'll need a lot of resources
and manpower.
Even if he has as many
as 50 people on the case,
I don't see how they could ever figure out
that I'm Kira.
I shouldn't look like anything other
than your average high school senior.
But the longer I let this person
keep following me,
the greater the chance
is they'll figure out who I really am.
Above all…
I need my stalker's name.
Once I figure that out,
I can get rid of him for good.
-[Ryuk] Light.
-[Light] Hm?
[Ryuk] I'm gonna let you in
on a little secret.
What makes a Shinigami and a human
who has a Death Note different?
Well, there are two things.
And why do Shinigami
have to write the names of humans
in their Death Notes?
You got any ideas?
Of course not. Why would I know that?
You know, you sure are talkative today.
It's because we are able
to take human lifespans for ourselves.
Huh? Wait, what do you mean by that?
Let's say you have a human
who is due to live until the age of 60
and a God of Death wrote
that this person would die at 40.
Sixty minus 40 equals 20.
Now those 20 years
taken from someone in the human world
are added to that God of Death's life.
Huh.
So, it means that
as long as we don't slack off,
even if someone
was to shoot us in the head,
or stab us in the heart with a knife,
a God of Death cannot die.
On the other hand,
no matter how many names
you write in your Death Note,
your lifespan will not increase.
That is the first difference
between gods of death and humans
who possess a Death Note.
[chuckles] That's something
about Shinigami
that I haven't heard before.
Pretty interesting stuff.
The second difference between us
will probably be
of even greater interest to you.
Though this has less to do
with lengthening life
and more to do with cutting it short.
What do you mean cutting it short?
Shinigami can tell what the person's name
is by just looking at their face.
We know instantly.
And do you have any idea why?
Because through a Shinigami's eyes,
a human's name
can be seen above their head.
Not only that,
we see their lifespan as well.
Their name and lifespan?
LIGHT YAGAMI
[Ryuk] That's right. I'm able to see
your name and lifespan right now.
[tense music playing]
[Ryuk] If I converted that to human time,
I could tell you
how many years you've got left.
But there's no way I'd ever tell you that.
I may have a big mouth,
but even I wouldn't go that far.
[laughs]
Shinigami never have to worry
that they won't be able to kill a person
just because they don't know their name,
and every time we do take a life,
we always know exactly how many years
we are going to receive.
Our eyes just aren't the same,
and that is the difference
between you and I.
However…
if a Shinigami drops his Death Note
and a human picks it up,
he can grant that human
the eyes of a Shinigami,
but only if a deal is made,
one that has been with us
since ancient times.
And what's the deal?
The price for having the Shinigami's eyes…
is half of that person's
remaining lifespan.
That's all it is.
Half of my remaining lifespan?
[Ryuk] Yeah.
In other words,
if you are supposed to live
another 50 years, it'll be 25.
If it was one more year, then six months.
I see.
And since you've made it clear
you're not on anyone's side,
and won't help me out,
you wouldn't just give me
the names of people I want to kill.
Basically, you're saying that I can't
simply borrow your powers.
I'd have to pay for them.
That's right.
It's a key part of the code
that all Shinigami are bound by.
I'll say this once more.
Give me half your remaining lifespan,
and I'll give you the Shinigami Eyes.
If I agree…
I'll be able to know everyone's name
just by looking at them.
If I had that power,
the Death Note
would only be easier to use.
So, what'll it be, Light?
Is it a deal?
[music concludes]
TO BE CONTINUED
[theme song playing]
[music concludes]