[theme music playing]
[Near] The Second L,
and the person I think is Kira,
can only be one man.
Light Yagami.
This is Kiyomi Takada from News 6.
I have an announcement
that comes directly from Kira.
His words are to become
the new law of the world.
I've just had an idea.
I think we can make use
of Kiyomi Takada.
Please excuse me.
[gasps] Kira...
-[Matsuda] He's removing the bugs?
-We don't have a choice.
Listen, Kiyomi…
I am the real Kira.
[gasps]
Light is... Kira?
SCORN
[Near] All the pieces
have fallen into place.
Now that things have come this far,
it's my turn to go to Japan.
Commander Rester?
Yes.
I'm afraid I need you
to return to New York immediately.
Right now?
Yes, I'm intending to go to Japan.
Alright. So you would like me
to stay in New York while you're gone?
Not at all.
Then what's the point of me
coming back there?
Truth is, I've never made
travel arrangements
or boarded a flight on my own before.
That's why I need you to come back,
so you can escort me.
Understood.
[plane engines roaring]
[Matsuda] We got 'em!
Both Yoshida Productions and NHN
are practically begging us now.
The Great Misa-Misa Comeback Plan
was a huge success!
These days, it's nearly impossible
for anyone to get into NHN,
but this will get us full access.
Yeah, that's right.
Mogi will be gaining entry
as Misa's manager.
It'll definitely be to our advantage
to have someone
who can go in and out freely.
In the meantime,
I'll continue investigating Takada.
-[beeping]
-[all] Hmm?
This is Near. I want to speak to L.
This is L. What is it you want from us?
I'm following through with my goal
to arrest Kira.
And that's why I'm in Japan now.
He's in Japan?
Why tell me?
He's up to something.
[Near] L, I presume
you've already contacted Takada
for the purposes
of your own investigation?
[men] Huh?
That's right. In fact, I'm investigating
her myself at the moment.
I see.
For the time being,
it's a given that if we want
to get any closer to capturing Kira,
we'll have to keep an eye on
Kiyomi Takada and NHN in general.
I want you to pass on a message.
Inform her that as of now,
several SPK members have entered Japan
in order to catch and arrest Kira.
Huh? But why do that?
To lure Kira out of hiding.
[all gasping]
[Near] I also want you to mention
the following to her,
so she'll relay it to Kira.
In total, there are only four
active members of the SPK.
That includes myself.
Kira won't be able to resist
such an opportunity.
Knowing him, he won't run.
Instead, he'll try to kill us
before we get too close.
That's where I'll beat him
at his own game.
[Light] Beat me at my own game, huh?
[tense music playing]
Alright, Near.
If that's how you want it,
I'll accept your challenge.
I am in Japan, as we speak.
I am in Japan as well.
Then we'll be quite close to each other.
Who knows? We might even
have the chance to meet face to face.
I hope so.
[Near] Well, that'll be something
to look forward to.
[Light] Yes.
[Near] When that time comes, we'll finish
this Kira matter once and for all.
[Light] Definitely.
It's all becoming clear to me.
From the very beginning and even now,
it's been a one-on-one fight against L.
And even though he's dead,
the battle's just shifted to his heirs.
Very well, Near.
Fine, I'll come out to play if you will.
It's only fair, after all.
And when we meet,
we'll find out which of us
is truly prepared to win
and whose wits will prevail.
When that happens,
this long battle will end
and I can finally begin
my reign at the top!
[Near] First, let's review
what we know so far.
L is Light Yagami...
and he's also Kira.
For now, we'll call him L-Kira.
There's also another one.
Someone who has the notebook
and is currently using it.
We'll call him X-Kira.
Judging by the pattern
of X-Kira's killings,
he has definitely made the deal
and acquired the Shinigami eyes.
L-Kira and X-Kira
can't communicate directly.
They must be planning to communicate
using Takada as a go-between.
So, given the situation as it now stands,
there are two ways to win against Kira.
One, the simple way.
We arrange to kill both L-Kira and X-Kira
and confiscate the notebook.
However, no matter what might happen,
we will never resort to that.
Why not?
[Near] That's not the way we work,
Commander.
"We," sir?
Yes, that's right.
We kill those two and the murders stop.
Such ex post facto justification
will not be tolerated.
That's not the way L and I do things.
Because that would be an insult.
Don't forget, L entrusted this case
to those who came after him.
[sounds of traffic]
[car engine revving]
So, Kiyomi, I heard on the news
the other day
that you receive an enormous amount
of fan mail every day.
[Kiyomi] Yes. I'm told, on average,
it's about two hundred letters a day.
[Light] Two hundred letters?
Wow, I'm a little jealous.
Man, this is kind of boring listening
to audio only without any video feed.
I think you should look through them,
even if they are just letters from fans.
You're right.
[Light] "Keep calm as you read this note
and the ones that follow.
Make sure not to let the people
listening to this conversation
hear your reactions."
Huh?
[Light] The SPK has started
to make its move.
You have to start thinking
about your safety.
Instead of only accepting messages
from Kira,
maybe you should consider making
a few demands of your own.
Uh, Light's getting down to business.
[Light] You shouldn't only be
a spokesperson.
Your voice should be heard as well.
Reach out to Kira.
Tell him what you think he needs to know.
[Light] "I have a different job for T.
In order to create the perfect world
that Kira has envisioned,
I want you to begin judging
and punishing people as Kira."
[gasps]
It's all right, Kiyomi.
I have faith in you. It's gonna be okay.
If you can do this, I'm sure
you'll be able to send Kira information
that you don't want the SPK to know about.
[Kiyomi] All right. I'll do it.
-We nailed it.
-That's our Light for you. He's good.
[Teru] Delete, delete…
Delete.
-[phone ringing]
-Hmm?
[Teru] Kiyomi Takada?
[phone continues ringing]
Yes?
I have an important message for you.
You are to send me a fan letter
that I'll be able to recognize as yours.
You will also enclose something else
in the envelope.
Five blank pages from the notebook.
Carry on with your judgments
and killings as usual
until I receive the letter and the pages.
And how about after you receive them?
You have to stop using the real notebook.
However, you must continue entering names
in a fake notebook.
-A fake?
-That's right.
Make a notebook that looks
as close to the original as possible
and act as if you're killing people
by using this decoy.
I understand.
[Teru hangs up]
God, what are you planning?
No, it's not my place to question God.
His will is absolute.
My job is to do what God wishes.
[dramatic music playing]
[upbeat theme music]
Huh? What's this?
It's the replacement for Kira's Kingdom.
God, what's wrong with these people?
[TV host] Welcome to the show.
Today, Ms. Takada will introduce
her four new female bodyguards
who were selected after
a rigorous screening process.
The first is the winner
of the 22nd World Karate Championships,
Ms. Tatsumi Ooyama.
The second is a former CIA agent,
Ms. Hal Lidner.
[Light] If there's an SPK member
among these bodyguards,
it would have to be Hal Lidner.
Looks like Near's conducting
his own investigation of Takada.
[reporter] A phantom killer
who stabbed six people
in Shinjuku's busy quarters...
[Near] Who would I choose
to be X-Kira...
out of all the people in the world?
[Kiyomi on TV] Educating our children
about the existence of Kira
and the meaning of his teachings
must be made mandatory.
Above all, we must teach our children
that Kira is good.
[Near] Takada was chosen
because she's a strong supporter of Kira.
So...
that means X-Kira must be someone who knew
that Takada was a Kira-worshipper,
someone who had a close,
intimate relationship with her
before selection.
Also, Kira will not forgive any crime,
no matter how small.
From this point onwards,
you should assume that any person alive
is a viable target.
[tense, dramatic music playing]
I'd like to hear Kira's voice.
I want to hear his thoughts once again.
We should follow his teachings,
exactly as Kira ordered.
To me, it's obviously the quickest path
to lasting world peace.
THINKING ABOUT THE RECONSTRUCTION OF JAPAN
Youth have a responsibility.
I think it is of the utmost importance
that young people do all they can
to contribute.
It's our duty to improve our society.
If there are no words or orders from Kira,
then we have only one choice.
We need to think for ourselves.
We need to consider
what Kira has taught us,
determine what he wants most
and make our own decisions from there.
[Near] L-Kira is Light Yagami.
Could X-Kira be Teru Mikami?
[voices] Kira's Kingdom... Spokesperson...
[dramatic music playing]
Everything seems to fit into place.
[Misa] That's what I've been asking.
So, tell me why I'm not the headliner.
You said I was supposed to be
the highlight
of the East-West Pop Music Festival.
Well, it's true that you're the highlight.
But when it comes to the headliner,
it's a little harder to secure that spot.
Huh?
[frustrated grunt]
[woman] That's why we should be
taking precautions.
Kiyomi Takada.
What an idiot!
She doesn't even realize that Light's
just using her for his investigation.
Don't say that. You might end up dead
if she hears you.
Duh, I know that.
That's why I whispered it quietly.
[chuckles]
[Misa gasps] Hey!
She snickered at me!
I'm going to go kick her!
Oh, hang on!
[Misa squeals]
What were you trying to do?
What was I doing? What about you?
[groans]
[frustrated grunt]
Lidner, that young lady
is actually a very good friend of mine.
Please, you shouldn't be
so rough with her.
[scoffs]
Of course, Miss Takada.
Please, excuse me.
[Misa yelps]
[Mogi] Uh, Misa-Misa...
Are you all right?
That was so frustrating!
L, this is Near.
I have a small request.
If Mr. Aizawa is there,
would it be possible for me
to speak to him for a moment.
Near, this is Aizawa. What is it?
I have a question regarding surveillance
for L and Takada's meetings.
Are you recording both audio
and video feeds of their conversations?
No, only an audio feed right now.
[Near] I see.
Only wire taps at the moment.
How interesting.
Thank you very much.
If they're only using wire taps,
then it's safe to assume
that L-Kira and X-Kira
have found a way to contact each other
through Takada.
Seems like Lidner could be in more danger
than we realize.
We knew the risks getting into this.
To be blunt, what's important is
that L starts focusing his attention
on Lidner and Takada.
In the meantime, we'll use the opportunity
to investigate Mikami further.
Hmm.
How are things, Gevanni?
Well, about Mikami...
It's strange, it's ridiculously easy
to trail him.
[Gevanni] He's not trying to hide
or anything.
He's lived at the same place
the past four years.
There's nothing unusual about him.
He also seems to be totally dedicated
to his career as a prosecutor.
I'm beginning to think he can't be X-Kira.
No, there is a very high probability
that Mikami is X-Kira.
Please be very careful.
[Near] Don't enter his room yet.
Just keep watch over him for now.
[Gevanni] Gotcha.
[Misa] Man, how many meetings
do I need to have with NHN,
for crying out loud?
And, seriously, how many times
do these people have to tell me,
"Be careful about what you say"?
What's with that?
[Mogi] Yes. Yes, of course.
I'll ask her right now.
Listen, Misa-Misa...
Takada would like to have dinner
with you this evening.
-Just the two of you.
-Huh?
That Kiyomi...
What's she up to?
Good idea!
The music festival's MC should have dinner
with the main performer at least once.
Tell her, "Okay."
[grunts]
Hello?
Miss Takada, she's accepted.
Great. I'm looking forward to it.
Oh, and Lidner?
Please book a nice private room for us.
And, also, I'd like you
to attend the dinner as well.
[gasps]
Yes...
[Christmas choir singing]
[Kiyomi] Misa, I'm sorry to have
to invite you to dinner so late at night.
I'm afraid it had to wait until after
the nine o'clock news was finished.
[Misa] No problem. I don't mind at all.
I'm a night owl anyway.
[Misa gulping wine]
Well, what is it?
I'm not really sure how to answer
a question like that.
So, Light must be pretty busy.
How do you two manage?
[gasps]
Why you...
She knows that I can't see him that much,
while she can be with him all the time!
How dare she?
Things are great between us.
Light is way more affectionate
than he looks, at least with me.
In fact, he starts clinging to me
as soon as he gets in the door
every night.
Ah, I see.
It sounds like you're doing well.
Thank goodness.
Yes. Actually, I should probably tell you,
since you are the MC...
I'm going to announce my engagement
to Light at the Pop Music Festival.
Does he know about this?
Of course, he does. It's an engagement.
It's not as if I can get engaged
to myself!
He proposed to me more than a month ago.
It was so romantic.
Don't you think it'd be exciting
to announce it
at the Pop Music Festival, Miss MC?
Why not?
If you're able to, that is.
What do you mean, "if I'm able to"?
What? Are you not going to let me
announce it?
Or maybe it's something else.
Maybe you're gonna get Kira to kill me.
Of course not.
Only Kira can decide
who he's going to punish.
I have nothing to do with his decisions.
Besides, I've always thought of you
as a good friend, Misa.
You shouldn't say such terrible things.
Anyway, I don't have any intention
of killing anyone,
no matter how horrible they might be.
[grunts in frustration]
Well, whatever.
I used to really like Kira too, you know.
But I know for sure
that Light's gonna catch him soon.
[Misa gulps noisily]
[exhales] Yeah...
Once he gets caught,
it'll be nothing but bad news for him.
And as for you, you'll probably be...
executed.
[Kiyomi gasps]
Miss Takada!
Are you all right?
Huh?
[Kiyomi chuckles]
Listen, Kiyomi. I am the real Kira.
Please, join me, Kiyomi...
and you will be
the goddess of the new world.
-[Kiyomi] Miss Amane?
-Yes?
I find this unpleasant.
[huffs] Oh yeah? I feel the same!
Obviously this was a bad idea.
I should've waited until you grew up
and learned a few manners
before I invited you to dinner.
I suppose I'll know better next time.
-Goodbye.
-Oh...
I'm older than you, Kiyomi.
And, anyways...
you're being childish for storming out
in the middle of dinner
over a silly little comment.
[Misa laughs loudly]
[door opening]
[classical music playing]
[Misa] Hey, Mochi!
Thanks for waiting, Mochi! How are you?
[Mogi] Are you okay?
[Misa] Of course, I am. I won, after all!
-Won?
-Yeah. It was easy!
[Misa giggles]
About tonight's meeting
between Takada and Amane,
they just talked about Light Yagami.
If you read between the lines,
they were arguing over
which one was his lover.
Your thoughts?
All I can determine is this.
Light Yagami is popular with the ladies.
And we know that Takada and Amane
both adore him.
Near, please be serious about this!
[Near] It is serious if they're both
truly in love with him.
They will not easily betray him.
In fact, they'll likely do
whatever he asks.
[train thundering past]
[woman] Please stop!
Come on now, lady.
I mean, wearing a short skirt like that
in the winter?
It's an invitation.
Please, someone!
Hmm?
A cell phone?
[gasps]
[Gevanni] Mikami's just taken out
a notebook.
[wheels grinding]
Delete…
He's writing something in it.
Could that be it?
[Gevanni] He's getting off the train.
[woman screaming]
[woman sobbing]
[suspenseful music playing]
TO BE CONTINUED
[theme music playing]