[theme music plays]
L, I want to meet you.
Daikoku Wharf,
an abandoned warehouse
known as the Yellow Box.
How about three days from now,
on the 28th at 1 p.m.?
That's fine by me.
Take off everything you're wearing
and put it all in that box.
You can use this blanket.
[Light] Miss Takada, are you all right?
Light, I did exactly what you told me to.
I made survival my first priority and...
And I did it.
Come quickly. Save me.
Kiyomi Takada.
Suicide.
January 26, 2013,
-2:32 p.m.
-[loud heartbeat]
[Light] Burns to death by setting fire
to everything around her,
including everything she wrote on.
It is with great sorrow
that I must announce the passing
of one of our very own colleagues.
The police have identified
one of the bodies found at the scene
as NHN's Ms. Kiyomi Takada.
A two-ton truck and a motorcycle
were also found in the ruins
of the burned-out church.
Investigators suspect
gasoline was used to start the fire.
But what I really want to know is
who's gonna be Kira's next spokesperson?
Kira's message still needs to be spread
and someone's gotta do it.
The death of newscaster Takada
was a horrible tragedy,
but I can't help but think
that if she was that careless,
she couldn't have taken her position
as Kira's spokesperson
that seriously.
It needs to be said:
this is not a woman's job.
Kira, please make me
your new representative.
KIRA'S KINGDOM
No. Give the honor to Sakura TV again!
Disgusting.
Yeah, I know.
I mean, they just announced her death
and already it's started.
Every TV station airing its own segment
on who should replace her.
It's like she never existed.
Last night's judgments
unfolded just as planned.
That means Takada and Mikami
have had no problems
contacting each other.
There's nothing to worry about.
[signal beeping]
[Aizawa] It's Near!
-Hello, L.
-[Light] Yes?
I don't mean to keep bothering you
but with regards to our meeting...
I wanted to confirm that we are still set
for the 28th at 1 p.m. All right?
Yes.
It's just as I predicted.
He's sticking with the original time.
There's no doubt about it.
Very well.
The 28th, the day after tomorrow.
Right.
[Matsuda] So, the day after tomorrow, huh?
Finally.
-Isn't it getting exciting?
-[Ide] Y-- Yeah.
I can't help but wonder
what Near wants to show us.
Matsuda. Ide.
When the day comes,
there's a good chance
we might all be killed.
Don't you understand that?
-[Near] Gevanni.
-[Gevanni] Yes.
[Near] Will you be able
to make it in time?
Yes, I'll be there for sure.
Commander Rester.
Lidner.
Gevanni.
Let's put our best into this, shall we?
JANUARY 28, 2013
[Near] Good morning, everyone.
[Matsuda] Good morning.
First of all, in regard to Misa Amane,
we've already set her free.
You may call her to confirm it.
[beeping]
[Misa] I don't know what's going on,
but this must be some sort of
compensation or something.
They totally put me up
in the penthouse suite at the Teito Hotel.
Can you believe it?
Now this is more like it! [giggles]
I understand. All right, Misa.
Please, stay there
for a little while longer
until I call you.
[Misa] Okay!
All right, Near.
I need you to connect me with Mogi.
We have the notebook
locked away here.
And in order to open the safe
it's kept in,
we'll need the PIN number
from each member of the team.
[Near] Understood.
I'll connect you to him immediately.
This is Mogi.
The number is 62-324.
[keys beeping]
All that's left is my number.
The killer notebook…
"How to use it…
The human whose name is
written in this notebook shall die.
This note will not take effect
unless the writer has the person's face
in their mind when writing their name.
Therefore, people sharing
the same name will not be affected.
If the cause of death is written
within 40 seconds of writing
the person's name,
it will happen.
If the cause of death
is not specified,
the person will simply die
of a heart attack.
After writing the cause of death,
details of the death should be written
in the next six minutes and 40 seconds."
Near, it's me.
We've discussed it
and it's been decided
that I'll be the one
to carry the notebook.
L, are you sure it's all right with you
if Mr. Aizawa carries it?
Be honest.
Of course.
I chose Aizawa for the job
because we knew you'd prefer that.
I have no problems with it.
[Near] I appreciate it. Thank you.
Well then, we'll see you shortly.
Looks like this is the end.
No, more like the beginning.
The perfect world of Kira.
And those who know
of the notebook’s existence...
all of them... will die!
[car door opens]
There's no mistake, Near is inside.
I checked it out.
All right. Let's do this.
[exhaust fan squeaking]
Near, you're far inferior to L.
You have no right
to be wearing a mask of L.
It's them. Those four are the SPK.
And the one wearing the mask is Near.
[grumbles] Hang on. Am I the only one
who sees something wrong?
He can go around
accusing people of being Kira,
but the fact that he is wearing the mask
says he's only trying to protect himself,
not anyone else.
[Near] It's just a precaution.
There is a good possibility
that Kira has already seen
the faces of everyone in this warehouse,
except for mine.
In fact, he may be writing down your names
as we speak.
So, I'd like to wait for one hour.
No, make it 30 minutes.
That should give us
more than enough time
to see if anyone is being controlled
before they die.
Huh? What?
You're gonna wait and see if we die?
No, it's not impossible
that Light really is Kira.
Especially since the rest of us
are of no use to him anymore.
[ticking]
[exhaust fan squeaking]
This is all just a front
to buy some time, isn't it?
I never thought it would be this hard
to keep myself from laughing out loud.
Near must be waiting for him to come.
It's all just as I predicted.
[squeaking]
[Matsuda] Near! It's already been
over 30 minutes.
-Nothing's happened yet.
-[Light] Of course not.
That's because Kira is not here with us.
Very well.
Everyone seems to be safe.
I'll remove my mask now.
You're quiet, Near. What's wrong?
Are you still waiting for something?
[Near] Waiting.
That's an excellent choice of words.
Yes, I am waiting.
For the arrival of the one who will
solve everything, once and for all.
Someone else is supposed
to clear this up?
[Near] He'll be here soon.
It's only a matter of time.
There's only one entrance
to this building.
And the only way to look inside
is by opening that door.
That means
he will either through that door,
or at the very least open it
and peek through.
And just who is this person anyway?
X-Kira, the one
who's currently using the notebook
and killing people on Kira's behalf.
He's bound to come here
and bring the notebook with him,
and then he'll see me
and write down my real name.
Or rather, he'll write down
the names of everyone here
who knows about the notebook
and kill them.
[all gasping]
[Matsuda] What?
What are you saying?
This isn't making any sense.
What are you trying to tell us, Near?
That some other guy
is gonna drop by with the notebook,
poke his head in and kill us all?
And you want us to sit back
and let it happen?
[Near] Yes, that's correct.
Now, listen carefully.
If someone comes in to the warehouse
through that door,
just let him in without resisting.
If the door opens slightly,
simply act as if you don't notice
anyone there.
But-- But that's just crazy!
[Near] He's already here.
-[squeaking becomes louder]
-[all gasping]
LIGHT YAGAMI
[Mikami] God!
[Mikami] Delete. Delete. Delete...
-Delete. Delete. Delete. Delete.
-[rat squeaking]
Delete. Delete. Delete.
Delete. Delete. Delete!
Delete. Delete. Delete...
Hold it! Don't do anything!
Everything is fine. You won't die.
[Light] How can you be so sure, Near?
-[Mikami] Delete. Delete. Delete...
-Because I modified the notebook.
[gasping]
[Near] We took repossession
of the notebook
-and replaced the pages.
-[Mikami] Delete....
[Near] The person behind the door
has been doing the killings for Kira.
He has also been using
exactly one page every day.
Based on that, I was able to replace
the page he'd use today,
as well as all subsequent pages,
so that no one else would die.
[Mikami] Delete. Delete. Delete.
Delete. Delete.
Delete!
[yells] Delete!
[sighs]
[Near] On the other side of that door
is X-Kira.
My guess is, in roughly 40 seconds
he'll look inside to see if we're dead.
That's when we'll restrain him
and seize the notebook.
Whoever's name is not written down,
must be Kira.
[Aizawa] It's true.
Kira would be the only one
that guy wouldn't try to kill.
But still...
[stifles laugh]
[Light] I knew it! I knew it! I knew it!
I knew all along
you had tampered with the notebook.
Near, you've been completely defeated!
The notebook you altered was nothing more
than a forgery I had Mikami prepare.
On the other hand,
the one Mikami's writing their names in,
is the real notebook,
which had been kept hidden until now.
[laughing crazily]
I had Mikami
create a fake notebook for himself.
He also sent Takada several pages
from the real one.
So, in fact, it was Takada, not Mikami,
who was doing the killings.
As for Mikami,
I had him write names in public
several times,
using the fake notebook.
That way he would be noticed
by anyone who was following him.
But Takada was the one behind the deaths.
Mikami simply sent the names and faces
by cell phone.
This little performance was
how I made the SPK believe
that the Notebook Mikami used
was the real one.
Mikami's daily behavior is so methodical
it's almost obsessive.
He always fills exactly one page
with names every day.
And Near,
you noticed this little habit
and thought you could use it
to tamper with the notebook.
All you had to do
was count ahead to the page
he'd use on the day of this meeting.
Then you replaced all the pages
from that day onwards.
You'd be confident that you
could prevent anyone from dying.
That was your big plan.
That's why you couldn't change
the date and time of our meeting.
But I was one step ahead of you, Near.
I always knew you were going to try
and alter the Death Note.
That's why I had Mikami
check the notebook every day
MATSUMOTO
for signs of tampering.
I've confirmed it.
[gasps]
TO: KIYOMI TAKADA
I'M DYING TO SEE YOU
I knew I'd won this game
as soon as I got that message.
Mikami brought a different notebook today,
the real one,
which had been kept hidden until now.
But you know, Near,
you did have a chance to win,
if only you'd taken it.
You were just too naive.
You're nothing compared to L.
L would have considered the possibility
of a fake notebook
from the very beginning
And he would have tested it.
You had the chance
but you squandered it.
I've gotta say...
I'm so disappointed in you.
This victory was no fun.
You tried too hard
to win in a noble way.
Well, that's fine.
Everyone here dies today,
thanks to you.
And as for me,
I, Kira, will have my perfect victory.
You there, outside.
Huh?
Have you finished
writing down the names in the notebook?
God!
[Mikami] Yes, I've written them.
[all grunt]
[stifles laughter]
No, I can't laugh yet.
I've gotta hold it in.
They're all gonna die 40 seconds
after he wrote down their names.
Thirty-five seconds...
I'll claim my victory then!
[Near] Don't you think it's rather odd?
Huh?
Why would he answer you
so quickly, calmly and honestly,
when you asked him
if he had written down our names yet?
[Light] Who knows? Maybe he's just honest.
Or confident that he'll succeed,
or perhaps he's seen
through your brilliant plan.
[Matsuda] Huh? In that case,
we're in big trouble.
Teru Mikami.
If it's not too much trouble for you,
won't you please come in
and join us.
I already know that you're the one
who's been judging
and executing people for Kira.
If you've already written down our names
then there shouldn't be anything
to be afraid of,
you can come right on in.
Teru Mikami, is it?
He's correct.
There's no reason to hide from us.
-You can come in.
-[men gasp]
God!
You've done well, Mikami.
How many seconds has it been
since you wrote down the first name?
Thirty seconds.
31... 32...
33… 34…
35… 36…
37...
38!
39!
Well, Near, looks like I win.
[Mikami] Forty!
TO BE CONTINUED
[theme music plays]