[theme music plays]
UNRAVELING
[all gasping]
[both] Huh?
[all] Huh...
I am L.
[Yagami] This is him?
[Matsuda] Hmm.
He's nothing like I thought he'd be.
Uh...
Hmm...
I'm Yagami of the NPA.
I'm Matsuda.
I'm Aizawa.
-Mogi.
-Ukita.
I'm very sorry we're late.
Currently, the five of us are...
Bang!
-Huh?
-What the hell was that?
Hmm.
If I were Kira you would be dead,
Mr. Soichiro Yagami,
Chief of the NPA.
[all exclaiming]
Kira needs a face and a name
in order to commit murder,
but I'm sure you've already figured
that much out, haven't you?
Please do not give out
your names so carelessly.
Instead...
let's value our lives.
I knew that he needed a face
to kill someone,
but I don't remember any evidence
that showed that he needed a name too.
There's no way to verify
if this is related to criminals
whose names were never released publicly
or whose names were spelled incorrectly
in the media have not been targeted.
We briefly went over it
at one of our meetings.
[L] That's enough small talk for now.
Come this way.
Oh, right.
[L] Please turn off
all your cellphones, handhelds,
and any other communication devices
and leave them on the table right there.
What? Do you think we're going to be
using our cellphones during this meeting
to leak information?
It's all right. Just do as he says.
[Matsuda] I realize he's been cautious
from the very beginning,
but I still can't tell
if he trusts us or not.
[L] No, I just find them distracting.
I can't stand it when people's cellphones
are ringing while I'm trying to talk.
Let me start by saying nobody takes notes
on anything that's said in these meetings.
That means, when we leave Headquarters,
any information we need
is committed to memory.
Please, make yourselves comfortable.
[grunts] Right.
[sips loudly]
[gulps loudly]
[groans]
-Excuse me, L?
-[L] Hmm.
And from now on, I'll have to ask
that you stop calling me "L."
It's "Ryuzaki" now, just to be safe.
Uh, okay, Ryuzaki...
if we know that he needs
a name and a face to kill,
couldn't we cut down on
the number of victims
by keeping criminals' names from the news?
If we do that, we'll only be putting
the general public at risk.
-The general public?
-Why?
Kira is childish and he hates losing.
But how do you...?
Just what do you mean?
Well...
I'm also childish and I hate to lose.
That's how I know.
Ryuzaki…
Would you mind being
a little more specific for us?
Early on in the investigation,
I tried to provoke Kira
with that broadcast.
[L] Up until then, we thought
that Kira would only go after criminals.
But as we all witnessed,
he didn't hesitate to kill my stand-in.
Also, as soon as I said we knew
he was in the Kanto region,
in defiance, he made sure his next victims
came from within Japan,
as if to say,
"What are you gonna do about it?"
[slurps]
He's met each of my challenges head on
and he's never missed an opportunity
to return the favor.
Now, what do you think would happen
if we tried to use media restrictions
to hide criminals from someone like that?
I guess...
"If you choose to withhold the names
of your worst criminals,
I'll kill petty criminals or the innocent.
I'm holding the whole world hostage,
so who's it gonna be?
I'm not the evil one here.
But all those who oppose me
by hiding criminals, you are truly evil."
[L sighs]
That's exactly how Kira thinks.
In any case, let's look at another way
we can use the media to draw him out.
But how?
How about something like this?
"Death of FBI agents infuriates the U.S.
Latest killings anger
the international policing community.
Nations agree to send 1,500 investigators
to Japan."
For Kira, this will be way beyond
what he faced with the FBI.
He'll see everyone as a potential threat.
Psychologically,
he'll start to feel cornered,
and that will cause him
to take some kind of drastic action.
T-- That's interesting.
So he'll think there are 1,500,
when there really are only seven of us.
And since none
of these investigators exist,
Kira won't be able to kill them.
It just might work!
Well, before we celebrate,
I'll tell you the rest of my thoughts
on the Kira case.
[all grunting]
Kira works alone.
He had access
to all our classified information.
What evidence do you have
that he's working alone?
Hold on, Aizawa.
Let's listen to his entire theory
before asking questions.
We know he needs
a name and a face to kill.
And, to some extent,
he can control a victim's' time of death
and their actions before dying.
[L] We already know that much.
Please keep that in mind...
and listen carefully
to what I have to say next.
On December 14,
twelve FBI investigators entered Japan.
ENTER JAPAN
And here we are on December 19…
Using prison inmates,
Kira conducts experiments,
manipulating his victims' actions
before they die.
12/19 TEST
12/14 FBI (12) ENTER JAPAN
In other words, during this window
of only five days,
Kira became aware of the FBI's presence
and obviously felt threatened.
Because he didn't know
any of their names or faces,
he was at a disadvantage.
He needed to know how much control
he had over his victims
before he could use it
against the twelve agents.
And as we all know, on December 27…
[Light] I got a hold of a file
which contained all the names and faces
of the FBI investigators in Japan,
and I succeeded
in killing each one of them.
It's practically impossible to guess
which agent gave the file to Kira.
But I have to make sure
that no one ever finds out
that I came into contact with Raye Penber.
12/20 BUS
Huh? How come you're not using
the Death Note today?
You studying for those entrance exams?
Those are the least of my worries.
Plus, it's a little late to start now.
Oh? Whatcha doing?
December 19 to December 27...
I've been most active during this period.
During this period,
to the best of our knowledge,
at least twenty-three individuals
died of heart attacks.
But these victims were different
from Kira's previous targets.
They were all alleged criminals,
ex-convicts,
or suspects in ongoing investigations.
So, legally speaking, they were innocent.
That's true.
What this indicates is that Kira had
to manipulate these lesser criminals
in order to kill those FBI agents.
He killed that many people
so we'd be unable to tell the decoys
from those who were actually used.
In truth, he probably only needed a few.
He waited eight days
so the FBI could investigate
other suspects,
which meant there'd be no timeline
linking him to their deaths.
I suspect Kira had to be one of the people
being investigated by the FBI,
between the 14th and the 19th of December.
In fact, I have no doubt.
[all gasping]
These are files provided by the FBI.
And they contain additional information
you might find useful.
For obvious reasons, you're not permitted
to take these out of this room.
-But...
-[Matsuda] Amazing!
There might only be five of us,
but with this much information,
we should be able to cover
a lot of ground.
[Aizawa] We'll split into two teams.
One team traces the FBI agents,
the other looks at
the heart attack victims.
There weren't that many people
who had access
to information from headquarters.
And of those, the FBI only investigated
a small group in the first five days.
Yeah. Yeah...
So, does anyone have any questions?
Huh?
[Yagami] Actually, Ryuzaki,
I do have one question for you.
And it pertains to what you said
to us earlier about how you hate to lose.
Does the fact that you've shown us
your face mean that you've lost?
By just being here,
are you admitting defeat to Kira?
That's right.
By showing my face to you now
and by sacrificing the lives
of twelve FBI agents,
I have lost the battle.
But I'm not going to lose the war.
This is the first time
I've ever put my life on the line.
I want to show Kira that we're all willing
to risk our lives,
if that's what it takes.
[chuckles] And that justice will prevail,
no matter what.
Hey, yeah, that's right.
I like the sound of that.
We can do this!
All right then. Let's do this, Ryuzaki.
[Yagami] Well, I had my doubts
about whether it was really him at first,
but there's no mistaking it.
This man is L.
Before we go any further, I have to be
absolutely sure that none of you are Kira.
So I'll need to speak with each of you
individually before you leave today.
Huh?
What's the deal?
He still doesn't trust us?
[Yagami]
No. I think it's a fair request.
Try to see it from his perspective.
Kira's been getting information
from our headquarters
from the very beginning.
So there's a good chance
that he's one of us.
Chief's right. Working this case
has given us a chance
to see him in person.
He's risking his life to be here.
[L] Things are going well.
Just one clue, a single decisive factor,
is all I need.
[Light] Just one oversight...
A single piece of evidence
is all it would take.
It could cost me my life.
-Just one thing…
[cars honking]
[birds chirping]
[Ryuk] You already finished studying?
I guess.
I'll be fine. I haven't missed anything.
The biggest risk I've taken so far
was that bus-jacking incident.
But they'll never be able
to connect it with Kira.
Fortunately for me,
both the police and L don't know
that Kira can kill people by means
other than a heart attack.
However, if anyone were
to discover that fact,
I'd be in a lot of trouble.
What? Does it have to be now?
Your father's been pulling overnighters
with no change of clothes.
So you're going to bring this to him.
But, Mom, I totally promised my friends
that I'd go out with them today.
Why don't I go? I could use a break.
Thanks, Light!
I owe you one next time.
So, I guess this'll give you a chance
to spy on the police.
I won't go further
than the reception desk.
[suspenseful music playing]
[Ryuk] Oh, you're bringing a page?
Planning to kill someone?
No, but lately, I've been bringing
a page with me every time I go out.
Just in case.
[Naomi] That day…
Raye said that he was planning
to go to Shinjuku.
That same day, four people died
of heart attacks in the Shinjuku area.
And... there was the bus-jacking.
BUS-JACKER DIES
AFTER BEING HIT BY CAR
There's no way it was a coincidence.
NATIONAL POLICE AGENCY
AND PUBLIC SAFETY COMMISSION
That's it!
Kira can kill in other ways.
It doesn't have to be a heart attack.
The mobile customer
you are trying to reach...
That's unusual for Dad.
[phone beeps]
[Light] I wonder if he's in a meeting
right now.
[Naomi] Please.
I need to speak directly with someone
from the special investigation Task Force.
It's urgent.
I'm sorry, ma'am, but I can't help you.
As I've told you already, there is no one
at Task Force headquarters right now.
There's no one at Headquarters?
Dad's cell is turned off.
What's going on?
[Naomi] Can't you contact them somehow?
I have information
relating to the Kira investigation.
The Kira investigation?
Look, I'll call Headquarters
one more time for you.
One moment.
Hi, I'm Detective Soichiro Yagami's son,
Light Yagami.
I brought my father a change of clothes
but it doesn't look like he's in.
Can I leave them here?
Sure. Hey,
I haven't seen you in a while, Light.
Oh, I'm sorry. Uh...
What? You don't remember?
You helped solve the insurance fraud
murder investigation sometime last year.
But, hey, no one remembers a receptionist,
do they?
Oh, I'm sorry. I'm terrible with faces.
I just need to sign my name
on this form, right?
So, Light, does this mean
you're going to be helping us
with the Kira investigation too?
Sure, if all goes well,
maybe I'll find Kira before L does.
Find him before L does?
As I thought,
there's no one at Headquarters.
You're gonna have to trust me
on this, ma'am.
I'll be sure to give them your message
as soon as I see them, I promise.
[Naomi] That's not good enough.
I have to tell them in person.
[Light] Excuse me.
My father is actually in charge
of the Kira investigation.
If you'd like, I could pass your message
on to him?
His cellphone is off at the moment,
but I should be able to contact him soon.
A number of FBI agents were just killed.
And a lot of detectives have quit the case
because they're afraid of Kira.
So he's pretty busy right now.
Uh, Light, it's probably better
if you don't discuss this with...
True, but it's practically
common knowledge at this point.
Besides, I feel like I can trust her.
You can almost see it in her eyes.
She's a wise and careful person.
You heard about what happened
and you must have figured out
that the police had a leak of some kind.
And that's why you wanted
to tell them in person.
You thought this through.
Well, am I right?
[gasps]
I'm sure my father will be calling me back
once he checks his messages.
When he does, I'll give you the phone
and let you talk to him.
You sure that's all right?
Oh, yeah.
You understand why I can't just give you
my father's cellphone number,
but I have no problem letting you
use my phone to talk to him.
You'll have to trust my father and I,
which I hope won't be
too difficult for you.
[chuckles]
[Ryuk] Why is he so happy?
Thank you so much.
[chuckling]
She walked right into that one,
didn't she?
I've gotta say,
you must be pretty brave
to be getting involved
in the Kira case like this.
[Naomi sighs] Not really.
[Light] So, according to you,
is Kira some...?
[clears throat]
Um, we've been talking, and I just
realized I don't even know your name.
My name is Light Yagami.
Light's written
with the character for "moon"
and Yagami with the characters
for "night" and "god."
Kinda weird, huh?
My name's Shoko Maki.
It's written with the characters
for "shining."
"Ko" as in "child" and "ki" as in "tree."
Ms. Maki, right?
[Ryuk chuckles]
[Light] Ms. Maki,
I've been thinking about Kira's powers.
And I believe they enable him
to somehow control his victims
before they die.
So do I!
It's odd that you say that because
that's exactly what I've been thinking.
Kira's able to control their actions
before he kills them.
But there's more to it.
If my analysis so far is correct,
Kira can kill in a number of ways,
not just with a heart attack.
[Light] She knows? Who is this woman?
I don't think anyone else knows this yet.
But if the police
are willing to consider it,
I bet it would help them catch Kira.
You know, that possibility
never even crossed my mind.
So, what you're saying is,
any time Kira wants one of his murders
to go undetected,
he wouldn't use a heart attack.
Right.
I'm almost positive that someone I know
may have met Kira.
Met Kira?
[Light laughs]
I'm sorry, but if a person came in
saying they'd met Kira,
the police would be more
than a little skeptical, to say the least.
[Naomi] I know.
That's why I need to explain it in person
to someone from Task Force headquarters.
Otherwise, I'm afraid
they'd just write me off.
But wouldn't it be better
if your friend spoke to them instead?
He probably would,
but he's no longer alive.
He was one of the twelve FBI agents
who came to Japan to investigate Kira.
An FBI agent who met Kira...
Could it be?
[Naomi] You see, he was also my fiancé.
While he was working, he got caught up
in a bus-jacking
and I have reason to believe
that he met Kira on that bus.
Raye Penber!
Is something wrong?
Nothing. I'm sorry to hear
that he passed away.
So... what makes you think
he met Kira on that bus?
Because eight days
after that bus was hijacked...
he died, along with the other
FBI investigators.
The same man had attempted to rob a bank
two days before he hijacked that bus.
And he dies in an accident?
Just like that?
I mean, really, what are the odds?
I've come to believe
that Kira set up that bus-jacking.
It was planned to bring him
into contact with my fiancé,
in order to obtain information regarding
the identities of the other FBI agents,
so he could get rid of them all.
Anyway, what stands out to me
is that the hijacker died in an accident.
In other words,
it suggests that heart attacks
aren't the only way Kira can kill people.
[Light] Okay, so the bus-jacker
didn't die of a heart attack.
And based on that, you're saying
Kira has other ways of killing people?
Yes.
Don't take this the wrong way, but I think
that's a bit of a leap of faith.
There's no other way of looking at it.
If Kira was controlling the hijacker,
chances are he killed him too.
[Light] I still don't see it.
I've been wondering about that bus-jacking
ever since my fiancé
first told me about it.
After he calmed down,
I asked him for details.
He didn't mention any names
or anything like that,
-but he told me one thing.
-[Light] What did he say?
That he'd been put in a situation where
he had to show his FBI ID to someone.
Hmm?
The operation was undertaken secretly
without the NPA's knowledge.
He wasn't allowed to show his ID.
I think, whoever saw his ID that day
was responsible for the deaths
of all of the agents.
[Ryuk] Unbelievable. She figured it out.
This must be the oversight
Light was worried about.
[Light] I understand.
You're the only one who knows any of this.
And you want nothing more
than to avenge your fiancé
by bringing Kira to justice, right?
And now you're convinced that Kira
can kill without using a heart attack?
Yes.
[Light] There's no doubt in my mind
your deductive skills are excellent.
But you can't deny that you have
a personal interest in the case.
Still, your theory is worth looking into.
That's for sure.
Your testimony could be central
to the case.
It could.
If what you're telling me is true,
then it will only be a matter of time
before the police catch up with Kira.
The person your fiancé showed his ID to
on the bus that day...
it had to be Kira.
That's right.
[Light] That was close.
This woman...
If she'd spoken to the police
before I met her...
But it seems there's a god
on my side after all.
And not just a god of death.
TO BE CONTINUED
[theme music plays]