It's no use...
We can't win!
Save me...!
The chance to be a hero is long gone...
Dug myself into a hole with no way out
Back against the wall... I
mean, how could I resist?
"This wasn't supposed to
happen," I keep denying
I wish I could just disappear...
I can't stand myself
Moping around, spouting lies,
grieving a broken heart
I hold on desperately to these
feelings and shut my eyes
So why does this stupid
guilt refuse to go away?!
I suffocate under its weight
The chance to be a hero is long gone...
Always discouraged by my weaknesses,
I drop to my knees and grovel at your feet,
clinging selfishly to
the hope for forgiveness
Dug myself into a hole with no way out...
Full of regret and powerless to change,
I feel my heart being torn apart
on this night of endless shame and despair
Why can't I get my act together?
Got nothing but this pathetic self of mine...
Episode 4: Peter Grill and Bathing Etiquette
Luvellia-senpai!
Save me...
Peter-kun!
It's pure evil...!
Can Peter-san handle that
creature all on his own...?
Of course!
He'll be fine. Don't worry.
How dare you lay a hand...
ON LUVELLIA-SENPAI?!
The man you see before you is the
strongest warrior on the planet.
Hell yeah!
Incredible...
He totally kicked that thing's ass!
Whoa, talk about awesome!
No one stands a chance against Senpai!
We're lookin' at the strongest
man alive, Big Sis!
Yes... Right you are, Mimi.
This merely reaffirms our mission to incorporate his
genetic superiority into our bloodline at any cost.
Aren'tcha glad we hightailed it to the Warriors Guild as soon
as we caught wind of him?!
Witnessing such extraordinary
combat prowess...
Horny
Makes me wet!
Same!
Are you hurt?
Thank you, Peter-kun.
This serves as proof...
That I'd be completely lost without you.
Luvellia-senpai...
Peter Grill! Peter Grill! Peter Grill!
Well, this is... awkward.
Fortunately, Luvellia-senpai
suffered only minor injuries.
And the local townspeople were grateful
to us for ridding them of the creature, too.
So then... why?!
What's with this raging boner?!
Leftover adrenaline from the battle, maybe?
No, it's been several hours. There's no way!
And in the aftermath...
Check it out!
The dude rescued an entire village
and yet he's still so humble!
Of course.
Real heroes don't walk around
actin' all high and mighty.
Wait a minute...
Could it have something to do with
the spell that Elf cast on me...?
Right on the money!
Y-you?!
It appears you've grown since
we last met, Peter Grill.
Let me guess:
You're beginning to regret your foolish decision
to refuse an arrangement with the
exquisite Vegan Eldoriel, aren't you?
So the reason I've been
pitchin' a tent is...?
Precisely, a forbidden curse passed
down amongst my brethren:
"The Eternal Erection."
Subjects upon whom the curse is cast experience
a sense of insatiable arousal in their nether regions.
Before long, this causes damage
to the penile tissues...
Resulting in the permanent
inability to pop a pocket rocket!
WHAAAT?!
Losing a major function of your manhood
and turning into a dusty old geezer
at such a young age sounds
awfully miserable...
Please, not that! Anything but that!
I'm begging you!
Come again?
You'll have to speak up.
I couldn't quite hear you...
Please!
Please break the curse!
DAMN ELF...!
Very well. Calm down!
If you insist, I shall break the curse.
However...
Once this type of magic has been cast,
there's only one way to reverse its effects.
To put it simply...
You must deposit your juices...
Right here!
Spilling your sweet gravy inside
of me is the only option.
Wha-?!
You can't possibly expect me to do that!
Luvellia-senpai is the only woman for me!
Peter-kun...
Luvellia-senpai?
So it WAS you.
I thought I heard a familiar voice.
This hot spring is wonderful, isn't it?
And the water is so soothing...
I can feel my cuts and
bruises healing as we speak.
By the way, Peter-kun...
Have you heard the legends
surrounding this resort?
Huh?! Wh-what are you talking about?!
The village itself is famous
for its hot springs.
However, this particular spring is unique.
It flows from a special source and is
said to have a rather fascinating effect.
According to the rumors,
those who soak themselves in these mysterious
waters shall be blessed with children...
So, um...
What do you think?
You could join me...
And we...
We could test out the effects
of the hot spring together...
S-SAY WHAT?!
Am I dreaming?! Hallucinating?!
Senpai...
SHE'S... asking ME?
I never thought I'd see the day...!
This is...
In the past two years,
we haven't progressed towards any sort of
physical intimacy other than holding hands.
This is a once-in-a-lifetime chance
to take things to the next level!
There's just one problem...
My crown jewels are practically
on the verge of exploding!
So, what will you choose?
The suspense is killing me...
I absolutely CANNOT afford
to waste this opportunity...!
But...
But...!
Luvellia-senpai...
I...
I...!
Forgive me!
I'm afraid I can't...
Now isn't a good time...
O-Oh...
Well, it was a bit sudden.
And besides, the others might see us.
Although, it's a shame...
Perhaps if we took a bath and
said a prayer together...
The stork would descend
upon us from the heavens...
With our future child in tow...
I'm sorry!
I'm so sorry, Senpai...!
A wise decision.
Now then, Peter Grill...
Shouldn't you be pleading for mercy?
Isn't there something you wish to ask of me?
I'm begging you!
Please, take it!
End this torture and take my load!
Game over...
Any shred of self-respect
I had left as a warrior...
It's been smashed up into little pieces...!
Still...
I'm merely doing what's necessary
to protect my future with Senpai!
Come, it's time to drop
this pathetic charade.
I'm ready when you are, Peter Grill.
Exactly!
This doesn't count...
It's not even CLOSE to cheating!
I've got no choice...
It's totally...
Out of my hands...
Y-You've got some pretty good moves...
It started out as a simple crush
Suddenly, you were my
biggest source of strength
Till death do us part,
let's grow old together
This is my sincerest wish:
Stay with me, stay with me
So long time, by my side for all eternity
Beaten down by our daily struggles
Or soaked by a storm of rage;
If you get drenched, I won't hesitate
To be the umbrella that shields you
It's not so cold... I'm by your side
That's good enough for me
You're my rock, my strength
That smile of yours puts my soul at ease
I could search the whole world over
And find no one like you
You're my rock, my strength
Just the sight of you fills my heart with joy
No matter how much it may hurt,
I pledge my life to protecting you
Dear Sir Peter Grill,
Word on the street is you're working
as a diplomat these days.
Just goes to show how much everyone
in the Warriors Guild trusts you, eh?
Episode 5: Peter Grill and
a Blind Date with an Orc