Agape-san...
Agape...!
Given the circumstances...
Perhaps our best course of action is to draw up an
official set of terms concerning Peter Grill's seed.
Indeed.
We must approach this situation
in an efficient manner.
Huh?
A TREATY REGARDING THE ALLOCATION OF
PETER GRILL'S REPRODUCTIVE RESOURCES
A-Are they about to strike
a deal over my crotch?!
The chance to be a hero is long gone...
Dug myself into a hole with no way out
Back against the wall... I
mean, how could I resist?
"This wasn't supposed to
happen," I keep denying
I wish I could just disappear...
I can't stand myself
Moping around, spouting lies,
grieving a broken heart
I hold on desperately to these
feelings and shut my eyes
So why does this stupid
guilt refuse to go away?!
I suffocate under its weight
The chance to be a hero is long gone...
Always discouraged by my weaknesses,
I drop to my knees and grovel at your feet,
clinging selfishly to
the hope for forgiveness
Dug myself into a hole with no way out...
Full of regret and powerless to change,
I feel my heart being torn apart
on this night of endless shame and despair
Why can't I get my act together?
Got nothing but this pathetic self of mine...
'S-Scuse me...
Can anyone hear me...?
Using magic oughtta be banned!
That impact play of yours
is what ought to be banned!
It stimulates the flow
of Senpai's slam chowder!
Episode 8: Peter Grill and the Secret Treaty
Uh...
It stimulates the flow of Senpai's slam chowder!
It stimulates the flow
of Senpai's slam chowder!
Ladies...?
It stimulates the flow of Senpai's slam chowder!
Well, my magic can control
the way he shoots his goo
Hello...?!
Well, my magic can control the way he shoots his goo
Well, my magic can control
the way he shoots his goo
M-more importantly...
I'd like to point out a major
issue with this schedule.
It's biased in your favor!
How observant of you.
It seems you're more than just a pair
of walking boobs, after all...
Unlike that wimpy, long-eared
freak over there!
Who're you calling "wimpy"?!
Hey...!
Then let's reassess the agreement and create
a final draft once we've reached a consensus.
Fine.
Um, what about me...?
Agreed.
Roger!
Um, what about me...?
C'mon, are you listening?!
Don't I get a say?!
Am I invisible or something?!
Gimme a damn break, would you?!
The terms introduced by a unilateral
interspecies treaty were enforced thereafter.
In accordance with the treaty,
Peter Grill carried out his usual,
rigorous duties on a daily basis.
Until...
...the first day of rest following the
treaty's enactment had finally arrived.
What's up, Peter?
You're in a good mood,
gettin' all decked out...
Why, I'm glad you asked, Tim!
Today is a rest day, as
established by the treaty.
I'm going to revel in my freedom and spend
some quality time with Luvellia-senpai...!
I'm well aware of your situation.
A long-overdue date... Have fun, dude.
Hello, Peter-kun.
I hope...
...you weren't waiting for too long.
Is something the matter?
N-No, it's just...
You look even more beautiful than usual.
I couldn't help but stare...
As the old saying goes, "Flattery
will get you nowhere."
Shall we?
I'm in heaven...
When I'm with Luvellia-senpai,
I feel at peace...
The food here is exquisite, isn't it?
As long as you like it,
that's all that matters.
Some of the guys down at the
Guild rave about this place.
I apologize for dragging you along
on my shopping trip, Peter-kun.
Oh, don't mention it.
I had a great time today.
To our future.
May it be bright.
Your hand...
You still have a scar.
How shameful of me...
Carelessly leaving a mark on the world's
strongest warrior like that...
This scar is a badge of honor.
And it's the reason why I get to spend this type
of quality time with my beloved senpai.
But you used to despise
me back then, didn't you?
Don't tease me like that, Senpai.
I wish this moment would last forever...
No way!
Is that you over there, Senpai?!
What a coinkydink!
Is this a joke?!
What the hell is she doing here...?!
Are you on a date, Senpai?
W-Well...
What do you want?
Today's a rest day, right...?
The heck are you talkin' about, Senpai?!
Now's the perfect time to get
a jump on those other guys.
That way, I get to hog your
hog all to myself, y'know?!
Listen here, you...!
Isn't the whole point of a contract
to obey the damn thing?!
W-Wait... Senpai!
You and this young Ogre seem to have become
quite close friends lately, Peter-kun.
Th-That's right!
She asked for my help with combat training.
It's been a real hands-on process...
Oh?
You're kiddin', right?
The only hand involved in that process
is mine wrapped around your
You're comin' with me!
Please excuse us for a
moment, Luvellia-senpai.
Sure...
C'mon, cut me some slack!
This date is a big deal.
Don't blow it for me!
Then how's about we start off with a quickie?
That'll keep me happy for a while!
Don't say "start off with"
like it's an appetizer!
A-Although...
If she keeps hanging around,
the short time I have left with
Luvellia-senpai will go to waste...
WOW!
Senpai...!
A-And once again...
See ya!
I've committed yet another
heinous act of betrayal...
I'd better hurry back before
she gets suspicious...!
You got this!
Luvellia-senpai!
OF COURSE SHE'S HERE, TOO!
For today, let's start off
with something quick and easy.
What about my rest day...?!
A rest day is the perfect time to get
a jump on those other guys!
A rest day is perfect.
The others won't interrupt us.
*Note: The "right to veto" possessed by Peter
Grill is assumed to be largely non-existent.
It seems you and this Elf have grown quite
close with each other lately, Peter-kun.
Y-Yeah...
Fate has a twisted sense of humor...
Bye for now!
O-Okay...
I somehow convinced her to leave...
Luvellia-senpai!
GODDAMMIT!
S-Sir?!
I-It's no use...
They're a total disaster...!
NONE of them have any intention
of following the rules...!
Peter Grill!
You are far too concerned
with the pursuit of strength!
Settling for second best isn't the
right attitude for a captain!
D-Damn it...!
Look out, Captain!
I'm just glad you're safe...
Luvellia-senpai...
Peter-kun...
Perhaps I've had too much wine...
I had a wonderful time today, Peter-kun.
I'm sorry for letting them ruin our date...
Not at all.
As the world's strongest warrior,
your popularity is only natural.
N-Nah...
Well, I must bid you good night.
Father tends to make a fuss
when I return home late.
O-Of course.
Y-You're right...
The Guildmaster can be...
kind of a worrywart.
I wouldn't mind going on a trip together
outside of our Guild duties.
Just the two of us...
Somewhere calm and relaxing...
Th-That sounds nice...
Should I... stop her?
Letting her leave with this
awkwardness between us...
Luvellia-senpai...!
Sir Peter!
Nut butter...!
If something doesn't change...
I'm not sure how much longer I'll be
able to endure their torture
and still manage to protect my
relationship with Luvellia-senpai...!
It started out as a simple crush
Suddenly, you were my
biggest source of strength
Till death do us part,
let's grow old together
This is my sincerest wish:
Stay with me, stay with me
So long time, by my side for all eternity
Beaten down by our daily struggles
Or soaked by a storm of rage;
If you get drenched, I won't hesitate
To be the umbrella that shields you
It's not so cold... I'm by your side
That's good enough for me
You're my rock, my strength
That smile of yours puts my soul at ease
I could search the whole world over
And find no one like you
You're my rock, my strength
Just the sight of you fills my heart with joy
No matter how much it may hurt,
I pledge my life to protecting you
Dear Sir Peter Grill,
I received a letter from
Luvellia-san the other day...
Episode 9: Peter Grill and
the Treaty's Aftermath
Did something happen?