At last, the time has come...
C'mon, Spartokos...
Show 'em what you learned.
Go for a flawless victory!
A Seductress
in Disguise
And for the love of God,
get that woman far away from me...!
Begin!
Attaboy, Spartokos...
Thanks to our training...
They oughtta be on equal footing now
No, his skills are bound
to have surpassed hers!
She's laughing...?
Why's Spartokos moving so slow...?!
N-No way...
Is she using her boobs to distract him?!
Spartokos!
Try as you might, you shall
never defeat me in battle!
It was her boobs the whole time?!
What's the matter?
Sir Peter!
The match is over...
What'd you say?!
Huh?!
Boing! Boing! Boing!
Seriously...?
Winner: Big Sis!
Piece of cake, huh?
I call foul play!
Spartokos is a virgin!
Swinging those giant udders
of yours around isn't fair!
I don't believe that this is a proper
technique for a soldier!
A fight's a fight!
What's the big idea,
insultin' us Ogres with your dumb accusations?!
Spartokos...
Your efforts to lead a life of total
discipline cost you everything...
Unfortunately, it would seem that this, too,
is the fate of the creature known as "man"...
You poor soul...!
The chance to be a hero is long gone...
Dug myself into a hole with no way out
Back against the wall... I
mean, how could I resist?
"This wasn't supposed to
happen," I keep denying
I wish I could just disappear...
I can't stand myself
Moping around, spouting lies,
grieving a broken heart
I hold on desperately to these
feelings and shut my eyes
So why does this stupid
guilt refuse to go away?!
I suffocate under its weight
The chance to be a hero is long gone...
Always discouraged by my weaknesses,
I drop to my knees and grovel at your feet,
clinging selfishly to
the hope for forgiveness
Dug myself into a hole with no way out...
Full of regret and powerless to change,
I feel my heart being torn apart
on this night of endless shame and despair
Why can't I get my act together?
Got nothing but this pathetic self of mine...
Episode 12: Peter Grill and
the Warrior that Shouted Love
Th-The duel...!
Bad news, my friend...
It cannot be...!
I have lost yet again...?!
Spartokos...
Even if he were to demand another rematch,
I doubt the outcome would be any different.
His combat skills aren't the problem...
C-Come in!
E-Excuse me...
Is Spartokos-san awake yet?
Mitchie Peregrym!
Um, sorry for showing up out of the blue...
Wait...
Come to think of it, the answer is obvious!
Um, sorry for showing up out of the blue...
I, uh, didn't startle you, did I?
The missing piece of Spartokos' puzzle...
Woman... Woman...
Woman
Feeling comfortable around women!
Not at all! I apologize for such a pathetic display...
That's all he needs!
Ahem!
Spartokos-kun, got a sec?
So, listen... What do you
think of Mitchie-kun?
I-I'm afraid I don't understand...
Between you and me...
Mitchie's known for being a connoisseur
of guys with huge, rippling muscles.
And with an enticing physique like yours,
I think it's safe to say that you'd
have no problem winning her over...
Wha-?!
What are you implying?!
Let me be frank: You aren't
able to beat Lisa...
...because you're far too susceptible
to the charms of the opposite sex!
Wha-?!
What did you just say?!
Your obsession with remaining abstinent
for Lisa's sake is a disadvantage.
Your eyes wander across her body during battle,
destroying your ability to concentrate!
That's why you need to build up
more experience with women!
What exactly are you
suggesting I do, Sir Peter?!
You would have me surrender my virginity
to a woman other than Lady Lisa?!
I-I mean, think about it...
Whenever Mitchie was around...
Spending time with her gave you
butterflies in your stomach, didn't it?
W-Well, I...!
Nevertheless, I-I have devoted
my entire life to Lady Lisa!
I have sacrificed every
waking moment for her!
Exactly!
That way of thinking isn't healthy!
You're depriving yourself of other possibilities because
you're way too focused on chasing after this one woman.
And that is connected
directly to your weaknesses!
B-But...!
Spartokos-san!
Lady Mitchie?!
Nice!
Were you listening this whole time?!
You care deeply for Lisa-san,
and I'm fully aware of that.
However...!
I, too... perhaps just as deeply...
...feel the same way about you!
Lady Mitchie...
Sir Spartokos...
Looks like the walls surrounding that
innocent heart of his were paper-thin.
Lady Mitchie...
Looks like the walls surrounding that
innocent heart of his were paper-thin.
Sir Spartokos...
Looks like the walls surrounding that
innocent heart of his were paper-thin.
Lady Mitchie...
All he needed was a little push.
Sir Spartokos...
I have nothing left to teach you.
Fare thee well.
Lady Mitchie...
S-Sir Peter...?
For some strange reason,
I feel as though a burden
has been lifted from my shoulders.
Yup, you're a changed man.
Totally different than the
person you were yesterday.
And that power coursing through your veins...
It should be more than enough
to defeat Lisa Alpacas!
C'mon!
Let's go request another rematch right now!
Sir Peter...
I must admit, it was exactly as you said.
By pouring my time and effort into
the pursuit of a particular woman,
I had lost sight of the
path to true happiness.
What...?
Tokos~!
Oh, Mitchie!
Here, you forgot your lunch!
How thoughtful of you!
Eat this, and tonight you'll
have more muscles, muscles!
Muscles, muscles!
Uh, hello...?
What about your rematch with Lisa...?
Oh, Lady Lisa?
Yeah, Lisa!
That's all water under the bridge now.
Hey Tokos, you should join our Guild, too!
Goddammit...!
I suppose so...
The guy gave up as soon as he got a girlfriend!
The guy gave up as soon
as he got a girlfriend!
I could've sworn everything was
going according to plan...!
What a relief...
It would appear that he's finally
found a suitable partner.
Lisa?!
Muscles!
Despite his sentimental nature,
that man is the best our army has to offer.
Muscles!
Despite his sentimental nature,
that man is the best our army has to offer.
Muscles?
Despite his sentimental nature,
that man is the best our army has to offer.
Muscles, muscles!
Despite his sentimental nature,
that man is the best our army has to offer.
Muscles! Muscles!
He's a top-notch soldier
and a capable leader.
I expect that this situation will dispel
any doubts and encourage success.
I owe you a debt of gratitude for your
assistance with this matter, Peter Grill.
"The path to happiness..."
I couldn't have said it better myself.
Have you considered giving any thought to it?
Huh?
What does "true happiness" mean to you?
Marrying that naïve, oblivious Luvellia?
Getting stuck with that senile old
Albatross as your father-in-law?
Be honest.
Is that what you'd call "true happiness"?
W-Well, I...
If you were serious about our relationship...
...there's a possibility that you could
become the king of an entire nation.
What'd she just say...?!
Think it over carefully.
Which path is it you seek?
Where does your true happiness lie?
"True happiness..."
Peter-kun!
That's right...
I already told myself that
I'm done being indecisive!
Peter-kun!
Luvellia-senpai!
My mind is made up...
I know that this is my path to happiness!
Peter-kun!
Luvellia-senpai!
Where have you been?!
Please, you have to come with me!
It's the Goblins!
Huh?
N-No way...!
The Goblin Invasion is finally upon us!
A feeding frenzy of despicable creatures called
Goblins who devour every man in sight...!
We've already received numerous requests
for backup from villages across the area!
A mass outbreak of Goblins...
If we don't nip this in the bud,
the effects could be catastrophic.
I just hope we make it in time...
Look out, Luvellia-senpai!
I wouldn't mind going on a trip together
outside of our Guild duties.
Just the two of us...
I'll protect you!
No matter what happens, I'll keep you safe!
Same here. I have faith in you!
When this mission is over,
it's just you and me.
I can't wait to go on vacation together!
Agape!
Meet Agape Jr.!
91 points!
What is this, amateur hour?!
I knew it...
A woman admired by Sir Peter
isn't to be trifled with!
Don't be silly.
Our record still stands at over 100 points!
Losing to Albatross' foolish
daughter is NOT an option!
Peter Grill, regardless of which
path you choose to take...
...those precious juices
of yours belong to me!
It started out as a simple crush
Suddenly, you were my
biggest source of strength
Till death do us part,
let's grow old together
This is my sincerest wish:
Stay with me, stay with me
So long time, by my side for all eternity
Beaten down by our daily struggles
Or soaked by a storm of rage;
If you get drenched, I won't hesitate
To be the umbrella that shields you
It's not so cold... I'm by your side
That's good enough for me
You're my rock, my strength
That smile of yours puts my soul at ease
I could search the whole world over
And find no one like you
You're my rock, my strength
Just the sight of you fills my heart with joy
No matter how much it may hurt,
I pledge my life to protecting you
Dear Sir Peter Grill...
An Elite Squad of Hobgoblins
"The Three Stars of Hell"
Looks like it's our turn next...!
Wait for me...
Big Brother.