Since I was a child, I've hated
losing more than other people do.
If We Could Go Back to That Day
My report card described me as "an ambitious
child overflowing with vitality."
However, we can't avoid losing in life.
Academics, athletics, and arts.
There are limits to all of our abilities,
and there was always someone better than me.
Except in looks.
At 16 years old, I auditioned
to become an idol.
It was the only time my talent
would be utilized.
She called herself Yuki Mitsuya.
I'm sure you'll pass.
After all, you're exceptionally cute.
She'd been practicing classical ballet
and gymnastics since she was a child.
She was apparently on a track
team at the same time.
Her father was prominent
in a traditional performing art.
That exposure to good taste meant
she had a discerning eye.
She was nothing like me.
She was accustomed to
being in front of an audience.
She was experienced.
She was my age, and she had worked hard.
She knew defeat. She didn't fear defeat.
I heard that I had passed.
I'm your manager, Yamamoto.
That well-built man was my manager.
His name was Yamamoto.
I believe pushing you girls
to the top is my mission.
Including me, three of us passed.
We'll do our best together.
As expected, Yuki Mitsuya passed,
as well as Shiho Ichimura.
Yamamoto announced that I'd be the center.
Day after day, we attended lessons
while also attending school.
For the first time in my life,
I had to work hard.
On top of that, Yuki Mitsuya
remained on her track team.
It made me angry.
A year and a half later,
we had our first concert.
I was already 18 by then. I was impatient.
I participated in several events for work.
Comedy duos I'd never seen
or heard of poked fun at me.
It was humiliating.
I thought they must be losers
accustomed to defeat.
On the way home from an event,
I ran into Baba on the train.
I became increasingly annoyed
with this unsuccessful comedian.
I thought I'd never see him
again, so I said to him...
Doesn't it frustrate you?
You're working tawdry events
with unknown idols.
How does it feel to see
your contemporaries and juniors
achieve success before you?
What a surprise. My partner
says the same thing.
Doesn't everyone think that?
At first it frustrated me,
but I've given up.
My life is way easier now.
I'm happy for my contemporaries'
and juniors' success.
I thought that mentality must
mean a person was finished,
but I also thought it would be easier
if I could be that way, too.
For whatever reason, we exchanged
contact information.
That's when it was decided that
we'd make our major debut.
Finally. Our major debut.
Yeah. It's like a dream.
Why did the two of you want to become idols?
My family's poor.
I don't have my own room, so the bath
is the only place I have my own space.
I wanna get rich so I can move
into a place with a big bath.
I see. You'd better work hard, then.
Yeah.
How about you, Mitsuya-san?
Honestly, I just joined
to make some memories.
But I thought we might be able to
achieve something amazing
once I met you, Nikaido-san.
I agree. We're lucky to be in the
same group as you, Nikaido-san.
We'll have to work hard to make
sure we don't hold you back.
The three of us would rise together.
We'd win together.
I thought it sounded all right.
We had a recording session coming up.
Morale was high.
That's when a producer who had come
to watch our lesson said it.
Let's make this girl the center.
Excuse me.
On October 4th, I asked
Yuki Mitsuya to meet me.
Come to the agency office.
I have something important to tell you.
What? But the trains aren't running.
Take a taxi. I'll pay for it.
I'm in Nerima. It'll be expensive.
I was about to make a lame request.
I didn't want anyone to see us.
I can try to make excuses for myself,
but I think my desire to kill her
was already growing by this point.
Mitsuya-san, are you here?
Mitsuya-san?
Yuki Mitsuya was already dead.
What are you doing?
Hey, Nikaido.
Did you kill her?
I told him everything.
That I was going to ask her to
step down from being the center.
That I planned to kill her
if she didn't agree to do it.
I showed him the messages we'd exchanged.
I told him the truth
about the events of that day.
Who killed her, then?
I felt the same way.
Apparently Yamamoto believed me.
We don't have a choice.
After about an hour, Yamamoto
headed downstairs and let two men in.
A huge thuggish guy and a man
who spoke in a strange rhythm.
Apparently they knew the agency president.
Talk about gross, man,
I don't like this at all.
I might've grown up on the streets,
but corpses make my skin crawl.
Looks like she was bludgeoned,
then seems like she was choked.
As a man who wears tailor-made
suits from Don Quijote,
that's how I think she croaked.
There isn't much pedestrian
traffic in that area.
But since it was the middle of the night,
if anyone saw us, we'd stand out.
I exercised extreme caution.
There weren't even any
security cameras around.
I'd confirmed that multiple times
before asking Yuki Mitsuya to meet me.
It was a nightmarish sight.
After this, Yamamoto would have to return
to the office and clean things up there.
In order to prevent her
from being found by GPS,
he'd have to take Yuki Mitsuya's phone
someplace far away and dispose of it.
It was a lot of work.
The rapper explained to us
what would happen next.
As usual, I couldn't understand
what he was saying,
but essentially, he wanted to know
what Yuki Mitsuya did that day.
If she'd told anybody where she was going
or had been seen by any security cameras,
then we'd have to deal with that.
We'd analyzed her phone, but it would
be faster to utilize the police.
We'd have her family submit
a missing persons report,
and find a way to make them withdraw
it after gathering information.
Apparently the cost of disposing of the body
was half of Mystery Kiss' future profits
and to allow them to use our members
however they pleased for work.
That was the agreement we reached.
Even after she sank,
I kept staring at the water.
The sky was beginning to lighten.
Would we be all right? Would it go well?
We were too exhausted to worry.
Several days later,
Yamamoto introduced us to a girl.
I'm from Kyushu.
My name is Sakura Wadagaki.
Nice to meet you.
I've explained the situation to her already.
She'll be working under
the name Yuki Mitsuya.
Huh? What about the real Mitsuya-san?
She's missing.
What?
I can't get in touch with her.
But don't you think it's a little soon
to add a new member?
You're about to debut. We don't have time.
Except for Nikaido, you'll wear these.
We convinced Yuki Mitsuya's family
to let us use her name
so that she could resume
working once she returned.
Until Yuki Mitsuya returned, they'd wear
masks when out in front of people.
Ichimura accepted that explanation.
I felt bad for her,
but it couldn't be helped.
Hey, hey! Hey, hey!
Everyone must've thought,
"If only Yuki Mitsuya were here."
I'd crush those thoughts.
I swore I would.
We need to get used to it, so I'm going
to call you Mitsuya-san. Sorry.
That's okay. I'm here to be Yuki Mitsuya.
Mitsuya-san, you don't mind
not using your own face or name?
Not at all.
When I failed this audition,
I refused to accept it.
I went to speak directly with Yamamoto.
"Lemme in, lemme in, lemme in!" I said.
That's impressive.
I mean, when I failed, they told me
I was their fourth choice.
Isn't that frustrating?
I almost made it. I was so close.
You didn't think about
auditioning somewhere else?
Nah. After all, I heard you had passed.
I knew you'd be famous.
You want to be famous?
I do.
I'm from a single-parent home.
I want to get famous, so my mom
back in Kyushu can take it easy.
Even though she works, she wakes
up early to pack a lunch for me.
I see.
I feel like I've always caused
nothing but trouble for my mom.
I don't have any strengths, you know?
Sometimes I wish I could just disappear,
but seeing idols on TV cheered me up.
We waited for the right
moment to hold a concert.
Yamamoto said we received passing
marks, but I wasn't satisfied.
I'd tasted defeat.
We could've done better.
"If only Yuki Mitsuya were here."
I couldn't escape the thought, either.
That's when the news broke.
"Nerima high school girl goes missing."
Yamamoto spoke with Yuki Mitsuya's
family, and they submitted
a missing persons report to the police.
Since her father was famous,
they made sure that her name
and the fact that she was
an idol wasn't reported.
The police came to the agency.
I assisted with their
investigation numerous times.
That day, Yuki Mitsuya got in a taxi
in Nerima, and now she's missing.
They just needed to trace Yuki Mitsuya's
movements until she arrived at the agency.
The problem was the taxi
she took back then.
I was afraid of what the driver might say.
She may have been recorded by his dash cam.
It was imperative that
we identify that taxi,
but that was a job for
the rapper and Yamamoto.
All we could do was keep
steadily working on being idols.
Since we gathered some information
from the police and news reports,
the next step was to withdraw
the missing persons report.
While investigating Yuki Mitsuya,
the rapper discovered something.
A connection between Yuki
Mitsuya's father and a criminal.
Becoming an idol was Yuki Mitsuya's dream.
However, concerned about the connection
between her father
and a criminal organization,
she believed that at that rate,
she couldn't become an idol
and decided to run away from home.
That's what we told Yuki Mitsuya's parents.
Eventually, the missing persons
request was quietly withdrawn.
I returned to my everyday life.
Did anybody see us?
What if somebody already knows?
What if someone taps me on the shoulder
from behind while I'm walking around?
My heart palpitations worsened.
I began breathing heavily.
I couldn't stop sweating.
My hands shook. I wanted to scream.
I wished desperately to turn back time.
Then I returned to my everyday life again.
Perhaps I'd repeat this cycle
for the rest of my life.
I thought I'd lose my mind.
Wait, don't say it yet. There are rules.
What's for Lunch?!
Asking People Around
Kichijoji to Lunch!
Okay, here we go.
Hey, what's for lunch?
It was Baba who supported me.
I hadn't told him anything, of course.
I was simply saved by his existence.
He was my only comfort.
I hated to lose, and his way
of living permitted that.
It was okay if I lost. Of course,
it was okay if I won, too.
It didn't matter, either way.
I could believe that.
I wanted to make him happy.
Winter came. It came suddenly.
The deceased is Nerima City resident
Yuki Mitsuya-san, 18 years old.
Nerima City, Tokyo
Yuki Mitsuya-san (18)
Breaking News
Shibaura Wharf Abandoned Body Case
Body Identified as Belonging
to Member of Popular Idol Group
Yuki Mitsuya-san was a member
of idol group Mystery Kiss.
Fans have been shocked by
the sudden news of her death.
The tree is so cute.
It sure is.
The body of Yuki Mitsuya-san of idol
group Mystery Kiss has been discovered.
Body Found at Shibaura Wharf
Belongs to Idol Group Member
Her agency will be holding
a press conference after this.
It's happening one week from
now on December 25th at 16:00.
I should be waiting in the
parking lot at that time, right?
Yeah. Did you see the news?
Yamamoto the manager
probably won't be coming.
Lucky us. The fewer guys Yano has,
the easier this'll be for us.
That's a problem.
What?
Nothing.
Right. There is a problem.
Yuki Mitsuya's body was
found near Yano's hideout.
It's possible that they've moved.
And if they have, then the route
I assumed they'd take is useless.
Fuyuki Yamamoto
Oh, you picked up.
What is it?
You're not going with Yano's crew today?
I don't have time for that
right now. You know that.
I'm sure you don't.
Can I go now? I have
a press conference to attend.
I want to confirm one thing.
What?
The Yuki Mitsuya in the photo
shown on the news
and the Yuki Mitsuya I drove
in my taxi are different people.
Fuyuki Yamamoto
Are you sure you're not confused?
I drove you guys together.
The girl who likes fried chicken.
That reminded me.
The girl I drove on October 4th was...
Huh?
Fuyuki Yamamoto
Call Ended
Seriously?
I can't use Yamamoto. Which means...
Damn it. What is he doing?
Little Daimon
Sorry, but you'll be staying
here until Christmas.
I don't care anymore.
The concert's been canceled.
They're not releasing their CD.
I can't believe Yuki Mitsuya-san is dead.
When I first saw her in concert,
I thought she was such a good dancer.
Now that I think about it,
the Yuki Mitsuya-san wearing the mask
was a different person.
Today's the day Dobu-san goes down.
I'll force him to award me the crown.
Scraping by on the boss' opinion of me.
Best Christmas ever, this'll turn out to be.
The wind's blowing today. It's cold—
Excuse me...
Hey country bumpkin, shut your face!
It's my turn right now, know your place.
But I guess there's no need
for me to be screaming.
I could say you're my patron,
in a manner of speaking.
Sentimentality aside,
what is it you're seeking?
Could you put on Mystery
Kiss's press conference?
This isn't good. That taxi driver
remembers Wadagaki's face.
Of course he does.
Is there any way we can
put a positive spin on it?
If the world finds out that
we tried to cover it up...
We're just starting to taste success, too.
I'm sure some of the five guys who attended
our first concert remember her, too.
It's just not possible.
You're right.
Hello?
Yeah, I'm fine. I'll do my best.
Yeah.
Good luck with the loser's bracket.
I promise I'll come back from this, too.
You okay? Sorry I didn't notice.
I'm not capable of trying hard.
Okay. But don't push yourself too hard. Bye.
Hey, what are you doing?
Sorry.
Let's review our jokes.
We just did that.
We still don't know which
jokes we're performing.
I thought we agreed on the café hideaway.
Given the atmosphere, the time
machine bit could be better.
Loser's Bracket
I remember the time
machine bit. I'll be fine.
Don't you care about this at all?
If we fail here, we're through.
What?
You're the one who'll be
in trouble if we split up.
Hey, Baba. You've gotten awfully puffed up.
You used to be funnier.
I can't watch you fall apart.
You think all the movies,
TV shows, and comedians
that are popular these days aren't funny.
You're the one who's out of touch.
I get that you like manzai comedy.
I know that I'm holding you back, too.
So I'm sorry, Shibagaki.
Let's split up, as of today.
Space Observation Technology Advances
Cancer Research Raises
Alarm in Healthcare Industry
We're closing soon.
Married Couple Found Inside Car That
Fell Into Sea, Possible Double Suicide?
"Married Couple Found Inside Car That
Fell Into Sea, Possible Double Suicide?"
"Around 4:15, at Takeshiba
Wharf in Minato Ward,
office worker Kiyoshi Odokawa-san
of Chichibu City in Saitama Prefecture,
and his wife Yumi Odokawa-san,
were found dead inside a car that
had sunk to the bottom of the sea."
"Their son, who is in fourth
grade, escaped on his own,
but is unconscious and
in critical condition."
"The police are investigating the
possibility of a forced double suicide."
I'm sorry for all the trouble we've caused.
We've been unable to conceal our shock
since we learned that Yuki
Mitsuya was found dead.
In October, Yuki Mitsuya's
mother contacted us
to tell us that her daughter
hadn't returned home.
We did everything we could to help look
for her, but failed to locate her.
Also, as Mystery Kiss
was set to debut soon,
we had another girl who auditioned
take Yuki Mitsuya's place.
Ultimately, that meant we deceived
the world and those involved,
and for that, we are terribly sorry.
I've heard the police are
investigating this case as a murder.
Do you have any idea what happened to her?
Well, she was underpaid
before the group debuted.
I believe she promoted
herself on social media
and may have been close with fans as well.
You mean she was killed by a fan?
No, I'm just saying that's a possibility.
We take responsibility for failing to protect
her privacy and provide adequate security.
We cannot regret what happened
more than we already do.
We also can't bear to face
Donraku Shofutei-san
Live: Talent Agency
Emergency Press Conference
who entrusted his daughter to our agency.
Oh, my.
You can't be serious.
Hey.
I never thought I'd be helping you guys.
Shouldn't you get in position?
Since they moved their hideout,
I'll be following them from the bank.
I see.
Where's your best buddy and brother?
He hasn't come into work for a while.
I noticed something off about his behavior,
but I can't believe my meek little
brother is ignoring my calls.
Hey, taxi driver. Did you
say something to him?
Yeah, right. We're on the same
side now, aren't we?
When you put it that way, broadly speaking,
we've been on the same side
since the beginning.
It's time.
You know what'll happen to you
if you go off-script, right?
I was referred to you by Dr. Kato
at Minami Nakano hospital.
My name is Goriki.
I'd like to ask you about Hiroshi Odokawa.
Hiroshi Odokawa-kun was my patient.
Could you describe to me
what he was like then?
He spent about two months
here in the hospital.
He was supposed to continue
outpatient rehabilitation after that,
but the courthouse told us
that a benefactor had shown up,
and he'd moved to Tokyo.
We don't know what
happened to him after that.
How was his mental state after the accident?
He had absolutely no memory of the accident.
We observed no problems with his basic
motor functions and language abilities,
so we had him keep a memory notebook
to work on his mental recovery.
His mental condition seemed stable to us.
Tell me more about this memory notebook.
He recorded the rules for life
at the hospital, his medications,
his bathing schedule, and other
information pertaining to himself.
It was like a diary.
What impression did you get
from reading the notebook?
I thought he was a strange child.
Do you have that notebook?
Yes.
Since you said you'd be coming,
I read it for the first time in 30 years.
May I take a look at it?
I know you said you're Hiroshi
Odokawa-kun's current doctor,
but it's not meant for a GP like you to see.
I'm not asking to see it
because I'm his doctor.
I'm asking because I'm his friend!
Next Time: Not Enough
You eating properly?
Yeah.
It's important to live an orderly life.
I know.
And drive safely.
Okay.
And stop making everyone worry about you.
Sorry.
You should establish a family—
Shut up! You're not my dad!
We're the same age!