This is a pretty unusual combination.
Not Enough
Yes, that's right...
It's nearly time.
Imai, please check it.
Check a second duraluminum case.
You're certain that this is the right car?
Yes.
Would it be all right
if we checked the contents?
Of course. Imai-sama did
just check earlier, though.
They're definitely real.
In that case...
Hey, yo. Ten duraluminum cases in a row.
But we still haven't checked
the ones down below.
I can spot the difference
between fake and real.
Like a plugin with enhanced
functionality, you feel?
It's a difference a penniless
pauper couldn't perceive.
Now excuse me, as I grab one of these.
Randomly reaching out, like Romeo and Juliet.
No guarantees these
aren't all counterfeit.
With a single verse, I make
all these rhymes fit.
This eyesight is a gift from Santa Claus.
I can see your darting eyes,
your powerless paws...
We should leave this place first.
There's no telling what might happen.
We can check the contents later and
if there's a problem, we'll settle it then.
You got their cards, right?
Ah, yes...
Congratulations on winning the lottery!
Niji Bank Building
Good work.
You did well. Now hurry up.
Are we going to be all right? They're not
going to retaliate later, are they?
You'll be fine. Once they lose the
contest, they'll leave this town.
Now, hurry up.
You'll get paid once I check the contents.
Looks like it went well.
For now, yeah.
Wow.
First time seeing this many bills?
Definitely my first time seeing this many.
Bet you wish you were
getting a cut now, huh?
No, I don't need that. But you're
gonna pay your taxi fare.
Small price to pay.
Hey.
They're heading south.
Then they should being heading
towards Hinode Wharf.
They've got a hideout there.
Dobu
I'll stop them at the bridge
just before the wharf, then.
Got it. I'll head there right away.
You're up, taxi driver.
Where to?
Head towards Hinode Wharf.
National Traffic Safety Campaign
Special Fraud Prevention Campaign
Taya Police Station
Did he quit?
I heard he lost his gun.
He's too scared to report it,
so he's running away.
He's such an idiot.
The biggest.
You sure that isn't made up, too?
What do you mean?
What if he actually fired it?
It's possible. After all, he's an idiot.
The little brother really is a huge idiot.
I'm sorry I couldn't help you, Don-chan.
It's all right.
The police and media are doing
a good enough job distracting me.
I don't know what to say.
Let's get a drink again sometime.
You're sure it's all right to meet with me?
They could be monitoring
this phone call, too.
Yeah, I don't care anymore.
I want to take a break for a while.
I see.
We'd like to continue, please.
I'll call you once things have
calmed down, Kuro-chan.
Donraku Shofutei Distraught! Sheds Tears
Over Daughter's Body. Extended Hiatus?
Hey, apparently he stepped down from judging.
Surely he'll judge the main event, right?
Losers' Bracket
Stop being so precise about it.
Thank you.
We're doing the time machine bit.
Got it.
If you screw it up, I'll kill you.
With 14 years of experience
in the business, it's Homosapiens.
Hello, we're Homosapiens.
Thanks for having us.
My life is full of regrets.
Where'd that come from?
I'm already beginning to regret saying that.
It was pretty pessimistic.
You're overthinking it. You'll be fine.
How can I avoid having regrets?
The only way is to do your best
so you can live without regrets.
You see it in movies and stuff.
Y'know, when kids travel back using
a time machine and meet their parents.
Yeah, I've seen that. There's something
they regret, so they go back to fix it.
It's moving, isn't it?
I'm sure anyone would be moved if a child
they'd never seen before came to see them.
I think I'd like to try that.
Sure, let's do it.
I didn't say anything weird just now, did I?
You're already regretting it.
It'll be fine, I'll do it.
For real? Let's try it, then.
Dad.
Are you...
Dad, I'm your five-year-old son.
What?
Oh, Dad. My father, who gave
birth to me five years ago.
I'm going to die within the next five years?!
Judging by my son's behavior,
I'm clearly gonna die!
You made that really obvious!
I'm sorry I couldn't do
anything for you, Dad.
And there's nothing I can do about it?!
You're not even showing up
to save your dying dad
because a cure was found five years later?
If that's the case, just leave me alone!
But I, uh...
What else do you regret?
Uh, you know...
My life is full of regrets.
Yeah, I know that. Like what?
Shut up, idiot! I regret teaming up with you!
What was that for?!
I regret becoming a comedian.
I shouldn't have chased my dreams!
There's a police car
that's been following us.
Shall I lose him?
Everybody stay calm now,
don't do anything weird.
He's just looking for an excuse
to stop our car here.
If he uses the law as a shield,
we'll have to yield, so keep going.
But there's nothing here
for him to find.
We're just moving some cash
and its owner, how kind.
If he gets the wrong idea,
I'll just sit and grin.
Even if he's a cop, he won't
have a reason to take us in.
Understood. I'll keep driving
while following all traffic laws.
I'm near the bridge.
Got it.
Wait here.
I'll be running the meter while I wait.
Black HiAce, pull over
to the left side of the road.
What should we do?
Do as he says, nothing else to be done.
I bet we'll enjoy looking back on this one.
What is it?
I heard over the radio that some
bank robbers are on the run.
Could I take a look inside your car?
We're in a hurry.
I'd appreciate your cooperation.
What are all these duraluminum cases for?
I'm going to open one.
Wow, incredible. Fat stacks of cash.
Now this is suspicious.
He won a lot of money in the lottery.
Who did?
Uh, m-me.
You're sure?
Yes.
I'm gonna check the others, too.
These are fakes.
W-Wait a sec. That's not possible!
Why don't we chat in my patrol car?
Damn it!
What the hell is this?! It's newspaper!
Are these other ones, too? All of them?!
Y-Yano-san!
What?
Your rhymes...
Y-You're not rhyming!
Shut up.
Damn it! Someone set us up.
Who was it? Hey, cop!
Look into those bankers, chop-chop!
Let's chat in my car, first.
No friggin' way. Why?!
Everything went so well, we were flying sky high!
Yano-san, let's do as he says for now!
We'll be fine as long as we can
clear up the misunderstanding.
You just won the lottery, right?
Yes.
Sorry for the trouble. You can go.
What? From here?
I'll question you later.
For now, you can head home.
Um, what about the money?
I'll make sure to get it
back for you, so go.
You don't wanna die, do you?
Why'd you let him leave?
That doesn't make sense.
Let's have a nice, long chat.
I'm telling you, he won the lottery.
We were just helping him out
since he doesn't have a ride.
We didn't know about
the counterfeits, someone lied!
What's your relationship with him?
Why'd you ask for cash?
Where were you headed?
Where does he live?
Enough rapid-fire questions. He's a friend!
Why'd you ask for cash?
That's how he wanted it!
Hold on, Yano-san.
Hey, are you really a cop?
Of course I am.
Show us your badge, then.
Hey, follow that car!
No, we've been screwed!
That's Dobu's accomplice Daimon, my dude!
To the parking lot in Shimbashi.
Got it.
The panic on Yano's face was exquisite.
We did it. The perfect victory.
You're right. We can't
let our guard down yet.
We need to collect the 900
million in the parking lot, first.
What's with you? Not
gonna congratulate me?
Well, I guess there's nothing in it for you.
Oh, were you speaking to me?
What, acting like we're strangers already?
Stick with me for a little longer.
Of course. I'll take you to the parking lot.
You don't need to put on this weird act.
I'll be taking your dash cam.
Were you planning
to turn me into the police?
There's no point. Big Daimon's on my side.
Odokawa, don't even think
about betraying me now.
If you turn on me now, I'll crush
you with everything I have.
Even if I'm arrested, no matter how
many years it takes, I'll find you.
Shirakawa, too.
What are you going to do to Shirakawa-san?
I'll kill her.
Fine. I almost forgot that
you're that kind of guy.
I can't afford to worry
about appearances anymore.
Is your boss that desperate for money?
The boss has only one rule for us.
What's that?
I'm not telling you.
Hey, hold on. Who's that?
Isn't that the guy behind the skull mask?
You're right. That's my gun.
What should we do? Should we run for it?
No, it's all right. I'll get out.
Won't everything be ruined
if you get shot here?
That gun had six bullets. Count 'em.
Two shots at the cabaret club.
One shot into your house.
Two shots during the car chase.
One shot at me at the harbor. He's out.
Hey, who are you?
I don't have business with you.
I'm here for the driver.
That's my gun. Not only that,
but I've been shot.
I've got plenty of business with you.
What do you want?
I don't know what I want anymore.
At first, I lost something important.
I wanted to get revenge on him
for taking that from me.
That alone was sustaining me.
But unlike with games, I guess I got bored.
Hold on. He took something
important from you?
So, what do you want, then?
I want him to apologize.
I harassed him plenty,
but I've lost a lot, too.
Nothing will satisfy me,
so I just want him to apologize.
That doesn't make any goddamn sense to me.
I guess you should start
by apologizing, then.
Um, I have no idea what
you're talking about.
You nearly ran me over with your car!
You broke my phone!
By something important,
you meant your phone?
Spare me the scornful old man lecture
about young people loving
their phones too much.
That's not what I meant.
Okay, fine.
Uh, I was probably in a hurry.
I know that's not an excuse for
taking something important from you,
but as a taxi driver, I think
that was inconsiderate of me.
I'm sorry.
Hey.
Where did you get this?
Huh? I gave that to Shirakawa.
Why do you have that, Odokawa?
Why did you have this?
My superior—as I guess you'd
call him—knows Donraku.
It ended up in my hands.
When?
When? More than 15 years ago?
Nah, I forget. It was a long time ago.
Only one of these erasers was sold.
It's the only one of them in the world.
No, wait. There could be leftover
inventory at Donraku's house.
It wouldn't be odd if an acquaintance had one.
What are you mumblin' about? Give back my gun.
After that, we can settle—
ditch-11.
Huh?
What?
Does the name "ditch-11" sound familiar?
d-i-t-c-h-1-1.
Dunno.
Do you know what Zooden is?
Huh? Yeah. The game, right?
Do you play?
Never played it.
Right now the number one ranked
account in Zooden is ditch-11.
I sent that account a message
to confirm something.
I asked them if they used
online auctions 16 years ago.
Oh, really?
They said they did.
Which means they're the person who
conned me out of 100,000 yen 16 years ago
when I was in grade school.
What are you going on about?
I don't give a shit about that.
I'm in a hurry. Give back my gun, already.
Let me see your phone. I want
to check if Zooden is installed on it.
If you're not them, I'll leave you alone.
I told you, it's not!
Then I'm not giving up.
You might be a new boss
that I have to defeat.
I'm going to kill you.
Bring it on. Do it, kid.
H-Hold on. I'm not sure I follow.
Zooden accounts have icons, right?
Show me ditch-11's icon.
It's him.
Wait a minute. How—
That's right. You can tell.
Yeah, I remember now. I used to play Zooden.
I haven't played in so long, I'd forgotten.
Why did you lie?
Hold up. You lied, too.
Nobody contacted me
about any online auctions.
You tricked me.
You lied because you have
a guilty conscience!
You're the one who conned me
out of 100,000 yen 16 years ago!
Since then, my life has fallen apart!
It's your fault!
I know you don't have any bullets left.
Don't try to act tough.
Damn... Why were there still bullets left?
Don't speak. Stay still.
Take me to a doctor, Odokawa.
There's an unlicensed doctor
I'm well-acquainted with.
Hurry up. Put me in your taxi.
Otherwise, the police...
Found it.
Hey.
You should go to a normal hospital.
Receive proper treatment.
I'm sure someone's already called
the police and an ambulance.
Wait. The car. What are
you going to do with it?
I'm going to return the money to its owner.
It finally caught up to you.
Don't screw with me, Odokawa.
This is what they call retribution.
This is goodbye for you and me.
Hello, Imai? Where are you now?
I'm in Akasaka.
I don't have any money to take the train.
Come to the parking lot
in Shimbashi, right now.
There's a black van parked there.
Your money is inside, so don't worry.
Take the taxi. The keys are under the car.
Really? I'll head there right away.
I'm getting out of here.
The police might be at the parking lot,
but stay calm and get
in the car, like you belong.
Yano-san, he was with Dobu-san!
He's working with him!
That's him, huh?!
Shit. I'll give you the 100 million later.
After him!
Bro...
Bro, you always called me an idiot,
but in the end, you were the bigger idiot.
Yeah, maybe you're right.
Was it Yano's crew that beat you up?
Yeah.
Let's go arrest them for interference
with public duties, inflicting bodily injury,
stealing a patrol car, and—
I can't. I'm gonna be arrested, too.
Of course you are. After all, you're evil.
You sided with Dobu.
I'm going to arrest you.
You know, because you're evil.
You're right.
Why'd you have to side with Dobu?!
You idiot! You're such an idiot!
Liar! You lied to me, Bro!
We promised we'd punish evil together!
Do you remember this?
What's that?
I think I remember seeing it when
we graduated from police school.
They give it to you once you stop
receiving payments from the foundation
for kids orphaned by traffic accidents.
What about it?
The person who gave this
to me is Dobu's boss.
That's why you helped Dobu?
Yeah, I'm sorry I didn't tell you.
You've got a strong sense of justice.
I didn't think you'd forgive me.
I won't!
No, I will! After all, you're my brother!
But the law won't forgive you!
I wish it would, though!
But... But...
What Yano and his guys did
is even more unforgivable.
We're gonna go arrest them!
Let's go, Bro!
Next Time: Where To?
I'm clumsy with words, so I'm not
good at this kind of thing,
but in any case, thank you, everyone.
If I'm able to return
to my normal life, then—
What? Last train?
In that case, have
a Happy New Year, everyone.