Tanaka's Revolution
I'm serious, man!
Maid Café
Welcome Back, Master
Hey, you! What are you trying to do?
Our story begins four years ago.
At that time, I had just started
working for a game company.
In order to examine our competitors' games,
There's broad demand for the
combination of intuitive puzzle games
I was playing several free-to-play games.
and anime characters.
Honestly, I don't like modern games.
Last year, Namico's Puzzle
Fantasy made over 40 billion.
Games are supposed to be
an escape from reality.
Having friends gives you an advantage.
Seriously, I'd go if I could.
Having money and time
gives you an advantage.
You never show up!
I promise I'll go next time.
It's no different than reality.
Going back even further, when I was
a third-year grade school student,
Hey, that's the new Gandum!
I won it in a giveaway!
eraser collecting
was briefly a fad in my class.
Lemme see!
Wow!
Found Around School
It was due to our homeroom teacher
being rather fussy about the wealth gap.
All our possessions were standardized.
Students were instructed not to
deviate from the average.
However, there was one loophole: stationery.
Among such products, a wide variety
of erasers were available in circulation,
so as a class, we threw ourselves
into collecting erasers.
Wow.
Who had the most erasers.
Who had the rarest erasers.
That alone determined our class hierarchy.
No, that's an exaggeration.
Actually, it's a lie.
As you might expect,
athletic kids, smart kids,
strong fighters, attractive kids,
artistic kids, and funny kids
naturally stood near the top.
But for the rest of us
who didn't have anything,
The PE teacher's shirt
was hanging out during class.
eraser collecting was our last hope
for squeezing into the top.
No, this is also an exaggeration and a lie.
Did you see his face when he noticed?
Even among the kids who had nothing,
there were only two of us
who collected erasers seriously.
Me and another kid named Sato.
Sato was a nuisance.
His parents frequently traveled for work,
which meant he was lonely.
He received an allowance as well,
and would ask his parents
to bring him back rare local erasers
as souvenirs from their business trips.
I think the reason I participated
in this pointless showdown
between the two of us
was because I already
possessed one rare eraser.
It was an eraser shaped like a dodo.
My relatives bought it for me
on an overseas trip.
I loved birds.
I read my bird encyclopedia again
and again until the pages wore out.
You're an unusual bird, aren't you?
Pet House
Once, I begged my father
to get me a pet bird.
My father took me into the pet shop with
the understanding that we'd just look around,
but in the end, he bought me
a gray male cockatiel.
I named him Maru.
Later he told my mother that he was
helping cultivate my aesthetic sensibility,
but thinking on it, it was probably
just that he wasn't very expensive.
They bought my brother
the expensive otaku computer games,
and Maru must've been cheap in comparison.
While doing my best to care for him,
a relationship of trust was born between us.
But back to my story.
My dodo eraser certainly was rare,
Sato-kun, where'd you get those?
but the erasers that
I could afford on my allowance
Wow.
didn't stand a chance
against Sato's collection.
Can I touch them?
Sure.
A tiny handful of students fawned over him,
and I found it unbearably frustrating.
I'd smugly return to using an ordinary
eraser after trying a bunch of others,
or utter great insights like,
"this is what they use instead of erasers
at art colleges," while using bread.
But those low-class techniques that I pretended
were high-class were obviously ineffective,
and every day I tasted defeat.
Then something happened.
One-of-a-kind Super Rare Original Donraku Eraser
A Donraku eraser...
Auctions > Toys > Games > Figures > Erasers
One-of-a-kind Super Rare
"This is it," I thought.
There was only one of them in the world.
It was my only chance to turn things around.
I'd show him.
I returned home, and
once my family was asleep,
I took my father's credit
card from his wallet
and wrote down his credit card number.
Considering how I was going to pay
for it, I needed a credit card.
It was a typical card.
One accessible to everyone.
The kind of card a student might use.
When I learned that later,
I became a little sentimental,
but that's another story.
My dad bought this for me
when he went to Dubai.
Just you wait.
That day, after leaving school,
during the limited period
when my brother wasn't home,
Number of Bids
Bidding History
Time Remaining
3 Days    Details
Current Price
I prepared myself and registered an account.
Place Bid
Seller Information
Follow
No refunds, no returns
Overall Rating: 24   |  Positive Ratings: 30
3,000 yen, huh?
There were zero bids with
three days left on the auction.
Since my time at a computer was limited,
I didn't have time to strategize.
I bid immediately.
The price was 3,000 yen.
It was hardly inexpensive for me,
but it was possible that its price
would rise even higher.
Hilarious! Joke Hit Battle!
Newbies to Watch: The Walrus
Short Skit "Convenience Store"
What the hell kind of
employee are you? Enough.
I erased the history and any other
trace that I'd used the computer
Thank you very much.
and ate dinner with my family
as though nothing had happened.
Mom, do we have anything for dessert?
At that time, I felt elated, as though
I'd become a super hacker.
The next day...
It went up.
I had a rival.
In retrospect, this piece of shit
was hardly worth it.
Bid
Maximum Bid
yen
Place Bid
I entered 3,600 yen into the bid field.
On the final day of the auction...
What?
4,000 yen?
My rival was stubborn.
I felt his passion and determination
to acquire the eraser, no matter the cost.
Battling against an opponent with
unknown intentions and budget
is the charm of online auctions.
However, I was determined.
I input 4,100 yen.
Number of Bids
Bidding History
Time Remaining
12 Minutes  Details
Current Price
Free Shipping
Place Bid
Damn it!
There's no time.
Bid
Maximum Bid
yen
Place Bid
Current Price
Yen
Free Shipping
Place Bid
Current Price
Yen
Free Shipping
Place Bid
It was as though I'd been
arrested on false charges
and was desperately trying
to prove my own innocence
while the police presented more
and more physical evidence.
I remember feeling that kind of despair.
No, that's also an exaggeration and a lie.
But it's true that I experienced
a despair that's difficult to describe.
That's when it happened.
I'm home.
Maximum Bid
yen
Bid
Maximum Bid
yen
Place Bid
He'll outbid me. I know he'll outbid me.
Bid
Maximum Bid
yen
Place Bid
Hey.
There was something I wanted to look up.
I told you not to touch my stuff!
Congratulations! You have won the auction.
One-of-a-kind Super Rare
Original Donraku Eraser
Auction ID: 32976128739
End Time and Date: 9/22 17:32
Number of Items: 1
Final Price 100,000 yen
Begin Transaction
Seller Information ditch-11
It was me. I definitely won the auction.
Begin Transaction
Seller Information
I had lost my mind.
Let's play soccer.
Let's sprint to the field.
In Japan, a group of citizens
once staged a revolution
due to their discontent
over the economic divide.
What is the Hyakushou Ikki
Tenant Farmer Uprising?
Edo Period
Tenant Farmers
Feudal Lords
In this classroom, our teacher's efforts
to prevent the wealth gap from widening
produced a twisted backlash
in exactly one student.
It wasn't an organized movement
like an uprising or rebellion.
It was a revolution brought
about by just one student.
I called it Tanaka's Revolution.
Once again, I returned home
and messaged the seller
regarding the shipping
address for the eraser.
All that remained was to wait for
my original Donraku eraser to arrive.
Tanaka
One week passed.
One month passed.
My original Donraku eraser had not arrived.
I recalled the words
"no refunds, no returns."
I realized now that there were
plenty of things I could have done.
Maki-chan, let's compare answers.
But at the time, I was bound firmly
by the words "no refunds, no returns,"
You just want to copy her homework.
I always let you see my homework.
and had no options.
Besides, I consented
to bidding on the eraser.
I had no right to demand compensation,
and I had nothing to return.
Sato and the rest of my classmates
had already lost interest in erasers.
Third-year grade school
students grow up fast.
And when my father reviewed
his credit card statement,
he beat me to a pulp.
As he was beating me,
I wondered whose fault this was.
My teacher. My classmates.
Sato. My brother. My father.
The seller. The bidder.
Me. My country. History.
Civilization. The government.
God.
No matter how I looked at it,
it was clearly my fault.
And if there was a loser
in this situation...
Honey, honey!
...it was me.
And so, Tanaka's Revolution ended.
Returning to a previous topic,
since then, I've come to despise
anything without a real form
as well as competing with others.
Good night.
Games are meant to be played alone.
All alone, battling against the developer.
Raise slimes...
Let's bike!
Purchase
Dragon Slayer
Exhilarating action
Purchase
That's when I encountered a certain game.
Zoological Garden
Gather and raise animals...
Purchase
Sengokusou
Live with generals Purchase
Purchase
Zoological Garden,
commonly known as "Zooden."
< Back
Zoological Garden
Purchase
3245 Reviews
You raise unique animals
and put them in exhibits.
As zoo director, you compete
for ranks on a worldwide scale.
I had plenty of fun playing
as much as I could for free.
I think collecting erasers back then
became the basis for this.
My rank was awful, but I was
happy when I gained guests,
and when I acquired a rare animal,
my brain tingled dangerously.
Super Rare
Snow Leopard
There was a character
I was determined to acquire.
The dodo.
Dodo
A now-extinct species of bird that once
lived on Mauritius Island off of Madagascar.
Due to its underdeveloped wings, it cannot fly.
Attractiveness
Care Difficulty
Maintenance Cost 200 fpt    Exhibit Area 12 Squares
Not yet acquired!
In the game, the rarity of animals were ranked
using terms such as Normal or Rare.
As an extinct species,
the dodo was Special Super Rare.
Apparently it could be pulled
from the free gacha,
but the odds were extremely low.
Looking back, I took part in eraser
collecting because I had the dodo,
and I was playing Zooden in order
to acquire the dodo.
When I made that comparison,
I felt as though it was
my destiny to acquire it.
Maybe I'd spend a little money.
I figured that would be it.
I added 500 yen to my account
and pulled the gacha.
Purchase Hagenbecks
6 Hagenbecks
24 Hagenbecks
68 Hagenbecks
Dugong
The Dugong. Endangered species. Super Rare.
Super Rare
I think I'd already lost
all restraint by this point.
I looked at my own rank.
It was terrible as usual,
World Ranking
but out of curiosity, I looked
to see who was number one.
ditch-11...
It was the name that conned me
out of 100,000 yen back then.
No, maybe it didn't arrive
because of trouble during shipping.
Besides, I bore them no resentment at all.
It wasn't even necessarily the same person.
But. But.
I couldn't believe that it was coincidence
I'd been reunited with this string of letters.
I felt that it was destiny.
If I were to take revenge,
it would be on my past self.
And it would be my present self
who would save my past self.
I added 100,000 yen.
If I were to take revenge,
it would be on my past self.
And it would be my present self
who would save my past self.
That was four years ago.
I'm still playing Zooden.
Thanks to the addition of new systems
and events reflecting the real
world keeping the game fresh,
its content is still popular
around the world.
Good morning.
I'd like to acquire new users
with a new design.
In total, I've spent over
five million yen on this game.
We need to capture people's interest.
My rank is still only in the triple digits.
Why don't we conduct some research?
I still don't have a dodo.
Good idea.
We're spending our budget on research?
But we have to.
Hey, Tanaka. Are you listening?
Tanaka-kun?
Tanaka!
Tanaka-kun!
The bird that went extinct
without ever learning to fly.
Tanaka!
Perhaps I was projecting myself onto it.
It was just like me.
No, if I died here without achieving
anything, I wouldn't even be Rare.
I'd be just Normal.
Buy/Sell Zoological Garden Account
Purchase
Account with numerous Super Rare characters
Seller: tarou
First come, first served!
3 Super Rare characters
Seller: sakio
Assortment of 5 Super Rare characters
Seller: kinopi_22
As a game that enjoys worldwide popularity,
Account with 10 3-star characters
Seller: yakitori45
Great deal! Account
with numerous endangered species
Seller: tarou
First come, first served!
10 Super Rare characters
Seller: kondo11
Assortment of 20 Limited Rare characters
Seller: kitanotakeshifan
its market size is naturally large.
There are even intermediaries
who buy and sell entire accounts.
My triple-digit-ranked account
that I've spend over five million yen on
would only sell for a few hundred thousand.
If ditch-11's account
appeared on the market,
it would go for a lot of money.
An account with a dodo could be mine
for several tens of thousands of yen.
But that's not it. It's not the same.
"What is it about, then?" I ask myself.
The romance? The catharsis?
The release from oppression?
The need for social recognition?
The desire to feel superior to one's peers?
I try on gussied-up words
and phrases for size.
No. The truth is, I already know.
I know those fancy words don't apply.
It's simpler than that. Yes.
A sickness. It's a sickness.
Shut up!
I didn't say anything...
I'd begun spending tens of thousands of
yen on the game like it was nothing at all.
I was completely numb.
Everything I did was
to get my hands on a dodo.
To get revenge on the boy
I was 16 years ago and save him.
And to get closer to ditch-11,
who continues to reign
from the number one spot.
You just wait, ditch-11.
Super Rare
Red Panda
Okapi
Ultra Rare
Dodo
A dodo...
Ultra Rare
Dodo
My four years...
No, my 16 years...
It finally paid off!
Yes! I did it! A dodo!
Your backed up data
has been restored—
Snow Leopard
Dugong
Dodo
Animal List
My mind went blank.
I couldn't think.
I don't remember walking home.
The loss I felt over the dodo
I had definitely acquired
robbed me of all my willpower.
But fate is cruel, and God had
taken something else from me.
I think that's when the blue flame
inside of me finally came to life.
At the very least, it wasn't God
who took my dodo from me.
It was that taxi.
It's not as though someone
took Maru from me, either.
The life expectancy of a
cockatiel is about 15 years.
He lived a full life.
It just happened to be today.
But sometimes, thinking about
this unfortunate coincidence
makes me wonder if there is a God.
In games, often the player
acquires a valuable item
just when they think
they've reached a dead end.
It's convenient. Of course it is.
After all, somebody made it that way.
Then there must be someone
who made this world, too.
Perhaps this world has been programmed.
Hey, God. It's you.
This happened three days ago.
Taxi... Kill... Maru... Dodo...
Ow. Hold on, buddy.
Apologize when you bump into someone.
That's common sense.
Don't you think?
Wait, wait. Hold on, buddy.
What's wrong? You've got
the face of a murderer.
Sorry. I'm just curious
due to the nature of my job.
Hey, you. You're from the countryside.
Why'd you come out here?
The countryside?
I guess compared to Tokyo,
it is the countryside.
Are you chasing a dream or something?
That's right. I came to Tokyo for
status, glory, and big money.
But, you still haven't gotten those.
Well, Rome wasn't built in a day.
What do you think you need
to do to get them?
If I knew that, my life would be easy.
My partner said it's luck, though.
Your partner?
He's like my business partner.
Luck, huh? You're right.
Maybe luck is involved,
but I don't want to give up
on the things I can control.
There's plenty to consider besides luck
when trying to figure out how to survive.
You're saying the dodo was unlucky, then.
What?
What does that mean?
I thought you and I were
following the same road.
You're telling me we were actually
on the highway and subway?
I feel like I've always been
searching for something.
At the same time, my life has
always been lacking something.
And desperately acquiring that something
yields only a moment of pleasure.
Far from being good fortune,
it's simply a moment of pleasure
produced by the release of dopamine.
And?
The single word that always follows
after I've acquired something I want.
"And?"
"So, what?" my other self asks me.
It's always there,
hand-in-hand with nihilism.
A truly formless pleasure.
But right now, I'm experiencing being alive.
It's because I found what I wanted
the moment I lost my dodo.
Unlike before,
it wasn't just an addition to my
collection that ended once acquired.
What shall I do next?
Just thinking about it excites me.
It's a Rare Item with
potential for development.
I believe everyone possesses
the impulse to attack.
An impulse to attack that's
more exciting and justified
the less you are to blame.
I've been walking for three days since then.
I'm used to chasing odds
far more mind-boggling.
But this time, it's different.
I felt something like a premonition.
Earlier, I said that I could seize it
if I let go of my attachments,
but there's another way
to acquire what I want.
And that is by holding tightly
onto a powerful attachment
that transcends all else.
Hey, you! What are you trying to do?
Next Time: Don't Call Me an Idol
I've never actually seen
someone point them all out
when they say something
is full of mistakes or flaws.
Why don't you carefully verbalize
each and every one of them, huh?
Probably too stupid to do it.
You're pretty drunk.
Man, maybe I'll win the lottery.
Your job is like a lottery.