Fried Chicken
Don't Call Me an Idol
Hello? Mitsuya, where are you?
I told you, the lesson starts at seven.
I'll come pick you up. Stay there.
Vacant Taxi
To Harajuku Station, please.
And hurry. Drive right up
to the speed limit.
Why are you in such a rush?
I'm picking someone up and need to
get to the studio in Sasazuka by seven.
You'll make it with time to spare.
Well, I'm picking up two people.
Huh...
Over here.
Driver, take us to the studio in Sasazuka.
Drive quickly, but safely.
Yamamoto-san, where's my fried chicken?
Here.
All right. Thanks for the food.
Don't eat too much.
If you gain five kilos, you're fired.
I know.
You like fried chicken?
Yeah. I'm from Oita.
Is that related somehow?
Does that mean everyone from
Hokkaido likes soup curry?
I have an attachment to it.
It's my soul food.
What's soul food?
I don't know. It's just a feeling.
It's like local cuisine or the taste
of your mother's cooking, right?
Yeah. The fried chicken my mom
used to make was so good.
Is Nikaido-san coming today?
She's showing up late.
Don't you think she gets
too much special treatment?
Lucky... I wish I got the same.
Keep working at it, Mitsuya.
Didn't you promise your mom you'd follow
your dreams when you came to Tokyo?
Yeah, but...
Hey, a fried chicken restaurant!
Head inside and start
practicing by yourself.
Aw, what?
Don't whine. You're the newest, Mitsuya.
You need to work harder than the others.
Fine...
Give me a minute, driver.
Ichimura? Where are you?
At a public bath in Ogikubo?
Excuse me, could you head to Ogikubo?
What are you doing? I told you to be
at the studio in Sasazuka at seven.
Just head someplace I can find you easily.
Sounds like a tough time.
Handling girls requires
careful consideration.
I didn't think we'd be
picking them up separately.
I deal with this kind of thing all the time.
Like pairings and seating arrangements...
I thought it'd be better
to keep them separate.
Public Bath
You were visiting the baths again?
Yeah.
Hey, Driver. Take us back to that studio.
Here. It's that bath
additive you mentioned before.
Thanks.
What's wrong, Driver? Let's get going.
I feel like I've seen her before.
Where?
I'm not sure. Maybe on TV.
If you recognize her face, you must've come
to her concert before she debuted.
She keeps her face hidden.
Is she an idol or something?
That's not it, then.
I've never been to a concert.
Forget what happened today, Driver.
One way or another, she'll
become a public figure someday.
I consider myself something
like an authentic bartender.
You mean you've heard a lot of things.
Are you tired?
Is Nikaido-san coming?
Later.
I can't keep up with her ambition.
You can work at your own pace.
She's incredible. I bet she'd
kill someone just to get ahead.
She probably already has, honestly.
What are you talking about?
Maybe I'm not suited to this job.
There you go again.
I don't know what my purpose is anymore.
I'm not as alluring as Nikaido-san,
and I'm not good
at dancing like Mitsuya-san.
You've got your own strengths, Ichimura.
Like what?
Well, uh...
You know, you're charming and innocent.
You've got a cute face, too.
Don't I wear a mask because
I'm not cute, though?
No. It's the agency's strategy.
Try to understand, would you?
Exchanging messages with
old dudes is exhausting, too—
Hey.
Mitsuya's already inside.
I don't like her. I liked
things better before.
Ichimura.
Your innocence is your strength,
but consider the time, place, and occasion.
Driver, to the office in Kamimeguro.
Boy, am I delighted.
As a taxi driver, that's the number
one thing I want someone to say to me.
"Follow that car."
It's hard. It's hard work, Driver.
But I want to show them
the view from the top.
Huh...
I've got a chance.
A chance?
That girl I mentioned earlier, Rui Nikaido,
is a pure carbon gemstone.
I've heard of Rui Nikaido.
I think a passenger mentioned her.
I'm not talking about a diamond in the rough.
She's a proper carbon gemstone.
Why not promote her alone, then?
That's not how things work these days.
You have to promote them as a group.
And besides, while I feel bad for
the girls you drove earlier,
you need people to prop up a carbon
gemstone so it can shine even brighter.
In other words, I'm a jewelry designer
working with a carbon gemstone.
Without me, it's difficult for
the world to spot carbon gemstones.
Just call it a diamond.
By the way, Driver,
could I get your business card?
Ideally, I'd like to use the same
person to drive them around.
You seem tight-lipped, too.
I won't always be available,
so don't get your hopes up.
Driver
Hiroshi Odokawa
Also, Driver, you should help us advertise.
Could you keep our fliers in your taxi?
Mystery Kiss
People actually want them?
I wouldn't have to work so
hard if success came easily.
Is your office in Kamimeguro the place
with the bar on the first floor?
Yeah, that's it. You know the place?
I was just thinking about
how I once drove a girl there.
What? When?
About two weeks ago, I think.
She must've been from your agency.
It was probably one of
the girls you drove today.
The only group we manage is Mystery Kiss.
Maybe.
Girls that age, especially ones trying
to be idols, all look the same to me.
You said you recognized
the second girl, Shiho Ichimura.
It must've been her.
She's a calico cat. The other girl
was a little different.
We're here. This is it, right?
You're sure?
About what?
Where you dropped off that girl.
You're sure it was at this office?
Yeah.
That'll be 11,940 yen.
Driver
Hiroshi Odokawa
Listen, Driver.
Huh?
Does this car have a recording device?
Why?
Sometimes you see them in the news.
You know, in stories about robberies.
Yeah, I've got one.
Any chance I could get your data?
I thought it might be interesting
to include some candid shots
of the girls in a taxi for our next PV.
Their faces are visible, though.
We'll edit around that.
I'll pay, of course.
You can have their data.
No, I want all of it.
I can't make that decision by myself.
I'll consider it if I can
settle the privacy issues.
Fine.
I'll be in touch.
And I appreciate your cooperation
regarding today and going forward.
Sure. I'm not that
interested, so don't worry.
Thank you for riding.
Goriki Clinic
Sorry I had to ask you to come in.
Clinics are terrifying at night.
Well, Odokawa? Have you been sleeping well?
Thanks to you, I haven't been.
You haven't prescribed me more medication.
What's with calling me in for
a consultation at this hour?
You could go to another clinic.
They'd give you the same medication.
If I were a hairdresser, maybe I'd think,
"I've been building my vision for
this guy's hairstyle for so long,
and this asshole went to another salon."
"He ruined everything."
But I don't run a salon. I run a clinic.
That was a lot of words for a boring payoff.
I'm going to be closing
the clinic for a while.
Why?
My medications aren't adding up.
Were they stolen?
Yeah. Apparently it's been
happening for a long time.
Did you call the police?
No. Apparently it's an inside job.
If this gets out, I'll go from
victim to perpetrator.
I'm thinking about closing the clinic
so I can pretend it didn't happen.
You're doing it to protect yourself.
It's embarrassing to admit, but yes.
Not to protect Shirakawa-san.
Nobody said it was Shirakawa-san.
She's been having money problems.
That's not enough to accuse her.
I remembered something.
A little while ago,
after dropping off a hippo guy,
I saw Dobu and Shirakawa-san
together in an alley at night.
Dobu knew about
Shirakawa-san. It makes sense.
You got a good look at them?
I saw Shirakawa-san from behind.
You don't know it was her, then.
And it was at night.
There are plenty of people
who look like her from behind.
No, I could tell it was her.
You've changed, Odokawa.
It's like you've warmed up recently.
I'm gonna go.
Where?
Unusually enough, two people
asked to meet me today.
You, and...
Hey.
Couldn't you have picked
a better place to meet?
What's wrong with here?
You figured out who wants
your dash cam data?
First, I have question for you.
Sure. That's the only one
I'm answering, though.
You always try to dominate the situation.
That's how negotiations work.
I'm the one helping you, here.
I thought we had a deal.
Huh? Has there always been
an Orvis speed camera here?
Well, there goes your one question.
You're the type who'd waste his wishes
if he found a magic lamp.
That wasn't a question for you,
it was a spur-of-the-moment inquiry.
I'm sure the genie would understand.
Whatever. What's your question?
You and Shirakawa-san
are connected somehow. Right?
If you don't answer me
honestly, I'm not telling you.
You used Shirakawa-san to threaten me.
If you and Shirakawa-san are connected,
then the premise doesn't hold.
Yeah, that's right.
You told Shirakawa-san
to approach me, didn't you?
I don't know crap about that.
She did that on her own.
Shirakawa-san's been stealing
medication from Goriki Clinic.
You've been selling them illegally
for money. Am I right?
That's a lot of questions.
Including the Orvis one,
that's your fourth.
Answer me.
That's mostly correct.
That's cheap work. No wonder
Yano looks down on you.
I'm the one shouldering Shirakawa's debt,
and she's paying me back.
That's all there is to it. It's not a job.
I answered your questions.
Now it's your turn.
Now that I know that, there's no reason
for me to keep my promise, is there?
C'mon, I'm surrounded by enemies.
I've made blunder after
blunder. I'm desperate.
I lost something important
that the boss gave me.
And recently, a video of some
amateur claiming he'll catch me
has gotten ten million views.
I'm having an awful time.
Really? You're famous.
If I don't get the name of the
guy who wanted your dash cam data,
I'll have to kill you.
How will I kill you? Well, let's see.
Why don't I tie up your arms and legs,
throw you into an empty tub,
and slowly fill it with water?
Thankfully, I'm quite good at figuring
out exactly what people don't like.
It's Mystery Kiss's manager.
Mystery Kiss?
Their fliers are back there.
Yano. That asshole.
He was sticking his paws into this, too?
So, what did this manager say?
He asked me to sell him
the data so he could use it in a PV.
Does that mean one of them
is the boss's classmate's daughter?
It could be a good idea to sell him the data
with the parts he wants cut from it.
See how much he'll pay for it.
I'm not getting involved in your business.
Do what you want with the information.
It's none of my business.
Stay away from me.
Hey, are you really that
upset about Shirakawa?
Kakki, do you come
to places like this often?
Well, I mean, I might come once a month.
Wow, I've never been anywhere like this.
Oh, yeah?
Excuse me. Could I get
another glass, please?
Seriously?
Don't laugh.
Shiho-chan, when are you the happiest?
When I'm in the bath.
Really? You like baths, huh?
I grew up poor, with a lot of siblings.
The only place I could
be alone was in the bath.
Poor, huh?
I asked Santa for bath
additives for Christmas.
You know, those ones that fizz up.
I see. That's... kind of cute.
Is the bath at your house
as amazing as I think it is?
Can you stretch your legs out?
Huh? Uh, yeah.
It's got jets and stuff. Of course it does.
Really? Can you watch TV from the bath, too?
Of course.
I'd like to visit.
Huh? Wh-What? Uh, I think it's maybe
still a little too soon for that.
L-L-Listen, why don't we go to
Yufuin sometime instead?
I'd love to go. Where's Yufuin?
Oita Prefecture. It's a short flight away.
Do you have a private jet
or something, Kakki?
I'm not that rich.
Aw, shucks.
Shiho-chan, you're a college student, right?
That's right.
You're so young.
Why are you getting ma... mar...
Thank you for waiting.
Thanks.
You don't need to hold your glass.
Oh, so that's how you guys do things.
Enjoy.
So, what were we talking about?
Shiho-chan, do you actually
want to get married?
Yeah. It's always been
my dream to get married.
I think the sooner I can, the better.
Being surprised with
an engagement ring would be amazing.
In that case, would you—
Hey, look at this.
Imai@Nikaido fan account
@Nikaidorui_love – 1 day ago
I can't stop shaking...
It says he won one billion yen.
Do you think it's true?
One billion yen, huh? Wow.
Not even I have that much.
He's a Rui Nikaido fan, huh?
Huh?
Nothing. Do you know about this?
Everyone's talking about it right now.
Hello, Taichi Kabasawa here.
[Declaration of War] I'll catch Dobu
by the end of the year! [Taichi Kabasawa]
I have an announcement to make.
I, Taichi Kabasawa, will capture
Dobu by the end of the year.
You see, ten days ago, Dobu happened
to be in a photo I uploaded.
I was interviewed by the media.
It went a little bit viral,
so I'm sure some of you know
about that, but I don't know.
Some of you might be wondering if it's
okay for me to use such a sensational title,
but this is, without a doubt,
my sense of justice.
For those of you who don't know who Dobu is,
I'm not sure if he's a thug or yakuza member,
but the police are after him.
But according to the intel I've acquired,
the police haven't been able to catch Dobu.
I don't know if he's backed up
by someone important or something.
Anyway, this Dobu guy is such a bad dude
that people think he's committed
every crime under the sun.
Theft, robbery, fraud, assault,
extortion, sexual assault,
Theft
Robbery
Fraud
Assault
Extortion
Sexual Assault
placing rocks on railway tracks,
arson, kidnapping, and murder.
Rocks on Tracks
Arson
Kidnapping
Murder (?)
Anyway, his crimes are too numerous to list.
Oh, I guess the rocks on
the tracks stand out from the rest.
As a matter of fact, I know people
who were beaten half to death by Dobu.
I'll take this out of your way.
Thanks. Uh...
I heard about it from a friend of a friend.
It's possible that some of you
have met one of his victims.
Even if they weren't directly harmed by Dobu,
it's possible that he was responsible.
I'm sure some people have had
their bike seats stolen, right?
Anyway, I, Taichi Kabasawa,
will catch that Dobu!
I've been looking for a job for a while.
Is something the matter?
Could I get the check?
But when I asked myself
what I really want to do,
Please wait at your table.
I knew I didn't want to be a cog in society.
Oh, so that's how you guys do things.
I didn't want to ride packed trains.
Can you really call that living?
[Declaration of War] I'll catch Dobu
by the end of the year! [Taichi Kabasawa]
While thinking about my life,
I recalled a dream I had as a kid.
I wanted to be a hero who helped people
in trouble. I'm sure you guys did, too.
So I'll catch him.
I'll put off finding a job
and my schoolwork to do it!
What will I do once I catch him?
He'll apologize. I'll make him apologize.
I'll upload a video of him
on his knees. I'll rehabilitate him.
If the law can't punish him, then I will!
No, we will. Including you,
person watching this video.
Together, we'll catch Dobu!
I'm Meisei University
student Taichi Kabasawa!
I won't run. I won't hide.
I'll stand in the line of fire.
So I'm accepting any
and all information. Help me.
Crimes must be punished.
Together we shall defeat evil!
Justice will win!
This video has received a storm of praise.
It's been viewed ten million times.
People are saying, "He's so cool. God-like,"
and, "Kabasawa-sama, I support you."
Crazy, right?
Here's your check.
Thanks.
Yikes.
What's wrong?
Oh, uh... That's all, huh?
Give me one minute.
You're not paying by card?
Since I look at digital
numbers all day long,
I prefer to use cash
when interacting with other people.
You don't even carry a wallet?
I had a B-Bottega Veneta, but I gave
it away to one of my subordinates.
Huh...
Statement
Transactions
Loan
Interest Rate (True Annual Rate): 18.000%
Late Charge (Annual Rate): 20.000%
Next Payment Due Date: 2021/10/25
Total Payments: 2
Takotako Loans
Next Time: Let Me Hear You Say, "What the Hell?"
Odokawa-sama, I'm delighted to see
that you're doing well.
Don't call me that.
Do you believe in fate?
It's fate that brought us together again.
I pick up repeat passengers
in that area all the time while cruising.
But one billion—
Shh! Keep your voice down.