Let Me Hear You Say, "What the Hell?"
Driver!
Hey, you're the Mystery Kiss fan.
You remember me?!
More importantly,
I'm glad I got to see you again.
Why?
I wanted to thank you. To Shinjuku, please.
Did I do something for you?
Man, you practically saved my life.
Saved your life?
Well, maybe I wouldn't go that far.
Seriously?
But you changed my life.
In a manner of speaking, you're a god.
Hey, it's Mystery Kiss!
Tell me, Driver—no, God—
It's Odokawa.
Odokawa-sama, did you get
hooked on Mystery Kiss?
I, uh... I guess so.
I knew you would, Odokawa-sama!
What did I do?
I actually won the lottery using
those numbers you gave me.
Really? That's amazing.
That's not much of a reaction!
I mean, I picked those numbers at random.
You just haven't heard how much I won.
I won one billion yen!
Really?
Really!
I haven't claimed my winnings yet,
but I've checked it about a hundred times.
If that's true, you shouldn't
be spreading that around.
It's my first time telling
someone in real life.
I had to tell you.
What do you mean, in real life?
I told people online, but that's online.
Imai@Nikaido fan account
@Nikaidorui_love – 1 day ago
I can't stop shaking...
Besides, this is too big
for me to keep to myself!
I had to tell someone.
Now you can buy Mystery Kiss CDs.
That's right. I've been keeping
my winning ticket on me
so I can claim my winnings right
when their CD comes out.
You'd better not lose that.
Anyway, Odokawa-sama, I wanted to thank you.
You don't need to do that.
No, no way! I've gotta do something!
Isn't there anything you need money for?
Not particularly.
Then, maybe your family or someone
you care about is in trouble?
Nope.
Do you just not feel desire?!
In that case, Odokawa-sama,
are you free right now?
As you can see, I'm right
in the middle of work.
I'll pay you whatever you'd make today.
Come with me.
Kabukicho Ichiban-gai
You don't have to do this.
Where are we going?
Here!
I'm a waiter at a cabaret club.
Since you don't want anything,
I'm offering you something:
free service for life.
This is VIP Odokawa-sama.
Everything is already paid for,
so order whatever you'd like.
Really?
So cool.
Wow!
Odokawa-san, what would you like to drink?
Actually, I've got to drive...
Is it okay if we drink?
Sure, go ahead.
Hooray!
Shall we open a Dom Pérignon Rose, then?
Odokawa-sama, where are you going?
I've had enough. I'm leaving.
Don't be like that.
Enjoy yourself a little more.
Are you looking for something in particular?
Huh? Uh, no.
Miho Shirakawa
Missed Call
Don't ever get involved
with me again.
Wh-What happened?
I don't know. Someone came in with a gun.
A gun?
Go out through the back door.
It's hidden from the front of house.
Hold on. What are you doing?
What is this? Is this for Halloween?
It's not Halloween yet.
Don't you think you're being hasty?
I've heard people riot every year,
but this is the first time
I've seen a one-man riot.
Shibagaki, what were you trying to do?
Honestly...
I thought it'd be funny if I got shot.
You're crazy.
What?
What did you mean when you told me
not to get involved with you?
Odokawa-san is ignoring me!
Hey, be quiet. You're
bothering the neighbors.
Let me inside, then.
We'll talk outside.
Is someone in there?
What happened to your car? Were you robbed?
They didn't take anything.
You'd better get it fixed soon, or else.
You know, or else.
I have no idea what you're getting at.
Leaving something broken makes
people break it further.
The broken windows theory?
Yeah, the broken windows theory.
It applies to hearts, too.
What do you mean?
So, what do you want?
You told me not to get involved with you.
I know.
The way you think that depending
on what I do, you might still
be able to salvage
the situation is obnoxious, too—
Wait.
Honestly, I was little—no,
I was really happy.
I'm ashamed of myself.
Please.
Don't use your feminine wiles on me, coward.
Because of you, Goriki—
Okay, I get it. I'll tell you everything.
You don't have to tell me what you know.
It's true that Dobu-san and I used to date.
You're starting with something I didn't know.
It was for about four years.
I couldn't say no to him
because of the money.
I'm not listening to you
if you're going to cry.
Besides, it's none of my business.
Please wait. I get it.
I borrowed a large amount
of money from Dobu-san.
I was paying him back little by little.
I couldn't say no to him.
So you stole medication.
I'll tell the police.
Goriki knew it was you
and didn't turn you in.
You should let him handle it instead
of doing something you shouldn't.
And?
Yes?
Why did you approach me?
Dobu-san told me to
bring him the patient list.
He must've had plenty of methods
for turning personal information into profit.
When he saw your name on the list,
he asked me what you were like.
What did you tell him?
That you're a grumpy taxi driver.
Then Dobu-san told me to get close to you.
But over time, I really did begin to—
Spare me.
So, what's Dobu's actual goal?
He said he was going to rob a bank.
He probably needs a taxi
as his getaway car.
Rob a bank? In this day and age?
He said now was the time to do it.
So he wanted to use me as his getaway.
He must think I'm a sucker.
I want you to believe me.
I approached you because he told me to,
but partway through, I had no
intention of turning you over to him.
I don't care about that. What else?
That's all, I think.
Got it.
Don't tell Dobu that you talked to me.
What are you going to do?
Leave him be.
Maybe I'll even pretend
to help him rob a bank.
Okay.
By the way, how much do you still owe Dobu?
Three million yen.
You still owe that much after four years?
Because of the interest,
the principal never went down.
With that exorbitant interest, you should've
borrowed the money from someone else.
You even became an accomplice to his crimes.
He'd beat me.
And he's actually a weak man.
I couldn't just leave him.
Oh, really? I don't care about
your codependent relationship.
Wait, Odokawa-san.
I told you nothing but the truth today.
I want to pay off my debt
and leave Dobu-san. Really.
I'll apologize to Dr. Goriki. Because...
Because I love you.
Don't ever get involved with me again.
I'm tired.
Are you okay? I saw a little
online news story about it.
It was seriously shocking.
I had a gun pointed at me.
The police interviewed me afterward, too.
Headline: "Shibagaki of Homosapiens
encounters armed robber at part-time job."
"Part-time job" sounds so lame.
And why didn't they interview me properly?
I'm the one who chased off the robber.
Really?
Really.
How?
I told him to shoot me if he could.
And then?
In deference to my
manliness, he settled down.
He actually said that?
That's what the eyes
behind the mask told me.
Could you be more specific?
What exactly was the situation?
I can't say much. My employer
doesn't want me to talk about it.
You're the one who always says we
should throw ourselves into trouble
for the sake of interesting stories.
Takotako Loans
If you can't talk about it, what's the point?
What have you been up
to this past week, then?
I've been shooting my drama.
I think some details on it
have been released by now.
Ah.
Plus my regular TV appearances,
so I haven't slept much.
Young guys who have just tasted
success always brag about that.
I've been thinking lately that comedy
that doesn't hurt anyone is best.
No way. I think it's okay to hurt
one person to make ten people laugh.
It just makes people dislike you.
Just look at the guys who are successful
these days. They're all amiable.
You think that makes people laugh?
I mean really laugh?
When we were kids, we laughed
until the very cores of our bodies
were numb at words prickling
with sharp edges.
Yeah, and I think times have changed.
What, then? You think
making weird faces is funny?
You think rolling your eyes is funny?
You think that makes people laugh?!
Since Shibagaki-san has gotten overexcited,
let's move on to fan mail.
This one's from radio name
"When asked where they live,
most people who respond with Osaka
are actually from Amagasaki."
I know what you mean.
Amagasaki is in Hyogo prefecture,
but their area code is 06.
What about that guy?
Who?
That smart-ass high school student
who always sends us mail.
Satoshi Nagashima-kun?
We don't have anything from him today.
Yamabiko
Where's Odokawa-san today?
He said he'd finish work early today
and come if he was feeling up to it.
You've changed recently, Kakihana-san.
Really?
Baba-san!
Will you shake my hand?
Sure thing.
Can I have your autograph?
Thank you.
To Nakameguro, please.
I know exactly what you mean.
What?
What's so funny about rolling your eyes?
Your understanding doesn't mean shit to me.
Who are you, anyway?
Let's go, Driver.
I'm Nagashima! Satoshi Nagashima.
Hello, Taichi Kabasawa here.
[Shocking] Video of shooting at Shinjuku
cabaret club acquired! [Dobu]
Do you guys know there was
a shooting yesterday
at cabaret club "White dolphin" in Shinjuku?
It was on the news,
but would you believe it?
A listener who happened
to be there sent me a video.
This must be Dobu.
More and more of Dobu's vile acts
are being exposed to the light of day.
What really makes me happy
is that they could've made a fortune
selling this video to the media,
but they sent it to Taichi Kabasawa
instead for free! Totally free!
I'm sure it's because they
despise Dobu that much,
but I believe Taichi Kabasawa's
unifying force has grown that strong.
That this is a blessing.
Proof that I've grown closer
to becoming a god.
Divine Judgment
Dobu, your time has nearly come!
I have a million followers. I am a god.
You're looking haggard.
Are you prepared to pay for your crimes?!
I guess you're surprisingly delicate.
I feel like I'm being blamed
for all the crimes in the world.
And I didn't understand the kind
of influence the internet has.
Everyone looks like an enemy to me now.
It definitely serves you right.
The gun this guy used was definitely mine.
That's what's so bad about it.
Was it that Yano guy?
I don't think it was Yano.
If it were Yano, it would've
seemed more purposeful.
If you look closely, it seems like
he's searching for someone.
You were in the bathroom
when this happened, right?
Are you saying someone's
got a grudge against me?
If your car window being broken
was also a coincidence,
then you've got horrendous luck.
Nothing was stolen. Naturally,
that includes my dash cam data.
That's exactly my point.
If we're looking for a purpose,
then I'd say someone's trying
to torture you to death.
Mentally first, and then physically.
I'm surprised you're so
calm about all of this.
It's like you're actually not afraid to die.
I'm scared. Of course I'm scared.
Why don't we join forces, then?
Join forces?
This Halloween guy is trying to kill you.
I need to get this gun back.
Why don't we fight together?
On an unrelated note,
regarding Mystery Kiss,
if Yano is involved, then I can't touch it.
I want you to help me gather information.
I'm doing all the work here.
I ain't asking you to do it for free.
I'll make sure Goriki
can return to his clinic.
Fine.
You'll help me, then?
It's been a long road getting here,
but you and I were destined
to become allies.
I want to add another condition.
What is it?
Release Shirakawa-san.
Write off her debt.
Fine. I promise.
I'm gonna look for the man with the gun.
Odokawa, I need you
to catch Taichi Kabasawa.
This guy, huh? I gave him a ride once.
I know. I saved our group photo.
We know Taichi Kabasawa's identity,
so we can do something about him.
But how are you going to find
the guy with the gun?
Halloween.
On Halloween, I'm going to
dress up as the man with the gun
and walk around town.
You're going to wear a skull mask?
I see. Since everyone knows your face,
you can't walk around town on any other day.
He might go out wearing the same outfit.
Either way, I expect I'll run
into him some way or another.
He's the self-aggrandizing type.
I'll go directly to Taichi Kabasawa's
university and pick him up.
University? How many students
do you think you'll find there?
I'll be fine. I'm good
at finding people in a crowd.
Why? You've got good eyes or something?
What do you mean, why?
If anything, I find it strange
that you guys are so bad at it.
Camera rehearsal is good.
Homosapiens
Baba-sama
Hey, you've been making lots
of money recently, haven't you?
Homosapiens
Baba-sama
I wouldn't say that.
You've been named the number one
breakout entertainer.
Huh? Oh, really?
I knew you'd get there, Baba-kun.
It's hard to explain, but there are guys
who are loved despite being stupid, y'know?
Stupid? I'm not—
I didn't mean it in a weird way.
What other way could you have meant it?
It's hard to put into words
what's good about you, Baba-kun.
Don't give up so quickly.
Please list everything that's good about me.
You've got a certain virtue or grace.
At the end of the day,
you've got good breeding.
I bet not many people say they dislike you.
Nah, my partner probably hates me.
He's always calling me
a worthless piece of junk.
You should cut ties with him.
What?
In this world, the weak are weeded out.
Your partner's just being a sore loser.
But, Shibagaki is—
Oh, right. I'd like you to appear
in a special end-of-year program.
We're recording next Friday.
We really want you to be in it.
That day is Round 3 of the N-1.
I could do it after that.
You're still doing that? Give it up already.
I spent a year working towards that, so...
I see.
We'll make some adjustments, then.
I'm counting on you, Baba-chan.
I've got high hopes for you.
Boo!
Hey, what are you doing?
I saw the producer leaving.
You can't come in here.
I haven't seen you at all recently, though.
Sorry. These days I don't
even have time to sleep.
I told you that you didn't need
to become this successful.
Rui-chan, what are you doing today?
Are you recording something?
Our debut single goes on sale on Christmas.
I'm promoting it today.
We're doing a concert at a
2,000 person venue that day.
Really? That's amazing! I'm happy for you.
You're moving up in the world step by step.
You always said you wanted to
climb higher, Rui-chan.
Yeah. And if that goes well,
they said they'd get us the Budokan.
Really? I'm rooting for you.
I'd better work hard, too.
You don't have to work so hard.
I like that you're the opposite
of my excessive ambition, Baba-san.
You keep saying that, but I'm still a man.
It's true that I lack ambition, though.
Then what's the problem? C'mere.
Are you sure you don't think of me as a pet?
I don't want a pet with a horse face.
Whoa!
I knew I'd find you here.
Recording is starting. Let's go.
That was close.
Coming.
Baba-san, please.
Now that you're becoming successful,
I'm sure you understand.
This is a really important time for her.
Yes. I know.
Let me know if your schedule
opens up. I'll match yours.
Hello?
You wanna meet up now
to discuss our material?
Sorry. I've got a shoot.
What are we gonna do? Round 3 is next week.
What should I do?
How about after your shoot today?
I've got a wrap party.
How about tomorrow?
I've got an all day, on-location shoot.
The day after that?
Filming a drama first thing in the morning.
And the day after that?
On-location close coverage shoot.
Recording a special.
And the day after that?
Overseas shoot.
Next Time: Trick or Treat
Hey, Little Daimon.
Is the investigation going well?
Listen here, Odokawa.
Local Civil Service Law has got
this thing called confidentiality.
I don't know what that covers,
but information doesn't make its way
down to lowly grunts like me!
Don't make me say it!