This guy was a dud.
He's actually part-time janitor.
Not only that, but he's drowning in debt.
Drowning in debt and desperate.
Thought he could get away
with lyin' about it.
The only thing he had on him was this ring.
An engagement ring? I could cry.
So desperate to tie the knot he lied?
Have middle-aged men's brains liquefied?
Will he tie a noose instead
after being tossed aside?
An article of tribute for his fake honey.
If you ask me, this wasn't worth the money.
Who's got any use for this counterfeit?
I've got a few ideas 'bout where he can stick it.
Where's Shiho-chan? Is she all right?
Hey, Kakihana-chan.
If you still trust that girl you wanted to
get with, your brains are in the trash can.
That calculating girl who flirted with you
for your money took off and ran.
In other words, it was a scam.
I'm the one who told her to wait and
see what your lame ass would do.
Let you think you'd won before
sucking you dry and killing you.
That's all for today.
I'll come up with a new plan.
Fuyuki Yamamoto
Incoming Call
Hey, isn't this the guy you said
wanted your dash cam data?
That's right.
Answer and put it on speakerphone.
Hello?
Ah, Odokawa-san. Could you
come pick me up right away?
This is sudden. Does it have to be me?
Aren't most pickups sudden?
It's one of those girls who
can't be seen by the public.
Where?
A short distance away from Shibuya.
Got it. I'll be there in ten minutes.
Thanks.
What should I do? He'll probably
ask for my dash cam data.
Let me ride in the trunk.
I'll eavesdrop on your conversation
through your phone.
I can't do that. As far as I'm concerned,
he's a harmless passenger.
Then ask him why he really wants the data,
and if he's connected to Yano,
then tell me about it later.
Don't you think he'd lie about that?
That's right. That's why violence
is the only way to get people to talk.
Let me meet him.
I'm the one who has the dash cam data.
I'm sure Yamamoto wants to meet me, too.
I can't let you do that.
I have to go. I told him
I'd be there in ten minutes.
Fine. If he asks for your
dash cam data, tell him this.
You'll sell it to him for one billion yen.
Sorry, Odokawa-san. Could you take us
to Shibaura Harbor in a hurry?
The harbor?
Hey, it's the girl who likes hot springs.
A calico cat. Where have I seen one before?
What are you talking about, Odokawa-san?
Hey, am I going to meet Ya—that guy?
Yeah. I'm sorry, but if you want to quit,
you have to tell him yourself.
I worked really hard, though.
Apparently, that target didn't work out.
What? You mean he didn't have money?
Is that old man serious?
Oh, right. I just remembered.
Have you considered my request
to hand over your dash cam data?
Yeah, sure.
Really?
I'll sell it to you.
For how much?
One billion.
That's the kind of price
a child would come up with.
What? You're being serious?
Super serious.
This is ridiculous, Odokawa-san.
You're gouging me here.
I found someone who said
they'd buy it for 900 million.
That's why I want one billion.
You're lying.
Who is it?
I can't tell you that.
If that's true, then I need
to discuss this with someone.
Discuss it all you want.
I wouldn't mind 900 million or one billion.
I'll be in touch.
Doesn't this seem like not enough profit?
Is this all we make from concerts?
They weren't the only ones performing today.
Why's she here?
She doesn't want to run
badger games anymore,
so she's here to talk to Yano-san.
Ah.
He's busy right now.
More importantly, I've got some bad news.
Could I talk to him for a few minutes?
Bad news?
It's about the dash cam.
Shiho-chan!
You're being tricked, right?
I'll protect you from these guys!
It's okay, Shiho-chan.
I'm actually pretty strong.
I've mastered every martial art there is,
from sumo for kids to whatever-jiujitsu.
Don't get the wrong idea, mister.
Seriously, I can't even.
Shiho-chan, they're making
you say that, aren't they?
Didn't we have fun together?
We ate lots of good food together!
Spending time with you was painful.
That's why I want to quit
running badger games.
You're lying! Liar!
You're not the kind of girl who says that!
Shiho-chan, you're a liar!
You're the liar, you bum. You're broke.
Why?! Why would you say that?!
I don't believe you! You're lying!
Shut up.
Ayumu Goriki
Can you tell who this is?
It's Kakihana, you unemployed bum.
Wanna get drinks at Yamabiko right now?
It's been a while. I guess I'll go.
Goriki Clinic
Can you tell from this photo
that this is Kakihana?
I guess I'd believe you
if you told me it was him.
I doubt I'd know if I were just
shown this photo without context.
Yeah.
It only took Odokawa-san
a second to identify him.
Does that tell us anything?
At first I thought Odokawa
had an exceptional memory,
but it doesn't feel right.
You're right. I thought
maybe he had good instincts.
It's almost like synesthesia.
Synesthesia?
It's when one sense is stimulated,
and a completely different
sense is triggered.
Like seeing colors or feeling textures
when you hear sounds or see letters.
Maybe Odokawa has some kind
of indicator for telling people apart
and is basing it on that.
I don't know if this is related,
but apparently Odokawa-san has been
speaking to someone in his home,
and he's clearly not talking to himself.
Regarding that, if there really
isn't anybody there,
then maybe it's an imaginary friend.
Like a figment of his imagination?
Yeah.
You might already know, but he's lived alone
since his parents abandoned him
when he was in grade school.
Alone?
Apparently some kind of NPO
that supports orphans
sent him money to cover his living expenses.
He pretends that he wanted for nothing
and experienced no
difficulties because of that.
But if he's invented an imaginary friend,
then he may be under more
stress than he realizes.
When did the two of you meet?
About three years ago, I think.
I thought it was this year when he first
started seeing you for consultations.
Had he been coming
to the clinic before that?
No. I rode in his taxi as a passenger first.
It's finally starting.
Sure has.
We used to broadcast in just Osaka,
but now we've gone national.
That's right. Starting this year,
the Homosapiens have expanded to Tokyo.
For real. I'm overjoyed.
Could you turn that off? It's annoying.
For sure.
Got here sooner than I expected.
Yeah, seriously.
Guess we should keep trying, then—
How old are you?
38.
We're the same age?
You seem so dignified, though.
Hey, that's rude. Mind your manners.
Manners? You act like you're real important.
What, do you think
the customer is always right?
I bet you look down on taxi drivers.
You got some kind of pent-up anger, or what?
It's not anyone's fault
that your life isn't going well.
It's not your environment's
fault, either. It's your fault.
You should resolve it yourself
without bothering others.
Of course. Doctors speak
differently from the rest of us.
Hey, that got to you.
That's charming. Good for you.
How'd you know?
I'm psychic.
Then why didn't you know my age?
Psychic powers come in a variety of flavors.
I can see souls.
And your soul's been screaming, "I'm a doctor."
As for your age, I couldn't tell because
your soul and body are so separated.
In other words, you look old.
You're funny.
In that case, can you hear what my soul
is shouting now? What's it saying?
"Don't turn. Head straight ahead."
Turning here gets us to your clinic faster.
I was shocked. It really was a shortcut.
At first, I thought he had
an exceptional sense of smell
that allowed him to pick up on the
distinctive hospital smell coming off of me.
But you think it's synesthesia?
When I asked how he did it later,
he said it was nothing.
He'd just had me as a passenger before.
So you thought it was his memory.
Yeah. I thought it was impressive, if true.
That's why synesthesia makes sense to me.
I'm going to Yamabiko for a drink.
Shirakawa-san, do you want to come with me?
If I go, I imagine Odokawa-san would leave.
Mochi kinchaku and daikon radish.
I'd like some kind of nerimono, too.
Wait a minute. You've got
a Donraku Shofutei autograph.
To Yamabiko
Donraku
That's right. He stopped by the other day.
Really? Wow.
You sure do like him, Odokawa.
He sat right over there with an
incredibly cross look on his face.
He came alone?
He had an attendant with him,
as well as a driver outside.
What did they talk about?
How young comedians these days
are obsessed with innovation
and don't have the basics down.
Or how he pretends he doesn't mince words.
Or how being a commentator
or judging comedy contests
doesn't benefit him in any way.
I thought he was getting mad,
but then, he started cackling
while reminiscing about his old mentor.
You totally eavesdropped.
Oh, right, Odokawa. Let me quiz you.
What's gotten into you?
Does losing your job make you
turn back into a child?
I'd like to play, too.
Sure. You can join us.
Can you tell who this is?
Is this your thing these days?
How am I supposed to know?
Exactly. But Odokawa
identified him immediately.
It's clearly Kakihana.
But that's just how Odokawa-san is.
He remembers the faces
of customers I don't recognize.
I bet you'd be good at customer service.
I can't unless they make an impression.
That's not the question here.
Do you know who this is?
Inbox
Got it.
I'll stop by later.
Of course not.
Really?
Really.
Odokawa-san, are you psychic?
Like Psychometrer What's-his-name?
What's this, then?
A bird?
Even I know that one. It's a bird.
Correct.
Are you making fun of me?
Next, this one.
Shirakawa-san.
What the hell have you been up to?
That's Shirakawa-san?
Is this some kind of kink?
Mixing your personal and professional
lives? My, how scandalous.
I see.
What are you trying to pull?
Nevermind. Let's drink.
Ma'am, drink with us.
Perhaps I'll have a drink, then.
Must be nice being unemployed.
To Yamabiko
Donraku
I know. Why don't we call Kakihana?
I bet he'll come if I say I'm paying.
Goriki
So, Yamamoto, what's your bad news?
It's about the dash cam data.
Apparently someone else has
offered to buy it for 900 million.
900 million? He's lying so he can gouge you.
I hope you're right, but we need to get
that dash cam data soon.
It was on the news the other day.
I haven't been able to sleep since then.
I keep expecting my doorbell to ring.
Quit your whining!
Mystery Kiss is doing great right now.
Their CD is about to go on sale!
You mean they'll make more money?
Yes, and a guy who's a fan of our Nikaido
won one billion yen in the lottery.
I'm not sure if it's true or not,
but I imagine he'll spend
quite a lot of money on us.
One billion? Robbing him
would be more profitable.
That won't help Mystery Kiss get big!
Okay, okay. Nikaido sure is cute.
Ask her if she'd like to spend
a night with me nude.
I was picturing that future but still listening to you.
My instincts tell me Dobu-san is involved.
Like the cop from those books.
Inspector Totsugawa, I think he was called.
Dobu-san offered to buy
the data for 900 million?
That's what I'm thinkin'.
He knows the guy who has
the one billion, let that sink in.
He's tryin' to get us to
rob him, and earn a free win.
Or Dobu-san himself is planning
to rob the fella, I know.
I can see his train of thought
clearly as it comes and goes.
That's what makes me the best, y'know?!
So, what should we do?
What should we do? We do what we can.
For now, we'll just play
along with his little plan.
He's a tasty target for us, too, so I'm a fan.
A few million would be another story.
But playing the odds
for a billion? Mandatory.
Dobu-san's trying to make
money by ripping off my act.
Without a doubt, he's a shitty copycat.
I'd like to take him down,
but I need forty winks.
Game set for tonight,
tomorrow it's time to think.
What should we do with him?
He's an extra life in video game terms.
We should hold onto all the sacrificial
pawns we can, as far as I'm concerned.
The more you have, the more
prepared you'll be for misfortune.
You understand that, right?
Then don't speak, okay?
I'll be thinkin' about you night and day.
Until he cashes that lottery ticket,
we'll be keeping you locked away.
So, Kakihana, live as long as you can.
Are you of sound mind?
This might be the last time, man.
Mom
Talk to her before you forget how.
I called her number for you just now.
Hey, Mom. Sorry for calling so late.
No, it's nothing.
I was just wondering how you're doing.
The other day, I said I might
be getting married, but...
It's not happening.
Hey, Dobu. To your left. It's Kabasawa.
[Assault] Dobu's violence finally caught on camera!! [Injury]
As you just saw, I finally
succeeded in filming him myself.
The Kabasawa Online Salon
closed community met in Shibuya
wearing skull masks for a million yen prize
for whoever catches him,
but one of our members became his victim.
He won't get away with this!
So, everyone, let's corner Dobu.
If you'd like to help, please join
the Kabasawa Online Salon.
We're trying to break ten thousand members.
For a limited time, the monthly fee
is just ten thousand yen!
Anyway, didn't that video
strike you as a little odd?
That voice at the end shouting,
"Hey, Dobu. To your left. It's Kabasawa."
Who was that?
I think there's a traitor in the salon.
After all, I was wearing this then.
How did they know?! It doesn't make sense!
Whoever finds the traitor
gets a million yen, too!
The Online Salon is jumping at shadows now!
Show them our solidarity! Catch them!
Catch Dobu! Catch the traitor!
This thing has a ton of views.
I bet he's made a lot of money.
That's right, you!
I promise I'll expose you!
I know, right? But apparently
he's starting to gain haters.
They say he's a one-hit
wonder and a coward.
New message
Taeko
I haven't heard from Kakihana-san in a week.
Do you know where he is?
N-1 Grand Prix 2021
Results – Schedule
What is N-1 2021?
The N-1 2021 is a hardcore national contest for
professional and amateur "manzai" comedians.
30 Semifinalist Groups
Callop
The Goose
Bam Bam Bigelow
Japan's Section Chief
Yamori-tei
Jerry Don
Kyoto Hoteison
Mrs. Osborne
Ao-momiji
Orange Victory
Homosapiens
Fuyu and Hikoki
We made it to the semifinals.
Yeah!
So, Yamamoto the manager seemed flustered?
Yeah. He wanted to know who
was trying to buy it for 900 million.
He was heading to a warehouse
at the harbor, right?
He's definitely connected to Yano, then.
Was the boss's classmate's
daughter in the dash cam data?
I checked, but I don't know
which passenger she would be.
And it's not like I can show the boss.
So, what are you going to do next?
I'm gonna rob a bank.
What? Sorry, I wasn't listening.
Recording 1.wav
Apparently my friend is missing.
I'm going to rob a bank.
Are you stupid? How, in this day and age?
To be precise, I'm going to rob someone
who's at the bank to make a withdrawal.
I want you to help me.
Is the risk-return worth it?
Nobody walks around with that much cash.
It's worth the risk. After all,
he'll have one billion yen.
What do you mean? Explain.
It takes a week or two to get
enough cash for a large withdrawal.
They're supposed to contact me
when that happens.
They'll let me know who's receiving
how much cash on what day at what time,
because I've bribed a bank employee.
And then you're free to do
what you want with them?
That's right. That's when
the real crime begins.
Where did the number one
billion yen come from?
The bank in question exchanges
lottery tickets for money.
Anyone who wins a large
amount has to go there.
Even so, nobody would withdraw
that much money in cash.
But recently, someone has
appeared on the internet
claiming to have won one billion yen.
Yano's probably aware of him, too.
Because I demanded one
billion from Yamamoto,
Yano will go after that guy
for his one billion yen.
I don't know if they'll threaten him,
but they'll force him to withdraw the money.
I'll be waiting for that opportunity.
It's what you call fishing
in troubled waters.
Can you trust someone
who makes that claim online?
If it's fake, that's fine.
Somebody won one billion yen.
Yano and his crew will find them.
How much is one billion yen in cash?
Can it be easily stolen?
It weighs about 100 kilos.
Not impossible to carry.
I doubt the bank employees will help you.
Do you have other allies?
Among the police, yeah.
Who?
You've been asking some very thoughtful
and expository questions.
Like you're trying to get me to commit
to answers for a third party to listen to.
I'm getting involved in a major crime here.
Of course I want to know the details.
Who, huh? I'm sure you have some idea.
I don't. Who is it?
Daimon.
Really? Which one?
The older brother.
Recording 1.wav
End Recording
Is Kakihana your missing friend?
Yeah. I'm worried about him.
I'm going to look for him
where I think I might find him.
Be ready to go anytime.
Stay nimble and alert.
We haven't found skull mask
or Kabasawa yet, either—
Don't treat me like your henchman.
Thank you.
You could definitely see half her chest!
Hello?
Well, if it isn't Odokawa-sama.
I'm coming to pick you up. Get off work.
What? Really?
To: Little Daimon
Subject:
Attachments:
Recording 1.wav
Message Sent
Your message has been sent.
Back
Eiji Kakihana
Calling
What is that monkey doing?
Kabukicho Ichiban-gai
What is it, Odokawa-sama?
When are you going to cash
your one billion yen?
Mystery Kiss' CD is going
on sale on Christmas.
I thought I'd time it with that.
I'm going to pre-order
300,000 this time.
When you think of it that way,
one billion doesn't seem like much.
Could you wait a little longer
to redeem your ticket?
Some gangsters are after your money.
Seriously?! That's super scary!
It's because you posted
about it online, you idiot.
I want you to change residences
and lay low for a while.
Also, is that picture of your
winning lottery ticket still online?
Huh?
Edit it and re-upload it.
Say you actually didn't win.
That you wanted to show off.
Pretend you're a pitiful idiot.
Will that work?
I don't know if this will
make you feel better,
but you do want to live a long life, right?
Yes. I can't die until Mystery Kiss
takes over the country.
Mystery Kiss has been
through a lot of hardship,
but their spring's finally on the horizon!
Ow. What was that for, Odokawa-sama?
What did you just say?
Before that.
Mystery Kiss' CD is going
on sale on Christmas.
I thought I'd time it with that.
I'm going to pre-order
300,000 this time.
When you think of it that way,
one billion doesn't seem like much.
That's too far back.
What? I can't die until Mystery
Kiss takes over the country.
After that.
Their spring's finally on the horizon.
My spring's finally on the horizon, though.
Kakihana-san!!
Good luck at work
Well, read it and weep.
How could I forget about that?
Stupid, stupid, stupid!
She's a calico cat.
Next Time: The Hero's Melancholy
Good to see ya, Odokawa!
You gettin' enough to drink?
Is your glass empty?
What are you...
Hey, Kakihana. What's gotten into you?
All these painful memories
came flooding back...
You sound totally screwed.