The Hero's Melancholy
I listened to the recording.
Pretty conclusive evidence, isn't it?
Dobu only named my brother.
Little Daimon
Maybe he lied out of desperation.
All we know for sure is that Dobu is
planning to rob a bank. That's all.
Your love for your brother is beautiful.
But that's good enough for me.
I want to let Dobu keep going for now.
Where are you now, Odokawa?
My friend may have been kidnapped.
I'm going to rescue him.
Sounds like a case, Odokawa.
That's right. Evil is afoot.
That's unbelievably evil. And if evil is
afoot, then it's time for me to act.
You're going to help me?
Of course. Punishing evil is my job.
Where should I go?
Shibaura Wharf.
Outside my jurisdiction.
Don't come, then.
Wait.
I doubt you're aware, but there's this thing
called extra-jurisdictional authority.
You're welcome to help as Little
Daimon the private citizen,
but for now, I don't need
help from the cops.
That's incredibly insulting.
I'm doing this to exterminate evil.
If you don't tear it out by the
roots, it just comes back.
Little Daimon
That's right. You're quick on the uptake.
I'm trying to get rid of
them all in one fell swoop,
so I need the cops to wait a little longer.
Damn it.
It's frustrating, but if the alternative
is being overrun by evil,
then I'll have to turn a blind eye to it.
Where the hell did you learn those words?
I'm in a hurry. I'll talk to you later.
#dobu #taichikabasawa #judgment #amazingepisode
[Shocking] Video of shooting at
Shinjuku cabaret club acquired! [Dobu]
2,450,000 views – 1 week ago
Share    Download    Save
Taichi Kabasawa
2,100,000 subscribers
Subscribe
Posted 11/01/2021
Dobu sightings and fan letters ↓
kbsw_t@jmail.com
Official Kabasawa Zwitter ↓
Subject:
1 hour from now, Dobu will
show up at Shibaura Wharf.
Be a real hero.
You haven't uploaded any videos recently.
You should catch Dobu soon
and become a real hero.
You know you've been
getting more haters recently?
They're saying you're not a hero.
That you're just an approval-hungry monster.
That you're scared of Dobu.
That you brainwashed them into making
offerings, but they've come to their senses.
That once you peel back your pretense
of divinity, you're just an ordinary guy.
That you're just a one-hit wonder.
That you're sleeping with
your female followers...
Oh, I guess that last one is true.
It frustrates me, y'know?
I can't just tell them
Kabasawa-sama is the real deal.
Looking at you lately,
I realize that you really are—
Shut up.
You don't know me!
Society made all this fuss about me!
They thrust this attention
on me, put me in the line of fire!
I didn't ask to be deified!
You don't know the kind
of pressure I'm under!
I'm so scared, I don't know what to do!
This is who your god is!
This is who your hero is!
Leave, bitch!
11/7 Sunday
1 hour from now...
1 hour from now, Dobu will
show up at Shibaura Wharf.
Be a real hero.
You're treating me like your bodyguard?
You've really made it, haven't you, Odokawa?
Still acting like my superior, I see.
That's right. Sorry.
Our goals are different,
but we're partners on the same level,
who are temporarily working together.
So, where's Kakihana?
Shibaura Wharf.
Hold on. Isn't that—
The girl Kakihana met through a dating site
and the girl who was with
Yamamoto are the same person.
Kakihana went missing at the same time
Yamamoto and his girl headed to the wharf.
They're probably running a badger game.
That would make it Yano's job.
I can't do anything about that.
I don't care about the decorum
of your criminal activities.
I only care about rescuing Kakihana.
This is gonna be a pain in the ass.
Isn't Yano your junior?
You're the one obsessed with hierarchies
and pledges made over sake cups.
You should be able to
resolve this by talking—
That doesn't work with Yano.
There's an unspoken rule that we don't
interfere with each other's business.
I may not get along with Yano,
but we're both trying
to make money for the boss.
If I can't save Kakihana,
I'm not helping you rob a bank.
Wouldn't that mean Yano
is interfering with your job?
You think you're so witty, don't you?
Get down!
Shit, it grazed me.
Park us somewhere. I'm taking back my gun.
No way. He's trying to kill me.
I thought you didn't care if you died.
No, no, no. I don't like pain.
He's terrifying. What's his problem?
Are we still in Japan?
Ow...
Let's run for it.
Looks like we lost him.
Why did you run?
That was a one-in-a-million chance.
I can't let you or I die right now.
Excuse me.
Um, excuse me.
Huh? Again?
You got a tiny bladder, or what? Jeez.
This is just like the problem
of keeping death row inmates
who aren't assigned
to penal labor incarcerated.
You gotta take care of 'em.
I'm leaving, so you'd better get it all out.
I'll come back to check
on you in about three days.
Why are you scared of water?
Who knows? Maybe
I drowned in a previous life.
Well, phobias don't always have a reason.
I'm sure Yano-san will find a way
to turn your life into money.
A way to use—
Here we go.
Well, if it isn't Dobu-san.
What do you think you're doing?
Sorry, Sekiguchi.
I'm here to rescue a kidnapping victim.
What did Yano-san have to say about this?
I haven't talked to Yano.
Then please leave.
It's cold out here. At least let me inside.
Who is he?
A taxi driver.
You made a man with
an honest job your underling?
You've fallen far, Dobu.
And you're out runnin' badger games,
so I could say the same of you.
Hey, taxi driver. I'm gonna
chuck this guy into the sea.
Take Kakihana and get outta
here in the meantime.
Odokawa...
Sorry to keep you waiting.
What are they doing?
They're idiots.
They're idiots, so they don't know how
to express their feelings.
They use duty and human nature
as an excuse for violence.
I guess it's what you'd expect
from living creatures.
I get to go home?
Yeah, let's go home. You must've been cold.
Wait a minute, Dobu-san.
I let Kakihana escape.
If you beat me, then I won't
be able to face Yano-san.
Not my problem.
It's your fault that you couldn't beat me.
Why don't you take this opportunity to quit
doing low-tier jobs like badger games?
Odokawa, I don't know what to say.
I'm so pathetic.
Damn it! Skull mask...
I thought you were an amateur.
Huh?
Remember how we went to Hakone
for off-campus education in high school?
Yeah, we sure did.
You bought a yosegi puzzle box
as a souvenir, remember?
Yeah, I did.
One with 36 steps.
Is that right? I'm surprised you remember.
You kept it in your bag for a while.
You'd perform all 36 steps and
open the thing, like a showoff.
I feel like I remember that...
Do you remember what happened to that box?
What happened?
You put your family's stamp inside it
and left it on top of the shoe
cupboard in your entryway.
When a delivery arrived, your mom tried
to open it through trial-and-error.
The deliveryman watched her the entire time.
Ultimately, she smashed it open
and got the stamp out, like an otter.
You got in a lot of trouble later.
Yeah, that's what happened. What about it?
What are you trying to say, here?
You've been pathetic ever since then.
I did it. I finally did it, everyone.
I got Dobu. Me!
Hey, Dobu!
I'm Kabasawa. Give it up, you punk!
Apologize, you bastard!
Apologize to everyone in the world.
Hey, haters. And you shitheads who did
nothing but heckle me from safety.
You all talked a lotta shit about me.
Well, who's the punk now?
In the end, I got Dobu all by myself!
I'm the only charismatic leader you need!
You're all my slaves!
Huh?
You have a gun?
Do you have a gun?
All right. Then let's
hear what you have to say.
Or would you rather duke it out?
I s-surrender!
What?
As you can see, I can't beat you in a fight.
Is that the extent of your sense of justice?
You vowed to catch me,
when your resolve was this weak?
You never had any sense of justice
or resolve to begin with.
Why don't you try reflecting on
the principles that drove you to act?
I wanted attention.
You got it. Now, why not dig a little deeper?
Why did you want attention?
I don't know.
It's because you wanted approval
from others, yeah?
And why did you want approval from others?
Because you have no self-esteem.
Because you have no confidence,
you can't approve of yourself.
But despite that, you're more
narcissistic than anyone.
No! I'm not a narcissist.
I hated who I was before I had attention.
That said, receiving attention didn't
magically make me like myself.
But it felt so good, so I kept escalating.
Now I'm so scared, I don't know what to do.
I regret it. I've always hated myself.
I despise who I am.
I've always wanted to disappear.
I've always wanted to die.
I'm saying your extreme rejection of
and hatred for yourself is narcissism.
Normal people aren't that
interested in themselves.
What should I do, then?
Find a mentor you trust, not an
unspecified large number of people.
One you can respect.
If you've got a baseline to measure
yourself from, you won't waver.
If that's too difficult,
then approve of yourself.
In any case, you need
to learn to accept yourself.
I understand!
I appreciate your words,
Dobu-san. I hear you.
From now on, I, Taichi Kabasawa,
shall return to university,
resume looking for a job,
and live my life one day at a time!
Because of you, my eyes have been opened.
Thank you!
Excuse me!
Hey, wait. I'm not running
a self-improvement seminar here.
As you know, I don't make an honest living.
I need you to compensate me
for all the harm you've caused me.
Please don't kill me.
And what can you give me, if not your life?
U-Um, I bought an a-apartment.
You can have that.
A-And a car. I drove it here today.
I have some money left, too.
Please... Please forgive me.
Well, that's the wisest choice.
You did make that money off me.
So... Will you forgive me?
Yeah.
I'm not going to die?
You're a good person, Dobu-san—
One more thing.
Goriki Clinic
He's such an idiot.
His mind and body are
in a pretty weakened state.
He'll have to stay here for a while.
He doesn't have any money.
I'll give him a discount.
Hey, Odokawa. What are you doing?
Didn't you go with Dobu to save Kakihana?
I'm going to take down Dobu.
I'll use whatever I can, and ultimately,
I'll take out his whole organization.
You're just a taxi driver.
Why do you need to do that?
Don't do anything dangerous.
Are you avenging Shirakawa-san?
She's a good girl at heart.
Dobu got his claws in her
before she knew any better.
He used her. She's a victim.
But in some ways, she brought it on herself.
She may have been controlled by fear,
but it was her weakness that
made her follow Dobu's instructions.
She must've had plenty
of chances to leave him.
Shirakawa-san threw those chances away.
She didn't bring it on herself.
Aren't you a doctor? Have you
heard of Stockholm Syndrome?
It's when kidnapping victims develop
affection for their kidnappers, right?
Following Dobu's instructions
was her strategy for survival.
She felt that cornered.
She was controlled by violence and threats.
It was an unfair situation.
But that's no reason for you
to cross this dangerous bridge.
Do you love Shirakawa-san that much?
Taichi Kabasawa-san has uploaded a video.
[Shutting Down] Taichi Kabasawa Defeated [Surrender]
To everyone watching the
Kabasawa channel, as of this day,
I, Taichi Kabasawa, have decided to stop
uploading videos and holding online salons.
All Kabasawa accounts will be
erased in a few days.
I am not a hero, nor champion of justice.
I apologize for ultimately
deceiving all of you.
Dobu—Dobu-san has nothing to do
with this, so don't get the wrong idea.
I simply lost to myself.
So I ask that the rest of you
leave Dobu-san alone, also.
Also, um, I'm not offering refunds
for the online salon.
I appreciate your understanding.
He's a tough guy.
Both Sekiguchi and Kabasawa lost to him.
Did you post it?
Yes. It's done.
What?
Nothing. I'm just grateful that
I made it through this unscathed.
I'm sorry.
Well, I'll be taking your car.
Hey, you'll fall if you
don't quit messing around.
I'll be fine.
Odokawa-kun, are you home?
His car's not here. I don't think he's home.
Really? Well, that's a problem.
Oh, I'm the landlord here.
Who are you?
I hadn't introduced myself yet.
I'm Odokawa's friend, Goriki.
What's the problem? Did something happen?
Oh, all sorts of things lately.
First the police showed up,
then his window was broken.
Odokawa-kun said he was going to move
because he didn't want to cause trouble.
How is that a problem?
It's a huge problem.
I'm Odokawa-kun's guardian,
and I've already received enough rent
for him to live here for life.
From the foundation?
That's right.
But since Odokawa-kun started working,
he's been paying more than his rent.
He told me to return the money
to the foundation's representative.
How long has Odokawa been living here?
Since fifth grade.
Alone? He's been living off
the foundation's money?
Yes. Sometimes he'd eat at my place,
but for the most part, he'd refuse.
He said he didn't want to trouble me.
I helped him with any necessary business
at school and the public office.
I just felt so bad for him.
Could you tell me the name of that
representative or the foundation itself?
I don't know if I can.
Their condition is that in exchange
for not seeking any profit or tax benefits,
our identities are kept secret.
But you deposit the money you get
from Odokawa, right?
Of course I do.
You think I'd steal it? How dreadful.
That's not what I meant.
If Odokawa-kun is moving,
then I intend to return the money
I've been holding onto.
Do you know where Odokawa lived
before coming here?
I think it was Shiroku in Chichibu.
Shiroku in Chichibu.
Anyway, he lived alone?
Was living at an orphanage
or with family not an option?
It's what Odokawa-kun wanted.
I guess so. His parents
might return someday.
What are you talking about?
Are you really his friend?
I heard Odokawa's parents are missing.
Odokawa-kun told you that?
It's what I was told.
Maybe that's what he believes...
They're not missing?
They're dead. Both of them.
Next Time: We Have No Tomorrow
Capoeira.
Uh, okay?
You said before that you didn't know
how people pick up capoeira.
Oh, yeah. Did I?
Do you want me to hit you
with a cabeçada into an aú batido?
Sorry, sorry. I don't know what those
techniques are, but they sound scary.