Now there's a sight
that makes it feel like spring.
"Shinichi Sakurai, 19 - College Sophomore"
Sakurai-senpai!
Huh?
Uzaki... right?
Hana Uzaki! I'll be your junior again here.
"Hana Uzaki, 18 - College Freshman"
Here's to a great year!
Huh? You don't swim here in college?
Nope. They don't even have a swim club.
And you worked so hard at it in high school...
Ah, there's plenty of stuff to do in college.
Senpai...
Y-Yep, there sure is.
Or so I thought.
"Spring"
Oh, Senpai!
What the...
"Summer"
What in the...
"Autumn"
What in the what?
"Winter"
What in the what?!
"Spring"
"Again" "Spring"
I kinda thought this year
would turn out like that...
"Shinichi Sakurai, 20 - College Junior"
Senpai!
Whoops! Overshot you!
Uzaki... right?
All alone again today, huh?
I guess I'll have to hang out with you!
"Hana Uzaki, 19 - College Sophomore"
Your college loner lifestyle ends today!
"Uzaki-chan Wants to Hang Out!"
"Episode 1: Uzaki-chan Wants to Hang Out!"
What's for lunch?
Mmm... the dining hall, I guess.
"Lecture Overview"
"New Location"
"Canceled"
Hey, can we come, too?
Canceled, huh? Now my afternoon is wide open.
Senpai!
No work today, either. What to do...
Eek!
That glare!
S-Scary...
"Super Huge"
Senpai!
Maybe I'll just bum around on my own for once.
Can't get any quiet time once she horns on in.
Senpai, Senpai, Senpai, Senpai!
It's like I always tell you:
quit yelling so lou--
I kept calling you,
but you just weren't hearing me!
So! Where ya headed, Senpai?
What the hell are you doing, Uzaki, you idiot?!
Oh, going out for lunch today?
Aw, too bad. My friends and I already ate.
But if you insist, I could watch you eat.
I've got no classes this afternoon.
I'm just going for a stroll.
Later.
Uzaki... why are you following me?
Yikes, that face!
As it turns out,
I'm suddenly free this afternoon, too.
Given half the chance,
I know you'll do the old loner thing.
And two has gotta be way more fun than one!
Mind your own business.
Besides, I've told you a million times
that I find quiet time alone more relaxing.
Here we go again. Being a loner is no fun!
Stop calling me that.
That's right: you're not
a loner--'cause I'm with you!
Quit tagging along, you damn pest!
Feeling self-conscious?
I am not!
So where are we going?
Not telling.
Karaoke? Bowling?
Aw, tell me!
No.
Ugh! Why are you being so cold today?
It's my mood.
Your mood?!
What's the deal? You hung out with me before!
Huh?
Treating me according to your moods...
Isn't it sooo convenient that you get
with me only when you feel like it?!
Watch your phrasing when there's people around!
Enemy of womankind.
Utter trash.
Scum.
Okay, fine! Come along, then!
Hooray!
Hey, once we're done, let's get some food, huh?
I'll gladly go with you to dinner!
I'm not paying.
Aw, cheapskate.
Are you trying to sponge off me?
Wait, were you going to see
a movie by yourself today?
Huh? That's right.
Solo movies!
What's so funny?
That's a prime loner move, right up there
with solo BBQ and solo sushi-go-round!
Shut up for once, would you?
You're going to make enemies
in all sorts of places.
At least talk a little more quietly!
Listen, this is the "people are people" era.
We all want to find time in our busy days
to see the movies we want the way we want.
Uh-huh, uh-huh.
Shouldn't we all spend
our leisure time however we please?
Don't laugh at other people's hobbies
judged by your standards.
Uh-huh, uh-huh.
Plenty of people watch movies as a hobby.
They don't declare when and with whom.
That's how it is.
I see.
Spoken like a true loner!
Can I wallop her--just once?
Anyone can go to the movies
alone whenever they feel like it.
The scheduling alone is a hassle
with more people in the mix.
I see.
But you can't loudly talk spoilers with
your friends afterward when you go alone!
That's like one of the worst possible
things you can do as a human being!
It's okay. I get it.
You're determined to soldier
on alone despite your loneliness.
Don't give me that affectionate look!
Honestly. I knew I shouldn't have brought you.
I was planning to follow you
all sneaky-like anyway.
What's your deal? Is that your idea of fun?
Huh?
It'd be funny if I spotted you going
into some weird store or something!
I know I'd laugh myself silly
if I saw you buying dirty DVDs!
Ow! Ow! Ow, ow, ow!
"Pulling the nose upward is fairly painful"
Senpai, I--Senpai--Senpai! Uncle! Uncle! Uncle!
College students are adults!
No mocking people's hobbies
or digging into their private lives!
Sorry! I'm sorry!
Sheesh.
I haven't even been able to pick
a movie with you all up in my business.
You came without a movie in mind?
It was a last-minute thing.
Besides, choosing at the theater
is one of the thrills of solo movies.
Oh, is it, now?
Uzaki.
Yes?
If there's something you want to see, I'll pay.
Huh? Really? What about your solo movie?
It's not like I have to go solo.
And with you here,
I can watch something different.
I figure my points will cover the two of us.
Seriously?! Well, if you say
so--I'll let you treat me! Thanks!
Let's see...
This one! What a bargain:
heroes as far as the eye can see!
Ooh, that's a great one. I saw it once,
but I was thinking about seeing it again.
Huh!
Two college students, please.
I'll use my points.
Certainly. One moment.
She has her moments,
but she's still so smackable.
She seems happy.
I guess I can do this much for her.
By the way, Senpai...
You've seen enough solo movies
to pay for someone else's ticket!
That's a turn-off, all right!
You would say that after I've paid, dammit!
You're, like, a pro-level loner!
Huh? Uh, wait--Senpai?
Kidding! Sorry! I'm sorry! Yow! Stop! Stop!
Will that couple ever shut up?!
That was great!
Yeah. A good film's always worth a rewatch.
All those points you banked
by going to the movies alone--gone!
That's your standard for "great"?!
So much for being nice.
Hey, can we stop by the electronics store?
I need new earbuds.
Yeah, sure.
See, it's that kind of thing.
Huh?
What is it about this shop that makes me think,
"Since I'm here, I should buy something"?
Hey, nice.
Senpai!
Yeah?
Over here! This way!
What about your earbuds?
C'mon, the next seat's open!
Will you listen?
Ah, might not be so bad after a movie.
That's right! It's great. It works!
Oh, this is nice. Real nice.
Right?
Though with me, it's always
my shoulders more than my back.
"LO"
Shoulders?
"HI"
Wha--where did that come from?
"She's just sitting in a massage chair"
Oh, sorry... I can't help
but make noise during a massage...
My, uh, my shoulders have always been tight--
Well, um... i-if you keep on doing that...
"She's just sitting in a massage chair"
I would buy this in a second
if I had the money...
It... It just... It feels sooo good...
"Seriously, she's just sitting
in a massage chair"
"Look, she really is just
sitting in a massage chair"
Let's go, shall we?!
That wasn't even five minutes!
Shut up! Save... Save that for home!
Save what?
Jeez, this dummy... making all
those weird noises in a public place...
Hey, Senpai!
What now?
Ten minutes of standing on this,
and it's like getting a full workout!
Well? You try!
Oh, my God! You're such an idiot!
"Innocent"
Whoa! Check it out!
What is it this time?
"VR Experience Booth"
Look: it's VR! VR!
Huh! So this is virtual reality...
Would you like to try?
Yes! I sure would!
My view goes with me when I turn!
VR is amazing! This is really cool, Senpai!
Okay, okay. Just keep your voice down.
My weapon! No! Not this one!
Ammo! I'm outta ammo!
Hey, is there anyone behind you?
Huh? Behind me?!
Here they come! Look at 'em all!
Your reactions are the best.
They should put you in a commer--
They got me! Wow, VR is awesome!
Er, are you all right?
I'm fine.
What is it, Senpai?
Um, would your boyfriend like a turn?
I'm not her boyfriend.
But... okay.
Something not so dangerous.
These ocean graphics are something else!
Hey, you look like a regular person with
those goggles. They hide your bad-guy face!
Shut it, dimwit.
Whoa! That's huge! A giant shark!
Wait, is it coming this way?
Huh? Is it?!
I-It's biting me! It's totally biting me! Yow!
You're way too scared!
You're one to talk!
Let me go! Hey!
I'm gonna get this disgraceful display
on video and tease you about it later!
Uh, miss? Don't get too close to the player...
Just so huge!
Hmm? What's this?
A jellyfish? Octopus? Sunfish?!
It's so big. And soft! And kind of frightening!
I never thought much of VR, but it's amazing!
So powerful--and it even reproduces touch!
Are you all right?
Yeah, it's okay. I'm fine.
You said that VR made you want
to do something physical--
now you're swinging that bat all excited
and racking up a pile of strikes!
Focus!
Will you shut up?
Here comes the next one! You can do it!
Knock it out of the park! Home run!
That's enough out of--
That so didn't fly straight!
Dammit.
You said you did this before.
You totally didn't!
You really tick me off, dammit.
I played for one year in junior high.
Ooh! I wanna try, too!
Here's my card. There's still some on there.
Thanks!
Don't stand too close or the ball will hit you.
Got it!
If I hit a home run, dinner's on you!
Eyes forward! You want to get hurt?
Okay... plant the feet...
Swivel the hips...
Like the real deal.
Huh? Wait--did--
Did you stretch?
Oh.
It... It hurts...
Are you nuts,
whipping out a full swing like that?!
Lay down this instant!
I heard a pop...
Yeah, I'll say!
I copied you... and look where it got me...
A novice can't just start
putting their hips into a swing!
Of course you're gonna hurt yourself, dummy!
This pain is all your fault...
How so?!
Just go home and get some sleep.
And see a doctor tomorrow.
A doctor, you say?
Let's get dinner!
Do you ever give up?!
"Taneda Ramen"
Let's eat!
You can walk fine on your own,
so it's probably nothing serious.
If it still hurts tomorrow, see a doctor.
And you really should head
home now and go to sleep.
I'll be fine.
Yummy yum yum.
You don't get a lot of exercise, do you?
That injury is proof
you haven't been very active.
What did you expect? I'm just starting out!
Beginners need to warm up, at least.
Back injuries are a big deal.
Fine.
You realize that would never have happened
if you hadn't elbowed
your way into tagging alo--
Huh? My chicken...
Hey.
Why are you eating it?
Huh?
Did you eat them all?!
Eh?
W-We're not sharing?
We are not, you idiot! And how is
it sharing when you eat them all?!
Keep it!
Temper, temper! Your poor girlfriend!
She's not my girlfriend...
Another order of chicken, please.
Coming right up!
Your chicken's so good,
my chopsticks just kept going!
Good one, miss!
Talk about a sunny personality.
Here you go--on the house. Eat up!
Wow! Are you sure?
Oh, no, we couldn't!
Go on--it's fine!
Delish!
Honestly.
It's rude not to accept this kindness, Senpai!
Oh, uh... I guess you're right.
Okay, don't mind if I--
Why do you eat everything?!
Sorry! I didn't mean to!
Here's your chicken.
Again?!
Senpai!
Good morning!
Hey.
I had fun yesterday!
What? All you did was hurt your back.
Huh? C'mon, it was fun going for
a whole day without being a loner, right?
I made it clear from the very beginning
that I intended to spend the day alone.
Oh, look at you, pretending you're not happy.
Watch it.
I've never been to a batting cage with
my girlfriends before, either. That was new!
Teach me how to swing, okay?
Next time I wanna really send it flying!
Hey, how 'bout we go again today?
I have work.
Aw. Next time, then!
"Next time," huh?
This idiot really doesn't let a
little pain get in the way of having fun.
I don't know when she got like this...
Like this? Or like this?
Well, I won't be bored.
I can put up with her a little, I guess.
Yeah, next time.
Uh, Senpai?
Hmm?
After that thing we did yesterday?
My back still hurts!
It's all your fault, you know.
Phrasing!
It even hurts to walk!
Carry me! C'mon--it's your fault!
Shut up!
"Episode 2: The Café Owner Wants a Glimpse!"