Are you gonna be home today, Senpai?
Can I come over?
Yeah, I guess.
Great! I'll be right there.
Uzaki's everyday visits have become a habit.
Whatever. I'm done fighting it.
But...
...she always leaves her junk here!
I'm going to have to say something.
There she is, the jerk.
Check out the jumbo beanbag
I bought today, Senpai!
See? It's a big ol' frog!
It's way too big!
But it comes with a little frog!
Okay, that's cute... but still!
"Uzaki-chan Wants to Hang Out!"
"Episode 11: Does Sakurai
Want to Hang Out, Too?"
What's your take on this place?
My take? Oh, like spiritually?
Don't sweat it. The person
behind you is just passing through.
That's not what I meant!
Cut that out--I'm serious!
Your stuff is taking over my apartment!
Start taking some of it home today!
What's with the giant beanbag, anyway?
I mean, I'm always sitting on
the floor for our gaming marathons.
My butt hurts! Are you okay with that?
Isn't it the host's responsibility
to make his living space welcoming?
Or would you rather be responsible
for my butt cramping up?
The nerve...
Therefore, I plead not beanbag-guilty!
Fine. The beanbag can stay.
But!
This is the problem!
Huh! It's really piled up, hasn't it?
Don't pretend it's not on you!
You're going to choose what stays and what goes.
Ugh, what a drag!
And no fun until we're finished.
Aw!
Everything you don't need goes
in this garbage bag today.
Everything you do need goes home with you.
Fine...
"The 1008 Lousy Cats"
"Boring D-movie DVD"
This?
Don't need it.
"Paper bags, large and small"
These?
Nope.
"Empty toy capsules"
And these?
Nuh-uh.
See? You don't need any of this!
Don't bring it to my place--throw it away!
Oh, gosh!
Sometimes you can't make up your mind, y'know?
And something that's really been bugging me...
Oh, this?
This is a real laugh!
You blow through this thing here.
Like so.
Well?
Toss it.
What?! But it's funny!
It'll be a huge hit on Halloween!
Who cares? Besides, you only
left it here because you didn't need it.
True, true.
That was too easy! I knew you didn't need it!
It's like, sometimes I have to show things
to you first before it's all settled.
What the hell?!
There we go. Nice and roomy again.
I'm pooped!
It was only some huge chore because you'd
brought all that crap over.
I know where this is going.
Buying all those extra phone chargers...
You just don't think, do you?
Yep: it's lecture time.
Hey, are you listening?
Uh, yeah. Sorry.
Say, I'm thirsty. I'm gonna grab a drink!
Hey! Don't you run away from me! I'm not done!
See, you're always... huh?
What's with the bag?
Did you put that in there?
Oh, uh...
No, that's something else.
Are you kidding me?
Now you're putting your stuff in my fri--
I-Is this...
Oh, gosh!
I thought I'd cook for us today.
It's been a while.
Uzaki, I... well...
I'm sorry. I shouldn't
have jumped to conclusions.
Senpai?
Yeah?
What would you like for
the main dish? Fish or beef?
Fish.
I'm sorry about earlier.
And... this is really good.
I like this sincerely contrite side of you.
He's so easy.
Sakurai?
Yes?
Want to try your hand at food prep?
Eh?
Why not? It'd be a big help if
you could handle cooking, too.
Uh, but I--
Oh? You're gonna cook, Senpai? Can you cook?
Are you sure about this?
It's not as easy as it looks!
I'll do it.
Oh! Will you, now?
Seriously?
You probably think I can't
cook my way out of a paper bag.
It just so happens I do cook from time to time!
Um... what is this?
Spaghetti Napolitan.
What on earth?
Wow.
I'm sorry. Go on: laugh.
Too much laughing!
I'm just doing what you told me to do!
L-L-Let me go!
Ugh, enough! Quit fighting!
Harder, Senpai...
Yes... you're so good at this, Sakurai...
That's enough! My hands are tired!
Man, kneading udon dough is really hard work!
I was surprised to see you here
for a crash course in cooking.
Sorry about that.
I'd intended to do it at my place.
He doesn't have the right tools for the job.
Besides, Mom, you're my cooking instructor!
Thank you in advance.
Just leave it to me. And try to keep up!
You boys and your muscle. Must be nice!
That's one thing this himbo has going for him.
Hana! Hey!
It's okay. I get that all the time.
All the time?
Well... you know.
I apologize for my daughter's nasty mouth.
What's this?
I've been having a normal conversation
with Sakurai all this time!
But how?
Oh, I see! Sakurai's gaze is focused
on the udon--his eyes aren't frightening!
When I can't see those eyes of his,
he's well-mannered and actually easy to talk to!
I'm sorry about everything, Sakurai.
Huh? It's fine, really.
Let the dough sit for about 20 minutes.
I have laundry to put away, so...
I'll leave the rest to you youngsters.
Want something to drink, Senpai?
I bet you got a little sweaty.
Yeah. Thanks.
Cats.
I was anxious at first, but I managed
to hold a proper conversation with Sakurai.
He really is a serious and kind person,
just like the people at his job said.
And now I know I'm fine
as long as I don't look at his eyes.
Yes, I've made great strides today.
And just think: a boy wanting
to learn how to cook!
Kids these days. He'll make a great husband!
I'm telling you, Senpai, it's fine. Go ahead!
You did say you wanted to get some petting in.
Petting?!
Not with high-alert mode still active.
I'd hate to scare anyone off.
I-I-I-I mean, I am scared, but-but-but I never--
It's fine! I saw that one
sneaking peeks at you. She's interested!
I... I was looking at him,
sure--but not like that!
You just gotta go for it! Bam!
Hana?!
No--I should be more of a gentleman.
Sakurai?!
Uh-oh--I might just be warming up to all this!
I just do not understand kids these days!
And why is Hana trying
to pimp out her own mother?!
No. I can't give up. There's still time!
I'm back...
I have to put these kids on the right
path--show them the error of their ways!
Let's... get the udon boiling... shall we?
That is an adult's duty!
Homemade's the best!
Right?!
It really is your treat today?
Sure is--as thanks for the cooking lessons.
All riiight! I've been thinking
about rock-climbing for a while now.
Glad to hear it.
That recent dip in the ocean reminded me
how fun it is to get my body moving.
I see. Most pick-up
sports tend to be ball games,
but rock-climbing really
has you using your muscles.
Your strength control is all over the place!
Phrasing!
In rock climbing,
you use these holds
to move up this climbing wall.
The general rule is to
start from a hold labeled S
and climb to another
labeled G in the same color.
You'll start out with holds
meant for all four limbs.
Look for the same color labels
as you make your way up.
Looking good!
Okay!
Good job up there. How'd it feel?
That was fun!
I'm dying here!
Complete opposites...
I couldn't even... think...
my muscles... at their limit... so quickly...
Enough...
I don't know about this sport...
No? I'm starting to enjoy myself.
Oh, I bet. Your face is just
glowing with vitality. Ticks me off.
See, I knew you didn't get a lot of exercise.
You're the weirdo for
actually liking this extreme stuff!
How do you have so much energy?
I work out in my spare time.
I bet you're just sore
because you can't one-up me here.
What?! I'm not either
sore--not in the slightest!
Great job training up
those useless muscles of yours!
Ah, I see you're still raring to go!
Let's bump up the difficulty for this next one.
The rules are the same as last time,
but you'll be climbing a taller wall.
This is a rope-climbing wall;
you'll be wearing a roped harness as you climb.
I'll go first.
You catch your breath.
Bleah.
I get it... the height on
this one makes it even tougher.
Uh-oh--I'm starting to enjoy this!
Whoops! Where's my foothold?
And I can't look down, either.
Move your other leg first, Senpai.
Step with your right foot first--then
it'll be smooth sailing.
Where to?
Just above your right knee.
I'm not getting it. Where?
He's holding himself up with his arms!
Is he really a beginner?
He looks like some kind of insect.
That was pretty fun!
Look at you, completely unfazed.
You're a himbo, all right--through and through.
Have you recovered, Uzaki?
He's having so much fun,
my jabs don't reach him!
Shouldn't you be resting?
What?! I can totally do this! Just watch!
What are you so mad about?
You all right, Uzaki?
I... can't do this.
She looks like a chrysalis.
I'll just stay here forever.
Can't go forward, can't go back.
I'll spend my life here.
That's a weird way to pout.
I'll lower the rope.
Go ahead and relax your body.
That was a little too much, huh?
Rest a while. Let me know
when you're ready to go again.
But...
You look like you're done
for today. Want to leave?
Go on and climb, Senpai. I'll watch.
But...
You're having fun, aren't you?
Really making use of your body... it's been a while.
Man, you got me.
Never thought you'd pick a contest
where you had the complete upper hand.
I hereby wave the white flag
at your cheap and heartless trap.
If you feel bad about it,
you can buy tonight's dinner, too.
Why, you little...
You look like you did back
in high school, Sakurai-senpai.
"Nadamesukashi Negotiation"
"Kano and Uzaki-chan"
Oh, you didn't have to stop for us!
Sorry to interrupt!
That's right, Senpai. Please--continue!
C'mon, don't sulk in a corner like that.
We said we're sorry!
You look like a stray cat who's
trying to say "Never trust a human!"
Can't say I'm surprised, though.
This is the same senpai who's into solo movies!
You would be doing solo karaoke!
Sorry, but could you add two more to room 25?
Apologies for the late addition.
We were out drinking and
decided on karaoke for the afterparty.
That's when we spotted you here!
Oh, order us some beers, would you?
I am definitely going further
afield for karaoke from now on.
"Solo Karaoke"
Solo karaoke!
True to its name, it's using an
entire karaoke room for "one, please!"
It's an effective way to practice songs
without worrying about an audience,
and its adherents are growing in number.
"However!"
However!
Karaoke is very much seen as a group activity,
"Karaoke is a group activity"
so if you're spotted going solo,
odds are you'll be teased
at school or work the next day.
"Reception"
Even the reception desk...
Loner loser.
...is no stranger to this sentiment.
But compared to the shame of being
unable to sing well in front of friends,
compared to the embarrassment
of whiffing the rap part,
such treatment is nothing!
In other words, anyone who attempts solo karaoke
requires a psyche that stands apart!
C'mon, Senpai! Don't be mad, Senpai!
You damn drunk...
Look, even if we all go to the
same college and work together,
you two need to respect people's privacy!
Enough with the maracas!
Hey, Hana!
Shouldn't we show Sakurai some
sincerity--you know, by way of apology?
Huh?
Sakurai, we're gonna hit the restroom.
Sure.
We're back!
Ta-da!
Wh-What the hell?!
They were loaning out cosplay outfits
at the front desk, so we tried some on!
I'm kinda embarrassed!
But why?
C'mon, it's fine!
Here, have a drink.
Wh-Why am I in the middle?
Call it a little bonus.
We feel real bad for barging in on your karaoke!
These guns are incredible.
Aren't you crowding him
a little over there, Ami?
Well, Sakurai? Has your mood improved?
Um, actually... I'm just... flustered.
Is it not to your liking?
"Sakurai is confused!"
It's not about liking or disliking
or this liking or that liking...
I'm begging you--spare me!
You're a tough customer. Very well!
How's this?
Well, uh... that's an interesting question...
Um, Ami, I don't know about this costume...
You're fine, just fine!
It has more fabric than a swimsuit!
Well, Sakurai? Has your mood improved?
I was just thinking that this is
no place for anyone in his right mind.
So chill!
I guess I am the only sober one here.
Okay, yep, I'm not mad anymore.
Let's sing some karaoke and have fun.
Yahoo!
Yippee!
I like that about you, Sakurai!
Sure, yeah, thanks.
Anything I say now will
only escalate the situation.
I'll just nod and smile my way through this.
Can I put in the next song?
Uh-huh, yep, go ahead.
Can I order more drinks?
Okay, sure, but don't drink too much.
Hey, Sakurai, what was your favorite cosplay?
Yep, uh-huh, I like the bunny girl.
Oh, wow, I never thought
you'd give a straight answer.
No! I, uh--you see--that--that was--
Pervert.
C'mon, shake it off! Not many guys
who don't appreciate a bunny girl!
I think I'll have that drink now.
That you, Uzaki?
Hey, about yesterday...
when I said "bunny girl," I--
What happened?! Here, come inside.
I'll grab a towel.
Senpai.
I can't hang out with you anymore.
Huh?
"Episode 12: Uzaki-chan Wants to Hang Out More!"
Senpai!