I can't hang out with you anymore.
Huh?
I... I did something
that can't be undone. Again.
Now just calm down and tell me why. Okay?
But... I don't want to be a bother...
Idiot. Who cares about that now?
If there's anything I can do, I'll do it!
Senpai...
Did you just say you'd do anything?
Well, that's not--
What's with that face?
I discovered I hadn't even touched that report
I had for homework over summer break!
What?
Same screw-up as last year!
Why do college students still
get summer homework, anyway?
Now my mom's mad,
my little brother's teasing me--it's awful!
Hey! Why'd you close the door?!
If you want me to hang out with you
this summer, help me with my report!
Shut up! Do it yourself!
Oh, c'mon! Please? Senpai!
Senpai! Open up! Senpai!
She really is hopeless.
"Uzaki-chan Wants to Hang Out!"
"Episode 12: Uzaki-chan Wants to Hang Out More!"
That's Hana, all right.
It's not funny.
She's getting more comfortable by the day.
I'm telling you; she must have been
hiding her claws way back when.
Meow.
I see...
Oh, boss, let me handle the heavy stuff.
Please. This is nothing.
Boss!
Threw out your back, huh?
That hasn't happened in a while.
W-We'll close for today.
I'll get to the chiropractor.
I guess we have no choice.
Who has a driver's license?
I do.
I'm making an appointment at the clinic.
Could you take Dad there in our car?
Hana, you and I will close up.
Got it.
Or...
I could be manager for a day.
And I'll come back to find
my café's been hijacked. Close it.
"Closed"
Thanks for cleaning up.
Here. It's on the house.
Yay! Thank you!
How's it compare to Dad's?
It's good!
I like the depth of flavor in his coffee,
but I like the fresh taste of yours, too.
Will you inherit the café one day?
Inherit it? Yeah, I'd like that.
Or... take it, maybe?
Why reword it to sound so threatening?
It won't be happening anytime soon, though.
There's so much I still need
to be able to run a business.
A driver's license, for one thing.
"Chiropractic Clinic"
Thank goodness Sakurai was around today.
He's always been like that:
surly but accommodating.
Don't be afraid to use him.
He's not a tool, Hana--
Huh?
What's wrong?
Nothing.
What were you two like in high school, anyway?
Eh?
You were in the swim club together, right?
Did you flirt--er,
hang out then like you do now?
Oh, we actually started hanging out
a little after we started college.
Huh! That's a tad surprising.
We only saw each other
for club business in high school.
Even the first time we met--
Let's see... it was...
The swim club?
I'm not much of a swimmer...
No, no--you'd be a manager!
You're not in any club, are you?
We can both join!
I know some cute third-years
there from middle school. C'mon!
I don't know...
Please! I'm too chicken to go alone!
What the heck?
We have two first-year
managers joining us today.
Look after them, all right?
Calm down! Ugh, pathetic!
As you can see, we're a pretty big bunch.
It won't be easy, but do your best.
Okay!
Uh-huh.
This third-year manager will show you the ropes.
Thanks!
Sure thing.
Welcome!
Thanks for having us.
Let me explain what you'll be doing.
Mornin'!
Ah, Sakurai.
Sorry I'm late. I was cleanin' up.
We've got two new first-year managers today.
Yeah? That's somethin'.
N-Nice to meet y--
Hey. I'm Sakurai. Second-year.
I'm gonna go warm up.
Good luck!
S-So scary! Those eyes--too fierce!
We have upperclassmen like that?!
It's my first day, and I'm ready to quit!
He's so frightening! Just... yikes!
Hana?
So, yeah, that first impression was the pits.
Huh! His eyes never
really bothered me all that much.
But as you know, he's a serious,
earnest person at heart.
Attaboy, Sakurai! That's a new record!
Thanks!
These're heavy. I got this.
Thank you, Sakurai.
Go for a new record! You can do it, Senpai!
Aren't you hungry?
He's just so awkward
and prone to misunderstandings...
I realized right away
that he wasn't scary at all.
And so you got friendlier
and friendlier with Sakurai.
You even started to talk like him.
Huh?
Eh? I mean, you haven't
been talking slangy with me.
Huh?
Wait, what? Do you only talk
like that when Sakurai's around?
I-I'll be on my way!
That's enough remin... reminiscin'!
Oh! I'm sorry! I must have touched a nerve!
Hadn't you noticed?
Goodbye! I'll be...
...seein' ya!
Did I just dig up a landmine?
Or the greatest treasure around?
Either way, I've got to get her to talk!
I've been thinking:
What's Senpai like when he's drunk?
I realized I've never
actually seen him like that.
Does he cry? Laugh?
Get combative? I can't picture it.
Hmm... Usually you reveal
whatever you've been holding back.
Personally, I'd like him
to be a strip-naked drunk!
That's personal, all right.
Sakurai can hold his liquor,
so he might not get drunk at all.
Sak's no lightweight, but he does get drunk.
He just knows his limits and sticks to them.
Aha! So one of Senpai's rare
friends has seen him drunk!
"Rare friends"? Jeez...
So what was he like?
How much does he have to put away?
Hey, are you trying to go
after Sak while he's asleep?
No. I hate that he's seen
my booze-related screw-ups.
I'm trying to drag him down with me.
I mean, I think you had it coming...
C'mon, please! This is the perfect time
for scheming, with Senpai off work!
I guess you can't cause too much trouble.
But she could cause some fun.
Hooray! Thanks a ton!
We'll need to set up a drinking party.
What's a good time?
Given how it went with you last time,
Ami, I think I'll go it alone.
Oh, no! Hana's mad at me!
Whatever did you do to make
Hana shut you out, daughter of mine?
Hey, you're here! Come on in.
H-Hey there...
Why'd you want to come over
to drink all of a sudden?
Don't tell me...
I-I finished my report, okay?
Oh, you did? Well, that's good.
Let's go all-out today!
I'll handle the cooking, see?
The going-home's the hard part with Sak,
so he rarely drinks when he's out.
Which means he'll lower
his guard if he's at home.
Phase 1: check!
Wow... You really are a great cook, Uzaki.
Go on, eat up!
Don't mind if I do.
Who knew you could make chili shrimp at home?
Yum! You're a real pro!
Now that is an exaggeration.
Put out spicy snacks with
a lot of flavor to keep him drinking.
And then...
"They Attack in Packs!"
"Massive!"
"The Original Shark Movie!"
I rented some DVDs, Senpai. Wanna watch?
We've got five different killer-shark flicks!
Ooh!
Distract him from his drinking
so he won't think about how much he's having.
Phases 2 and 3: check!
And since Sak tends to match
or beat whoever he's with,
if you're drinking,
he'll naturally keep drinking, too.
Pretend you're drinking... just pretend...
Here, Senpai. Have some more!
Thanks!
Now for the main event, Senpai!
"Don't drink too much or
make anyone else drink too much"
When Sak's drunk, he's useless.
Useless?
He can hold a conversation of sorts,
but his judgment is way off.
And he starts looking
really sloppy, too. Sloppy Sak.
Oho!
That's pretty useless, all right!
You seem happy.
In that state, Sak can't lie--and
forget trying to be cool.
His mental defenses are zero!
He's big on minding his limits because
he doesn't want to show that side to anyone.
You sure do look like
you're feeling no pain, Senpai.
Cut that out...
I'd never even dreamed
of this level of vulnerability!
Uzaki...
What's up?
Y'know... thanks... for all your cooking.
Oh, is that where you're going?
Though I'd be happier if you could give me
your honest opinions without the alcohol.
Can't do that... too shy.
So you've been holding back?
Well, here's your chance to come out
with allll the stuff you couldn't say before!
Love...
...your cooking...
I stopped by to see how it was going.
Good thing I told Uzaki
to leave the door unlocked.
Hey, Sak, you okay?
Itsuhito? What are you...
Don't worry about that.
Look, I laid out your futon. Get in there.
'Kay...
You should be under covers, too, Uzaki.
Sleep easy. I'll lock up.
Yeah... thanks...
Sweet dreams.
Something...
...is weird about this...
But what?
Why is she in my futon?
Why is he in my futon?
Hmm. I see.
So neither of you remember
anything about last night.
Right...
You didn't have to come in
on your day off, you know.
I had my suspicions and gave them today off.
W-Well, why don't you try remembering
things in order, one by one?
One by one?
I definitely remember making dinner...
And eating and drinking while we watched movies.
A crazed shark slammed
into the hero of the third movie,
who then got reincarnated into some other world.
I was like, "He's crazy strong!"
I think that's all I can remember...
What kind of movie is that?
After that... I enjoyed Senpai's
pitiful tipsiness for a while.
Hey!
I get the sense it was extremely amusing.
And when I woke up,
we were in the same futon somehow.
"Closed"
Apologies. Could you say that again?
We're listening closely this time.
Talk about an obvious bribe!
You heard me the first time!
When I woke up, Uzaki was beside me.
Did they do it?!
Shinichi!
We didn't do anything!
I really can't remember at all!
If you don't remember,
you can't be sure you didn't do anything.
Right?
These two really are a pain at times like this.
W-Well, I was there, and I'm saying
nothing happened! Isn't that enough?
Two young people and nothing happened?!
That's the problem here!
You're mad at me?!
Tell them, Uzaki!
You were up longer than me, right?
I'm trying to remember...
It's all so fuzzy. I can't say for sure that I--
Love...
Why are you grinning?!
Was I?
You don't actually remember
anything from last night, do you?
Something definitely happened.
Something good. And yet...
All we can do is imagine whatever
marvelous event it could have been!
I should have joined them--even
if I had to force my way in!
Why is my daughter like this?
Please let me tag along next time!
Uh, yeah, sure.
At your place again!
What for?
Buy a guest futon, would you?
How about you go home?
Hey, how about we do it again today?
Two nights in a row!
Huh?
What are you talking about?
Classes start again tomorrow.
Huh?
"Huh" nothing.
Aha. I see. Huh.
So that means...
Summer break... is over?
That's right.
She's acting like it's the end of the world.
Did you seriously just realize this?
Then I guess... I'll just be
sleeping until winter break...
Is hanging out the only
thing you ever think about?
Hana! Time to wake up!
Okay...
Morning...
Mom, Hana's looking even more dopey than usual.
Shut it, Kiri.
Here.
Strong coffee for
your first day back at college.
Perk up a little, would you?
Yeah...
Some college student.
What an aggravating big sis.
See you later.
"Super Huge"
Huh?
Good morning, Senpai!
Oh, Uzaki. Morning.
You actually came to campus.
I was sure you'd whine and moan about it again.
Who do you think I am?
Although I'm still feeling about
90 percent of that end-of-summer shock.
You're not over it at all!
We didn't hang out nearly enough!
If it were always summer,
I could hang out with you so much more.
Don't be stupid.
Harsh!
Senpai! You need to
consider a woman's feelings--
It doesn't have to be summer.
We can hang out whenever.
We'll always be together.
Huh? What is it, Uzaki?
Wait! No--no, wait!
What I meant was that we still have
plenty of time before we graduate!
Not... whatever you were thinking!
Oh? And whatever was I thinking, hmm?
Damn you...
If you want to hang out with me so badly,
I guess I'll have to oblige!
You can thank me now, Senpai!
Argh! You know what you are?
Annoying as hell!
"Uzaki-chan Wants to Hang Out!"
C'mon, Senpai--let's go hang out!