So you see,
if we can show them that
we have love in our hearts,
neither animals nor demon beasts
will try to harm us.
Oww...
Damn those demon beasts.
They really got you, huh?
You okay?
Yeah. I'll make them pay for this.
Demon beasts must be slain!
Don't you agree, Shigure?
Yes... You've told me about this
many times, actually.
It's important!
Damn. The eastern guilds
took heavy damage, too.
It's kill or be killed with
these demon beasts, huh?
They can understand how we feel, you see.
They got us again!
Honey!
Daddy!
Father!
We'll get them for this!
Love! It's all about love!
We'll fill this world
with love for animals!
Kill all the demon beasts!
And I've got just the way!
What is it?
I'm going to open a pet shop.
That sounds great!
But what's a pet shop?
I have to start there?
"Quest x Demon Beast Killer"
Keeping demon beasts in your homes?
Is that possible?
Shigure, were you listening to me?
I'm going to raise demon beasts
so they can live with humans
and become a bridge
between them and humanity.
And that's the job of a pet shop.
But it's not a charity.
We'll be raising the demon beasts
and then taking money
from the people we give them to.
So we'll be taking quests from the guild,
capturing demon beasts
and taking the reward for that,
and then training the demon beasts,
then selling them to customers
for lots of money!
So you get twice the money, huh?
Exciting, isn't it?
Being surrounded by demon beasts!
Getting all that money!
All right, I'm in! Let me help
with your "pet shop" thing!
But first, I need a place to live
and a place to keep the demon beasts.
And that means I need money.
Um, well...
I need to pay back Edgar...
I'd like to form a party with you...
Of course!
Of course you can, Shigure!
Um...
What part of me were you looking at
when you made that decision?
So we can choose from this list?
Yes.
What's that?
That contains information
on the demon beasts,
to help you defeat them.
But you won't need it, demon beast killer!
What did you just call me?
Everybody's talking about you.
You took down five cerberuses
in a single instant.
Now everybody's calling you...
the demon beast killer!
Who are you calling a demon beast killer?
What the hell kind of name is that
to give an animal wrestler?
But this looks useful!
Now, I'd like a match
with a high payout, but...
I can't read this.
But it's our first quest,
so shouldn't we avoid anything hard
and try something simpler?
But I want money fast.
Which one pays the most?
This one, I guess.
"Defeat the Salamander," it says.
Sure, we'll go with that.
Were you listening to me?
It's our first time, so we should
pick something easy.
Listen to me, Shigure.
Whenever I'm prepping for a match,
I always emphasize
the mental aspect of battle.
If you're always running,
running becomes a habit.
I've seen wrestlers where that's happened.
I don't follow...
So, which one of these is a salamander?
This one. A giant, fire-breathing lizard.
This is...
Genzo, your face! Your face!
Sorry, I couldn't help it...
I'm going to need to learn to read, though.
A salamander, huh?
That's gonna be a tough one.
Hey, that's Heat Haze.
The strongest man in the guild,
and the demon beast ki...
Stop it! Don't say that name!
You seem like a newbie hunter.
No, I'm a pro wrestler.
Want to join up with our party?
We can split the reward if we succeed.
Really? That's great!
Well, it's to celebrate your first victory.
Don't worry. I'll kill the salamander
with a single stab of my sword!
You're going to kill an animal, huh?
Leader!
Are you okay?
Hey, wake up...
Never say something so stupid again.
Did Heat Haze just say something stupid?
I don't know...
Shigure, let's go.
Okay!
Look! Somebody forget their sword!
Well, it's mine now!
That was Heat Haze's, right?
Yeah, that was definitely Heat Haze's.
Look, Shigure!
It's alive! It's moving!
Hot! Hot!
Whew! These flames are your love, huh?
It's okay. You're so cute, huh?
Yoshiko!
He gave it a name?
Yoshiko is mine now.
Yoshiko?
The salamander.
A salamander for your first quest, huh?
I'd heard the rumors, but I can see why
they call you the demon beast killer.
I keep telling people not to call me that!
We got quite a lot of money, huh?
Now let's go.
Go where?
Bro, I'm bored.
Want to go wander around the town
and do something bad?
Good idea.
No... not today.
Don't tell me he still
can't forget that pervert...
Hello!
Wh-What do you want?
Um... is Edgar in?
Not right now.
I wanted to make this month's payment...
Put it there.
I'll make sure Edgar gets it.
This looks delicious!
Mistress, it's time for dinner.
The same as always: orc meat,
goblin meat, troll meat...
I'm sick of all this nasty meat!
I want to go out into the wider world
and eat all kinds of yummy foods!
Foods! Foods! Foods!
Our next targets are soldier monkeys.
It said there were a lot of them.
Genzo, do you have a plan?
Let me think...
I bet they've got nice butts!
I didn't ask if you
thought they were cute...
I wonder how many there are...
I can't wait to meet them!
Forget it.
I think it's about time...
Look.
There's so many!
Okay! This is great!
It is not great!
The soldier monkeys look really mad!
Don't worry!
Just wait...
Come on, guys!
Don't come on!
It's an apple.
An apple.
Glance.
Now they're all best friends...
Wow.
It's love. Love, Shigure.
It's a talent, kind of.
So, we've got quite a lot of them now.
Is this okay?
My dream is coming true!
I'm so happy...
Genzo.
How are you guys so cute?
Genzo!
Genzo, are you awake?
Oh, Shigure.
I had the nicest dream.
In the dream I was surrounded
by demon beasts...
It was so great.
That's not much different
than reality, I don't think.
And look at them all...
If somebody finds all these demon beasts
you'll be in trouble.
You're right!
What if somebody stole them?!
No, I don't think you need
to worry about that.
Either way, we need to do
something about them.
We need to find a place for them to live.
And for us to live, too!
Oh, yeah.
But we'll need a decent amount
of money to get a house.
So we need a big quest, huh?
Which of these pays the most?
This one.
Fighting orcs.
They want you to deal with the orcs
that are stealing their crops.
Orcs?
Look.
What?
Huh? You're much less excited than usual.
This guy's not an animal, though.
Is that a problem?
But they can understand speech, you know?
Then they're basically human.
An orc's an orc!
There's some with nice
hair and big fangs, too.
Huh? You're much more excited
than usual, Shigure.
It pays a ton!
If we can pull this off
we can get a house for you
to live with your demon beasts!
What? Then that changes things.
Let's do it.
Now it's orcs, I guess.
You can't handle orcs solo.
No, maybe he can.
What? The mistress is gone?
Yes...
I'll bring her back.
And if anybody tries to stop me,
I'll kill them...
Want to take a break at the lake up ahead?
Yeah...
I don't want to walk all night
and get there exhausted for the fight.
You're really spoiling
for a fight today, huh?
To me, orcs and demon beasts
are in the same category, though.
They're totally different!
But I guess it's easier
since we can talk to the orcs.
You don't get it, Shigure.
Sometimes words can get in the way.
Really, sometimes I don't know
what Genzo's talking about at all.
But the fact that he doesn't discriminate
against beast people makes him great...
Genzo, you per...
Look at you... Look at you...
Mami!
You're so pretty!
Aww, you're the best!
Somehow this makes me just as mad...
I smell something.
That.
You stay out of this.
First, I'll talk to them.
No, just because you can talk to them
doesn't mean they'll understand...
Okay!
Come on out, damn it!
Who are you?
You wanna fight?
Wasn't he going to talk to them?
Whoever's the strongest
of you, come on out!
What?
Did somebody call me...
It's not you, is it?
I'm the one in charge here.
What do you want, human?
I heard you're stealing crops
from the villagers.
What of it?
I don't think that's got anything
to do with you.
I'd thought I could try
resolving this peacefully.
The gong's been rung!
I don't understand what that means...
But... that was a good kick.
An animal drop kick.
Remember that name.
I don't know what that is,
but it seems you've really made me mad.
Bring it!
Okay, got him!
Fool!
He took a punch from the king!
Okay!
That was a good punch from you, too.
You could star in a main event!
Who are you?
I am a pro wrestler!
Genzo...
Yes!
Get 'em!
Heck yeah!
The king has made the pose of submission!
A new king is born!
A new king?
I don't understand... but Genzo won, right?
You're amazing.
I'm impressed.
It was a good match.
Okay, I'm leaving the king in charge here.
Everybody, do what he says.
Yeah!
Weren't you going to talk things out?
I did! We talked with our fists!
Is that what you meant?
Is Mami okay, you think?
Who's Mami?
The unicorn we met in the lake!
I'm so worried she's run off!
Shigure, let's hurry!
Wait up a second.
What? You brought the orcs to heel?
Do you know how many strong
hunters have fallen to them?
So, how'd you do it?
They talked with their fists!
Amazing, demon beast killer!
I told you not to call me that!
I see.
So, did you buy a store?
Yes, of course.
With the money from the guild's quest,
we were able to get it.
It's even got a barn!
Now you want a loan for funds to pay
the government to open a business.
Indeed.
If you want a loan for the full
amount that you need,
you'll need to have at least 20% of
the amount in hand before we can accept.
Twenty percent?
So much?
We don't have anywhere near that much!
Also, I had a question.
What is a pet shop, even?
You don't know either?
Next time: "Runaway Girl x Attack."