"Animal Mask x MAO"
It's time for the main event!
Will this bring an end
to their long rivalry?
What kind of match do they have
in store for us tonight?
"Animal Mask vs MAO"
It's finally time...
Knock it off!
If I can pin my hated foe, Animal Mask,
to the mat in this match...
MAO, it's time.
Right!
So it's finally time...
Making his entrance into the arena,
it's the knight who always
counts his wins and losses,
weighing in at 178 pounds,
the Macadamian Ogre!
AKA MAO!
Hell yeah!
The man who loves
animals a little too much!
Weighing in at 198 pounds,
it's Animal Mask!
It's finally time...
Will MAO get his revenge?
Animal Mask, today I'm
sending you to your grave!
Today's the day! Today's the day!
Today's the day... I defeat you!
And now he's jumped!
They've started to glow!
What is this?
They disappeared!
Animal Mask has disappeared!
What?
Animal Mask!
Where the hell did you go?
"Animal Mask Disappears During Fight"
"Animal Mask Disappears:
Part of the Show?"
He ran from the fight!
If a guy runs from a title match,
I'm gonna call him a chicken nugget!
MAO, you can just call him a chicken.
You don't need the nugget part.
Nobody cares!
Hey, Animal Mask!
What kind of wrestler runs
'cause he's scared of losing a fight?
Get back here and finish this!
Where'd he go, though, really?
Animal Mask...
Genzo...
Well, who cares!
My job is women's pro wrestling now!
"MAO Enraged"
"'Where Did You Go, Animal Mask?'"
Genzo!
Eat up, and grow up big and strong!
He won't even pick up the phone!
This is getting bad!
Find him a new opponent!
He says he doesn't want to fight
anybody but Animal Mask.
It's true. Animal Mask is
the only guy he's never beaten.
"Interdimensional Title Match"
It's true. Animal Mask is
the only guy he's never beaten.
"Animal Mask Entrance Theme"
What do we do, though, really?
"Grand Opening"
We just did a remodeling!
Animal Mask...
Where did you go?!
Genzo!
There you are.
I've been looking for you.
Can you go without me today?
Again?
What are you saying?
I want to stay here, where Masao needs me!
He's asleep.
For now, yes.
But think about it.
He hasn't been here long at all.
If I'm not here when he wakes up...
What if that happens, Shigure?
I'm not sure how you
want me to answer that.
I want to be by his side
every waking moment,
at least until he gets
used to his new home.
But cu sith don't even get along
with humans, they say.
I don't think he'd make a good pet, do you?
So this will be a long-term project, then.
Hey. Were you listening to me?
Now, no more excuses.
It's not an excuse!
Right, right. Let's go!
Wait! Wait, Shigure!
Stop it! Wait, Shigure!
Demon! Monster!
Stop it!
Hiroyuki, hold down the fort!
We're heading out!
Masao!
The others are waiting for us.
Let me go, Shigure!
They finally left, huh?
I thought we wouldn't get a shot today.
Are we really doing this?
I've never seen that beast before.
I can't imagine how much
some rich weirdo will pay for it!
We've got no choice but to take it!
But what if he comes back?
I think we'd be better off just
staying away from that pervert.
You fool! I need to get my revenge!
For what he did to me...
What he did to you?
Mischa, you just remembered it, didn't you?
Stop! Stop! Don't remember!
Don't laugh!
I'm sorry!
Let's do this!
Right!
Is this really going to work?
Don't worry about if
it'll work. Make it work!
Right, right.
So what's the plan?
Listen. I've got the perfect plan.
First, we use this expensive ham
to lure him over.
Think that'll work?
And then we lure him outside...
We lure him over, and once he's close,
you grab him with the bag,
and we split!
Perfect, right?
I don't know...
Let's go!
Okay!
I hope this works...
I don't see the dradradogola anywhere.
Yeah.
Is it really out here?
Yes, according to the clerk at the guild...
You sure it's not bad info?
There's no food here either.
What should we do?
Leave it to me, Mistress!
Wait...
I have a bad feeling.
Let's head back.
There you go again...
No, it's true.
It's some kind of message
from the spirit world,
telling me that something horrible
might've happened to my beloveds!
I can smell your lies.
You're saying it's a bad feeling,
but you're actually just not interested in
the dradradogola 'cause it's a plant.
No!
This is how it was with Keiko, remember?
It was a lie when you said that
about Toshihiko, right?
I'm back.
Gang! Mischa?!
What happened to you?
Edgar, well...
Bro came up with the idea
of stealing that little beast
from the pervert to teach him a lesson...
And you two morons
did it without telling me?
I told him you wouldn't like it, but he...
I'll finally get the chance
to see him in tears.
I hope so.
Okay, let's go.
Right...
Okay, come on!
Mischa!
Ready whenever!
He's kind of cute, huh?
What are you doing, bro?
We need to get him in the bag!
Yummy, isn't it?
Bro, wake up! Don't give into temptation!
Bro!
Bro, we need to hurry!
He's just so cute, though!
My bro...
I survived 'cause I'm
a fast runner, but my bro...
An ant... a huge ant... save me...
Sheesh. Looks like he's got
more trauma to deal with...
That scream was a dradradogola!
What? A voice?
From which way?
That way!
So there are demon beasts here!
What dummy said there weren't?
Genzo, what's wrong?
Did the dradradogola get him?
You finally died, huh, Genzo?
I'm so disappointed!
What? Nobody said that thing
was carnivorous!
Genzo!
Don't worry.
I'll make your corpse serve me forever!
Genzo?
He's alive, huh?
Hey, these are plants after all.
You don't have to get so disappointed.
It's our job.
Their terrible screams made you
pee your pants though, I bet.
It's our job, okay?
You guys take over. I'm going home.
I know they're not animals,
but could you at least try?
Cowardly human!
Shut up, vampire.
I'm not the noble creature
they call a vampire!
Look at this one!
Isn't it kind of cute?
Cute? Shigure, I think
your eyes are broken.
Are you okay?
Not now!
See, Genzo?
Not cute at all.
Is so!
I said it's not cute and it isn't.
It's creepy.
I'm leaving.
Wait! We're not done here...
Shigure, I thought you understood.
Understood what?
Money doesn't move me.
I act out of one thing only:
my overwhelming love for animals!
Yeah right, Genzo. I bet you like
money as much as you like animals.
No! That is not true at all!
Enough talking!
Let's just do our jobs!
The dradradogola's voices...
They all...
stopped.
Hanako, did you...?
We're back.
What? Hiroyuki was almost kidnapped,
but you fought the kidnappers off?
So, what did they look like?
Listen, I'll take my time in coming up
with a way to get back at that pervert.
Until we're ready, stay put!
Okay...
I'll never go after him again...
Hey!
It was you?!
You scared my partner, did you?
I was willing to let you go
because you were fluffy, but...
It looks like you need
to learn your lesson!
And learn it hard!
Listen up!
Never touch my Hiroyuki again!
Yes!
It's been a while since I've
done anything like wrestling.
Since my last bout, huh?
Shut up!
Leave me alone, damn it!
MAO!
You've got Animal Mask withdrawal.
Withdrawal?
You're too obsessed with Animal Mask.
That's impossible.
He ran from me 'cause he was
scared of losing!
That's called being obsessed.
You need to take up a new hobby.
Something that'll take
your mind off things.
Damn it all!
Princess Altena of Edgardo is believed
to have summoned a hero.
This is a serious threat.
Thus, I, next leader of the vampires
and one of the four Dukes of Darkness,
asked the Demon King for
permission to defeat the hero.
What we are summoning here is
the Demon King of another world.
And with the help of that Demon King,
I will defeat the hero!
Darkness of the dark, give us power!
Animal Mask...
He's here!
I am one of the four Dukes of Darkness,
servants of the Demon King.
Daughter of Valei
Joannascore Adorian Uljika.
Joanna Joannascore Adorian Uljika!
Demon King of another world, brought
here by the dark gods of darkness...
Help us defeat the hero!
What is your name?
MAO.
So you're the Demon King
of another world, huh?
Next Time: "Loser x Master."