He's here!
What is this place?
I was just in my room, doing some knitting!
Welcome.
I am one of the four Dukes of Darkness,
servants of the Demon King.
Daughter of Wallen
Joannascore Adorian Uljika.
Joanna Joannascore Adorian Uljika!
Demon King of another world, brought
here by the dark gods of darkness...
Help us defeat the hero!
What is your name?
MAO.
He's the Demon King!
We've succeeded in summoning
the Demon King!
So you're the Demon King
of another world, huh?
This is the hero summoned
by Princess Altena of Edgardo.
What?
He fled from the castle after being
summoned, and this poster was...
It's him!
So this is where he's been hiding?
Your job is to defeat him.
You don't need to tell me!
Animal Mask!
The Demon King from
another world knows this hero?
"Knows him"?
It's a lot more than that!
It'll take more than a couple words
to describe our relationship!
Wonderful to hear.
Right, Rose?
Indeed.
"Loser x Master"
What a coincidence.
Or perhaps we should
say it's "fate," Joanna?
So the Demon King from
another world hates the hero?
Yes. My own hatred and his,
if the two of them come together,
the power of the dark side will swell.
Indeed.
This time, I'll crush her.
My hated foe,
Fafnir Gildomela Grind Lindabulea.
Well done, Joanna.
You're looking good.
You may be able to win
the next tournament at this rate!
The winner is Fafnir
Gildomela Grind Lindabulea.
Thank you.
Wait!
Yes?
I request a rematch!
A rematch? Now?
Yes!
Impossible.
Why?
I'm kind of hungry...
This is delicious!
Somebody else's home cooking always
tastes so good compared to your own!
Thank you for the meal!
I lost to somebody like this?
Shall we begin, then?
One more time!
Just one more time!
The sky's so blue...
Why?
She was the first person
to ever defeat me in combat.
After that, I became obsessed with her.
I watched her to find out
the secret of her strength,
but I never could figure out
where her power came from,
or actually, how I lost to a girl
who can't do anything but eat!
Like that time, for instance...
Joanna?
Hurry up, Mistress.
Carmilla.
So that's the lesser vampire
that serves the dragons?
All four dukes' families
are coming to this party!
Let's be nice and energetic, Mistress.
I heard the nation's finest chefs
will be doing the cooking...
Really?
Let's hurry, then.
Okay!
Hey!
It's been a long time, Lindabulea.
Umm...
Have you forgotten?
She's Joanna Joannascore Adorian Uljika!
Aaah!
"Aaah"? "Aaah"?
Hi there.
Bye there!
Wait!
What do you want?
I'm in a hurry.
The nation's finest chefs
are doing the cooking.
If I don't hurry the food will run out!
You're as hungry as ever, huh?
Thanks for the kind words!
They weren't kind!
Your servant there is
a lesser vampire, right?
Lindabulea, as you know,
there are three classes of vampires.
First, the great ancestors.
Then, the elders.
Then beneath them both, the lessers.
Of course, my servant, Rose,
is an elder vampire.
And?
At her rank, she shouldn't be able to serve
the family of one of the four dukes' daughters.
Lindabulea, I knew you were strange,
but I think you should put more
thought into choosing your servants.
She didn't choose me!
I begged to serve her!
Shut up.
You're not worthy to speak
to Joanna, lesser vampire.
Lindabulea, if you like,
I can use my authority
to get you a servant of the proper status.
I heard rumors about Carmilla.
She's a total loser.
I'm sure even a girl like
Lindabulea must be sick of her.
Well, Lindabulea?
You're thinking about it?
You're thinking about it, Mistress?
Please don't think about it!
I'll send her an elder vampire that's
under my control and
find out her weaknesses!
Well?
Thanks for the offer, but no.
Very well. I'll have preparations
made immediately...
Did you just refuse?
Yes! Now, bye!
Wait!
You don't understand!
She's almost completely useless!
I know!
It's an embarrassment to our clan to
allow a woman like that to serve a lady.
So, how about we put my Rose
and your Carmilla to the test?
If Carmilla can win, I'll accept her.
Carmilla!
Very well!
Mistress!
We'll work out the details later!
Why did you accept?
'Cause if I don't hurry
the food will run out!
That's not a good reason!
She's an elder vampire!
I'm going to lose!
Carmilla.
If you want to be my
servant, then work hard.
Mistress...
Now let's hurry!
I'm starving!
Okay!
All according to plan.
This time, I'll win.
I've been waiting!
Sorry to keep you waiting!
Let's go over this one
more time before the fight.
If Rose wins, you'll fire Carmilla
and replace her with an elder
vampire that I recommend.
Okay!
Let us begin.
Here I go!
The battle is over.
It's not over yet...
It's clear who's stronger.
A lesser vampire can't
beat an elder vampire.
Now tell her to surrender.
It's the least you can do for
someone who's been your servant.
Even if I die, I will never admit defeat...
Elder or ancestor, I'll fight
for the Mistress's sake.
You don't know when to give up.
I can't give up...
Admit that you'll never be
as strong as me...
I can't lose!
Hey, stop it!
Don't grab my skirt! You'll pull it off!
Stop it!
I can't lose! I can't lose!
Let me go!
Let me go! Let me go! Come on, let go!
I request that the battle be stopped.
Carmilla can't win.
There's no meaning in continuing to fight.
Enough. Stop.
The winner is Rose.
It wasn't even a fight.
I lose...
But I don't want to leave her!
What are you talking about?
You lost, lesser vampire!
Please, Mistress!
Please!
Give it up.
I'll send you your new servant tomorrow.
A talented elder vampire.
Take her.
Wait.
Carmilla is a loser, yes.
But I can't just abandon her.
I'd like to continue using her...
What's this nonsense?
I certainly didn't expect that.
If you're going to go back on your promise,
you'll have to give me
something in exchange.
In exchange?
Mistress, what are you doing?
She'd go that far for her?
For the first time, I think I've won!
Rose, let's go.
Joanna, what do we do with her?
Leave her.
As you wish.
I can't believe she got on her knees!
That's right.
She's not my foe anymore.
Yes. She looked pathetic.
What?
Lindabulea...
The moon's so beautiful tonight.
I apologize for earlier.
Carmilla's such an
embarrassment sometimes...
She fails at any task you give her.
She's the biggest loser I've ever seen.
A fool like none other.
If you thought so,
then you should've gotten rid of her.
But even if she goes about it
in the wrong way sometimes,
she does everything
she can for me, her master.
And I always feel so at ease
when she's around.
And that's why...
She's very precious to me.
What are you saying?
You want me to apologize
to her? Accept her?
Is that why you're here?
No. She's always been a loser,
and there's no helping that.
And it was a fair fight. I'm not going
to complain about her losing.
Then what did you come to do?
The Fafnirs are the most warlike
of the four houses.
If she loses and I don't do something,
the rest of the family
will never shut up about it.
I see.
So you want me to never tell
anybody that Carmilla lost?
Then you'll have to pay.
You've already humiliated
yourself by kneeling before me.
So now you'll need to do
something even greater.
Oh, that's not what I want at all.
I'll just ask for a moment of your time.
What? Are you going to strip naked and beg?
You don't have to go that far!
What are you doing?
Oh, no. My clothing would rip, that's all.
A lady must remain in control
at all times, I've been taught.
But it seems I still have a lot to learn.
Even a dummy like her
is a dear servant to me.
I'm sure she's very upset right now.
So as her master,
I think I need to take revenge.
I, Fafnir Gildomela Grind Lindabulea,
challenge you to a duel!
Just thinking about it makes my blood boil!
Yes, I feel the same way.
My spies tell me that Lindabulea
left her castle right after
the hero was summoned.
She probably intends to find him
before anybody else
so she can have the glory to herself.
I thought she was only interested in food.
I can't believe she got the jump on us.
I'll defeat the hero myself!
I can't let her get to him first!
Of course.
I'll find her,
and this time, I'll crush her!
The lady Joanna requests that you
take any weapons you like.
Using any of this stuff
would be against the rules!
It's been long enough.
It's time to go on a quest.
Not yet.
Until I recover from all the wounds
I took during yesterday's quest
here in this impure soil,
I'm not taking a single step.
You're talking like you
actually did something.
Feel free to thank me at any time, Genzo.
Thank you?
I can't believe you're saying that.
I did my best to stop you, but...
Stop!
Mistress! I'll get a nice snack for you!
You ran on ahead and got eaten!
Now get out of there and work.
Stop it!
Get out. Get out. Get out.
Stop slapping my face!
Goodbye, then.
Mistress...
Mistress!
You're back!
I'm so glad!
I was so worried you'd given up
all hope for me and run away!
I was just about to cure my wounds as
fast as possible and go looking for you!
Where have you been?
I was so worried I couldn't sleep!
Mistress...
Sheesh... She's so dumb.
Maybe I'll just bury you here!
Fine, I'll let you go for today!
Yeah, let's just cover you in dirt.
Stop burying me!
Also, I don't know what that
"power spot" stuff you talk about is,
but that's Hiroyuki's toilet.
Eww!
Next time: "First Student
x Pain in the Butt."