Looking good.
"Money x Bonds"
Morning! Genzo, this morning let's...
Good boy... You're so cute!
Carmilla came home in
the morning again, huh?
Jeez.
Everybody's the same as usual today.
For now, I'm making breakfast!
Genzo!
What, you're back, Katherine?
It's Altena!
I'm the princess of a kingdom!
Very noble!
Why do you keep forgetting?
'Cause I don't care.
Rude!
Well, for now, I'm not
going to worry about it.
Genzo, today I need you to promise
you'll do your duty as a hero.
I refuse!
You never learn, do you?
You're like an obsessive stalker.
Who are you calling a stalker?
Oh, Shigure, can you get me the salt?
The breakfast in this household
is always so bland...
You're really rude.
Now that we've all finished our meal,
Genzo...
What?
According to my knights,
the Demon King from another world
attacked a village of orcs nearby...
Oh, yeah. The orcs said the same thing.
What's this Demon King like, you think?
What? You knew, and yet
you still did nothing?
His name was MAO, yeah...
You know him?
Genzo! Genzo!
What's the Demon King
from another world like?
Well, he was MAO,
that's all I can say...
It's an obvious lie, Mistress.
Even if Genzo is a monster without
a trace of compassion in him...
What kind of life did you live where
you got to know the Demon King, Genzo?
Listen to me!
I don't know why he did it,
but this Demon King from another
world mercilessly struck down
the orcs on his own side.
There's no telling what other
horrible things he may do!
You're right, actually.
Well, that's how you can tell
he's from another world.
He doesn't care about friendship
between us monsters at all.
"Us monsters"?
No, it's nothing.
It's possible that the people of
this town may be his next target.
So...
Altena...
Yes?
I want to take Hiroyuki for
a walk. So please move.
You can shake like a newborn deer,
but I still won't love you.
What's wrong?
Hiroyuki's gone!
Where's the hero?
From the way the orcs
reacted, he must be close.
Knock it off!
Come on, show me!
What's wrong? What are you doing?
Cut it out, man.
Joanna! Get this!
He nabbed something from the orc village.
Are you stupid?
I mean it! Are you that dumb?
I'm sure it's something naughty!
Shut up! Shut up! Shut up!
Naughty? I don't understand.
But let me see it.
'Kay.
What are you showing my lady?
This angle. This bridge.
It's him!
I've finally found you,
Animal Mask! Genzo Shibata!
Joanna, this is Carmilla, too!
She probably fell under
the hero's sway, just like the orcs!
She's just a lesser vampire.
And her mistress is worthless anyway.
I'm sure Lindabulea also...
Yes, that's doubtless the case.
I'll avenge your defeat.
It's the least I can do.
Aww, they took it from us.
It had all that stuff about "death grip"
and "unbearable shame."
It was probably really naughty.
Hiroyuki! Hiroyuki!
Where are you?
Genzo!
Have you seen Hiroyuki?
No...
I see.
Bye.
Hey, Hiroyuki!
Normally Genzo would notice
that I changed my shampoo.
What am I thinking? How silly of me!
Hiroyuki!
Come out!
Mistress.
That animal doesn't matter, does it?
Carmilla, Genzo does a lot for us!
We have a responsibility
to help him look for Hiroyuki.
And he's very important
to me... as well...
Mistress.
Um, excuse me?
Oh, Princess Buttocks...
I mean, Princess Altena!
Have you seen anybody named
Hiroyuki around here?
Actually it's an animal,
a brown beast about this size...
No, not really.
I see!
Look! It's Princess Buttocks!
Princess Buttocks! Princess Buttocks!
The scent drops off around here.
Was he taken away in a bag
or some kind of box?
Which would mean
the crime was planned...
Oh, is something wrong, Shigure?
Clause! Well, actually...
You saw Hiroyuki?
Yes. I saw him when I was visiting
a certain noble's mansion today.
What's he doing at a noble's mansion?
Who cares?
Let's go!
Wait for me, Hiroyuki!
Wait, Genzo!
I'm coming for you!
I'll bring you back!
Hiroyuki!
Hey!
I'm on my way!
Over here, Catherine!
Maria, why don't you
give Catherine a treat?
Okay, Daddy!
Let's go, Catherine!
Don't trip!
Why should I give her back?
I paid a high price to buy her
from a merchant this morning.
And Catherine's taken
a liking to my Maria.
His name's Hiroyuki!
Somebody stole him!
Not my problem.
She's now Catherine.
My animal. That I bought.
Um, Hiroyuki was originally ours,
and we'd like him back.
Shigure, what he's saying isn't wrong.
But...
Even if Hiroyuki was stolen, if he bought him
without knowing that, he did nothing wrong.
I don't know what's going on,
but that's brilliant, Mistress!
You keep your mouth shut.
Then there's no problem
if we buy him back, right?
You're Princess Buttocks...
Silence!
How much did you pay?!
This is the receipt from
when I purchased him.
It's so expensive...
Father, Catherine just...
Hiroyuki!
Is it yummy, Catherine?
Father, she says it's yummy!
I'm sure it is!
I had my chefs make it
for her especially.
Hiroyuki...
This is the perfect chance
to get Genzo in my debt!
There should be enough money
in the castle treasury...
If I buy back that little animal,
Genzo will have to do what I tell him!
Now I can get him to
do his duty as hero!
We're leaving, Shigure.
You're sure, Genzo?
We don't have a choice.
We don't have the money.
I'm glad you understand. Now go.
Genzo...
Are you... crying?
What a wuss!
Be happy, Hiroyuki!
Um, was Catherine your dog?
Yes.
He's been with me through
so much sorrow and joy.
He's a part of my family!
Father...
What is it, Maria?
Can I give Catherine back to him?
What are you saying, Maria?
Listen, I paid for her...
If I'd had Catherine
ever since I was little,
and then she went to another
person's house, I'd be sad!
And I think she's very sad now!
So...
But...
Well, if that's how it's going to be...
No, I can't let you have her for free!
I paid all this money!
I need at least half...
Half? Even that's too much...
Father!
You're ten years too young to look
at a man with eyes like that, Maria...
Okay, half of the half, then!
No, half of that!
Actually, half of that!
And another half... and another half...
And yet another half...
and another half...
One more half!
You have to pay that much!
If you don't have that much money,
Catherine is better off at our home!
Father!
But we still don't have that kind of money!
Mistress, look at what
Genzo did to my stomach!
Please rub this painkiller lotion on it...
Let your pretty fingers
run across my belly...
What do we do?
Without money, Hiroyuki will...
Maria was a nice child, wasn't she?
Genzo?
Hiroyuki may be happy with her.
He can have his fill of yummy food...
What's gotten into you?!
That's what I really wanted
to do with my pet shop.
Meeting an animal.
Interacting with them.
Sharing in their joys...
So maybe I'm better
off letting him go...
Are you really sure, Genzo?
Give me a second.
What's this money?
I didn't know we had
so much in this house...
I was saving it in case
we ever needed it.
I knew if I told you about it,
you'd just spend it all.
You can use it to buy back Hiroyuki.
Shigure...
It's fine.
I was hoping we could use it
to open the pet shop, but...
Whether we use it now or use it in
the future, it's still there to help you.
It's a deal, then.
Bye-bye, Catherine.
His name's Hiroyuki.
Come by and play sometime.
Um, can I ask something?
Who was the merchant
who sold you Hiroyuki?
There were three of them actually,
and they were quite strange.
A bearded man with an eye patch.
A wolf beastman and a cat beast woman.
I didn't think it would go this well!
I heard he was running around
the whole town crying!
Why am I being petted?
It just feels right.
I haven't had such
good drink in a while!
Drink, drink! This is
the drink of victory!
Gulp it all down...
So you thought you could
sell Hiroyuki, did you?
You're not even worth petting anymore!
I just spent all the money to open
this shop you're smashing up, too!
You pervert!
I can hear my bones snapping!
Please forgive me!
Nope!
Genzo!
I've avenged you, Hiroyuki!
They're not dead, right?
I'm back, Genzo!
Now use this money to...
Huh?
Okay, Hiroyuki.
It's dangerous out there,
so sleep in my bed tonight!
What's wrong?
That's...
Mr. Birdy! Mr. Woof!
What are these demon beasts doing here?
Genzo, did you bring home even more...?
This smell...
Somebody's inside our home.
I've been waiting.
Lindabulea, I never thought
we'd meet again like this.
Um...
Did you forget again...
My name is Draculius
Joanna Joannascore...
We meet again, Genzo Shibata.
My name is Draculius Joanna Joannascore...
No, Animal Mask!
He's the one who attacked
the orc village?
Then this...
Hey, MAO.
I thought you were lying!
But you really do know
the Demon King from another world?
Yeah, I do.
So it was you who summoned the
Demon King from another world?
And what about you? You should be
defeating the hero, not living with him.
You're a traitor to our lord.
That's right!
Well, I've got my reasons, I guess...
I bet you lost to the hero and begged
him to save your life, right?
Cowardly!
Hey, you don't get to talk
about her like that!
Shut up, lesser vampire!
Know your place!
Stop talking!
Let's have a match!
Fight me!
That's why I'm here!
Joanna, what's a "match"?
I'll tell you. A "match" is a... a battle
to the death they do in other worlds!
Two men enter, one man ends up dead!
What?
Lindabulea, I challenge
you to a "match," too.
Joanna!
Um, I don't know who you are.
But you're bothering
the neighbors, so quiet down...
That's a good idea.
C-Clause! Where did you come from?
I was thinking it's about time
for a second tournament.
We're doing that again?
A fighting tournament? Perfect!
I'll bury you in front of a huge crowd!
This time, don't run when
you fight me, Animal Mask!
This time, I'll pay you back
for what you did!
Fight me, Lindabulea!
Mistress, we can't lose this fight!
Another tournament?
Will there be more yummy food?
Let's do it! This is our
chance to be rich, Genzo!
Pay you back, huh?
Very well!
It's a fight, MAO!
MAO... I'm up against
a real pro wrestler!
A totally different fight than
the amateurs I've battled thus far.
Carmilla? What's wrong?
There's someone I need to beat.
And I'm willing to do whatever it takes.
Genzo!
Please... please teach me pro wrestling!
Very well.
Next time: "Pride x Loyalty."