Here you go! Here you go!
Eat up!
Is it yummy, Akemi?
Hey!
You're so cute...
Hey, Genzo!
When are you going to teach me
You're so cute...
how to be a pro wrestler?
You're gonna ask me that, are you?
I told you yesterday
that we'd start training at dawn!
Hey! Wake up! It's time to start training!
Are you serious about this?
Yes! Yes! Yes, I am!
So let me go!
Then let's see how serious you are!
"Pride x Loyalty"
This is the design for the arena.
The pain!
We can hold
far more people than last time.
My bones are breaking!
They were flowing out into
the streets last time, after all.
Please stop the pain!
They were flowing out into
the streets last time, after all.
Please stop the pain!
I've placed VIP seats here.
They cost ten times as much
as the normal seats.
I see!
Genzo, please...
Ten times!
Where are the food stands?
Why are we doing this? Why?
Oh, they're around here.
Where around here, specifically?
This whole area.
We have two, no, almost three times
as many stands as last time.
Wonderful!
No more!
Food stalls!
I think it's broken!
And we have so many people
wanting to sponsor.
I think it's broken!
I'm screaming with joy.
Really?
I can't do it! I don't think I can do it!
Now we just need to have
Genzo decide who'll be in the fights.
The body can't bend that way!
I'll tell him!
I'll be going, then.
What's wrong? Out of the fight already?
The sunlight...
I don't see any sunlight.
I'm sick of this "weight lifting"
training anyway.
Teach me some moves!
Not a chance in hell!
You can't learn moves
without doing the lifting!
But there's no time...
Quit your whining!
You need to train your basic endurance
before you get in the ring!
Genzo, you...
Don't you want to win?
Yeah.
This time, I want to win.
No, I have to win.
For my mistress's sake!
Excellent. So, Carmilla...
What?
About this person you want to defeat...
Just like my mistress, she's...
Hey!
I have a childhood friend named Joanna.
She has a servant named Rose
who Carmilla once fought,
and Carmilla got her ass kicked.
I see.
Hanako, I thought it might be
faster if you fought...
No, that won't do! As a vamp...
I can't get involved.
And I'll be busy checking out
all the new food stands!
Well, anyway.
It'll be hard to train her if I don't know
how strong her opponent is.
The time has come.
That's all there is to it.
It's time to show him what
a real wrestler looks like!
What is that?
You don't know, Rose?
Huh?
That's the victory dance from his world.
Is that what that is?
If he's dancing like that before the
battle's even begun, he's sure to win!
Joanna!
I must defeat the hero,
and pay back Lindabulea, too.
Of course!
You lost once already?
Yes. And when I did,
I caused problems for my mistress.
It's my fault...
I need vengeance.
Wait, Genzo...
You know that Demon King
from another world, right?
Yes. He was supposed to be
my last opponent in my old world.
What?
Genzo!
Demon King!
I see.
So this fight means a lot to you, too.
I suppose so, yeah.
Genzo!
Coming!
Okay, train on your own for a while.
What?
You haven't taught me anything yet!
Do this.
Okay, but first I need a little break.
I've worked hard, I deserve this!
You don't get any more
until the match is over.
Give it back!
Alcohol inhibits muscle metabolism!
I don't care!
Give it back, you pervert human!
You want to win, right?
So what will you do?
The line-up?
"1 Heat Haze, Celes"
"2 Orc King, Kobold"
I did come up with something...
"3 Carmilla vs Rose"
"4 Genzo vs MAO"
I did come up with something...
There were supposed
to be five fights, right?
My demon beast army versus
your group! Five rounds!
And the last round is
a one-on-one between you and me!
Well?
Sounds great!
Yeah, that's the thing...
We need another match, don't we?
Calm down, fluffballs!
What do you want? Just leave us alone!
I can't do that, fluffy cat girl!
Why?
I need you.
I know you can do this.
You know we can do...
what?
You want to be in a pro wrestling match?
No!
Quit your whining and come!
I'm scared! I'm scared! I'm scared!
If you won't, I know
what's in store for you!
No!
Who's a good boy? You are!
We'd get paid about this much, say?
No..
This much.
We're in!
"1 Heat Haze Celes"
"2 Orc King, Kobold"
"3 Wolfgang, Misha"
"4 Carmilla vs Rose"
"5 Genzo vs MAO"
And that does it.
I think the first match is a little dull.
You're always so harsh.
The Hunter Guild gladly
accepted my offer, but...
What? Pro wrestling?
Of course you'd want the help of the
strongest hunter in the guild, demon beast...
Teacher, let me do it too!
It's the first match, so I'd like
to really get the crowd riled up.
Good point.
Can we throw in somebody else
to make it a group match?
I heard the news, Genzo!
The Demon King came here personally!
Just like a moth-wyvern to a dragon-flame!
Crush him, please!
So, is there something I can do?
Just say the word!
That's it.
Come to our wrestling tournament!
Exciting battles await!
Lots of yummy food!
The fights will be even
better than last time!
There's more money to be made!
Right this way!
Here you go!
Yes! I got a good seat!
Takoyaki!
No! No!
Tickets on sale over here!
Please form two lines!
Monsters, come this way!
Please allow us to check
your personal belongings!
No weapons or magic items!
Today your fate will be decided!
That's my line, damn it!
Oh, you're here as well?
Good evening.
Can you see, Maria?
I sure can!
But what is pro wrestling, exactly?
That's a good question.
Ikarumie Alimaran!
It's finally time!
Time to head backstage!
I'm sure everyone is all excited...
Huh? Hanako-san!
Hey!
Where's the gift shop?
Oh, sorry.
I'm too busy to do it this time.
Sorry!
I'm all fired up!
Listen up, everyone.
It matters who wins and who loses.
But what matters more is to fight
in a way you won't regret!
Genzo's philosophy is wonderful.
Every word he says echoes in my heart.
Yeah! I won't forget his words!
If you win, you'll be getting
a good amount of prize money.
So do your best.
Hey, were you listening?
It's not about winning, or money.
Yes. A true man does not concern
himself with such things.
Right, Genzo?
Correct.
With that prize money I can open
the pet shop of my dreams!
So I'm winning and getting
that cash no matter what!
That's not what you said...
It's time!
It's a full house, guys!
Why do you look so upset?
That's a good thing.
But I don't want them
seeing me in this outfit...
Don't worry.
You've got this.
I don't want to wear that either!
What is it, even?
I need to win for my mistress's sake.
No matter what.
No.
Mistress?
You don't need to fight for my sake.
Human t-shirts! Demon t-shirts!
Which will you pick?
It's time, everyone!
It's time for "Cluster Bank presents:
Team Hero Genzo versus
the Demon King's Army!"
For our first match,
coming from Team Hero Genzo...
Heat Haze, the fake hero from the
Hunter Guild, and once again, Celes XXL!
And the mysterious masked warrior,
God Save the Queen At-lena!
I'm the princess!
Why do I have to dress like this?
Everyone's staring at me!
Their gazes pain me, but...
It's like a massage...
It hurts, but it feels good!
But... It's wonderful!
Facing them is the demon beast army!
Will they show us the power
of the demon beasts?
We've got a great match for you tonight!
Come! I'll be your opponent!
Hit me with your hard body!
What did you say, bouncy girl?
Hey, don't taunt him like that!
Calm down.
Calm down, please.
We need to come up with a strategy...
If you won't go to me, I'll go to you!
I've seen those buttocks before...
Sure it's not Princess Buttocks?
That's right! It's Princess Buttocks!
What humiliation!
I can hear the crowd's disgust with me...
One, two, three!
The winner is Team Genzo!
We did it, Teacher!
It's finally time for me to get
the credit I deserve as the chosen hero!
Don't look at me like that, everyone!
The second match is beginning!
One, two, three!
Winners, Team Genzo!
We did it!
Hell yeah!
A brainless brawl between
two groups of muscle-heads!
It's so intense!
Honey...
Bro...
Round three!
The winners are the Demon King's army!
Hey, entertain us!
This is why I didn't want to do this...
Now, our next match features
the drunk loser girl
who goes to sleep holding
other women's clothes: Carmilla!
And her opponent, the black knight
who'll do anything and take
any risk for her lady, Rose!
Let the battle begin!
I've already proved that a lesser vampire
can't beat an elder vampire!
Shut up!
What?
What's going on?
Damn you, lesser!
This is an amazing fight!
Get her!
Don't lose!
She's weaker than you!
Beat her quick!
Listen, focus on your opponent!
No matter how strong they are,
they'll let their guard down!
Watch for your moment!
I can't lose! I can't!
She's a coward who does nothing but run!
Show her how to fight!
Go!
What?
Did I win?
Yes!
I defeated an elder vampire?
I did it!
I won!
What are you doing?
Pin her!
Mistress, I did it!
Carmilla!
One...
two...
three!
The winner is Rose!
Well done!
Of course...
I lost.
You'll never beat me.
You let your guard down.
Why did you give her an opening?
But it was a good fight.
Mistress?
Carmilla, you fought for your own sake,
with your pride on the line, and you won.
No, Mistress... I...
I lost!
No.
To me, it was a victory.
And I'm proud of you.
Here's your reward.
Mistress!
You're such a crybaby.
Mistress gave me food for the first time!
Is that what it was?
Genzo Shibata, no, Animal Mask!
It's been a long time
since anybody's called me that.
It's time to fight!
I'm getting excited!
Next Time: "Hero x Demon King."
Make sure you watch it, okay?