It's time for the main event!
Animal Mask vs. Macadamian Ogre, AKA, MAO!
The masked wrestler, Animal Mask,
will face off against
former Judo fighter MAO!
Will this bring an end
to their long rivalry?
What kind of match do they
have in store for us tonight?
It's finally time...
Being a pro wrestler was
the first chapter in my life.
And if I can win tonight's
world championship title match,
the second chapter in my life will begin...
It's almost time for the fight!
The world championship title bout!
Big Saigo, I'm monologuing.
Don't interrupt me.
Oh, I see!
So, what will you do if you win tonight?
There's mountains left for you to climb!
Yes, that's exactly right.
When I win tonight's match,
the second chapter in my life will begin.
Oh, what is it?
You're quitting pro wrestling to do MMA?
No, maybe Muay Thai or Capoeira?
Very well. I'll tell you... I'm going to...
Whoops, looks like we're out of time.
Break a leg and all that.
Go out there and smash up
that Macadamian Ogre guy.
Big Saigo.
He's always in a hurry.
"No Pets!!" The second chapter in my life that
will begin when I win tonight's title match...
Is when I will live my life
surrounded by the animals I love,
and share the joy of living with animals
with people everywhere!
"Interdimensional Title Match
Animal Mask vs MAO"
Let's go, Hiroyuki.
The Macadamian Ogre!
And now, entering the ring...
The man who loves
animals a little too much!
Weighing in at 198
pounds, it's Animal Mask!
It's finally time...
My rival, MAO.
A worthy opponent for my last match!
The second chapter of my life will begin
after I slam you into the mat...
and that is!
Opening a pet shop!
Strongest warrior from another world...
You're as strong as ever, Mao!
Impressive!
However!
I pray you answer my call!
Animal Mask has climbed up onto the ropes!
And now he's jumped!
So has Hiroyuki!
Wait! They've started to glow!
What is this?
They disappeared!
Animal Mask has disappeared!
Huh? What?
Are you the hero?
I am Animal Mask!
Did the hero-summoning ritual fail?
Why is he in his underwear?
Is he a pervert?
I don't care who you are!
If you've answered our call,
then you are our hero!
What's going on?
Another trick of Big Saigo's?
No... this isn't the arena.
So where am I?
Please, Hero, will you defeat
the evil demon beasts that stalk this land
as well as the Demon King?
Evil demon beasts?
Yes, terrifying animals called monsters...
Exterminate every one of them
from this land...
Hero?
It appears I heard you right after all.
You're telling me to
defeat animals for you?
Yes. They're terrifying
and disgusting beasts...
Um, Hero?
We can do that after you
defeat the Demon King...
Or at least when nobody's watching...
Hero... Um, Hero?
Hero?!
Winner!
"Wrestler x Summoning"
The princess's noble butt
is being shown to the world!
Somebody, hide her butt!
Defeat animals?
So the blood of an animal lover
that flows through my veins
forced me to give that impudent
girl a German suplex?
You bastard...
Hero, I understand that you're angry
about being summoned like this,
but you can't do that to the princess.
I don't know what you're talking about
with this summoning and hero nonsense!
But... perhaps I went too far.
I know!
Drape.
Stop messing around!
Capture him!
Damn!
I was trying to be a gentleman
and help the lady out,
why are they mad?
What kind of lunatic waves
a sword at someone like that?
This definitely isn't the arena.
It's not even night anymore.
Where am I?
Who is that?
Where are his pants?
Is he a pervert?
We should stay away...
He looked over here.
Don't meet his gaze.
Somebody go call a hunter!
I guess I'll just find someone
kind-looking to ask.
Um, excuse me... Can
you tell me where I am?
I get it!
It's rude to ask people questions
while wearing a mask!
The moment I take off my mask,
I'm no longer Animal Mask...
I'm an ordinary man named Genzo Shibata.
Now no one will know...
Over there! That's him!
Watch out! It's a pervert!
What?
Impossible!
The pervert ran away!
After the pervert!
I'm not a pervert! I'm a pro wrestler!
I have no idea how they figured me out.
But don't worry, Hiroyuki.
I'll figure out a way out of this.
Sorry, Hiroyuki.
Forgive me for being useless...
Hiroyuki! I'm so glad you're here with me!
I don't know what I would've done
if I were here by myself.
I don't care about clothes! Not at all!
My goal is to find food for you tonight!
Bro, that pervert looks pretty buff.
We could sell him for a lot.
Yes. And that strange creature
would probably be worth a lot of cash.
You're so cute...
You there, in your underwear.
Wh-What?
Animal ears?!
A-And...
You're hungry, right?
Come with us and we'll give you some food.
An animal!
Do you like my hairy chest and tail?
You've got nowhere to go, right?
Do what he says...
Bro, this guy seems like bad news...
Y-Yeah...
So fluffy!
He's staring at you, not me!
W-We'll be on our way...
What the hell?
Do you want to fight?
You think you can beat a beastman
with your bare hands?
Get 'em, bro!
I see... you're a beastman, huh?
Bro!
Hey, you jerk! Get off my brother!
Stop sniffing him!
Misha, this guy is crazy!
He's crazy!
We're sorry, so stop! Let him go!
If you don't, my bro will... my bro will...
What's this guy's deal?
He's incredibly strong!
Don't worry!
You'll start to like it any second!
Oh, you like it when I rub you here, huh?
Stop it!
We'll pay you! Stop it! Please!
See? Feels good, right? Good boy...
Now, you're next...
Cat ears!
Shigure, give up already!
You're about to be sold!
No!
I don't want to live at some noble's house
and get walks and naps and free snacks!
Who said you were being sold to a noble?
If that was the deal I'd go myself.
But if they're willing to feed me
filet mignon every day,
I may be willing to let them sell me.
Nobody will buy a beast girl like that!
Let's go!
No!
A poor girl in unfortunate circumstances...
Stop whining and let's go!
It's not right for an outsider
like me to get involved.
And not because I'd
rather pet the cat ears...
That tail! Those ears! Is that a wolf?
I've had plenty of experience touching
cats and dogs, but never a wolf!
A girl with cat ears is
a hard thing to pass up,
but my priority now is the wolf ears girl!
Please...
All praise animal ears and animal tails!
That's far enough!
Mind your own business.
I don't know who you think you are,
but try anything and you'll regret it.
Really, who are you?
Edgar, he's dangerous!
He's a super-high-level pervert!
He just had his way with my bro...
What?
What are you doing?
Allow me to first correct
your misunderstanding.
I am not a pervert.
I simply love all animals
regardless of gender!
See? He's more dangerous than he looks!
Yeah. The way he dresses,
the things he says...
He's a pervert like none
the world has ever seen!
Why do you fear?
I don't know who you are,
or what reasons you may have...
No! Stop it!
If the wolf girl is upset, you are evil!
Damn it!
You pervert! We'll get you yet!
Come to think of it, I hadn't gotten
to pet the cat ears yet, had I?
Why did you have to open your mouth?!
You're right! I'm sorry!
Um...
Thank you for saving me!
Now I won't be sold.
Don't worry. I did it because I wanted to.
You were about to be kidnapped
by a slaver, right?
No, I'd borrowed money from him, so...
I see.
You were charged absurd amounts of interest
and then sold to pay your debts.
No, I'm the one who said
that if I couldn't pay by the deadline
he could sell me instead.
In exchange, I told him to give me a loan
with no interest and no collateral,
and then cried and sobbed
in front of his shop until he gave in.
I intended to use that money
to start a business and get rich,
but it didn't work out.
She's a loser.
What's that look?
I was making money for a while!
But then humans started copying me.
I am Genzo Shibata.
A pro wrestler.
My name is Shigure.
And this is Hiroyuki. My partner
and a mongrel of pure breeding.
Nice to meet you, too!
Um, I'd love to thank you
for saving me, but...
I'm broke.
But from what you said, it sounds
less like I've done a good deed
and more like I've committed a felony...
Don't worry!
Remember what I said about
people stealing my business model?
The guy who stole it was Edgar,
the guy you just saw!
See? That makes him
evil, right? Right? Right?
Well, I guess I could count that
as a good deed, just barely.
So...
You said you were broke, right?
You can pay with your body instead.
He's a loser.
I'll get him...
It's a shame, huh?
You okay?
Damn that bastard.
I won't just give up...
I don't think there's anything you can do.
Got a plan?
Yeah. That strange creature he had.
Oh, that?
What will you do with it?
What else? I'll steal it!
Great idea! Let's do it!
We're gonna do it!
Yeah!
We'll show that pervert who's boss!
I have nothing but a bad feeling...
So this is it?
Yes. The Hunter Guild.
Let's work here for a while
to make some money.
You seem to be really strong,
so there's probably
lots of great jobs for you.
So you see,
I have complete confidence
in my ability to love any animal
regardless of gender, species,
or even more specifically
hairiness, long-hair, short-hair,
eye color, or tail length!
So I'd like to maintain
a relationship of love
and caring with animals at all times!
What? What is he talking about?
And...
Even the fiercest, most violent animal will
respond to my overwhelming love for them.
So...
What do I?
What am I supposed to do here?
Trouble, Guild Master!
What's going on?
I'm saved!
Our party was wiped out by a cerberus pack.
What? Perfect.
Will you go too?
Cerberuses are terrifying monsters...
What?
Where are they?
Genzo! Wait!
What?
What sort of man isn't scared of a cerberus
and instead runs out to meet them?
What a brave man.
But... I didn't understand
a word he was saying.
It's deep in this forest!
Okay!
I don't think I've seen you before.
Are you going unarmed?
You can borrow this if you want.
Fool!
Do I look like a wrestler
who uses weapons to you?
He's going to fight them unarmed?
How confident is he?
Um, I'll borrow it...
Listen, we can't let
them get near the town!
Stop them here!
This is bad!
So these are cerberuses?
They've got three heads!
That means triple the fun!
So there are animals
like this in this world?
Okay, maybe they
look a little strange, but...
Are you scared?
Well, calm down.
Hey!
No, let's see how he handles this.
Yes...
Cerberus!
They appear to be a type of dog.
Which means that if I can become
friends with the pack leader,
the others will quickly
open up to me as well.
The leader is probably...
the one guarding the rear!
You?
Hello!
He ran in!
Gotcha!
He dodged them!
Good boy! Let's play!
And now for the leader!
Come here!
He pinned it!
What kind of move is that?
But there are others...
This is bad!
Should we help?
Stay out of this!
He's keeping us out of danger?
What a man!
I think I'm starting to figure him out...
Good boy! Good boy!
You like it here, huh?
Good boy... You're such a good boy...
He really pinned it with his bare hands...
Like you'd pin down a lady...
He's like a lady killer...
No, he's...
a demon beast killer!
We got enough money from the job
to get you some clothes,
as well as pay for an inn for a while.
Yeah.
So, what will you do now?
I've made my decision.
I want people to understand
how wonderful demon beasts are!
Indeed! I'll bring about a world
where demon beasts and humans
can understand each other!
That's impossible in this country.
No...
I believe I can do it.
So you must believe too.
Genzo, is the reason
you refused to be a hero...?
That princess demanded I defeat animals!
Animals and human,
beast people and humans...
I like it! Let me help, too!
Really? Then let's do this!
Let's do the best with the three of us, no,
the four of us including Hiroyuki!
Yes!
Four?
Who are you?
Next time: "Quest x Demon Beast Killer."