The fourth match ended
with a surprise victory by Rose!
A single moment's
distraction was all it took!
Carmilla was the hopeless loser
we all took her for,
and she lost badly!
Mistress!
There, there.
Now, to recap...
The winner of our first match
was the hero army!
It was a great match!
You did great, Princess Buttocks!
So many... It feels so good...
Why?
Even the name Princess Buttocks
that I found so humiliating...
Now I wear it with pride!
You probably got a new fetish!
And in the second match, the Orc King
and the Kobold won the tag match!
I'm honored to have been your tag partner.
That's my line!
You're the best, King!
That's why you're the king!
We'll follow you forever!
Honey!
Daddy! Daddy!
I won!
You're the best, Daddy!
You're so strong!
I'm glad you won, honey.
I fell in love all over again.
I'm sorry. That's how it is, Genzo.
I won't be able to be with you after all.
I'm sure you can find
a wonderful wife of your own.
Assumptions are awful things, huh?
And the Demon King from another world
won the third and forth matches!
I did it, Joanna!
That lesser vampire was no match for me!
No, you almost lost!
It's gotten exciting.
After the Demon King from another world
defeats that hero...
I'll be paying
Lindabulea a little visit.
You shouldn't underestimate him.
Lindabulea...
Joanna, I don't know anything about
the Demon King from another world,
but it won't go the way you think it will.
What do you mean?
You'll know when you see the match.
What? Are you trying
to solve this with violence?
That's right! Violence is wrong!
We'll talk later.
Why is she so confident?
Don't tell me...
The hero's wearing a mask...
Is that hero...?
In the blue corner,
weighing in at 178 pounds,
it's the leader of the Demon King army,
the Demon King from another world!
MAO!
In the red corner, weighing in at 198
pounds, it's the leader of the hero army,
Animal Mask!
It's our last match of the night!
Who will walk away the victor?
The Demon King? Or the hero?
It's a battle of fate!
Fight!
"Hero x Demon King"
The battle has begun!
What do they have in store for us?
There's a tension in the air.
I can feel the killing rage...
They're each planning
their first move, huh?
Teacher...
I can see why he's our leader...
Genzo!
They're both feeling each other out...
Neither are moving!
MAO's style is to go right for the throat.
So why?
Stay calm.
If you hurry and go right for
the throat like you did before,
he'll just counter you
straight into the mat.
The one who outsmarts
the other will win the day.
Right, Animal Mask?
The winner is Animal Mask!
Animal Mask is so good
at reading his opponent.
MAO barely got in a blow.
I must beat Animal Mask!
Don't push me! Don't push me!
It's so hot!
Just wait, Animal Mask!
But... on that day...
They disappeared!
Animal Mask has disappeared!
Ever since then,
my life's been nothing but suffering!
Do you know the misery
I've felt, Animal Mask?
But today's the day I finally...
Why are you attacking first?
Because you didn't attack at all!
Look! The crowd fell asleep
because we weren't doing anything!
You're right!
Damn it!
You've totally ruined the perfect
anti-Animal Mask plan I
spent months coming up with!
You spaced out and went wide open!
We're pro wrestlers! And we need to show
the crowd what it means to be pros!
We can finally see some action!
You're too slow!
Bullshit!
What it means to be a pro?
You ran from me! You're no pro!
Ran? What do you mean?
You know what I mean!
In our last match, you ran
because you were afraid of me!
I didn't run!
I was supposed to beat you that day
and become the new champion!
And I was supposed to beat you
and open a pet shop!
And instead I found myself here...
Wait, how'd you get here anyway?
I just woke up in a weird castle...
Wait, is that what happened to you?
I didn't see it, but probably!
Then you didn't run from my match with you!
Of course not!
A wrestler accepts all comers!
Then you'll fight me!
I already am!
Yes!
Stop laughing and get back to the match!
So what are you doing here?
I'm participating in this match to make
my long-held dream come true!
I want to open a pet shop!
A pet shop?
You mentioned that before.
What's this about a pet shop?
Well, after our match in that arena,
I was going to begin a
new chapter in my life.
What?
I decided to own a pet shop and live
my life surrounded by the animals I love!
Wait... this is a lot
to take in and I'm lost.
A pet shop?
Maybe I'll just forget it for now.
They told me I had to beat a Demon King.
I thought it had nothing to do with me,
but then you came!
What about you?
I was told to defeat the hero.
Are you the hero?
I keep telling them a wrestler, but yes.
What's gotten into him?
Joanna, you hear what the Demon King
from another world is saying, right?
Is he maybe just a giant moron?
Don't say that! It's way too late
to do anything, so don't even say it, Rose!
It doesn't matter, 'cause I'm
going to defeat you either way!
I'm done playing around!
Animal Mask uses
the dirtiest tricks every time...
He knows I'm scared of dogs!
No I don't!
He made that awful "Hiroyuki"
creature his manager?
That's right. My other weakness
in the battle against Animal Mask...
"Petting Zoo"
To overcome it, I...
"Petting Zoo" Hello, everyone!
See? It's so cute, isn't it?
"Danger
No entry!"
Hey! That's dangerous!
You jerk!
Next time, I'll get you!
Is he scared of Hiroyuki?
Joanna, is the Demon King...
scared of cute little demon beasts?
Don't say that! It's way too late
to do anything, so don't even say it, Rose!
Then Rose...
We can use that demon beast...
I see, Joanna!
Sneak, sneak, sneak...
Joanna!
Come over here!
Be a good boy!
You're so cute!
Hiroyuki!
We got him!
We won't let you use this
to weaken your opponent...
That's not fair, hero!
What the hell are you doing?
Okay, the threat is gone!
Wait, damn it!
Be careful, please! Be careful, please!
Rose!
We're sorry!
Be careful, please! Be careful, please!
They're coming this way!
Stay away!
Wait!
Why are we running, too?
No idea!
It's the only way to survive!
Keep him safe, Jeeg.
Get back in the ring!
One...
Fight me, damn it!
Did you make them go after Hiroyuki, MAO?
I can't take this anymore!
What did you say?
That's my line!
My shop!
You wanna fight?
Then you've got one!
I'm the strongest in the guild!
I may only be half beast woman,
but my feelings are 100% real!
Great! Give 'em hell!
Hey! Hey!
Clause, were you getting excited?
No. Of course not.
Nineteen!
I will win, no matter what!
For animals!
Taste my special move!
Cannonball 450!
One!
Two!
Three!
Rhino?
I lost again.
I can't match your love for animals.
People who have something
to protect are different.
I wanted to fight you more, though.
You can any time you want.
Pro wrestling really is the best!
The winner is Animal Mask!
How wonderful it is to
live with animals, huh?
One man uses a move.
One man takes the hit.
That's how pro wrestling begins.
The winners are the hero army!
Genzo!
Congratulations!
We did it, Shigure. We won!
The hero army gets the prize money!
Clause from Cluster Bank will be
handing over the prize money.
It's an honor.
That was a wonderful match, Genzo.
Let's do it again.
I thought you were
only interested in money.
Now your dream will come true.
Yes. My dream to open a pet shop!
Joanna...
Yes. There's no sense in staying here.
Are you leaving?
Lindabulea.
Tell me one thing.
Is he really the hero?
He is.
He is the true hero.
I do want to make one thing clear.
Carmilla and I will continue
to observe the hero.
Your help is not needed.
We'll get you yet!
Just not today!
Stupid! Dummy!
Have a nice day.
Great work today, Shigure.
You, too.
Now, let's get to the point.
We exceeded expectations
in a number of ways today.
Ticket sales and
merchandise and food sales...
Look at it all.
But unfortunately,
Genzo and the other wrestlers
far exceeded that number
in their destructive path.
Here's the repair bill
for the stalls and the tent.
Add in the food and drink costs
from Hanako and Carmilla,
and what's left for you is...
What's left for you is this.
Shigure?
Did something happen?
How much did you two eat and drink?!
Cheers!
Watch me!
This is great!
Drink up!
Genzo!
Shigure, that tournament was great!
Oh, you came at the perfect time!
Pay this whenever you can!
How much did you guys eat and drink?
Sheesh...
A pro wrestling tournament, huh?
When will the next one be?
Princess?
No. It's nothing.
Oh, Shigure!
Got something nice to sell me?
This, actually...
I don't know. We only deal in weapons.
But you can craft this into a weapon.
See?
Mythril?
That would work!
You're the best, Shigure!
I sure am!
You're leaving already?
Yeah. I want to train and then
have another match...
No, do more pro wrestling with you.
I see.
See you around, Animal Mask.
See you, MAO.
I wonder where this road will take me...
Let me finish my sentence!
Come on, kiddos!
Its time for lunch!
You're still here?!
Crap!
You were supposed to go to the guild
to get a quest to pay off our debts!
I was just leaving!
Where are Hanako and Carmilla?
Sheesh... None of you do any work
unless I'm here to tell you to do it!
Hey, don't lump me in with them!
Hey!
Big trouble! Demon beasts are...
What?
A minotaur appeared in the southern valley!
It's a very violent one...
How much does the job pay?
What does it taste like, you think?
Mistress, are you going to go?
I'll help you change clothes!
Okay, let's go meet the minotaur!