What the heck?
"Runaway Girl x Attacker"
Genzo, we've finally got a house,
but if you don't do something
we won't have any place to live!
Listen, Shigure.
Until these kids grow up to live
with their wonderful owners,
we need to make sacrifices
for the sake of our love for them.
That's what it means to be a parent.
I'm no parent to a demon beast.
And they cost a ton to feed, too.
Okay, I'm off to pawn these
and take a look at the guild board.
There might be something
high-paying we can do for a job.
Oh, you guys must be hungry!
There's plenty to eat, so chow down!
The road to my pet shop dream
is still a long and hard one, huh?
Oh? You're the new neighbor, huh?
Looks like you're working hard.
Yes...
Are you all right?
I'm just fine, miss.
I'm glad.
Um... I have to hurry and go shopping.
Bye!
Miss!
What a charming lady!
What's up, Hiroyuki?
What's this?
She has a wonderful
tail and horns of her own!
"Growl..."
Where am I?
Looks like you're awake.
Food's ready.
Here.
This is all I have,
but it's better than nothing, right?
Um...
Can I eat it?
Yes.
Thank your luscious horns and tail.
I thought humans always get
scared when they see these...
Nice to meet you, strange human.
My name is Lindabulea. Fa...
Fa?
Just Lindabulea.
I'm a half-dragon. A nobody.
A half-dragon?
Yes. A completely ordinary half-dragon!
I see!
I'm Genzo Shibata.
"Growl..."
Sorry. Eat up.
Okay! Thank you!
No! Not him!
This!
Oh, this is dinner?
He just looked so delicious.
I can't have you eating my partner...
You're fast.
By the way, Genzo, these monsters...
Yeah. I'm raising them so I can achieve
my dream of opening a pet shop.
A pet shop?
I see!
You mean a restaurant, right?
No!
This salamander looks especially delicious!
Listen to me.
Listen carefully.
A pet shop is a place where you
train the pets you've found,
sometimes with a whip and
sometimes with a carrot,
so you can someday sell them to good homes!
This world doesn't seem to have
the concept of keeping animals as pets.
But any living creature will respect you
if you treat it with love.
I want to teach the world that
humans and animals can coexist!
Genzo!
What kind of demon beast is this?
His name is Hiroyuki.
He's not an animal. He's a mongrel.
A mongrel...
May I have him, Genzo?
I'll raise him with love!
But he's...
I'll raise him with love and care...
And get him nice and plump and...
I knew you were going to eat him!
You meanie!
Do all half-dragons try to eat everything?
I still can't read well.
Tell me what page the half-dragons are on.
I forgot something important I had to do.
Bye, Genzo!
What's her deal?
What's wrong? Did you forget something?
Oh, it's you, Shigure.
Yes. I just got back...
A dragon! I smell a dragon!
Genzo! We're already almost broke,
and you brought in a dragon?
I did not bring in a dragon!
I just made some food
for a half-dragon, that's all!
I see.
But the dragon smell is pretty
strong for a half-dragon...
By the way, did you find
any high-paying jobs?
A suspicious person?
Yes. People are getting attacked
every night, we're hearing.
They want to hire the guild to help.
Not interested. Ask somebody else.
Hey, Genzo!
It wasn't a man that did it!
It was a demon beast!
Let's hear the details.
At first I thought what he said was just
the ramblings of a drunk, but...
Those big wings, those sharp fangs,
those ferocious eyes...
That was a dragon! I know it!
A dragon that eats anything,
from a demon beast to a rock!
I've never seen one and I
don't know what they look like,
but I'm pretty sure that it was
absolutely, probably a dragon!
A dragon! Something that amazing
is here, in this town...
A dragon?
Didn't I just hear that...?
I heard the story.
I, Heat Haze, can't turn down
the chance to fight a dragon.
This is the perfect chance to gain
the title of dragon slayer.
I will defeat the evil dragon
with my new magic sword, Dainsleif!
Let us battle the dragon
together, my friend!
Hell no!
Yay! Another sword somebody forgot!
Only you could handle a dragon!
Please, demon beast killer.
I told you not to call me that!
Okay, let's go, Shigure.
First we'll investigate the scene.
Maybe we'll find some dropped scales...
Even hearing it was a
dragon didn't scare him.
Just what you'd expect
from the demon beast...
What's up?
I'm sure of it!
This is the smell of a dragon!
Really?
And it's the same thing
I smelled in our house before.
What?
Genzo, who was it who came to our house?
My wrestler's intuition is telling me
that she wasn't the culprit.
But Shigure's sharp nose would never
make a mistake. Which means...
It's possible that the girl
is caught up in some kind of crime.
It's time to go.
Okay, now to just put down
this special extra-dry pet food...
If I'm wrong and she really
was attacking people,
I'll capture her myself.
This outfit is a symbol of my resolve!
She was very hungry.
Normally she wouldn't
fall for a trap like this,
but she won't be able
to resist the smell...
And what happens when I
can't resist the smell?
You're sure you're a half-dragon, right?
Yes.
Anyway, who are you? Have we met?
My name is Animal Mask!
Just an ordinary, run-of-the-mill wrestler!
But I have something to ask you...
Stop eating, first.
No.
What are you doing out here, Animal Mask?
I set a trap to catch you!
What will you do now
that you've captured me?
Will you...?
No! I'll admit your tail
and horns are attractive,
but I'm not a lolicon!
A pervert has appeared!
Look! He's clearly a weirdo!
The man in the cape
threw a woman in a cage!
W-Wait! I'm not the suspicious person!
It's the middle of the night and
you've got a loli stuck in a cage!
How is that not suspicious?
That's the definition of suspicious!
Oh, no!
They're absolutely right!
Damn! How did this happen?
I just wanted to help that girl!
You think they thought you were trying
to trap me and have your way with me?
I would never do that to a girl...
Wait!
Where did you go?
Hey.
What happened to the cage?
I pulled hard and the bars separated.
You tore up the cage yourself?
Are you really a half-dragon?
And why are you running away with me?
You said you had
something to ask me, right?
And...
You didn't seem like a bad person.
Get away from the mistress, pervert.
Who's that?
Carmilla...
You suspicious pervert...
I shall defeat you!
Foolish human... your struggles
will only prolong your suffering.
Stop it! Don't throw rocks!
That's not fair!
And mistress, were you throwing rocks too?
Is she with you?
I've never seen her in my life.
Mistress!
You just said her name
was Carmilla, though.
Sure you didn't imagine it?
Damn you!
I'll rip you apart for trying
to deceive the mistress.
What?
That's nothing compared to the claws of the
cruel wrestler I once fought, Jack the Rapper!
A mere human trying to match my strength?
I'll snap those arms of yours...
Huh?
She's tough...
My name is Animal Mask!
When I bear this name
and wear these clothes...
Oww! Oww! Are you really human?
Animal Mask!
I cannot be defeated!
You're going to break something!
I hear voices!
This way! Bring more people!
Surround him!
Let's go!
Right!
I'll get you yet!
Where did that pervert go?
He should be nearby.
Let's find him!
Right!
They're persistent.
What do we do?
We'll have to get creative.
What's this?
They're looking for a masked man.
But if you wear this, we'll just
look like an ordinary masked couple.
I see!
I heard that humans were smart!
That's a brilliant idea!
My name can be Maskoffsky.
And you can be... Hanako!
Destroyer Hanako!
Hanako!
Okay, got it!
Hey, glad to see you're
keeping the streets safe.
Everybody seems panicked about something.
Did something happen?
Well, there's a suspicious
person around here...
Genzo, what are you doing?
Nope!
I don't know who you're confusing me with,
but my name is Maskoffsky!
And this is...
Destroyer Hanako!
What is it, Shigure?
Nothing! Nothing!
I forgot something, so I'm going home!
Get moving!
Hey!
What the hell are you doing?
Wait, Shigure...
I just wanted her to...
You were actually Genzo?
You couldn't tell?
Listen, Shigure. You may have seen through
my disguise with your sharp nose,
but when I wear the mask
I'm a different person.
Normal people can't tell.
You sure about that?
So, the issue is you.
I've got questions.
Okay.
My name is Lindabulea.
Fafnir Gildomela Grind...
Hold it!
Genzo!
I'm going to go clean my room.
Don't be ridiculous.
This is important, so listen carefully.
B-But...
I'm a member of the Fafnir family,
one of the four families
that serve the Demon King...
Be quiet, Shigure. What's your problem?
We're doomed!
Now that we've heard that we're...
Wh-What?
Is that...?
You're the girl from before!
My name is Vanstein Carmilla!
You are in the presence of the mistress.
Now kneel before her.
This person is...
A while ago I was defeated by
a masked human.
Where did he go?
I thought he was with the mistress.
Masked man?
Did you meet her before?
Yeah. I beat her, too.
That stupid mask fooled her too?
More importantly!
Carmilla, these two
have nothing to do with this!
I'll go back, so don't...
No! All information about
the Fafnir family is top secret!
Now that it's leaked,
this human will have to disappear.
I didn't even ask! You just told me!
Genzo, use this on her!
What is this?
Just do it!
Now, foolish lesser beings!
Tonight will be your last night!
If nothing else, know that you died
in the presence of my great mistress...
Oww!
That's holy water
with the church's mark on it! It works!
Genzo, here!
Stuff it in her mouth!
I don't understand, but sure!
Garlic!
How could you?
Wait!
Can you forgive her?
She's an idiot, but she's
an important servant of mine.
I see.
So Carmilla came to bring you back
after you ran away?
Indeed.
I followed her scent to this town,
but she was always one step ahead.
But now I've finally found her.
I see.
Now let's hear what you
have to say for yourself.
Um, were you listening?
She's the daughter of the Fafnir family...
I'm not interested in the Fafna-whatsits.
I want to hear why you ran away from home.
No, I'm going home, so don't worry.
Fool!
Whatever reason it was,
it was enough for a kid like you to wander
around in the middle of the night!
Will you really have no
regrets if you go back?
Tell me what you really want!
I was sick of spending
every day in the mansion.
And spending every day
learning to kill humans as
the daughter of the Fafnir family...
Mistress...
And every day it's orc meat!
And if it's not that,
it's goblin meat or troll meat!
I'm sick of it!
I wanted to go into the outside world
and sample all kinds of new, tasty treats!
Is that why?
But...
It was fate that led me to this town.
Mistress?
I... I...
Fate? Does that mean...
Mistress! You can't, mistress!
I won't let you, mistress!
Genzo!
What?
Let me help you with your pet shop!
Rethink that, mistress!
No, I've made my choice!
Fate led me to meet you!
No matter what anybody says,
I won't change my mind.
So, can I stay by your side, Hiroyuki?
Him, not me?
Very well.
I'll tell the clan leader.
You're sure, Carmilla?
Yes. My highest priority is your happiness.
Wait!
We haven't even opened the store!
We don't have money to hire anybody!
As long as I have food and a place to live,
I don't need money.
You're hired.
Very well.
But we can't call you Lindabulea
or Fafna-whatsits, right?
Um...
Call me Hanako!
Just call me Hanako from now on!
You're sure?
Yes!
Okay! Glad to have you aboard.
Hey, so who was the
suspicious person, then?
Suspicious person?
You didn't attack any people, did you?
How rude!
Even I don't eat people.
Humans are omnivores so they
don't taste good, I've heard.
And you didn't try to find out
by biting one, right?
The people who were attacked
had bite marks on them.
Oh, that was me.
What do you mean?
While I was chasing after your smell,
I kind of got excited.
So I attacked some passing humans.
Keep it our secret, okay?
It was you?
Genzo, bubbles are
coming out of her mouth!
She's a crab?
Genzo, bubbles are coming out of her mouth!
She's not a crab, she's Carmilla!
Genzo, don't you think
it's time for snacks?
Next time: "Demon Beast x Part-Time Job."