Keep up the good work.
Your words honor me, Princess Altena.
So that's Princess Buttocks, the girl who
showed the whole world her butt, huh?
They all call me Princess Buttocks
behind my back now!
And it's all because of...
Because of...
Because of that, they all call me...
Princess Altena...
Princess Buttocks!
G-Good afternoon.
You, too?
Princess Altena, the demon beasts
are causing more damage by the day.
We'd like to hold a conference
on how to deal with them...
All right.
By the way, did you find
the man I summoned?
We're still looking currently...
Find him as soon as possible.
Of course! Even if he is the hero,
to humiliate Princess Buttocks...
I mean, Princess Altena!
I'm sure you're upset,
but please be compassionate.
That's on him.
I'll find you yet, Hero!
"Demon Beast x Part-Time Job"
"Shigure"
I need to fill three more boxes today...
Delicious!
They're high-quality, so...
Yes, they are. Here you go.
Oh, no... You can't pay more?
Sorry, the economy's been bad lately.
Let's go.
Yes, sir.
There you go! Eat up! Eat up!
This is really expensive food!
Have another bowl!
Grow up big!
Let's try and take down a griffon, then!
Yeah!
To our victory, and...
Have you decided, then?
Yeah. When we're done with the quest,
I'm asking her out.
If I do, I know her dad will finally...
Yeah.
That Genzo!
We're broke but he keeps
bringing in more mouths to feed...
It's weird that he'd bring
other girls into the house.
Who does that?
Really, he's such a softie.
He's tricking you, Shigure.
You know that, right?
But I want to help him with his dream...
I want humans and demon beasts to coexist!
I want to cheer him on.
Hold it! You can't fill
your stomach with dreams.
You need to scold them hard,
or men get lazy really quick.
I love you.
Please live in the same house as me.
I want to live with you forever.
What's your answer?
Do you understand my love, Akemi?
Your name's Akemi now!
From here on out,
we'll be together forever.
Well done, Genzo!
Genzo!
Hey... You're looking lovely today...
The way your neck curves is just so hot!
Oh my, Genzo.
You know I'm too old for you.
That's not true at all!
I want to bury my face
in your belly right this instant!
Genzo!
You should be saying that stuff to Shigure.
I'm married, you know...
Your husband's a kobold, right?
I can love both you and
your husband at the same time!
Miss...
Wait! I've got over 20 kids!
Not another word.
Miss...
Miss!
What are you up to now?
Shigure!
Oh, Shigure!
Look! This is our new family member, Akemi!
Mistress... You mustn't...
No! Really!
Mistress... Good morning.
Shigure, can I have some money?
First, look at this.
My artistic talents can't depict
the mistress's incredible beauty!
So I want to hire a
talented artist to draw her.
And then we'll merchandise it!
We can share her beauty with
the whole world, and make a mint!
Shigure, look at this.
Look at her eyes, like jewels...
Akemi needs a new bed,
and only the finest of cat food...
Toss.
Wait, Akemi!
Don't go!
Shigure!
Where do you think we're going
to find the money?
Excuse me.
I'm Clause with Cluster Bank.
Today's the deadline.
Don't mind me.
Do you have the down payment
for the loan we discussed?
I forgot.
We don't have it!
With all these people, you should be able
to get the money quick if you worked.
I can't do that.
Who will look after the kids?
Me neither.
I'm not interested in working
for anyone but my mistress.
Is there a job that involves only eating?
I see.
So that loan will just have
to be off the table, then...
What?
That's a problem...
Guys, we're off to work, now!
Right now!
Why should I listen to... you...?
I said get to work!
I'll help, too!
I can't eat food without money!
Hanako! You finally...
You finally decided to work, all of you!
Okay, let's get to work!
Yeah!
Here's your order!
"Winner of Eating
Contest Gets Prize Money"
Here's your order!
"Winner of Eating Contest Gets Nothing"
Hang in there! We're almost there!
Y-Yeah...
Here's your order!
You're all so cute!
"Winner of Eating Contest
Has To Pay Normal Price"
You're fired! You're fired!
How do we have less money
than when we started?
It was the strangest thing!
At some point, they started
charging me for food!
I tried to work!
But when I went into town,
the men started asking me weird things,
like, "How much for a roll in the hay?"
Hey, is that...
I took their money and tried to leave,
and they chased me!
My boss was a jerk!
All I did was share my love
with these kids for a few hours,
and he fired me for no reason!
Right, Shingen?
Right, Genzo?
You brought home another one?
Gimmie yummy food!
Now! Food!
Shut up before I yank your
feathers off, you stupid bird!
Let me go! Stop, damn it!
You want to talk back, huh?
Shigure, calm down!
Shigure!
I feel like chicken tonight!
Shigure, calm down!
So we're at the point where we
can't afford food, let alone a pet shop.
If you're in that bad of shape,
how about this?
This is...
The demon beast killer.
The perfect job for Genzo,
the demon beast killer.
A griffon?
Yes. The guild master
recommended it personally.
Look at this!
I'd love to track it down.
Yes, let's track it down
and get the bounty!
There seems to be a
misunderstanding, maybe.
Let's ignore them, Mistress.
With this much money,
we'll be back in the black in no time!
And you can get your pet shop!
So you're going after the same quest, huh?
But we'll be the ones
to complete the quest!
Behold!
This holy sword, Durandal,
given to me by the sage of the west!
Demon beast killer, I'll kill the griffon
before you using this holy sword.
Don't you dare kill it!
Oh? Did somebody else forget a sword?
Okay, Shigure, Hanako, Carmilla!
We're off to see the griffon.
I refuse.
Why do I have to obey a human?
Go by yourself...
I'll go, Genzo!
I've never nibbled on a griffon,
and I can't wait!
Do half-dragons nibble on griffons?
Let's go!
You can hold down the fort
by yourself, Carmilla!
That's right. I want my hands on that
bounty money as soon as possible.
Um...
That's right! Let's go meet
the newest member of our family!
Hey!
Wait! I'll go with you!
There's even more weirdos with him.
Leave it to me, Mistress!
She changed her mind quick.
I'll take down that griffon for you!
Don't take it down!
Oh, no! My spine!
Carmilla, that's an amazing
bend in your spine!
By the way, what kind of
demon beast is a griffon?
You took the quest without knowing?
I knew I could love it
the minute I saw the poster!
Its personality and the other
details are secondary!
You're a weirdo.
Here you go.
Oh!
"Griffon. A dangerous beast
with A+ class combat capabilities.
Gives birth to two children at once."
You've gotten really
good at reading, Genzo.
My love for animals makes it possible!
"The griffon makes its two children fight,
and only raises the winner."
What?
It says the loser is abandoned
by its mother and dies.
Griffons are no match for me and
my burning love for the mistress.
Say that after you've stood up.
Stand up first.
This place is a danger zone where
any demon beast can be found.
I think only stupid hunters, or hunters
with a death wish, come here.
Like them?
That's them!
That's pretty...
If it weren't for this sunlight,
they'd be no match for me...
It's cloudy, though.
Oh, fine! Genzo, you can have
the glory from this quest.
Hey.
My skull! My skull is bending!
So that's a griffon, huh?
What wonderful hair,
and such sharp beaks too!
Genzo, look!
That's what the book said,
about the children fighting!
Genzo!
Okay!
Let's run, everyone!
H-Hey!
What are you doing?
What do we do, Genzo?
The bell has rung!
Now there's no need
for this kid to be hurt!
Genzo!
No, but...
She lost! So I can have her, right?
If you're just going to abandon her,
give her to me!
So that was all you wanted?
Carmilla!
I have no choice.
Mistress, forget about me and run...
Genzo, Carmilla is...
Mistress!
In big trouble!
She's done for. Let's leave her.
I'm more worried about Kyoko!
You named it already?
Who's more important,
Carmilla or a griffon you just met?
She's got no tail, no animal ears,
she doesn't pay rent... Forget her.
You meanie!
But look at her!
The dazzling eyes, the beautiful beak!
Kyoko will grow up to be beautiful!
Stop being stupid and
give her back to her parents!
I refuse!
I will raise Kyoko in a loving household!
I'm her real dad now!
You...
Very well.
Shigure!
Hold Kyoko for me.
Hanako, get Carmilla back. If you
don't think you can, give up and run.
No, I won't run!
Look!
When I look at that plump meat,
I can't control myself...
I'll hold them down, so Shigure,
take Kyoko home!
No...
I can't run by myself!
If you escape safely with her,
you can put some meat or vegetables
in our soup tonight.
Leave it to me!
I'm so tired of soup
that's just salty water.
Let's go! Come and get me!
Go, Shigure!
Right!
Genzo!
Come on!
How are you so tough?
Because... I train hard!
I was waiting for this moment!
You've got his head!
Now counterattack!
This fur is so soft!
It's like a cross between a bird's
feathers and an animal's coat!
It feels so weird!
It's great!
Now to feel up your chest!
Genzo!
How could you?!
Breast meat. Thigh meat.
Belly meat. Leg meat.
I can't hold back anymore!
I'm back!
I'm so glad you made it back safe!
I took a bite out of the griffon
and it wasn't delicious, so we ran.
I see.
What's he doing?
Carmilla comes back to life faster
if she sleeps in impure soil.
We didn't beat the griffon,
so we didn't get the reward.
But...
The food costs...
Kyoko!
You grew up so big, Kyoko!
Too big!
Her fur is the best...
But the food costs, Genzo...
Get even bigger!
Please no!
Genzo brought a new girl home.
Another! That jerk!
Weren't you going to scold him?
I think that's part of his charm, though...
This is going nowhere.
You haven't got any money, though, right?
Actually, I've been bringing in
some cash lately.
This is the magic sword, Dainsleif,
and the holy sword, Durandal!
Where did you get these
incredible rare items?
I must have good luck, because
I just find them lying around!
Here's your money for this time.
Come back soon, missy!
Sure thing!
I see. A human hero.
Yes. Our preparations are complete,
Lady Joanna.
Next time: "Animal Mask x MAO."