Hello!
I am Celes the hunter!
I'm here in search of a man named Genzo!
You're Genzo!
The demon beast killer!
Chop to the head!
My head!
Hey...
Oww! Oww!
I'm sorry! Stop it!
"First Student x Pain in the Butt"
The fight lasted five seconds.
The deciding move was
the figure-four leg lock.
You okay?
Those weird techniques Genzo uses hurt.
The more you struggle the worse it gets.
Thank... you...
So, why are you here?
If you want to do an interview
talk to the maid first.
Who are you calling a maid?
I'm not your servant, you pervert human.
Get 'em! Go! Go!
Um, so did you need something?
I'll start over. My name is Celes.
A hunter who's just come here
to the town of Cluster.
The guild master said that
Genzo is an incredibly powerful hunter
nicknamed the demon beast killer!
So it's time for round two?
Sorry!
I don't know what I said
that pissed you off but I'm sorry!
That old bearded bastard.
Next time I meet him, I think it's time
for a figure-four beard lock!
So basically, you planned to challenge
Genzo because he's famous
and raise your own profile?
No!
Genzo, please... Please
make me your student.
Student?
I have a reason I have to become strong.
Please... please!
I refuse.
I'm busy!
I'm off to go lie down in front of stray
catsso they'll step on me with their paws!
Genzo, the neighbors are complaining.
They're telling you not to lay down
in the middle of the road.
Please!
I can't do much, but I will repay you!
If you want, I can even pay with my body...
I refuse.
Come back when you're
as attractive as a kobold.
I'm less attractive than a kobold?
Please! Please!
You're in the way!
If you don't leave me alone
I'll give you a cobra twist...
You're...
Sorry to both you.
Never mind what I said
about being your student.
Wait.
Wh-What are you doing?
So you're a lizardman, huh?
That's right.
No... my ancestors were lizardmen.
We look like demon beasts,
so people are afraid of us.
In my case, my genes showed up here,
and I have a scaly stomach and back...
Celes, a lady mustn't show
any more of her stomach!
You're in the presence of a man! Behave!
Genzo will go after anyone, and his eyes
are already getting dangerous...
Hang on, guys.
I'm not like that.
All right then, Genzo.
Will you make her your student?
Of course I will.
Are you stupid?
Really?
You should rethink this, Celes.
If you want, I'll teach you
my special move, "Death Roll"...
No, he accepted me
even though I'm a lizardman.
I want Genzo to teach me!
Somebody worry about me.
Okay! We're off to
the mountains to train, then!
Oh, fine.
We'll help...
as much as we can!
Strength starts with the posterior chain!
Hands above your head and squat!
Yes, sir!
One...
Two...
Three...
Four...
Tell me, my student.
Do your lizardman genes only show
on your stomach and back?
Do your thighs and biceps
ever get covered in scales?
Only my back and stomach, yes.
Oh, I see.
Forget the squats, then.
We're moving on to core and back work!
Get to work!
Um, I've only done four squats.
Genzo...
It's obvious what you're thinking.
If you want to train your legs and core,
I can teach you better than him.
Follow me!
Okay, Shigure!
Thanks...
She's fast.
To get big, you need to eat big!
Don't be a picky eater!
Hanako! Lizardmen... aren't like lizards!
We don't eat bugs!
But I went through all
the trouble of catching it.
I'll eat it then.
You don't have to copy that.
A strong woman is beautiful!
Copy my sexy pose!
Sexy pose...
Not at all alike.
There's nothing else I can teach you.
Well done.
Thank you for everything, sir!
No female wrestler is a match for you now!
Wear this name with pride!
Your ring name is...
Celes XXL!
Yes! My name is Celes XXL!
Your first student...
No!
What?
You don't like the name Celes XXL?
Hey, Carmilla, what do you think?
I think it accurately describes
her physical attributes.
Maybe XXL is too small?
It's not the name!
This isn't what I want to be!
You're saying you prefer
to fight without a mask?
No!
I'm not trying to become one
of those weird "wrestler" things!
Um...
I should've started by asking this,
but why did you want to learn from Genzo?
It is really late to ask that question.
It's a really boring story.
I'm sure it's more fun than
listening to Carmilla brag.
Genzo, let me hit you later.
Actually...
What?!
I will bathe in your blood!
Old Man!
Hey, Guild Master!
Get your ass out here!
Or I'll start executing every
hunter here, one by one!
What's wrong?
Execution!
Sir, wait!
Calm down!
Let me go!
Hey, is that the halfbreed?
You're right! The halfbreed animalis
still hanging around, huh?
Want me to hunt her?
Execution!
Hey, grab him!
He'll destroy the guild!
Sir...
Execution! Execution!
Stop it!
Execution!
Get 'em, Genzo!
You're being too loud!
What's going on?
Hi.
Really, what's going on here?
Let's hear your explanation,
demon beast killer!
Call me that one more time
and I rip your beard off.
Now, now, Genzo. Calm down.
Really, what's wrong with you?
What's wrong with me?
Oww! Oww!
Listen up, geezer!
You know that I'm a kind man whose heart
is filled with love for
all creatures, right?
Yes, I know.
I didn't understand a word you said,
but I got the fact that you're a weirdo!
Your piece-of-shit hunters
are bullying a lizardman
but I got the fact that you're a weirdo!
And doing all kinds of
naughty things to them!
Sir, calm down!
They haven't been doing
anything naughty to me.
Just teasing me...
and kind of messing with me...
Messing with you? Messing with you?
Was it your stomach?
Did they mess with your shiny stomach?
No, I mean...
They didn't?
So you're saying that my guild's hunters
have been harassing and
upsetting Celes the lizardman?
And so Celes came to you to train, and...
I wanted to teach the
other hunters a lesson.
But I realized that I was upset over
something that didn't matter at all.
Now that my teachers have
told me I've mastered the art,
and I've attained real strength,
I don't care about it anymore.
So it's okay.
Now I want to focus on being
a wonderful person like my teacher!
Celes!
We're sorry!
I'm sorry, for calling you a halfbreed...
Our hunts haven't been going
well lately, and we've been upset.
And since you're a demihuman and
the new girl, we took it out on you.
Sorry.
I'm not having it.
Listen, Celes.
Life is a battle. Survival of the fittest.
No human can let anyone underestimate them.
Sir, I'm a lizardman.
You're my student. And a wrestler.
A wrestler must accept any challenge!
Sir, I'm a hunter.
Listen up, Celes!
Don't spoil them just because they showed
the slightest sign of apologizing to you.
A lizardman was being abused!
I'm not letting it all end on a happy note!
As your teacher, I order you to fight them!
Beat them flat until they
understand how strong you are!
What a pain...
Sir, I appreciate it, but...
I'm really fine...
If you won't do it, then
I'll execute them all.
Genzo... cares about me that much?
That's probably wrong.
You should apologize!
He's serious.
Say sorry.
Bow to the both of them
and say you're sorry again.
All right, sir.
If it's a battle until one side gives up,
instead of a duel to the death...
I'm a little curious to see how strong
I've gotten after your training.
Sounds fun...
If you insist, I'll fight you.
But I won't hold back
just because you're new!
Celes, your legs!
Use your legs more!
What?
Damn it!
Celes! Bite 'em!
Bite his soft, delicious side,
and eat his intestines!
I won't let you!
Hey, if you're going to fight, don't lose!
Show her who's boss!
Don't let your guard down! She's good!
Turn it around! Get her!
Celes, you can do it!
The thigh! Aim for the chewy thigh first!
If you lose, no dinner for you tonight!
It's rather lively today.
Oh, Clause.
What is this?
A mock battle.
It's a long story.
Okay, now finish him!
Sexy pose!
Owww!
What the hell were you thinking?
Genzo, harder! Harder!
Hey, forget Carmilla
and focus on the fight!
Celes is in trouble!
What was that?
Were you training to
learn something so dumb?
I was about to change my opinion on
lizardmen and now I just feel stupid!
No...
It's over!
Celes! His arms went up!
What?
Hooray!
You did it!
His weapon's mine now!
That was amazing!
What was that?
I admit defeat.
You're really amazing.
I underestimated lizardmen.
No, it was a wonderful match.
And that wasn't a perfect victory.
I lost both of my weapons.
So it's a tie, then?
Yes. Let's try it again sometime.
Next time, I won't lose.
Not having it!
Genzo, what's gotten into you today?
Why are you being such a pain?
Everybody had their happy ending,
so let's go home.
I refuse to accept that someone can abuse
a demihuman and then
get off with just an apology!
Genzo, you're really being a pain!
Let me go, Shigure!
I need to make an example out of them
to prevent there from being a next victim!
When we get back you can rub my ears.
Um, Genzo.
Calm down.
They've been having trouble
with their hunts lately.
I don't give a damn...
They did say that...
Lately, a beastman with
a bare chest like a barbarian
has been appearing out of nowhere...
What? A beastman?
Yes, I think it's a weretiger or something.
Whenever we catch a demon beast,
it appears out of nowhere
and runs off with our prey.
I think it had some kind of weird cape.
It appears out of nowhere and
attacks us with strange techniques...
Even if we catch our prey, they still...
I know it's not your fault. We're sorry.
I guess that's an okay explanation.
Celes, forgive them.
Okay, I'm fine with that...
We're really sorry!
Genzo, may I have a word?
No.
Was the person they were talking about...
Shigure, it's a waste of time to even ask.
No idea.
I wondered where all those new
demon beasts were coming from!
May I have a word?
A public tournament?
Yes. I was very impressed
by that mock battle.
I think people would get very excited
to see combat as a form of entertainment.
In addition to selling tickets
to the event itself,
we could sell merchandise and food.
It should turn a considerable profit.
Sounds great!
I'll do anything to help fix our budget!
If you're selling merchandise, you
should sell some stuff for the Mistress.
It'll sell out in an instant!
There'll be food, right?
I think it's a great idea.
But I want to run a pet shop...
If you appear in the fights, we'll pay you.
Won't it help you get the money
you need to open your business?
Fight money, huh?
What is this feeling of excitement?
My muscles are screaming at me to fight!
If the training my body has endured
can now help the animals...
Very well!
A wrestler accepts any challenge!
So I'm a pro wrestler
in this world now, too?
Next time: "Animal x Event."