Well, Genzo?
We made it just like you told us!
Okay, the ropes and
the mat are looking good!
I can't wait!
We get paid for this, right?
I'm all set!
Lots of people are here
to participate in the tournament!
With this many people, we'll have
more than enough for the tournament.
No, not yet!
There's something missing.
Something...
That's it!
Animals!
"Animal x Event"
We need more animal stuff!
No, you can't put animals
into a fighting tournament!
No, it's a must-have!
An absolute must-have!
There he goes again...
Couldn't we get some
beastmen to fight, then?
It'd get more people talking.
That's it!
If I can turn beastmen into wrestlers,
I'll be able to touch them all
I want during the matches!
You're thinking of something bad,
aren't you?
Absolutely not!
But do you know of any beastmen
who might participate?
Hmm...
Oh, miss!
Oh, Genzo!
Fancy seeing you here.
You're even more beautiful
than ever this morning!
Your lush coat, your beautiful tail...
I'd love to take you away right now...
Oh, you mustn't!
Don't look at me that way...
I can't betray my husband.
Your husband?
Oh, right!
Miss!
I'm on my way to your house right now.
What are you going to do?
Is he going to fight my husband
to try and steal me away?
Wait, Genzo!
Miss, I'm on my way to
your home right now!
I'm home.
Who are you?
Say something, damn it!
You can't just walk right
into my house and...
You're pretty built, huh?
No! Don't fight over me!
"Over me"?
You bastard!
I wondered why she was taking so much
time to pick nits out of her fur
and trim her nails!
You stole her from me, you philanderer!
I'm not a philanderer. I'm a wrestler.
What the hell does that mean?
Take this!
Not bad.
I'm not done yet!
Honey... Genzo...
What's this heat in my chest?
I remember it so well...
I remember!
I felt this when I was trying to make
my way in the world using only my fists.
I lost, huh?
But you can be a good wrestler.
Come fight with me.
I remembered something
I'd forgotten, thanks to you.
I'm sorry, honey.
I want to chase that light again.
Honey!
What just happened here?
Bro, it's time to go outside!
You haven't left your room in days!
It's dangerous outside...
That pervert is there.
That pervert is out there!
He's changed.
And it's because of that man!
Ever since he met him, he's been...
Don't worry!
As long as we stay away from
his house, he won't come to us!
What are you doing here?
Hey! Fluffball!
What?
Be a pro wrestler!
A pro wrestler?
Pro wrestling is
the ultimate martial art!
The ultimate entertainment!
Here, look at this flyer.
Fighting tournament?
You're telling me to fight you?
No!
No! No!
Bro!
Bro's so scared because of him...
Can I be a pro wrestler, too?
Sure.
Genzo, where were you looking
when you made that decision?
So Misha and the kobold
will be participating!
I'd like a little more...
Will this do?
Don't plant them too deep!
Orcs? Planting flowers!
If it ain't the king!
How've you been?
What are you doing?
We were trying to find something
we could do for the town!
We're going green!
Will this work?
Oh, if it isn't the king!
Hey there.
It smells like the mistress!
What are you doing?
Genzo! Shigure!
When did you get back?
Just a little!
Hell no! You freeloader!
You're no better.
Give it back! Give it back, damn it!
Nothing good will come of
leaving you home alone.
You're getting in the ring too!
What are the orcs doing here?
No idea.
I see. I never understood
what "pro wrestling" was.
But it's a type of quest, I see.
Behold the magic spear Gae Bolg,
sealed within a northern cave!
With this new weapon, I will defeat...
Don't you dare!
Things are looking good!
Oops! Somebody dropped their spear!
Okay, I'll explain what
pro wrestling is now!
Pro wrestling is the
ultimate martial art,
where wrestlers battle it out with
all their might in a square ring!
What makes it wonderful is the
dynamic combination of skills,
constant action, the friendship
between tag partners,
and connection between the
fans and the fighters...
Hey, I brought snacks!
Snacks! They look delicious!
It's just our leftovers.
I'll bring more if you want,
but you'll have to pay for those.
Okay, let's fill up our bellies!
But you'll have to pay for those.
Hero... Where could you have gone?
Princess Altena!
There you are!
What is it?
Look at this!
This technique!
How about we put the names
of our sponsors on the ring
and the fighters' clothing,
and charge a fee?
Okay! We can charge them for better
spots for their food stalls, too!
We'll be doing live sparring
today, same as the real thing.
All right!
I'll fight you.
I've got more left in me!
Another drink!
I tried to hold back, but...
I won't lose next time!
Hanako, you're strong!
You too! Your stomach looks delicious!
Mistress, if you don't wipe off
that sweat you'll catch cold.
Go change, and then
give me those clothes!
I'm not satisfied.
There's more to being
a wrestler than just fighting.
You need to follow the rules of
the sport, and keep it entertaining!
Who cares, as long as
the crowd is into it?
No, it's necessary!
Absolutely necessary!
What a pain.
Genzo!
Look at all the food!
I think Shigure set up
a stall of her own.
Let's go!
Oh, Genzo!
What's wrong?
You look tired.
I've been busy teaching
people how to wrestle,
and getting ready for the tournament...
Take this!
Knowing how to take a hit
is part of the sport!
Endure the pain! Enduring the
pain is part of the sport!
You didn't train hard enough!
Listen! This is pro wrestling!
I also wrote a script
for the announcers...
It reminded me of when I just got
started and had to do grunt work...
Sounds rough...
Shigure, are you selling any food?
We only sell merchandise.
I see.
Is it that much of a problem?
You sure do know how
to make a buck, though.
I have a lot of freeloaders to take
care of, so I need to make some cash.
Genzo! That fried dark
tiger meat looks delicious.
You're still going to eat?!
Now!
What have you got with muscles?
I've got just the thing for you...
What wonderful muscles!
This is a limited print run,
so there aren't a lot of them.
I can't afford it!
But if I don't buy it I'll regret it!
Bro, I'll defeat that pervert
and avenge you, okay?
Go!
Get 'em!
I wanted to fight, too.
You tried to eat the
kobold and got kicked out!
The orcs are trying
to win with raw power,
while the hunters want
to win with technique.
Let's ask our commentator
Hanako for her opinion.
Well, orc meat isn't very tasty, with
the exception of the shoulder meat!
I recommend just adding a little salt
so you can enjoy the natural flavor!
One, two, three!
What was that?
That was an amazing fight,
wasn't it Hanako?
Yes, but I hope the next round
of fighters will be tastier.
In the red corner, the kobold man!
His passionate blood has revived!
And in the blue corner, Celes XXL!
Back to the lizardman! The match
everyone's been waiting for!
The crowd is getting into it.
Word has been spreading
since the match started,
and we're selling lots
of same-day tickets.
It's a big success!
I'm not satisfied.
We're missing the drama and rivalries
that make pro wrestling exciting!
I never understand a word you say...
Even without that, it's very exciting!
No, it's necessary!
Rivalries and drama are
an absolute necessity!
Genzo turns into a giant pain
whenever animals or
pro wrestling is involved...
One, two, three!
Hey, that was too fast!
Celes XXL wins with a huracanrana!
What do you think?
Kobold muscles have slow reaction times,
but they're very tight and juicy!
I recommend the thigh meat!
Grind it up and make it into hamburgers!
Now, the sky has begun to
darken for some reason,
but it's time for our main event!
Is it time?
In the red corner is Vanstein Carmilla!
Something's missing!
Her beauty's going to waste!
Genzo Shibata!
It's the messenger of love and animals,
and a total weirdo!
It may look like Beauty and the Beast,
but it's actually the
beast and the beast!
So you're a man after all, Genzo!
You made me your tag partner
because I'm so attractive.
You were just so unpleasant to deal with
that nobody else would partner with you.
What?
And in the blue corner, Heat Haze!
Mr. Sandbag himself!
Misha! The tomboy catgirl herself!
I'm here for vengeance!
Get 'em, Misha!
Clause, have you taken
a liking to pro wrestling?
No, of course not.
I'll go first.
I'm taking back the title of the
guild's top fighter, demon beast killer!
Who are you calling
the demon beast killer?
Genzo!
Okay, go!
Oops! My leg slipped!
That was an accident!
Very clearly an accident!
That was absolutely deliberate!
I have no idea what
you're talking about...
What?
Looks like they're
fighting among themselves!
Now!
Right!
Hey, hey, hey!
I knew I couldn't avenge him...
One, two...
That's Gang! It's you, Gang!
Bro!
You came!
No, I...
A new combatant is about
to enter the ring!
What's your take, Hanako?
A werewolf...
Their meat is chewy and nutritious.
You can use it in a stew,
but I prefer it smoked.
On behalf of the event's sponsors,
I request a replacement.
A new challenger has entered
the ring! Wolfgang the wolfman!
Bro!
Wolfgang! Wolfgang! Wolfgang! Wolfgang!
This excitement!
Is this rivalry and drama?
Some of you may know him...
Yes, this is the man who was hit by Genzo's
giant swing, and was easily defeated!
He was traumatized!
But today, things are different!
He's overcome his past traumas!
Behold, this is a new dawn for him!
Welcome, fluffball!
Bro, together, we won't lose to anyone!
No, I...
Bring it!
I'm about to rub your fur
all over again!
Stop it!
Rub, rub, rub!
No! Stop the match!
E-Everybody's watching!
"Genzo, Carmilla
vs
Wolfgang von Cratman, Misha"
"17 Minutes 26 Seconds" "Furry Cobra Twist"
Cheers...!
Cheers!
Well done, everyone!
Eat up, and drink up!
Genzo, the event was a huge success.
Maybe not that last match...
But since we made so much,
we can pay out a lot of fight money!
Yes! We're a step closer
to our pet shop!
It kind of makes you feel warm.
So this is what Genzo wants, isn't it?
Shigure...
Yes?
Time to pay out.
What the hell is this?
The bills for repairing all the stalls
and buildings wrecked during practice,
all the alcohol Carmilla drank,
all the food Hanako ate,
the money to pay the baker for
all that bread everyone ate,
the post-game party, the fight money...
It all wiped out every cent
I earned from my stall!
We're sorry.
We're back to salty water soup
and salted potatoes tomorrow.
Yes ma'am!
The hero has been here for a while.
He's probably formed a powerful party.
He was strong in tag matches too, yeah.
We should try to strengthen
our forces to fight him.
Got any ideas?
Yes. Make the demon beasts obey us.
Demon beasts?
Animals, huh?
Next Time: "Princess x Panties."