Hey, Carmilla.
Get off your ass and start working.
I refuse. I only listen to the orders
my mistress gives me.
Even an utter moron like you
can at least take Hiroyuki for a walk.
Are you stupid? Do you really think
I can go for a walk right out in the sun?
Did you take out your brains
and replace them with muscle?
You're going to regret that.
Okay! Okay! A walk, right?
I'll do it!
Her butt...
Black panties...
Some kind of foreplay?
Wow...
Why do I have to take an animal for a walk?
Just so we're clear,
Hiroyuki is a valuable creature,
the only one of his kind in the world.
If I sold you both, I'd get
more money for him than you.
What?
This animal is worth more than me?
You will refer to him as "Mr. Hiroyuki."
Mr. Hiroyuki...
Hey, it's the lady with the black panties!
Shut up, you brats!
What? Those are soldiers
from Castle Edgardo!
What are they doing here?
"Princess x Panties"
I'm back.
Swarms of vile little children
surrounded me and insulted me...
Shigure, make me feel better!
If I get my allowance I'm sure
it'll heal the wounds in my heart!
Sure, sure.
Preserved foods aren't that bad.
They do dry out the mouth though.
Make me feel better, Mistress!
If you let me sleep with
my arms around you,
I'm sure it will heal the wounds in my...
There you are!
I've finally found you!
You're the pervert who revealed
my buttocks before the entire nobility!
Hey, who are you and
where did you come from?
You're under arrest!
Let me go!
It must be some mistake!
You know I wouldn't do that!
Yeah, right!
I've seen how you look at the mistress!
I was just looking at her horns and tail!
You spread my legs and humiliated me
just this afternoon!
It's not like you need my help
spreading your legs!
That's a pro-wrestling move
called a shaming hold...
Mistress, let's execute this criminal!
I'll tear him apart with
my claws right now!
Wait, I...
Turn yourself in.
It's okay. I'll visit
you every day in jail.
Listen to me!
Do you think I'm the kind of guy
who'd spread a girl's legs for no reason?
Nonsense! Don't tell
me you've forgotten me!
Who are you?
I mean, I know I've seen you somewhere...
I remember!
You're one of the girls from
the red-light district
who keeps trying to seduce me!
Rude! Rude! Rude!
Am I wrong?
You're the one who
summoned me to the castle?
Is she...?
You finally remembered?
That's right. I'm...
You won't be able to hug
your way out of this...
It's time for you to...
This is my way of saying...
thank you!
Look, her butt.
Her butt is exposed to the whole world.
Is she a pervert?
You...
According to my servants,
the hero destroyed a herd
of griffons with inhuman powers.
He also attacked an orc encampment
and made them all his slaves.
Not a single demon beast remains
after he's passed through.
Oh, yeah? Well I'm much more...
If you want to pass,
you'll have to pay the toll.
Ayutees, huh?
Perfect.
I'll show you my power!
Who is this guy?
You bastard...
I give up! I give up!
Did you see that, Rose?
That's the power of the other
world's Demon King!
I did see!
But what are those strange
techniques he's using?
You don't know?
You do?
It's the other world's ultimate
assassination techniques.
He can use them to defeat
an opponent far larger than he is!
You're amazing, Joanna!
You're so smart!
Look, Rose!
A cute little garm baby
has taken a liking to him.
My buttocks was exposed in public again...
I think you should apologize, don't you?
No. What she did deserves a German
suplex followed by a shaming hold,
and then a rolling cradle
around the whole town!
Genzo, who is this?
Why did she end up with her buttocks
exposed to the whole world?
That's right. I haven't
given you my name yet.
I am the princess of Edgardo,
and its high priestess.
Edgardo Latis Altena.
I have come for you, hero!
Hero?
What's she babbling about?
He's just an animal-loving pervert!
He may be a pervert,
but he's not one of those disgusting
criminals called "heroes."
What is your problem?
A hero isn't a disgusting criminal,
and this is without doubt the hero
that I summoned as high priestess.
High priestess? Yeah, right!
What kind of princess shows
the whole world her ass?
I'm not letting the whole world see
my buttocks because I want to!
Do you know how I feel?
The rest of the castle calls me
"Princess Buttocks" behind my back!
Well, do you know how it feels to have
the kids in the neighborhood call you,
"black panties girl" or
"girl with her legs spread"?
Stop it, both of you!
The neighbors will hear!
Anyway, the hero is coming with me.
And then he's going on a journey
to defeat the Demon King!
Even if I am the hero, why do I
have to fight the Demon King?
Well, the hero is the strongest human.
A murderer who slays any
demon beast he comes across.
And the Demon King is the leader
of the demon beasts.
The one who brings together
all those disgusting monsters.
So of course the hero will fight him.
Who are you calling "disgusting monsters"?
Who are you calling a "murderer"?
The Demon King...
The king of the demon beasts...
Genzo, will you defeat the Demon King?
I refuse!
So you're saying you have no intention
of fulfilling your duty as a hero?
That's right.
If the Demon King is the head of
the demon beasts, I can't fight him.
And I need to make a pet shop first!
A pet shop?
Correct.
My goal is to have the people of this town
welcome animals as part of their families,
and earn money in the process!
It's a noble line of work!
You're sending demon beasts into
the homes of the townspeople?
You've fallen so far?
But unless the current hero either dies
or goes home to his old world,
a new one may not be summoned.
I have no choice, then.
Prepare to die, hero!
This will be your last...
He's going to resist!
Grab him!
Hey, are you okay?
Those are my kingdom's finest knights!
No!
Ro...
Ro?
Rolling Cradle!
Look, a butt.
Another butt?
This is the third one today.
What's her deal?
Did she come here
just to show off her butt?
Carmilla, think before you speak, please.
All my servants have gathered here.
This should be a sufficient number.
With my power and charisma
as the ultimate wrestler,
making these animals obey me
is easier than knitting a scarf!
Knitting?
Why would the Demon King be knitting?
Doubtless the "knitting" done by
the Demon King of another world
is different than our own.
He must knit terrible garments
to defeat the hero!
You're so smart, Joanna!
Let's go!
He's strong, sure.
But why do we have to obey him?
Look. That's the daughter
of the Draculius Family.
Really?
We'd better do what she says then!
No!
Would you just give it up?
No... I need you to defeat the Demon King!
Now that you've defeated my royal guard...
I'll just have to keep asking you!
I said I'm not doing it!
I'm not giving up, okay?
Every day she comes,
flashes her butt, and leaves.
What is wrong with her?
She really is the princess, though.
Look, Carmilla.
Genzo looks lost in thought.
I've heard of this!
When men look like that,
it's because they've fallen in love!
Genzo, what's gotten into you today?
You're just sighing all the time.
Shigure, will you hear me out?
Could it be Shigure?
No, usually when you're like this,
you're about to say something stupid.
So I really don't care.
You're always so mean.
Remember when that princess came
and talked about the Demon King?
Princess...
This is clearly not going in a good
direction. Can I just go shopping?
You're really mean.
Actually, I've been thinking about
the Demon King all the time since then...
What kind of animal could they be?
Could they be fluffy? Or maybe
they've got nice slimy scales?
Just thinking about it makes me drool.
If you're that curious
about the Demon King,
why not ask at the hunter guild?
Hello!
What's up? Here to set up
another fighting tournament?
Or a quest? Demon beast ki...
Excuse us.
Genzo has questions about the Demon King.
Are you here to talk about the Demon King?
Yes, they're my next target.
If a hunter of your strength
is willing to go after them,
the guild will cooperate in any way it can!
Me, too!
If you need people, just ask!
Looks like you're finally getting serious.
Can I get in on this?
It seems the time has come to unleash
the power of the Muramasa,
this cursed blade I found in
the ancient far east!
Now, let us go slay the Demon King
together, demon beast...
Shut up!
Oh, wow! A katana fell from the sky!
Nobody else can have the Demon King!
They're mine!
Wow! To him, the Demon King
is just more prey to hunt!
He doesn't want any help, huh?
He's a hero!
He's a true hero!
Hero! Hero! Hero! Hero!
No. I'm no hero.
I'm a wrestler!
I ended up not learning a single thing
about the Demon King...
Nobody knows anything about him...
Carmilla, that girl who keeps coming
every day, who says she's a princess...
She may be real.
If she was, it would explain
Genzo's incredible strength
and Shigure's reactions.
If that's true, we can't have Genzo asking
more questions about the Demon King.
True.
Understood, Mistress. Leave it to me.
Hey, Genzo! I'll tell you what
the Demon King looks like.
What?
Carmilla!
You've seen him?
Yes. He's got wings. And three heads!
And he's super-huge.
He's super-huge!
What else?
Hmm... what if he had tentacles?
Tentacles!
And he shoots laser beams from his eyes!
And his mating call is "pepepepe."
The Demon King's amazing!
He's even got eye beams!
Um...
I'm done!
Pepepepe.
The Demon King!
He's so cool! So this is the king
of the demon beasts, huh?
Mistress, why are you slapping me?
Hero! Today's the day I finally
persuade you to do your job!
You're back?
I couldn't defeat a Demon King
that looked this cool!
What are these scribbles?
Forget that.
The court magicians have detected
a spacetime distortion...
and...
Pepepepe!
Knock it off.
I'm not hurting animals for any reason.
But...
The Demon King's armies have summoned
a Demon King from another world!
The Demon King summoned
another Demon King?
Mistress, do you suppose she's just insane?
Rude! Rude! Rude!
So basically, there's now two Demon Kings?
That's right! So you have to defeat them!
That's awesome!
I want to see the new one!
What kind of animal is it, I wonder?
So that's the orc village, huh?
You wait here!
I can handle this myself!
Who the hell are you?
Do you know Animal Mask?
Animal Mask?
You're playing dumb, huh?
He uses the same skills as Genzo?
Genzo?
That's right! Genzo Shibata!
Where is he?
Oh, dear. It seems our guest
is lacking in manners.
What do you want?
I want to defeat Genzo.
Tell me where he is!
And if I say no,
what will you do?
I don't see any demon beast hordes.
They said there were a ton of them,
so I skipped lunch.
Don't eat them!
I can smell that they
passed this way, but...
The demon beasts were lucky
they didn't run into this pervert.
Genzo!
Perfect timing!
What's wrong?
The king...
What is this?
Mr. Orc King!
I failed in my attempt to defeat him.
What happened?
A man came leading a horde of demon beasts
and demanding to know where you were.
But the king didn't tell him.
He's a true man! A man among men!
He was the one they called
the Demon King from another world!
I'm never leaving the house again.
The outside is dangerous!
It's safest indoors!
My bro turned into a shut-in!
It's just not fair!
Edgar, let's get revenge on that pervert!
Yeah... I'm not the type to take
something like this lying down.
Let's do this!
Next time: "Money x Bonds."