Hey, Izuna.
What, please?
When's the last time you
thought a game was fun?
Sorry, Izuna, but you're going to lose.
Blank doesn't lose.
This is fun!
What?
A double jump? You've gotta be kidding!
Cheater!
I-Is that...
The ability that only a few Warbeasts possess
to overcome their own physical limits...
"Blood Destruction"?
I won't lose!
Now, then...
Rule Number 10
That's not just a double jump!
That's a bug!
I can't predict what she'll do!
Beyond physical limits, huh?
So this is her real cheat, huh?
The difference between their
strengths is overwhelming.
This battle is already over.
I predicted this to a certain extent,
but I never expected all this.
I can't calculate what to do...
I told you she's going beyond
physical limits, didn't I?
So physics equations won't help you.
Brother...
At times like this, leave everything to me.
Let your brother's bluffs take care of it!
With this kind of speed,
she'll predict that I'll dodge,
and try to block both sides!
And once she decides that I won't dodge,
she'll fire down the middle!
Two shots?
No!
This is what Izuna was after?
Sora and Shiro's heartbeats
have both gone flat.
A perfect headshot.
There's no way to disguise that.
You got them, Izuna!
I won!
I did it!
What was that?
S-Sora?
Was that okay?
Can I open my eyes now?
Shiro?
Are you two there?
Looks like it worked.
Yeah.
Was that their plan?
Even if you have a sixth sense,
you didn't see that coming, right?
When Shiro bounced her shot
off of Jibril's bullet,
she wasn't aiming for you.
I was aiming below...
...at Steph, who was being
carried by one of the girls below.
What?
NPC movement is controlled by certain rules.
In other words, you can
predict where they'll be.
And NPCs don't make a sound as they walk.
Since Steph was unconscious,
you couldn't sense
her desire to attack you.
It was impossible to detect her.
And before the game,
I bound Steph with the
pledges to obey any order
that Shiro had written on
the ground, but to forget it.
"Once your love power is restored,
wait until your energy is
just about to run out and
then fire straight ahead"?
All we had to do then was
calculate the NPC's movements
and lead her there.
Impossible.
That's not calculating, that's...
"Seeing the future," right?
Is that what you're thinking, mister?
You've been monitoring our
heartbeats the whole time and
telling Izuna where we were, right?
Impossible...
They knew it, and took advantage of it?
Ultimately, there are only two
actions you can take in a game.
Advance your own strategy,
or respond to another player's strategy.
It's a question of who has the initiative.
In this case, we held the initiative
throughout the entire game.
That's all there is to it.
You thought you were making moves,
but we were controlling what you did.
It wasn't precognition;
the result was inevitable.
The weak have their own way of fighting.
We leave it to the strong to
fight each other head-on.
Now then, can we get our
declaration of victory, old man?
The winner is Elkia.
In accordance with the pledges,
the Eastern Federation turns over
all rights it owns on the continent
to the kingdom of Elkia.
Hey, Brother...
You deliberately left my shirt,
so why did you aim for my panties?
Don't ask that! You know the answer!
I couldn't let all these
people see you naked!
You're talking like it doesn't
matter if they see me naked!
Now, now, your magnificent
actions won the day, Dola-chan.
Oh, Jibril. Good work.
You did everything according
to plan. Well done.
Yes. I'll do anything you order, Master.
Now...
Now... the Eastern Federation is...
The Warbeasts are...
Izuna, it's not your fault.
The home country decided it, and I ordered it.
That's not it, is it, Izuna?
You're confused and don't know
what to do, because you had fun.
Right?
That's impossible.
So many people are going
to suffer because I lost.
But you were
smiling then, Izuna-tan.
Why?
Why did I smile?
Because I did, the Eastern
Federation will be taken over,
and so many people will...
And it's all my fault for having fun.
Don't worry.
We would've won, no matter what you thought.
Well?
How does it feel to know
that there's an enemy you can't defeat,
no matter how hard you try?
To put it mildly...
It's awesome...
Right?
Your first loss hurt,
but that's why it was fun.
Once you understand that,
you're a friend of ours.
Welcome, Izuna.
You're a gamer now.
Next time, I won't lose!
You know, you seem to have
the wrong idea about this.
Nobody's going to die,
and nobody's going to suffer.
This world is a game.
Everyone here fails to understand that.
The wisdom to predict the future,
born of Imanity's learning and experience...
Fine. I'll believe in it.
Fi, we're heading home.
There's a lot to do.
Right.
I hate baths.
I totally agree,
but right now, your objection is denied.
Master, you're really into this today.
I was so excited about
washing Izuna-tan's tail.
That tickles!
You're sure getting along well now,
especially given how pessimistic
you were after the fight.
Brother talked to Izuna-tan afterwards.
He told her why nobody will suffer
even if the Eastern Federation
is absorbed into Elkia.
What is it?
Huh?
What lies did you tell to deceive Izuna,
you bald monkey?
Lies?
I only told her the truth.
What?
Don't worry.
Even if I told you,
there's nothing you could do.
Besides...
Oh, no! Oh, no!
The Eastern Federation...
The Eastern Federation!
The Eastern Federation moved all of their
major technology and
personnel off the continent
before the game started, right?
You knew?
I'd do the same thing, obviously.
So why didn't you stop them?
We managed to take back
the continent, but now...
It's fine.
The game isn't over.
Right,
Designated Representative
of the Eastern Federation?
You guys look like you're
having a great time.
May I join you?
The shrine...
The shrine priestess?
I'm the Shrine Priestess.
Nice to meet you.
Eastern Federation Capital, Kannagari
Welcome to the land beyond the sea,
where we read poetry beneath
the light of the moon.
Shrine Priestess's Shrine
Are you sure you want to let
these bald monkeys come here?
It's fine, it's fine.
The game's over, right?
Sorry.
A golden fox girl!
Can I take a picture?
Stop it! These are VIPs from another country!
You need to be polite.
Still, you really hurt us, bald monkey.
I'm impressed by the elves.
They were faster than I thought.
The elves?
What do you mean?
If we move our engineers and
goods off of the continent,
you can't make good use of your territory.
You'll come to challenge us again.
And then you could destroy us, you thought.
Truly...
Who could have guessed you'd use your
spy to make contact with the elves,
and expose the nature of our game
to ensure that we couldn't win?
But...
I expected that.
Actually, I thought you were
Elven Garde spies yourselves.
But I didn't expect
you to get Avantheim involved.
How long have you been planning this?
I may not look it,
but I was once a member
of the Council of 18 Wings,
the Avantheim government.
I have a formidable degree of influence.
Elven Garde, Avantheim, and Elkia.
With our tricks revealed to all those nations,
we might be able to beat Imanity,
but not the elves or the Flugel.
For goodness' sake...
And that's why...
The Eastern Federation is going to
take revenge on Elkia immediately.
Shrine Priestess?
Shall I say it again?
You really hurt us, bald monkey.
Your death won't be painless.
All right.
I accept your challenge.
I'm tired of complicated schemes.
Let's settle this quickly with a coin toss.
Not good enough?
No, it's just that when I think that half my life
has been utterly destroyed
by two bald monkeys,
and now it all comes down to a coin toss...
It's hilarious.
I knew it. You're a gamer, too.
Okay, if I win, Elkia gets all of
the Eastern Federation's territory,
including the island off the continent.
If I win, the Warbeasts get
the right to self-rule,
guarantees of their rights, and a guarantee
of resources from the continent.
For all your talk of revenge,
you're more concerned about
preserving the Warbeasts?
Either way, once the elves invade, it's over.
That's all I can do.
So... even if I lose,
promise you'll take care of
Izuna and Ino, and my people.
Shrine Priestess...
I've changed my opinion of you.
Just get started.
Let's start the world's most brutal coin toss.
You can pick heads or tails as it lands.
I'll take the other.
You're sure?
Yeah.
Okay...
Aschente!
Blood Destruction?
Blood Destruction surpasses physical limits,
allowing me to grasp
all signals and movements.
At the rate it's falling,
it will hit the floor after
142 and two-thirds flips,
bounce 4 times, spin for 5.2 seconds,
and stop on tails.
I don't detect any magic usage within range.
Did they underestimate my kinetic vision?
No, that's impossible.
But...
Tails.
Wh-What is this?
A draw.
A draw?
Wow, I didn't see that coming!
What a problem.
Did we both win or did we both lose?
Which is it?
Sora, you're not fooling anybody.
Truly.
This was your goal from the start.
If we both win, that means both
of our demands are fulfilled.
In other words, you end up
under Elkia's control,
Eastern Federation                          Elkia
but your rights are assured and
you keep the right to self-rule.
Warbeasts
We can both share the continent's resources.
The Eastern Federation becomes
the Elkia Federation.
Elkia Federation
Well?
Do we both win, or do we both lose?
Which do you prefer?
Weren't you going to take over the
Eastern Federation and destroy the Warbeasts?
That's totally wrong.
Why would I destroy my animal girl paradise?
It's a race filled with ultimate
pretty animals like Izuna!
Why the hell would I want to
destroy a treasure like that?
Cute is Ultimate Justice!
Animal Ear Love
You're too passionate, Brother.
Really...
So we really were playing into
your hands the whole time.
However, even if our nations unite,
thanks to you, the elves know our secrets.
Elven Garde will declare war on us someday.
I'm sure they will.
So when they do, let's kick their asses.
You think you can do that?
I can.
Our spy actually had
her memories altered by the pledges
before she reported to Elven Garde.
So she gave them the wrong
information about your game.
So the reason you fought Kurami for
the right to alter her memories...
...was for this day.
Now, when Elven Garde attacks us,
we're sure to win.
Then we get the elves' nation, too.
You thought it through that far?
"Checkmate" doesn't mean you've
simply cornered the enemy king.
It's a declaration that the enemy king is yours.
That's why I said it the first time I met you.
"Checkmate."
So, which will it be?
Do we both win, or do we both lose?
Are you really going to
make me say it? Meanie.
We both win.
Okay, now...
Find a place to stay
Learn about this world
Get a Flugel
Take over the Eastern Federation
The Elkia Federation is born!
What are you going to do?
Don't tell me you're going
to start another great war.
If I wanted that, I would've
taken your Race Piece.
Those must never be taken, so we won't.
Yup.
Our goal has never changed.
It's simple and straightforward.
Beat Tet.
That's all.
Beat him?
He's the one true god!
Yeah? And?
Is that a problem?
You're going to try and beat a god?
You come up with the funniest ideas.
Do you think you can do it?
Dunno!
We don't have a clue about the specifics,
but we have hints.
First, why are the Race Pieces shaped like this?
Second...
Why are there sixteen races,
the Exceed, in this world?
Third...
What are those things I see on the horizon?
In other words, gathering
all the pieces is what
gives you the right to challenge God.
But doesn't that mean you
have to take our Race Pieces?
Nope.
That would go against the pledges.
The pledges?
Fourth, why put a rule into
the pledges that doesn't
Ten Pledges
1. All murder, war, and robbery is forbidden in this world.
2. All conflict in this world will be resolved through games.
3. In games, each player will bet something that they agree is of equal value.
4. As long as it doesn't violate pledge three, anything may be bet,
and any game may be played.
5. The challenged party has the right to decide the rules of the game.
have to be followed?
What do you mean?
6. Any bets made in accordance with the pledges must be upheld.
7. Conflicts between groups will be conducted by designated representatives with absolute authority.
8.  Being caught cheating during a
game is grounds for an instant loss.
9.  In the name of God, the
previous rules may never be changed.
10. Let's all have fun and play together!
Did you forget?
Pledge 10.
10. Let's all have fun and play together!
Let's all have fun and play together.
In other words,
if we're not all together, having fun,
we can't beat the game.
We don't steal each other's pieces.
Each of the races, the sixteen
races who claim to be intelligent,
must use their wisdom and wit,
their talents and resources,
to build a tower of wisdom on Disboard.
"Prove to me that you have wisdom at all."
That's great! Wonderful!
This really is getting fun.
I really was right to bring you here.
I'm waiting.
Come to me, with all the races in tow.
And then...
He sure made it sound easy, though...
Tearing apart the largest country in
the world, Elven Garde, from within.
What are you going to do?
If there's a way, I want to know it.
But we have to do it.
That's the only way for Imanity to win.
Kurami...
A way for the weak to stay weak,
but still defeat the strong.
A way to stay who you are,
but surpass your limits.
To soar through the sky,
even if you can't fly...
He's always found a way,
inside despair, suffering, and darkness.
I'm not imagining it, am I?
You've changed a little.
Have I?
Maybe I feel like I can't lose now.
So...
Will you help me?
Of course!
I'd fight the whole world for you, Kurami!
Let's do it!
Just you watch, Sora!
Well, let's get going.
Yeah.
Brother, but there's still...
Oh, I know.
Wh-What?
Is there still something you
want from the Shrine Priestess,
you bald monkey?
It's not really something we want, but...
If you're a shrine priestess,
you must have one, right?
We've been wondering.
Wh-What is this?
What power!
Divine core manifestation.
Mind meld established.
Power setting: minimal.
Why have you summoned me,
you with finite lifespans?
Exceed Rank #1, Old Deus...
Exceed Rank #1?
Old... Deus?!
Okay...
Let's begin the game!