Nagumo-kun, is there anything
you could do about this army of monsters?
Nagumo-kun,
would you please help us?
If you don't, they'll destroy the town,
and hundreds of lives will be lost!
Well, that's unexpected.
I thought you always put
your students first and foremost.
Didn't think you'd ask one of them to lay
their life on the line for a bunch of strangers.
Of course, as a teacher,
my students always come first.
But I don't want to cast aside
the many people of this world
who I've met and grown to know.
I wasn't able to help you in your time of need,
so maybe these words
don't mean much to you...
But I don't want you to live
a sad life where you cut ties
with everyone and everything!
Sensei, no matter what happens from
here on out, you'll still be my teacher, right?
Of course!
No matter what decision I make,
even if it's not what you would've wanted?
That's right,
as long as you listen to what I have
to say before you make that decision.
N... Nagumo-kun!
There's an army headed this way.
I'm gonna wanna get ready.
Nagumo-kun!
Only 'cause my teacher told me.
Nagumo-kun, how are preparations coming?
Is there anything I can help you with?
Nah, I'm good, Sensei.
They'll be here soon.
Don't frown like that, Sensei.
It's gonna be fine.
This may sound hypocritical,
given that I was the one
who put you up to this, but...
Please come back safe.
Hey, Nagumo!
What's up, Sonobe?
Um... Thanks for what you did, back then!
Back when?
You might not remember it,
but you rescued me back in the labyrinth.
I wanted to thank you for that.
Rescued you?
It was probably just a fluke.
Even if it was...
I'm not gonna waste this chance!
You gave me a chance when you
rescued me, so I'm not gonna waste it!
Okay.
I'm going, then.
Sonobe.
Don't die, all right? You've got guts.
Well, for the most part.
Thanks.
Hey.
You're not even trying to hide.
What the hell are you doing?
I simply missed my chance to emerge!
A moment of your time?
I have but one request to make of you.
Might I ask for your ear?
Could you be engaging me in
intentional neglect to arouse me?!
This is so harsh!
I never knew such an act existed!
So what do you want, you pervert?
Oh, well, you will be continuing
on your battle-frought journey, yes?
Yeah.
If so, might I join you on said journey--
Hell no.
A-An answer swifter than I had imagined!
I would not join you
without recompense, of course!
I would call you Master and
offer myself to you in body and soul!
Go back to your den. Or maybe
just die and return to the earth!
Those eyes, so piercing!
I want you to see how fiercely
I fight in this coming battle, Master!
I promise you, my performance
will be more than satisfactory!
You will surely ask me
to join you after witnessing it!
She's crazy.
But she'll be a good asset in battle.
There they are.
Right then, let's go put
the finishing touches on it.
Finishing touches?
Now's the perfect chance to make
the Goddess of Agriculture, Aiko-sensei,
even more important.
That'll help protect Aiko
and the other students.
And that'll mean you'll be protected,
too, since you're her student.
Yep.
Listen up, brave citizens of Ur!
Our victory is already guaranteed!
A goddess, summoned by the heavens
themselves, stands in our midst!
Yes, you know her well--
The Goddess of Plenty, Lady Aiko!
As long as she stands
by our side, we cannot fall!
Wh-Wh-Wh-What are you doing?!
I am Lady Aiko's sword and shield.
She has asked me to protect you,
and I have come to heed
her command to the letter!
Witness me!
Glory to Lady Aiko!
Lady Aiko!
This is the power of the Goddess's blade,
enlightened by Lady Aiko herself!
It's my turn, now.
I'm getting pumped up!
I know full well he said this was a
mana reserve made with a Holy Crystal...
But if only he could tell me the truth!
How bold, proposing to me just before battle...
Hey.
I'm lending that to you, so you
better give it back when we're done!
Oh, no, perish the thought!
Use all those dragon powers
of yours to drain that reserve dry!
You can most certainly count on me, Master!
Take 'em out all at once!
What ecstasy!
I feel the love Master harbors for me!
Blow, tempest winds; rage, torrential flame!
Flame Tempest!
Lady Aiko!
Who's next?! Who's next!
Seems this is where I must stop.
The engagement ring!
Not bad work, for a creepy perv.
Take a nap and let me handle the rest.
I'm outta bullets.
Yue, how much mana you got left?
About two Mana Stone's worth!
Gravitic magic uses
much more than I thought.
That's fine. Use what you've
got left on the big ones.
Mm-hmm. Reward me later!
Let's go, Shea!
Aye aye, sir!
Lightning Wyrm!
Shea! Can you tell the difference
between these guys?
Some are being controlled like Tio was,
and others are totally useless, yeah?
That's right.
Most likely one of them's
leading all the brainwashed ones!
If we take him out, that'll be it!
I get it! Then they'll be
totally lost and confused!
Take this!
Sorry, man.
You picked the wrong guy to mess with.
He's gotta be some demon...
Will you tell me why you went and did this?
I just wanted to show you how great I was!
I see...
But, Shimizu-kun, I still don't understand.
How would this show us you were great?
Someone would see I was great.
The demons!
I went north into the mountains
to capture a monster.
That's when I met a demon.
They understood. They knew how great I was.
So I made a contract with them.
A contract? To do what?
A contract...
...to kill you, Hatayama-sensei!
You're more of a nuisance than the heroes.
You can't be left to your own devices,
Goddess of Plenty.
If I kill you, the demons
will hail me as a hero.
Shimizu-kun!
But what the hell?!
I had 60,000 troops, and they lost!
Why the hell do you
have such powerful weapons?!
Just what... what the hell are you?!
I understand that you want to be special.
It's not wrong to feel that way.
It's only natural.
But you can't join up with the demons.
Shut up! Why shouldn't I join up
with the side who'll treat me better?!
Because it's wrong.
I won't let anyone use
your pure-hearted intentions for evil!
You're my student!
I don't get you...
Shimizu, why don't we start things over?
I'll be rooting for you the whole way.
I'm so glad you understand.
Sensei?!
Don't move!
I'll stab her neck!
Listen up, this needle's coated
in monster poison!
Drop your weapons and put your hands up!
S... Shimizu-kun, please, listen to...
Shut up! Shut your mouth, you hypocrite!
Just keep quiet
so I can get the hell out of here!
Hey, you!
I'm talkin' to you, edgelord!
Don't look behind you!
You keep messing around,
and I will seriously murder her!
You think you can do it, huh?
Don't insult me!
So, what did you want?
Gimme your gun,
and all your other weapons!
Yeah, figured you'd ask that.
Shut up and hand 'em over!
Yeah, not happening.
Besides, when you bring
Sensei back to the demons,
they're just gonna kill her, right?
So what'd be the point
in giving you all my stuff?
Just shut up and give 'em to me!
Look out!
Shea!
H-Help your Sensei first...
The needle got her...
This looks pretty bad.
Okay, fine.
Sensei?
Hey, Sensei!
She's all right.
I-I don't wanna die!
H-Help me!
This wasn't supposed to happen.
It can't be... happening...
Shimizu-kun!
Oh, no...
Nagumo-kun, give him that medicine!
After he literally just tried to kill you?
I promised that no matter what happened,
I'd be there for my students!
Please, you have to!
Shimizu... answer me this.
Are you my enemy?
I-I'm not!
I'll swear loyalty to you!
I'll do anything, so please, let me live...
No!
Why?
'Cause he's my enemy.
No! Shimizu-kun was...
Was gonna turn over a new leaf?
Sorry, but I'm not that
much of a bleeding heart.
I don't believe that crap.
So why did you have to kill him?!
That's right, I killed your precious student.
I thought over what you said, Sensei,
but it doesn't change
my stance on enemies.
I won't show any mercy.
Nagumo-kun...
You want a reason?
I said it before. He was our enemy.
That's not a reason.
Had you done nothing, he would
have died within a matter of minutes.
Surprised you're keeping
that close of an eye on things.
Hajime, you're so nice to Aiko.
That attack was meant
to kill your Sensei, right?
Now she won't think that
a student died because of her.
It would've broken her heart,
but now, she can still be the same
great teacher she always was.
Aiko will realize what you did.
She's a teacher whose words
still live within your heart.
"Good morning," "Good night,"
all those simple things
are so dreamlike and beloved to me
Because I finally met you
Everything is so special, thank you again
I didn't think I'd be lonely all by myself
That is, until you found me
I wasn't afraid of anything
That is, until I thought of a world without you
Can you believe it?
I miss you, I'm so fond of you
I love you, don't forget it
Shine bright like the first star in the night
and stay closer to me than anyone else
I'll never let you go
I'll never let go of that hand
Stay by my side and shine
ARIFURETA: From Commonplace
to World's Strongest.