My, isn't that something.
She was wanderin' about
on her own in the western seas.
Hell of a good job there, mates.
A merfolk child...
We'll get a good price for her.
Right then, let's get ready for the auction.
Yessir!
Mama...
Pray forgive me, Ilwer!
I've burdened you greatly...
Don't be ridiculous.
I'm just glad you're home safe.
I didn't think you'd make it back alive.
He just got lucky, that's all.
Forget him, though.
I'm gonna need one more status plate.
You got it.
You're sure it was all right for me
to receive a gold top-rank status plate?
Mm-hm. Of course.
Oh, I got it!
You promised, Hajime-san!
You're so mean!
You promised me that if I worked real hard,
you'd show me all the touristy places in Fuhren!
Hajime-san?
I heard this city was
a great center of commerce,
but it seems there is more to the city than that.
Meh, no matter who might
come after us, I'll kill 'em.
No matter who, you say?
Yeah. They could be a god for all I care.
Our true enemy, God himself,
is powerful and wise.
But he is not invincible.
And there will come an age where he can
no longer continue with his dark machinations.
One day, there will come a being
possessing the ability to defeat him,
dear Tio.
All right, Father!
Live on.
Tio, you've come!
Yes, Elder.
I felt a strange thrumming in my chest.
Has something happened out on the continent?
It seems God has summoned forth alien beings.
And many of them, too.
I will go.
This anomaly will surely have
great effects upon our world.
Something within me tells me so.
Dear leader, beloved brethren.
I know not what awaits me,
nor what may happen.
But I feel as if everything is soon to change...
And it feels good!
When were you planning on waking up?
We're going shopping.
It's perfect weather for a date!
Look where you're going,
or you'll trip and fall.
Hajime-san, Hajime-san!
Let's go over there!
An aquarium?
Dang, a monster that can talk?
Its name is... Lehman.
So you can talk, huh?
We've never met, right?
Introduce yourself, then.
I'm Hajime. What the hell are you, Lehman?
If I asked you what a human was,
how would you respond?
Very well, if I must answer, then I am me.
No more, no less.
I have a question of my own.
How is it that you can sense
the presence of monsters?
Probably because I've eaten monsters.
Look, this fish is so cute!
Oh, wow, you're right.
You're gonna make me cry.
The goings got so tough
that you had to eat monsters...
Despite all that, you've turned out all right.
Uh...
Hajime-san, we're supposed to be on a date,
but all you're doing is talking
to this old man monster!
Whoa, I'm gettin' in the way of your date?
Sorry about that, Hajime, my boy.
Leh-san, it's time for us to depart.
One last question. Why are you even here?
Well, I was off on my own on a journey,
but I ended up swimming
into an underground current,
which brought me up to the surface.
What's wrong?
L... Leh-san, so, uh...
Do you wanna get outta here?
Thanks, my dude.
D-Don't mention it, Leh-san.
You know, when I was brought in here,
I remember there being
a little merfolk girl, too.
Poor thing. Seemed like she
was bein' bought and sold, too.
There's a huge gang of slavers in this city.
You'd better watch out, 'specially you, cutie.
I'll be all right. I hope you will be, too.
Thank you! Farewell!
Yue, surely you're not happy about this?
You mean him and Shea?
Indeed. In recent days, it seems there have
been some developments between them.
I'd be happy to hear that.
You would be happy that another woman
is growing close to the man you love?
She's not just another woman. She's Shea.
You sure are pigging out.
Is it really that good?
Yes! Oh, Hajime-san!
I was just wondering, were you
really okay with having Tio-san join us?
Joining us? She just took advantage of
the confusion back there and followed after us.
Do you not like her?
Huh? Eh, she's not a bad person, just a pervert.
How about you?
I like her a lot, even though she's a pervert.
What's wrong?
Oh, my Sense Presence caught on someone.
It sensed someone?
But we're surrounded by people.
I sensed them from down below.
Below?
In the sewers?
They were really small and weak.
It must be a kid.
Huh?
Here's your change. Thank you kindly.
At first, she was always clinging to Hajime,
and her ulterior motives were
obvious to the point of annoyance.
But after knowing her for a bit,
I understood something.
What, exactly?
She always gives everything her all.
She'll work hard for the things
she treasures, for the people she loves.
Good or bad, she faces it head-on.
Shea likes me, too,
just as much as she likes Hajime.
She doesn't like me in the same way,
but she likes me the same amount.
Isn't she cute?
Hajime-san, is she...
She's breathing.
What?! She got away?!
I'm sorry!
Do you know how much she'll sell for?!
Go find her, quickly!
Yes, sir!
She's one of the merfolk.
They live all the way in the western seas.
Why is one all the way out here?
And because they're
so beneficial to the kingdom,
they're the only race of
beastmen that are protected.
Well, it's obvious something
bad's brought her here.
What's your name?
Myu.
Myu? I'm Hajime. That's Shea.
Here.
Yummy?
Uh-huh!
All clean now?
Wow, Hajime-san, you're
pretty good at taking care of people.
Where's this coming from?
So let's talk about where to go from here.
We need to figure out
what we're doing with Myu-chan.
Yeah.
Here you go, miss.
I see, so Shea needs both you and my master.
But what of my master, then?
Do you not think she will
steal his heart from you?
You must see how incredibly charming she is.
I want Hajime to find
more things he can treasure.
But I'm the only one who's special.
If she thinks she can steal him,
then she can very well try.
Do you think you could?
Well, I certainly don't
want to pick a fight with you.
As long as he continues
to abuse me, I am very happy.
You pervert.
I see, you got separated
from your mother, and then...
Yeah.
Must be that gang of slavers
Leh-san was talking about.
Must mean they're running some kind of
black market auction or something to sell her off.
Selling a little girl as a slave...
Sounds like there's a whole lot
of shitheads hiding out in this city.
So what are we going to do with Myu?
Normal thing to do would be
to leave her with the city guard.
That's what you're supposed
to do when you find a lost kid.
Sure, but...
Myu's merfolk. I'm sure
they'll take good care of her.
Got it, Myu?
We're gonna take you to
some people who'll keep you safe.
They'll help you get home.
What about you, big bro?
Sorry, but this is where we part.
No!
Yes, I know, but--
I wanna be with you! I like you two!
Big bro...
Do you hate me?
What was that?!
Isn't that...
Hajime-san!
If you don't want the merkid to die,
bring us the white-haired bunny girl.
Hajime-san, I'm going to find her!
I'm going, too.
They're my enemies now, after all.
What a wonderful time this has been.
I thought I sensed you two.
Huh? Yue-san and Tio-san?
What are you doing here?
I could ask the same of you.
This is a bit much for a date, don't you think?
Master, have you become
embroiled in some sort of trouble?
We saved a little merfolk girl
from a bunch of slave traders,
but they took her away again.
Where is she now?
I can't find anyone who knows.
We were just torturing the information
about their hideout out of one of them.
So we figured we'd make
an example out of these guys
and take out all the gangs
involved in this business!
Will you help us?
Seems he's found
something else he finds important.
If it is your wish, Master, I cannot deny it.
I'll help.
All right, let's split into
two groups and search for Myu.
I'll go with Yue. Shea, you're with Tio.
Where the hell are they?!
Boss!
The hell are you doing?! Go find 'em!
Yessir!
You don't need to look very hard!
We're right here!
A trade that victimizes innocent children...
I must admit, I'm rather perturbed!
Reflect on your wrongdoings in hell!
Do you hate me?
Go on, cry! Scream!
If you can't do that,
then put on a little show for them!
Don't you dare give me trouble,
you useless idiot!
I should be saying those
exact same words to you, asshole.
You?!
You bastard...
Hey, Myu.
How are you always soaking
wet every time I find you?
Big bro!
Myu, close your eyes for a sec, okay?
Okay!
You can open them, Myu.
Wow! We're flying!
We're not really flying, but...
Anyway, you're gonna get
to see some real nice fireworks.
Fireworks?
You ready? Say "boom"!
Boom!
Well? Surprised? Those are fireworks.
Fireworks are scary.
Something came out of it!
Yeah, we're gonna destroy their hideout.
Her name's Yue. She's my lover.
No fair. She's so cute.
You did such a good job, Myu. Good girl.
What's this? Did you do something
mean to Myu-chan, Hajime-san?
Please, you think I could bully her?
If you want to bully someone, bully me!
Shut it, you perv.
Oh, that's our pervert--I mean Tio.
Thank you so much, big bro!
S-Sure. Look, could you
stop calling me "big bro"?
Just call me Hajime.
Okay, then you're Papa!
Wait, don't tell me, that's how merfolk say
"big bro" or "Hajime" in their language?
Nope! Papa means Papa!
Why "Papa"?
Because I don't have a Papa!
So big bro can be my Papa!
Please, can you not call me Papa?
I know I look older,
but I'm still only 17!
No, you're Papa!
Fine, you can call me "big bro"!
I won't complain anymore,
so just stop calling me Papa!
No! You're my Papa, Papa!
Hajime, I want a baby.
Me, too!
Master, I, too, am fully prepared.
Let us engage in procreat--
Save the jokes for when
you're looking in the mirror.
Why are you only admonishing me?!
"Good morning," "Good night,"
all those simple things
are so dreamlike and beloved to me
Because I finally met you
Everything is so special, thank you again
I didn't think I'd be lonely all by myself
That is, until you found me
I wasn't afraid of anything
That is, until I thought of a world without you
Can you believe it?
I miss you, I'm so fond of you
I love you, don't forget it
Shine bright like the first star in the night
and stay closer to me than anyone else
I'll never let you go
I'll never let go of that hand
Stay by my side and shine
ARIFURETA: From Commonplace
to World's Strongest.