Take the lead, Endo!
I haven't seen this part of the labyrinth!
G-Got it!
He one-shot that Behemoth...
There's no shortcut?
We must hurry to them by any means possible!
Here, huh?
Hold up, Endo.
What's up?
Found us a shortcut.
Huh?
What's that?
My Pile Bunker.
It's a pile driver
that utilizes the immense force created by
electromagnetic acceleration and explosives.
A pile driver?
Yeah. These long rods are made
from ore compressed with Transmute,
then coated with azantium,
the strongest metal in the world.
Endo.
I'm going on ahead. Follow in after us.
A hole?!
N-Nagumo?!
Oh, come on!
You two're still good friends, huh?
Hajime-kun!
Wait, Nagumo-kun?
Wait, what?! What's going on?!
No, really?! Is that really you, Nagumo-kun?!
Wait, what? What's going on?!
Calm down, Yaegashi.
You're supposed to be the cool
and collected one, remember?
Guys! I-I brought help!
Endo!
Yue, keep Endo and the others safe.
Mm.
Shea, go check out the fallen knights.
You got it!
Tio and Myu, take care of these guys.
Understood.
Okey dokey!
Okay, then...
Hajime-kun!
I'll be fine, you stay there.
Pray let us handle this.
Yeah, pray!
Never expected someone to come
down to hell on their own volition.
If you don't feel like dying,
then get the hell outta here.
What?!
That means if you leave now, I'll let you go.
Insolent human! You'll regret your
foolishness when you die by my hand!
Well, okay. That means you're my enemy, yeah?
Hajime-kun!
Hey, so, what kind of half-assed magic is this?
This is barely street magician level.
No way...
H-How did you know?!
Take this!
Damn it all!
H-Heal me!
What?!
He targeted the healer!
Looks like you're the one
who decided to take a trip to Hell today.
Who the hell is he?
I know it's hard to believe, but that's Nagumo.
What?
Huh?
L-Like I said, that's Nagumo!
The same Hajime Nagumo
who fell from the bridge that day!
Nagumo?!
I don't believe it!
I mean, he looks way different,
so I can get your reaction.
N-No way!
Nagumo died! You're just
making shit up for no reason!
I saw his status plate!
There's no doubt about it, it's him!
He must've forged it or something!
That's right, he's gotta
be plotting something bad!
Calm down.
Are you going to get in Hajime's way again?
Here it comes!
Hey, Taniguchi!
Suzu?!
I-I'm gonna...
Protect you!
It's okay.
Dark Firmament.
Gotcha!
I can't...
...believe you lot...
Yaegashi, take this!
Sorry!
It's so light, but it sliced
through like it was nothing...
Who are you?
That all you got?
Crashing Gaol!
Nagumo-kun!
Nagumo!
Papa!
Pa...?
So this is checkmate, then?
That's right.
My high-level magic meant nothing to you.
Are you sure you're human?
No, actually, I'm not.
You monster.
That hurts, Kaori!
She said Papa, didn't she?!
Kaori?!
Right, then. I'm not interested
in hearing your last words or anything.
What I want to know...
...is how a demon got their hands on those
monsters, and what you were doing down here.
You gonna tell me?
You think I'm going to talk?
Well, let me tell you what I think.
I think those monsters were
created by a form of ancient magic.
And demonkind gained the ability to use
that ancient magic by clearing a great labyrinth.
You came here to explore the pits of the hell,
or rather, get to the end
of the great labyrinth, yeah?
I see. If you're anything like them,
then your monstrous appearance
and inhuman strength checks out.
Like "them," huh?
So the monsters were a gift from the guy
who actually cleared the labyrinth, then.
Well, that answers my questions.
That's it, right? Then end me.
Fine.
But remember this. One day,
my lover will find you and kill you.
I don't care who comes for me.
Demon or god, I'll kill them.
But anyone who's just being puppeteered
by that god won't be able to touch me.
Stop, Nagumo! She can't fight us anymore!
You don't need to--
Nagumo!
Shea, how's Meld doing?
If we'd been one second too late,
we wouldn't have been able to save him.
We used the Holy Water just like you said,
but are you sure it was
okay to waste it? It's so rare.
Yeah, he's been a big help.
I don't want him dying on me.
Hajime.
Yue! Thanks a lot for taking care of that.
Mm-hmm!
Hey!
C'mon you guys, read the room!
Everyone's coming over here!
What happened to Meld-san?
That wound looked fatal...
He's fine. We healed him up.
Thank god... I thought he was done for.
I'm just so glad you're alive, Hajime-kun.
Thank you...
I'm so sorry I couldn't protect you back then...
I must've really had you worried.
But I survived and made it back,
so no need to apologize to me.
So, uh...
Don't cry, okay?
Hajime-kun!
Hug her already, c'mon!
Is he...
I see. It's been a while since he's ignored me.
Hey, Nagumo! Why'd you kill her?
She wasn't even resisting anymore!
God, you're persistent.
Amanogawa, you're not mad
about me killing her, are you?
You're mad at yourself
for not being able to kill her...
...and pretending you've got
a better reason for being pissed.
Wha-- No! I'm just saying what
anyone else would be saying!
It's kill or be killed in this world.
You've got to kill your enemies.
What's wrong with that?
You murdered her! Of course it's wrong!
I don't show mercy. I always kill.
If you're gonna stand in my way
and say you don't like that, well...
I don't care if we used to be classmates.
I won't hesitate to kill you.
Y-You...
Don't get me wrong, okay?
I don't think we're friends or comrades.
I came here because I owed Shirasaki.
Once I'm gone, it's goodbye.
Nagumo-kun's changed.
You think so?
Papa, Myu's hungry!
Okay, then let's go find us
something yummy to eat, yeah?
Papa!
Yo, what the hell?!
Oh, uh, my apologies.
We gathered a force to help the trapped heroes,
but we never thought you'd return so quickly.
And we had to believe the contents
of Ilwer's letter were true, to...
Oh, boy...
The heroes have returned unscathed! Dismissed!
This is who Hajime-kun is now...
Did he really change?
Okay.
Kaori?
Shizuku-chan, I'm going to do it.
Huh?
You got this.
Hajime-kun.
Will you let me come with you, Hajime-kun?
No--I'm coming with you, Hajime-kun.
Huh?
You don't have what it takes.
What it takes?
Are you talking about how
much I care for Hajime-kun?
I won't let anyone beat me there.
I sense imminent battle.
I love you.
Shirasaki...
I've got feelings for another girl.
I can't reciprocate yours.
It's Yue-san, isn't it?
Yeah, so...
So can I still stay by your side?
I'll make you see me that way, I swear.
After all, I'm not going to let
anyone love you more than I do.
Come with us.
I'll show you why I stand far above you, girl.
Don't call me "girl," call me "Kaori."
You can call me Yue.
I accept your challenge, Kaori.
Don't cry when you lose, okay?
Are my eyes okay?
Because it looks like there are dark clouds
and a lightning dragon behind Yue-san.
And I see a big white face behind miss Kaori!
Look at the two of them...
This will be quite the interesting journey.
I've been wondering about this,
but what's this "Papa" business about?!
Is that really your kid, Hajime-kun?!
Shirasaki--
Who's her mother?!
Yue, Shea-san, or that pervert?!
Tell me, Hajime-kun!
Kaori, calm down!
Don't tell me there are more!
How many women did you knock up?!
Am I gonna be okay?
We'll be okay.
We're the strongest!
Shirasaki!
We leave early tomorrow morning!
Don't be late.
"Good morning," "Good night,"
all those simple things
are so dreamlike and beloved to me
Because I finally met you
Nagumo-kun.
Everything is so special, thank you again
Thanks for this.
You can have it. You've been a big help.
Thanks.
It's made from the world's strongest metal,
made stronger by condensing it.
I didn't think I'd be lonely all by myself
You're not gonna find anything
tougher or sharper, I guarantee that.
That is, until you found me
Wow. You're incredible, Nagumo-kun.
I thought you couldn't fight at all,
I wasn't afraid of anything
but you've used your Synergist
skills to do stuff like this...
I'm sure I'll be using it so much,
it'll almost become part of me.
That is, until I thought of a world without you
Can you believe it?
I miss you, I'm so fond of you
She's the last boss!
Huh? Shizuku-chan?
Huh? What?! What are you two doing here?!
I love you, don't forget it
I'm just thanking her!
Why're you looking at me like that?!
Seriously, why?!
Shine bright like the first star in the night
and stay closer to me than anyone else
Kaori!
I'll never let you go
You're not going to say anything?
I'll never let go of that hand
What do you want me to say?
How long have you known?
Stay by my side and shine
For a long, long time.
Kaori's always held a candle for him.
I had no idea.
You're not going anywhere, are you, Shizuku?
Who knows?
Shizuku-chan...
Good luck, Kaorin! I'll always be on your side!
Take care!
Thanks, Suzu-chan, Eri-chan.
Off you go, now. Go to Nagumo-kun.
Shizuku-chan...
Whoa, what is that?!
I've never seen anything like it before!
I-Is that a car?
Um, Hajime-kun,
why are we all sitting like this?
This is how it always is!
Yue-san always gets to sit next to him,
but one day, I'm gonna sit there, I swear!
Tio-san, you're really all right
with this arrangement?
I can't say I'm all right...
To be honest, this sort of treatment is what
really gets me all hot and bothered inside!
You really are a pervert, huh.
Sexy neglecting!
Myu, where the hell
did you learn that word?!
Papa, I'm hungry!
I'm hungry, too!
Myself as well.
I swear...
Watch where you're going!
Me, too.
Wait, what? Why did she just lick her lips?!
I'm going to find my way home
and take Yue and the others with me.
Anyone who gets in the way
of that is my enemy.
And if they're my enemy, I'll kill them.
Even if they happen to be a god.