Damn, this is pretty impressive.
Could this be...
...the Maverick's lair?
If it is, then hell yeah.
Means we've finally reached our goal.
Crap!
Whoa, hey!
Look how big that is!
This has gotta be the final boss.
Don't worry.
We won't lose!
Yeah, we won't lose!
Glacial Sleet!
The white one heals it!
That means...
...we take that one out first!
Yue!
Crimson Javelin!
The yellow one defends, huh?
One heals, one attacks, one defends.
This thing's pretty well-balanced!
Take this!
Imperial Cannon!
Huh?
What?
It's me...
Hajime?
No!
Yue! You bastard!
No, you don't!
Hey, Yue!
Snap out of it!
Hajime?
Yep, it's me!
You okay?
Thank goodness,
I thought I'd been abandoned again...
I thought I'd be alone in the dark again...
Listen, we're gonna kill that thing and survive.
Then we're going to
the surface and going home.
Together.
Mm-hm!
Right, how do we take it out?
Yue, I'm gonna use Schlagen.
I can only fire one shot at
a time, so cover me, okay?
You got it!
Crimson Javelin! Force Lasher! Glacial Sleet!
That won't work again!
Using a debuff to try to make
me freak out? That's pretty intense.
But not for me!
I'll take 'em out all at once!
Heavenly Blaze!
Hajime!
Hajime...?
Hajime?
Hajime!
Hang in there, Hajime!
Drink, Hajime!
Hajime!
Heal, quickly!
This time, I'll save you!
I can't stop... I can't stop!
Please hit!
I'm going... to save...
Hajime...
Yue's crying...
Hajime... I'm sorry!
Huh?
Don't cry, Yue.
You've won.
Hajime!
So damn slow...
Hajime, run!
Don't worry.
His attacks are so damn slow to me.
They're not slower, you just got faster!
Yue, suck my blood.
I need your magic to help me.
Let's do this, Yue! We're gonna win!
What am I doing?
How long am I gonna lie here and take it?!
Do I really wanna lose
my beloved partner here?
To that crappy monster?
My beloved...
I'll kill you!
In that moment, something stirred within me.
"Air Walk [+Blink]"
Yue, when I give the signal, cast Azure Blaze.
Focus on healing until then.
Mm-hm. What about you?
I'm gonna go get set up!
Hajime!
Yeah, leave it to me!
This is for messing with Yue! Take this!
Transmute!
Yue!
Azure Blaze!
Hajime!
Yeah, that's about all I got...
You did a great job.
Yeah, so did you.
What is the meaning of this?!
You're forcing students to fight,
even when they don't want to?!
They just saw one of their friends die!
They need time to heal
from their grief and terror!
This loss was unfortunate, indeed.
If that's what you really feel,
then you need to stop this, right now!
If you don't, I won't
help on the farms anymore!
Then let me propose this.
I promise that those who do not wish
to fight will not be forced to do so.
Thank you.
Lady Aiko, your job class,
Farmer, is incredibly important.
We humbly ask that you use your abilities
to continue cultivating our farming efforts.
Excuse me.
Nagumo-kun, class...
I should have done this much earlier!
But your Sensei won't be
swept away ever again!
Kaori!
I'm okay.
Don't push yourself too hard, okay?
Thanks, Shizuku-chan.
Kaori, I love how kind you are,
but we can't let the death of
our classmate hold us back forever!
C'mon, Kouki!
Quiet, Shizuku, please!
Kaori, we have to move forward!
I'm sure Nagumo would've wanted us to move--
Kaori-chan, I'm here for you, so just let me
know if there's anything I can do for you!
That's right! You can count on your
friend Suzu to be your ally, Kaorin!
Right. Thanks, Eri-chan, Suzu-chan.
Break's over!
Time to move forward!
"Good morning," "Good night,"
all those simple things
are so dreamlike and beloved to me
Because I finally met you
Everything is so special, thank you again
I didn't think I'd be lonely all by myself
That is, until you found me
I wasn't afraid of anything
That is, until I thought of a world without you
Can you believe it?
I miss you, I'm so fond of you
I love you, don't forget it
Shine bright like the first star in the night
and stay closer to me than anyone else
I'll never let you go
I'll never let go of that hand
Stay by my side and shine
ARIFURETA: From Commonplace
to World's Strongest