This is supposed to be a labyrinth.
Why's there a bed here?
Wha--?!
Hajime...
Yue! Wake up, Yue!
Get the hell up already,
you sexy blood-sucking space cadet!
Hajime?
Yeah, it's me, sleepyhead.
Wake up--
Hajime!
Sorry. Looks like I had you worried to death.
What is this place?
The Maverick's lair.
Is it really?
So, what happened after all that?
After that...
The door opened, and we found this place.
Then, I put you on the bed...
It looked like the Holy Water
was starting to work,
and I had used my powers to their limits...
Thanks for all the help. I owe you one.
So...
Why am I naked?
You were dirty, so I helped clean you up.
Why are you licking your lips?
What's that laugh for?!
What'd you do to me?!
And stop licking your lips!
Where'd you find all these clothes?
Was the Maverick a guy, then?
I found more than just clothes.
Sounds like we've gotta
start searching the place.
What're you after there, Yue?
Nothing fits me.
Uh-huh.
The sun? No, it couldn't be.
At nighttime, it turns into the night sky.
Huh.
That's a pretty big house.
I looked around a bit and found
a lot of rooms I couldn't get into.
Stay alert, all right, Yue?
Mm-hmm.
It's an actual bath!
Man, how many months has
it been since I've taken a bath?
Want to get in together?
I'd rather take a long one by myself.
The library and workshop on the
second floor are both sealed off, huh?
Let's see the third floor.
Yeah.
Looks like this is the only room up here.
Almost like he was waiting for someone.
Yeah.
This room's gotta be the key
to finding a route to the surface.
My Transmute ability wouldn't
even work on those sealed rooms...
Yue, help me out if this goes south.
Mm. Be careful.
My name is Oscar Orcus.
I am the man who built this labyrinth.
You've done well to survive
my trials and make it here.
The term "Maverick"
should be familiar to you, yes?
So you're him...
Sorry, but you'll have to hold off on questions.
This is just a recording, after all.
Unfortunately, I can't answer your questions.
I just wanted to leave a message
for the person who made it here,
to share the reasons why someone who knew
the truth of this world chose to fight against it.
This is the 65th floor...
Yeah, we're down to the
deepest floor anyone's made it to.
Indeed. I was worried how
things would turn out at first,
but everyone's gotten so strong.
I was really surprised.
You're one to talk--you've
leveled up quite a bit, Shizuku.
Not as much as Mister Hero, here.
Focus, now!
This map only shows part of this level.
We've no idea what will happen.
Right!
Wait!
N-No...
That monster again?!
I thought it died!
Behemoth...
Nobody knows the respawn rate
of monsters here in the labyrinth...
...but it is normal for some monsters
to respawn after being defeated.
Here he comes! Don't forget
to secure an escape route!
Meld-san, we're not
the same as we were before!
We're hundreds of times stronger!
We won't lose again!
We're going to win this one!
That's right! Doesn't feel right
for us to keep up this losing streak!
Time for a rematch!
Comrades...
We won't let you take another one of us.
We're going to press past you
and keep moving forward!
Soar to the heavens with
the speed of a thousand wings--
Heavenly Flash!
We got this!
Shizuku, take the left!
Hiyama and the others, go behind it!
Meld-san, take the right!
Rear guard, prepare the
magic circle, a high-level one!
Direct, unwavering orders--excellent!
I don't think so!
I have the raging power to rend the earth!
Herculean Strength!
Now, hurry!
Crumble to ash, to splinters, to dust!
Overpower!
Still tough as ever, isn't he?!
Let me handle it!
Let this supreme strike slice through all!
Obliterate!
Let this gentle light envelop you--
Gentle Halo!
Luminous Burst!
O heavenly blessing, lend them your strength!
Divine Recovery!
He can still do that,
even with his horns broken...
Everyone, get ready to attack!
Huh?!
Enemies of God mayst
not tread upon His holy ground!
Herem!
I'm not gonna let you win!
Blessing of heaven,
reveal your secrets--Divine Strength!
Thanks, Kaorin! I love you!
Blazing Sun!
Limit Break!
D-Did we beat it?
We won!
Yes! Victory is ours!
Yes!
What's wrong, Kaori?
O-Oh, Shizuku-chan! It's nothing, really.
I was just thinking about
how we've finally made it here.
Yeah.
Kaori?
I don't know who you are or why you came here.
But there's something I want you to know.
I will give you my power.
Use it as you please.
Just please don't use it for evil.
Power?
That's all. Thank you for listening.
I hope you will be able
to live by your own free will.
Wh-What's happening?
It's like something's being
imprinted onto my mind...
Holy shit...
Hajime?
They weren't evil gods,
or Mavericks, they were Liberators...
What now?
I told you before, I don't give a crap
about what happens to this world.
I'm going home. That's it.
You worried about it?
I belong here.
I don't care about anything else.
Oh, also it seems like I've learned
a new kind of magic--ancient magic.
Really?
It's called "creation magic."
It lets me add energy to raw minerals
to give them special qualities.
You can make artifacts?
Yeah, seems like it.
That's incredible, Hajime!
You wanna learn how to use it?
But I can't use Transmute...
Well, sure, but it's ancient magic, you know.
No harm in learning how to use it, right?
If you say so, Hajime.
How's it going? Learn how yet?
I did, but artifacts are hard.
That so? Guess ancient magic's more
compatible with some casters than others.
In any case, this place is ours now,
so why don't we take care of his corpse?
Use it to fertilize the fields.
Bingo! Found it, Yue!
Looks like that magic circle
is connected to the surface.
But to connect it, we need Orcus' ring.
That's not a problem.
I grabbed it when we buried him.
So the workshop's full of
Oscar's artifacts and all his materials, huh?
We'd better take 'em with us.
Hajime, look.
So is that how it works, huh?
If I make it through the other labyrinths,
I'll get my hands on the
other forms of ancient magic?
You might find a way to get home.
Yeah. Guess that's what we gotta do!
Let's hit up those other labyrinths!
There are even more in here.
What's wrong?
Hey, Yue, let's stay here for a while.
I want to get up to the surface, but there
are too many things to learn down here.
And if we're going to go
through the other labyrinths,
we should prepare as much as we can.
I don't mind, as long as I'm with you!
Okay.
This is the best!
Feels good.
Now, little miss Yue, I think I told you
I was gonna bathe alone, yeah?
Mm-hmm.
At least cover your chest!
There were tons of towels!
I want you to look.
O-Okay, Yue, look, I'm--
Am I not your type?
Th-That's not it! You're totally my type.
Good!
All of me is yours, Hajime.
Take a good look!
I-It's touching me!
What is?
What do you mean, your--
Nope! I'm getting out!
You're not going anywhere.
Hey, hold on!
We're fully prepared.
I've learned all I can from monster meat.
We're all geared up, too.
It took us a whole two months.
Yue, my weapons and powers
aren't normal up on the surface.
The Holy Church and other kingdoms
won't be able to keep quiet about 'em.
I'd be fine if it were just them, but we
might even get targeted by godly beings.
It might just be us against
the world on this journey.
We may not have enough lives
saved up to survive it.
It's too late.
I'll protect you, and you'll protect me.
We'll be unstoppable.
And we're gonna defeat
everything and everyone...
...and surpass the entire world, together!
"Good morning," "Good night,"
all those simple things
are so dreamlike and beloved to me
Because I finally met you
Everything is so special, thank you again
I didn't think I'd be lonely all by myself
That is, until you found me
I wasn't afraid of anything
That is, until I thought of a world without you
Can you believe it?
I miss you, I'm so fond of you
I love you, don't forget it
Shine bright like the first star in the night
and stay closer to me than anyone else
I'll never let you go
I'll never let go of that hand
Stay by my side and shine
ARIFURETA: From Commonplace
to World's Strongest