I'm Ilwer Chang, head of
the Fuhren Adventurer's Guild.
Uh-huh.
Hajime-kun, Yue-kun, Shea-kun,
I've been looking for you.
There are rumors going
around the town of Brooke,
rumors of a group of three talented people
who easily made their way
through Reisen Gorge.
You've got the wrong group.
I believe your skills would make you well-suited
for a request I'd like you to undertake.
Not doing it.
Mind if I just tell you what it is?
Then I won't have to deal with the paperwork.
Can't say I expected less from
the head of an adventurer's guild.
You've got the right personality.
I thought she was strangely quiet,
but she's just sleeping.
We won't be stopping at all,
so let her rest while she can.
You want me to find a missing person?
That's right, specifically,
a party of adventurers headed
to the northern mountains on a survey.
Among them is the third son
of Count Cudeta, Will Cudeta.
I want you to rescue him.
A Count? Must've been
a pretty big party then, huh?
They're quite skilled, yes.
Which means if there was
something they couldn't handle...
...then lots of people will get hurt.
We don't know how powerful
this enemy is, after all.
That's where your notorious group comes in.
The Count's a friend of mine.
A friend, huh?
Could you take on this request?
Not a chance. We've got
our own goals to accomplish.
I'll make sure you're rewarded.
Sorry, but we're in a hurry.
Well, then. How about
if I agree to fully back you...
...if you ever get into trouble with the guild?
If you're going to go that far for our help,
then I guess I have to consider.
But I have two conditions.
And they are?
First, I want you to make us status plates.
And the second?
If we ever have need of you,
you'll do everything we say.
Very well. It's a deal, then.
All right.
So assertive, Hajime.
They want this Will guy back alive, right?
The more indebted they feel to us,
the more effective Ilwer's backing's gonna be.
Mm. But there's something else.
You figure it out?
Right now we're headed to Ur.
We'll spend a night here then
head up towards the mountains,
but on our way we'll apparently pass through
the continent's largest rice farming area.
Farming area?
Rice, man, rice!
It's a staple of my homeland's diet!
And I haven't had any rice since I got here!
Well, then, I want to eat some, too.
Good work today, everyone!
Fill your bellies and get ready
to work hard again tomorrow!
Right!
Let's dig in!
Ai-chan-sensei?
You thinking about Shimizu again?
Where could he have gone?
It's been a whole week.
Nothing like this has
happened with him before...
I should've kept a closer eye on him.
I'm sure he's fine.
He'll be back before we know it.
You're right. Worrying about
him won't solve anything!
How was your dinner tonight, friends?
It was delicious, as always!
I'm glad to hear that...
Mr. Owner?
Unfortunately, and I hate to disappoint you,
but tonight we used the last of our spices.
Huh? Does that mean we won't
be able to eat this food anymore?
Sounds like there's some
trouble up in the mountains,
and the traders can't get to the spices.
Trouble?
Rumors say a gang of monsters
has suddenly appeared.
And just the other day,
a group of high-ranking adventurers
ventured out there and didn't come back.
That's concerning...
Thankfully, we've got guests in today
who say they were sent here
by the guild leader in Fuhren
to search for that missing party.
Hmm. They must be pretty tough, then.
How many times do I have to ask you?
My, speak of the demons...
Will you stop excluding me
to retreat into your own little world?
Do you hear me? Hajime-san?
I hear you, I hear you.
I just don't wanna see you,
so I figured separate rooms would be good.
Sheesh! Did you hear that, Yue-san?
Hajime-san's being so cruel to me!
Bad boy, Hajime.
Yeah, yeah.
Wh-What did they just say?
And doesn't his voice sound familiar?
Like that one guy.
Nagumo-kun?
Sensei?
It really is you, isn't it, Nagumo-kun?
I'm so glad you're alive...
Nope, you got the wrong guy.
Huh?
Bye.
Please, wait!
You are Nagumo-kun, aren't you?
You called me "Sensei," after all!
No, you heard me wrong. It's, uh...
A regional dialect! It means "tiny"! Yeah.
Then you're being incredibly rude!
And there's no dialect like that!
You're just trying to trick me!
What happened to you?
Why do you look like that?
Why haven't you come back to everyone?
Nagumo...
Answer me, Nagumo-kun!
Get back. You're bothering him.
And who are you? I'm trying to have
an important talk with Nagumo-kun...
Then calm down a little.
I lost my composure.
Let's try this again. You're Nagumo-kun, right?
Yeah.
Long time no see, Sensei.
Hajime-san, are you sure
you should be ignoring her?
Did you know this place has curry?
Wait, you don't know what that is.
Anyway, they've got some
really good, spicy food here.
Then I want that, too.
I want to know what you like to eat.
Ooh, look at you,
nonchalantly jumping in on that!
Good one, Yue-san.
Excuse me, we'd like to order!
I'm not done talking to you.
The hell do you think you're doing,
ordering food like it's nothing?
First off, who are these girls?
I'm hungry. At least let me eat.
And let them say.
Yue.
I'm Shea!
And I belong to Hajime!
Belong...?
Hey. Yue might be right,
but don't you go saying that, Shea.
What?! You're so mean, Hajime-san!
How can you say that
when you stole my first kiss?
Whoa, how long are you
going to keep saying that?
You drowned, I just gave you--
Nagumo-kun.
Yeah, Sensei?
Not only did you steal a girl's first kiss,
but you're two-timing her?
If that's true, that is completely unacceptable!
Yep, no way am I going to let that go!
You're getting a lecture!
You'd better change your ways!
In any case, I'm glad you were all right.
But what happened after that?
I worked real hard.
Why is your hair white?
'Cause I worked real hard.
What happened to your
right eye and your left arm?
Happened 'cause I was working real, real hard.
Why didn't you come back to us right away?
Didn't have a reason to.
Give me actual answers!
We're eating here. Mind your manners.
Mind my manners?
I think you should be the
one minding your own manners!
You need to learn how to
speak properly to your superiors!
And what are you doing,
sharing a table with a filthy beastman?
At the very least, let me cut off
those horrid ears of yours.
Then you'll at least look human.
What's that look for?
Insolence! You're no Apostle;
how dare you disobey an order
from a member of the templar knights?!
What a small man.
Damned heretic!
I told you to mind your manners.
You're not getting a warning next time.
Stay calm, you're okay!
N-Nagumo?!
Slowly back away!
O-Okay!
I'll take it from here. You go!
Got it!
Yuukacchi, you okay?
Y-Yeah. I'm still just surprised.
Right? I still can't believe it.
I mean, look at him.
He's like a whole 'nother person!
Yeah. He's gotten so... wild?
And popular, too.
That was damn good.
I've got no interest in you guys, nor do
I want you to get involved with me at all.
I don't plan on telling you everything that's
happened or that's going to happen to me.
Go and do whatever you want, I don't care,
just don't get in my way.
Because if you piss me off,
like what happened just now,
I won't hesitate to kill you.
Hey, Shea. You still worrying
about what he said?
N-No...
This is normal out here.
There's no point in worrying about it.
You're right. I know that, but...
I didn't know that humans
thought my ears were disgusting...
Your ears are fluffy and cute, Shea.
You think so?
Uh, what do you think of
my ears, Hajime-san? Well?
They're whatever.
He likes them a lot.
He was petting them softly
when you were asleep.
You promised you wouldn't tell her!
Hajime-san!
You like my bunny ears?!
You've got it all wrong.
I was not petting them!
Till now I was terrified of him,
You can pet them whenever you want!
I don't want to!
but now I just wanna murder him.
Later, Sensei.
Nagumo-kun, wait!
I'm not giving up on you!
Mm-hmm, there's no way
I'm giving up on you!
I'm bringing you back home with everyone else!
Nagumo... I never got to thank him.
Nagumo-kun survived.
But what was with his violent attitude?
He must have endured a lot of hardships...
And there was nothing I could do to help him.
I don't care, you're still coming with us!
What're you making all those faces for, Sensei?
Nagumo-kun?!
How?!
Guess I should say,
"Through the door, like everyone else."
Huh? But I locked it...
I'm a Synergist, remember?
Opening a lock like that is a cinch.
You broke into a woman's room
at this time of night and snuck in!
That's nothing to brag about!
Sorry. I just didn't want the others to hear me.
What did you want to discuss?
I figured if I talked to you now,
you'd be way calmer about stuff.
Let me give you the reason
I'm not coming back with you.
Just after the ancient Age of Gods,
the world was plagued by war.
Humans, demons,
and the countless forms of beastman
fought ceaselessly against one another.
During those centuries of war, a group of
people who wanted to stop it came forward.
The leader of that group came
to realize their god's true intent.
Their god was using his people as pawns,
and the war was no more than a game.
As he lurked in the shadows,
pulling the strings to cause conflict,
heroes came forth,
united in their desire to stop him.
At the time, they were called The Liberators.
However, their plans fell apart
before they could fight him.
Their god declared the
Liberators the enemy of the Church,
hell-bent on destroying the world,
and turned humanity against them.
The Liberators, unable to fight
the people they were sworn to protect,
were relabeled "Mavericks,"
and taken out one by one.
In the end, only a few core members remained.
Realizing they could not
defeat him with their powers alone,
they then scattered across the world,
built labyrinths, and hid themselves away.
They prepared trials, and whomever overcame
them would be granted their Maverick powers,
so that one day, this champion would be able
to stop this mad god's games once and for all.
That's what I learned
in the bottom of the abyss.
It's up to you, Sensei.
You could say these are all just lies,
or you could choose to believe it.
Do what you want.
Nagumo-kun, are you on a journey, then,
to do something about this mad god?
Hell no. I don't care
what happens to this world.
I just want to find a way home.
The labyrinths are the key.
You can come with if you like,
but I think you'll just end up dead
pretty quickly if you do.
Shirasaki-san never gave up on you.
She wasn't going to believe you were dead
unless she saw it with her own eyes.
She's okay?
I got a letter that she's gotten stronger
and is working through
the labyrinth with the others.
Then you should tell her something.
There's something she should be more
worried about than the monsters down there.
Her so-called "friends."
Huh?
I got a good idea of the situation
from how the others reacted.
You guys think I fell down there
'cause of an accident, right?
One of the magic spells
lost control and hit you, right?
Lost control, huh? Figures.
But that's not the truth.
That spell was intentionally aimed at me.
Intentionally?!
Right. One of your students tried to kill me.
That's why you should warn Shirasaki
and the others to watch their backs.
No...
I've got an idea of what you wanna ask,
but go on, let's hear it.
We're coming with you!
If you're going to look for someone,
it's better to have more people helping, right?
Absolutely not. If you wanna go,
then go on your own.
If you came with us,
you'd just make us walk at a snail's pace.
Please, you're not telling us that you
can run faster than our horses, are you?
Get it now?
Well, we're off.
Get out of the way.
P-Please wait!
I have to hear more about what
happened from you, Nagumo-kun!
Huh?
Could we talk while you travel,
or while we're searching?
If we can, then I'll keep my word
and we'll part ways here.
Fine. But there's really not much to talk about.
I don't care. I just want to hear it
in your own words, Nagumo-kun.
You sure are stubborn, Sensei.
Guess you never change,
no matter what happens.
Of course not!
Hajime, we bringing them with us?
Yeah, she's gotta play teacher, no matter what.
She won't compromise
when it comes to her students.
And leaving her behind is gonna cause
way more trouble for me when we get back.
She sure cares a lot about her students, huh!
But you can only fit three people
on that motorcycle, can't you?
What about the rest of us?
If it's out of seats, get in the trunk.
O-Okay, everyone!
Here we go!
"Good morning," "Good night,"
all those simple things
are so dreamlike and beloved to me
Because I finally met you
Everything is so special, thank you again
I didn't think I'd be lonely all by myself
That is, until you found me
I wasn't afraid of anything
That is, until I thought of a world without you
Can you believe it?
I miss you, I'm so fond of you
I love you, don't forget it
Shine bright like the first star in the night
and stay closer to me than anyone else
I'll never let you go
I'll never let go of that hand
Stay by my side and shine
ARIFURETA: From Commonplace
to World's Strongest.