[theme music playing]
[theme music concludes]
ASSAULT
Regarding Naomi Misora's disappearance,
shouldn't we open
an investigation into this matter?
[Ryuzaki] If we do, it should be
coordinated separately from the Kira case.
Also, we'll have to use police sketches
instead of actual photos.
We're talking about someone who's been
missing for four months already.
Chances are she's probably dead.
If you're right about that,
I find it odd
that we haven't found her body yet.
If we did, it might provide us
with some much-needed physical evidence.
[door opens]
-[Watari] Ryuzaki.
-Hm?
Something seems to be happening
on Sakura TV.
In other words,
all of the reporters and staff here
are Kira's hostages.
Aside from that,
we have a professional obligation…
MESSAGE FROM KIRA
FOUR VIDEOS
…to share this message with you.
I assure you that this is not a hoax.
And that Sakura TV is not airing this tape
for the purposes of sensationalism.
[Aizawa] "Kira's hostages"?
[Matsuda] What is this?
[man on TV] Four days ago,
our program director here at Sakura TV,
received four tapes.
After a thorough examination,
there can be no doubt
that they are from Kira himself.
[Demegawa] Our audience ratings
should go up sixty…
no, more like seventy percent
after this.
[man on TV] The first tape we received
contained a prediction
regarding the time of death
of two suspected criminals
who'd recently been arrested.
And as predicted,
at the exact time that Kira had specified,
both men died suddenly of heart attacks
yesterday.
[Ryuzaki] If what they're saying is true,
it's clearly something
that only Kira could do.
[man on TV] Kira has instructed us
to air the second tape today
at exactly 5:59 PM.
And we do intend
to comply with his demands.
This tape should offer proof of his powers
by predicting yet another death.
Beyond that, we understand
that it contains a message
to all the people of the world from Kira.
[gasps] This has to be another fake,
don't you think?
I doubt it.
I'm pretty sure even Sakura TV
wouldn't stoop that low.
And now, the video.
[Kira clears throat]
[Kira] I am Kira.
If this video was being aired
on April 18th,
at exactly 5:59 PM, as I requested,
then the time now is 5:59:47, 48, 49…
Please change the channel to Taiyo TV.
The news anchor, Mr. Kazuhiko Hibima,
will die of a heart attack
at exactly six o'clock.
-What?
-Change it!
TAIYO TV
[Matsuda] It can't be!
[TV staff shouting indistinctly]
How could he?
Change the channel back.
-And I need you to bring us another TV.
-[Kira] Mr. Hibima continued to refer…
-Watari. No, make it two.
-[Kira] …to Kira as evil on air.
-[Watari] Yes.
-[Kira] This is punishment.
[Kira] I'll present you
with another victim.
My next target is NHN TV commentator,
Mr. Seiji Kumaizumi,
who is scheduled to appear
in a live broadcast.
He too has dared to defy Kira.
-[Matsuda] R-- Ryuzaki!
-Change it to Channel 24!
[TV staff shouting indistinctly]
[Ryuzaki] Please, change it back.
[Kira] Now that you have seen
proof of my powers,
you should have no trouble believing
that I'm Kira.
[Ryuzaki] Kira said that he was going to
send a message to the people of the world.
[gasps] Stop this broadcast!
-We can't let him finish!
-[gasps]
[Ukita] Get Sakura TV on the line!
It's no good.
I'm trying but none of my contacts
at the station have their phones on.
Nobody is picking up
at the reception either.
Damn it!
[grunts] Ukita!
I'll stop that broadcast myself,
if that's what it takes!
[Kira] People of the world,
please listen to me.
The last thing I want to do
is kill the innocent.
I hate evil and love justice.
I've always thought of the police
as allies, and not as enemies.
Damn you, Kira…
-[siren wailing]
-[Kira] I intend to create a new world,
a perfect world that is free from evil.
If you agree to join me in my mission,
I know we can make it happen.
And as long as no one tries to catch me,
I promise that the innocent will not die.
Come on!
[Kira] Even if you don't agree with me,
all I ask is that you do not publicize
your views in the media.
-If you can do that, you will be spared.
-[people whispering indistinctly]
All you have to do now is be patient.
I will create a better world
that we can all enjoy.
Say goodbye to the world as you know it.
Soon, we will have a new world
ruled by benevolence,
inhabited by kindhearted, honest people.
Try to imagine it.
A world where the police and I--
Sachiko.
Darling, this can't be good
for your health.
Please, you have to rest.
Sachiko.
Like it or not, I'm still in charge
of the Kira Task Force.
[sighs]
-[tires screeching]
-[siren wailing]
[Ukita panting]
[Ukita] Damn it! It's locked!
This is the police!
Open up!
You idiots!
-[heart beating loudly]
-[groans]
[groans]
-[Aizawa] Hello?
-[reporter] We interrupt
-this program to bring you live…
-Damn, I'm still not getting through!
-[reporter] …outside Sakura TV studio.
-Huh?
Aizawa! Look!
SAKURA TV
[gasps]
[reporter] As you can see, someone
has collapsed just outside the door!
Again, we're coming to you live
from the Sakura TV building!
[Aizawa] Ukita!
Damn it.
Kira did this.
[grunts] Mr. Aizawa.
Where are you going?
Where do you think?
I've got to go there!
[Ryuzaki] You can't.
Please, think about it rationally.
What? You want me
to just sit here and watch TV?
[Ryuzaki]
If this truly is the work of Kira,
you'll just meet the same fate
if you go there.
You told us
that Kira couldn't kill without a name!
So, how could this happen?
The aliases and fake police IDs
were worthless!
What are we gonna do, L?
You don't think Kira has
all our names already, do you?
That's a definite possibility.
However, if that's the case,
you'd think it would be easier for him
to kill off the entire task force
before making a move.
Initially, I deduced that Kira needed
both the name and the face to kill,
but from what we've just seen,
I'd say it's not entirely impossible
that Kira can kill with only a face.
All I know for sure is that Kira
is either in that TV station,
or he's somewhere close by.
In a place where he can watch
everyone who enters the building.
-Perhaps--
-If Kira is in the area,
then isn't that why
we should get down there?
[Ryuzaki] For all we know,
he could've just placed
surveillance cameras in the area.
If we rush down there unprepared,
-all of us will be killed.
-Wasn't it you
who said we would have to
risk our life to catch Kira?
I meant what I said, but…
risking my life to catch Kira
and doing something
that I know will cost me my life,
are two entirely different things.
Oh, yeah?
Please, control yourself.
We've lost Ukita.
I understand you wanna go there,
but if something was to happen
to you as well…
[sighs]
[Kira] I now await
a response from the police.
You must decide whether or not
you will help me create
a better world for all of us.
Please announce your decision
on the six o'clock news in four days.
I prepared two videos.
One to be aired if the answer is "yes,"
and another if the answer is "no."
Hm?
[gasps]
[police siren wailing]
[growling]
Huh?
[man screaming]
[groans]
What the hell is going on?
Hey! Step out of the vehicle!
[gasps]
The Kira video.
Show me which studio
they are broadcasting it from.
[reporter] A vehicle has just driven
through the front doors of the station!
Well, that's one way
of getting into the building
without being seen by Kira.
[Matsuda] But who would…
This is the police!
Stop this broadcast immediately!
Who are you?
Hand those tapes over to me!
Do you understand?
[Demegawa] Hold on, officer!
It's not that simple.
My hands are tied here.
If we stop this broadcast,
he will kill all of us.
Shut up!
You're gonna be killed right here and now
if you don't give those tapes to me!
Wha-- Come on!
What the hell do you think you're doing?
This is crazy!
This is happening because you chose
to make Kira a celebrity!
You're getting exactly what you deserve!
-[gasping]
-I want every single copy you have.
And don't make me ask you again!
[Demegawa] I-- I got it!
I'll give them to you.
No problem. Just please,
stop waving that gun around!
You're acting like a madman!
[siren wailing]
[reporter gasps]
We're still outside Sakura TV.
As you can see,
a police car has just arrived.
So, we are not alone.
There're still other officers out there
who are willing to stand up to Kira.
-[Ryuzaki] Mr. Aizawa.
-Huh?
You know Deputy Director Kitamura's
cell phone number, right?
[ringing]
Aizawa, I told you not to call me
on this phone.
-[L] This is L.
-[gasps]
There's something I need you to do for me.
There may be police officers
who'll see this broadcast
and feel moved to take action
in the name of justice.
If you don't take control
of the situation quickly,
there will be a disaster.
But technically, we are not supposed
to be involved in this case.
Huh?
[reporter] Two police officers
have just collapsed on the sidewalk.
I think we may be in danger!
We are moving away from the scene.
I understand, L.
I see your point now.
Tell me what I should do.
[phone ringing]
Detective Superintendent Yagami.
Call him back immediately,
and give me the phone.
I need to speak with Ryuzaki!
Yes, it's me.
Mr. Yagami, so you're the one
driving the police van.
That's right.
I couldn't just sit and watch.
I've confiscated all of the tapes.
I'm bringing them to you.
But what about your condition?
Are you all right?
I'm feeling just fine.
To be honest with you,
I don't think I've ever felt more alive.
So, what do you think I should do now?
I take going out the front
would be too dangerous.
But I could always
use the police van again.
Please, hold the line for a second.
Deputy Director Kitamura,
it was Chief Yagami
who just drove into the building.
Are your preparations complete?
It's done, as you requested.
Mr. Yagami, listen carefully.
In exactly five minutes, I want you
to come out the front entrance.
You want me
to exit through the front entrance?
[footsteps echoing]
[gasps]
[police officer]
Make sure there are no gaps!
Do not reveal your faces!
We know that Kira is not in the building.
He's outside!
Thank you.
I'll drive myself.
[Ide] I understand.
[police officer] Listen up!
There is a very good chance that Kira
is still in the vicinity of the station!
As you move out, proceed with caution.
You are not to remove your helmets!
[Koki] There you have it.
The police refuse to cooperate with Kira.
Instead, they're preparing to fight.
And as much
as I fear for my own life in saying so,
this is right!
And it must be done.
Kira has become a threat
to our very constitution.
And as citizens, we must fight back!
I am NHN's Golden News anchor,
Koki Tanakabara!
-[door opens]
-Huh?
-Chief Yagami!
-[Ryuzaki] Welcome back, Chief.
[grunts] Ryuzaki,
I apologize for taking matters
into my own hands.
I have to admit,
I got a little bit carried away.
-No.
-Here.
These are all of the tapes
in an envelope.
Everything Kira sent to the station
is in here.
[Ryuzaki] I can't thank you enough.
I think I'd better rest for a minute.
[groans]
[Ryuzaki] Mr. Yagami…
This won't go to waste.
The postmark is from Osaka.
But Kira can control his victims
before they die.
So, he could have delivered it from Osaka
without going there himself.
Mr. Aizawa.
Can you please take this
to the crime lab right away?
I still have a couple of friends
down there.
I'll make sure they
go over every inch of this.
That's good. Please, do so.
While you're doing that,
I'm going to watch these tapes
to see if they can tell us anything.
[Yagami] Well, what do you make of these?
They were definitely interesting.
If the police had said "yes,"
and agreed to cooperate with Kira,
tape number three
was supposed to be aired.
Tape four if the answer was "no".
Tape three covers
the terms of cooperation.
Put simply, he is requesting that
we broadcast the names of more criminals.
He seems particularly interested
in those who have assaulted others,
or those who have somehow hurt
or taken advantage
of the weak and defenseless.
Of course, Kira would
play the role of judge in all of this.
Furthermore, as proof that
the police are willing to cooperate,
he wants police officials and L
to appear on TV
to make a public announcement
that we plan to cooperate with him.
Huh?
[Ryuzaki] He needs us to reveal our faces.
That way, he can kill us
if the police do anything suspicious.
In other words,
he will hold our lives as insurance.
I see.
So, what about
the content of the fourth video
if we were to answer "no"?
The wording was different
but he more or less says the same thing.
Mr. Yagami, it should go without saying
that the answer is "no".
Please, have someone take tape number four
over to Sakura TV
and authorize them to broadcast it.
[Kira] I can only say it's a shame
that your answer is "no."
It's clear that the police
wish to oppose me.
This will not go unpunished.
So, I will start by taking the life
of either of the Director-General
of the NPA,
or the detective known as L,
who is currently
leading the investigation against me.
The Director-General or L.
Who will pay the price for your refusal
to cooperate in the creation
of the peaceful world?
You have four days to decide.
[chuckles quietly]
[sighs]
It looks like I've even got God
on my side now.
Well, I suppose it's actually
a God of Death.
[chuckles] Seems like it.
It would appear that another Shinigami
has come to the human world.
And somehow that Shinigami's Death Note
has fallen into the hands of
someone who agrees with Kira.
And this person most likely
has the Shinigami-eyes,
which makes him very deadly.
His power to kill surpasses even mine.
One thing is for certain.
If I leave things,
I'm pretty sure that L would be
finished off within the next four days.
However…
I can't forgive this impostor
for the way he's tarnishing Kira's image
with these senseless killings.
Not to mention,
if he slips up and gets caught,
the Death Note could be discovered,
and that I cannot allow.
I can't afford to leave him alone
for much longer.
[cackles]
Therefore, what needs to happen very soon
is for me to join the task force.
It will allow me to keep track of L
and this fake Kira.
Ryuzaki, I'm afraid it's as you thought.
Several of our member countries
have weighed in
and it seems they're in favor
of having the real L appear on TV.
I think that's the most appropriate choice
given the options.
Well, we still have three days
before it happens.
Maybe we can find
some countermeasure.
After all of this,
it would really annoy me…
if I'm killed by the first person
who jumped on the Kira's bandwagon.
-Ryuzaki, what do you mean by that?
-[swallows]
That there is a strong possibility
that this Kira is a fake.
No, we should think of him
more as a second Kira.
A second Kira?
I-- I don't understand.
Why do you think there's a copycat?
How did you come to that conclusion?
[Ryuzaki] I looked at the victims
he used as predictions on tape number one.
Their purpose was to prove
to Sakura TV staff that he is Kira.
Both their names were only reported
in tabloids and daytime talk-shows,
so they weren't exactly
hardened criminals.
The real Kira
has no need to prove himself
using such insignificant criminals.
But from the perspective
of the Second Kira…
[gulps]
He'd wanna make absolutely certain
that he didn't predict
the death of a criminal
who could be killed
by the real Kira first.
Hmm… Ryuzaki,
If you had to put a number on it,
what's the probability of a second Kira?
[Ryuzaki] This time, I'd say
it's more than 70 percent.
I really don't like the way he operates.
It's not like Kira.
Not like him?
[Ryuzaki] In the past,
he has traditionally
avoided killing innocent people,
with the exception of those
who were trying to catch him.
Anyway, if we can capture one Kira,
I think that will provide us
with a lot of insight
into how we can find the other one.
Mr. Yagami.
I'd like your permission to ask your son
to cooperate with us
in this investigation?
[gasping]
If you want my son to join the task force,
does this mean you no longer suspect him?
Well, I can't say
that he's been completely cleared,
but his deductive abilities would be
invaluable to us right now.
[Yagami] So that's what it means.
If my son wants to cooperate with you,
then I have no reason to prevent it.
[Ryuzaki] I appreciate that.
However…
please don't tell him that we think
this latest Kira might be a fake.
I don't want him to know that yet.
We want to make it appear to him
that we're still chasing the same Kira.
[sighing]
[Shinigami] Misa.
I gave that Death Note to you,
so why not use it for yourself?
[Misa] I am using it for myself.
Because I believe in what Kira is doing.
I want to know what kind
of person Kira is.
I want to meet him and talk to him.
That's the only reason I sent all those
videos to that TV station.
I had to find some way
to make Kira notice me.
And I'd say that probably
got his attention.
Don't you think? [chuckles]
It's a dangerous game you're playing.
There's a chance you could be killed.
Do you understand?
[Misa] It's all right. I'm sure that Kira
is kind to those with pure hearts.
And if it came down to that,
I'm still stronger than he is
because I have the eyes!
TO BE CONTINUED
[theme music playing]
[theme music concludes]