[theme music plays]
FRIEND
I understand.
I can't be your boyfriend,
but I can act like it.
Thank you so much.
I'll try my hardest to make you love me.
I promise.
[Light] I'll arrange for her to meet L.
She'll tell me his name
and then I eliminate
the entire Task Force.
And when that's done,
I'll kill her, too.
After all,
she's the only person
who knows Kira's true identity.
The only one.
I can't let her live much longer.
So, you'll just pretend?
All right. I guess it's a good start.
Well, now that we've talked about that,
could you show me your Shinigami?
I really wanna see him.
[Light] I need her to trust me,
I guess I have to.
Yeah, sure.
Could you please turn around?
All right.
You can turn back now.
Okay.
Hey there. How's it going?
Oh, look at that.
You're a completely different type
of Shinigami than Rem, aren't you?
I already know your name.
It's Ryuk, right?
Nice to meet you.
Yeah, same here.
Oh, and by the way, Light darling,
do you know how to kill a Shinigami?
[Light] Did you just call me "darling"?
Fine. Then, do you mind
if I call you "Knight" instead?
Because you're like my knight
in shining armor, you know.
[sighs] Let's just stick with Light.
[Aizawa] So, were you actually
planning to check all of the footage
we got from Aoyama on the 22nd
by yourself?
That's right. I think it's very likely
that Kira and the Second Kira made contact
with each other there on that day.
So, I want to check
all of these tapes personally.
-Also, Mr. Yagami?
-Uh, yes?
Please ask Mr. Mogi
to start following Light
so we can keep tabs on what he's doing.
[Yagami] You want him followed?
It's only a slim chance,
but if Light is Kira,
then, there's still a possibility
that the second Kira might try
to contact him somehow.
-Very well.
-[door opens]
I'm starting to wonder
if Ryuzaki is even human.
The guy never sleeps.
I saw him sleeping in that
exact same position the other day.
-Huh.
-[Matsuda] No, I'm serious.
Hmm.
So, if a Shinigami has feelings
for a human,
and kills someone else
in order to extend that human's life
beyond its natural end,
the Shinigami will die?
That's right.
[Ryuk chuckles]
Good luck trying to find a Shinigami
who'd volunteer to do that.
That's true.
I can't see you ever doing that.
By the way, where did you send
all those tapes from?
The ones that went to the TV stations?
Let's see. Osaka, the first time.
Then Tokyo.
This other one from Nagano.
I took the bullet train every time,
so that way the police couldn't pinpoint
my location.
All right, one more thing.
Do you still have
the video tapes and envelopes
with your friend's fingerprints on them?
Uh-huh.
Well, you'll have to dispose of everything
that was used to create those video tapes,
understand?
But before you do,
I need you to send one last video.
And make sure it's from a place
you haven't used yet.
It should say...
"I've decided to stop searching for Kira.
and I'd like to thank
the police department
for all of its advice.
However, I still plan to help Kira
in his mission.
And I hope that in time,
he'll come to see me as an ally.
I will start by punishing criminals
that Kira has yet to judge.
Also...
I will share my power with others
who I feel are worthy
and I will encourage them to do the same.
Together, we'll make this world
a better place."
"Share my power"?
We'll just add that part
to throw off their investigation.
They suspect that there are already
two people with this power,
so it wouldn't be a stretch to assume
there could be others.
And if they believe the numbers are
growing, then they'll start to panic.
Can you do this?
No need to ask.
Just tell me what to do and I'll do it.
I don't care what it is
because I'd do anything for you.
[Light] There's one more thing
which is very important.
What's that?
If you get arrested by the police,
or if you're ever brought in
for questioning,
you can never mention anything
about us or the Death Note.
As long as they don't get a hold
of that notebook,
there's no proof that you did anything.
Can you promise to say nothing?
I promise!
So this must mean that we're officially
boyfriend and girlfriend now, aren't we?
Well, sure. I guess.
Then, I'd like to add one condition.
You have to go on a date with me
at least once a week.
[sighs]
Unbelievable. She still doesn't get it.
-We can't.
-[gasps] But why?
Ugh, it looks like I'm gonna have
to spell this out for you.
L already suspects that I'm Kira,
do you see what I'm saying here?
No way! L is amazing.
I mean...
Everyone's been saying that he's getting
nowhere with the investigation
and that he's a complete idiot and stuff.
But he already knows that much?
Anyway, it's all worked out well for me
because thanks to that,
I've also been able to get close to L.
Huh? You and L are
in contact with each other?
Then, that's even more amazing.
This is getting so exciting.
Even though he suspects I'm Kira,
L figures he's safe as long as
I don't know his real name.
He came right out and told me who he was,
just to get to me.
However, he's only focusing on me
because he has no other suspects.
And he has no evidence.
At this moment,
I'm working with him on the case.
And little by little,
I'm winning his trust.
Great. So all you have to do
is take me to where L is,
and I can see his real name for you.
-[Light] I'm afraid it's not that simple.
-Hm?
Listen, it was difficult enough for me
to get close to him.
Besides, if all of a sudden,
someone I just met gets too close,
and at the same time,
the police detect changes
in Kira or the Second Kira's behavior,
that person will be suspected
of being the Second Kira.
And, of course, that will put me
under even greater suspicion.
We can't allow them to make
that connection.
Which means we can't appear
to be too close to each other.
Do you understand what I'm saying?
Well, I think I understand.
So, is that why we can't go on dates?
We can't be seen in public
because it will look too suspicious?
Look...
We need to take the time now
to come up with a good plan.
Some way that you can see L
without letting him know you exist.
Yeah.
[Light] I can't eliminate L without you.
So I'll call you and see you
as often as this situation allows.
You will?
-[Light] But...
-[Misa] Oh.
... to make sure that our meetings
don't stand out,
I have to make sure that I'm seen
with other girls, okay?
Huh? What do you mean?
You're seriously going to date
other girls?
Yeah, more or less.
-[yelling] I don't want you to.
-Huh?
If I see you with another girl,
I'll kill her.
Scary!
Look, sweetie...
"Sweetie"? [laughs]
This is not a game.
Both of us are risking our lives
to change the world, aren't we?
I know that, but...
I love you more than the world, Light.
It sounds like you're confused.
Maybe it feels that way to you,
but you're here because you admire Kira.
You don't even know me.
We just met.
Don't you believe in love at first sight?
[Light] No.
I admit that everything you said was true.
I did want to meet Kira out of gratitude
and respect, not love.
But from the moment I first saw you,
I knew.
[Light] What is wrong with this girl?
Popular as always.
Well, you can show me your love
by obeying me.
I thought you said it was okay
if I used you.
A minute ago, you swore
you'd do anything I asked.
Yeah, I did. But I never said
you could date other girls!
I mean, those are two totally
different things.
I think you're forgetting
I have both notebooks.
If you don't obey me,
I can easily kill you.
[Rem] I would never allow that,
Light Yagami.
If you do anything
that results in this girl's death,
the first thing I'll do is write your name
in my Death Note.
I will kill you.
I'm sure you realize
that I can see her lifespan.
If she happens to die before that time,
I'll know it was you who killed her.
[Light] But if you were to use
your Death Note to save her,
wouldn't that mean you die, too?
That's right. If you try to save me,
you would die too.
Yes, you are correct.
But I'm quite willing
to accept that outcome.
[Light] Is this Shinigami serious?
This is crazy.
-And this means, from now on--
-[knocking on door]
-[Sachiko] Light?
-[gasps]
Yeah, what is it?
It's almost 11:30, you know.
You really shouldn't have a girl here
this late.
Oh, of course.
I guess we lost track of time.
Sorry, Mrs. Yagami.
[Misa] I'm really sorry
for coming over so late at night.
-See you later, Light .
-Yeah.
Light, you should walk her to the station.
[Light] Eh...
[Light] I can't risk being seen with her
in public.
Oh. No, I'm all right, thanks.
Well, good night.
Isn't she cute.
Yeah, I know. When she got here,
I wasn't so sure,
but you're right, she's cute, Mom.
I like her!
[Light] That Shinigami is going to kill me
if I kill that girl?
Which means... I'm going to have her
hanging around me until she dies?
Not only that.
It also means
that I'll be forced to protect her
from being caught by the police
for the rest of her life.
Thanks to you, Rem, Light really is
going to be my knight in shining armor.
I suppose.
[Misa] But you can't really kill him,
okay?
For a Shinigami to die,
they have to use their Death Note
to save the life of a human.
A human whom they have
fallen in love with.
Ideally, I could kill Rem first.
Someone I was controlling
would attack Misa,
forcing Rem to save her, but...
No, that would never work.
If Misa's life was put in danger,
Rem would immediately suspect me,
and I'd be the one who'd get killed.
[sighs] As things stand,
she's a bigger nuisance than L is.
[gasps] She's-- She's famous?
Oh. I don't even want to imagine
what would happen
if someone found out about us.
Damn it! She's nothing but trouble.
What should I do?
No. More importantly, I need to think
of how I can use Misa's eyes
to help me kill L.
If I can eliminate him...
[Sayu] Good morning, Light!
Good morning.
Mom, Sayu,
could you do me a big favor
and keep Misa a secret
from Dad for now?
All right.
Actually, it's not just Dad.
You can't tell anyone else
about her either.
You see, Misa's an up-and-coming model
so people can't know about us.
What? Is she really?
I thought she was pretty
but I had no idea.
That's pretty impressive,
even for you, Light.
I'll keep it a secret... for 50 bucks!
-[Sachiko] Oh, stop it.
-[Ryuk chuckles]
TO-OH UNIVERSITY
Uh, on page 246...
[Light]
Misa's final message should arrive today.
Although, before it ever gets
to the TV station,
it'll be rerouted
to Task Force headquarters.
I have to go down there at some point
so I can see L's reaction first-hand.
[girl] Light. Light?
I thought you and I were
seeing each other.
That is, we're more than
just friends, aren't we?
Yeah, we are.
Exactly. And that's the reason why
I'm sitting next to you in class,
-wouldn't you agree?
-Sure.
But you don't look like
you enjoy being with me.
I mean,
you haven't even looked at me once.
That's not true at all.
I guess I was just thinking about
how everyone's going to be talking
about us now.
To think that I'm actually going out with
Miss Takada, the famous Miss Todai.
I mean, you're the most beautiful woman
at the school.
[Ryuk chuckles]
[clears throat] Why do you even care
about stuff like that?
Besides, I hate being called Miss Todai,
or whatever. It's embarrassing.
Yeah, you're right.
[Light] What do you know,
she actually likes all the attention.
We should forget about all that stuff
and just go at our own pace.
[Takada] Yeah.
[Light] Hello.
Oh, come in. Your timing
couldn't be better, actually.
We just received a new video message
from the second Kira.
Huh? Wow, that didn't take long.
[L] Yes.
I believe it's the last one.
Well, take a look at this.
[Second Kira]
I've decided to stop searching for Kira.
And I'd like to thank
the police department for their advice.
However, I still plan to help Kira
in his mission.
And I hope that in time,
he will come to see me as an ally.
I will start by punishing criminals
that Kira has yet to judge.
Also, I will share my power with others
who I feel are worthy,
and I will encourage them
to do the same.
Together, we'll make this world
a better place.
[L] After watching this...
I can only think that Kira and
the Second Kira
have managed to make contact.
What makes you say that?
Oh, come on. Didn't you sense it?
I was sure you'd come to
the same conclusion I did
after watching this one through.
[inhales]
Hmm.
First, consider how determined he was
to meet Kira.
So why the sudden change of heart?
And now he wants to punish criminals
that Kira hasn't?
All he wants out of it is for Kira
to see him as an ally? [swallows]
It begs the question,
why didn't he do this to begin with?
I'm guessing it's because he never thought
that far ahead.
He probably met Kira and was told
which criminals he'd be allowed to judge.
I suspect the purpose of this message
is to hide the fact that they met.
[Light] I see.
What I find really strange is
that it's unlike Kira to be so careless.
That's true.
Hmm. But are we to believe
that Kira made a mistake this time?
Or is this his way of letting us know
that they made contact?
It would be an effective means
of provoking us.
The idea of their union
is very threatening.
However, this is also one less reason
to suspect that Light is Kira.
[gasps] Ryuzaki,
what do you mean by that?
If Light is Kira,
I don't think this is the message
he would have had the Second Kira send us.
It doesn't fit.
He would have made the Second Kira
go through with his plan
to have me appear on TV.
Then, deny that they ever made contact,
letting the Second Kira shoulder the blame
for my death.
He'd make him say something like, hmm...
"Although I agreed not to go through
with this,
I have come to realize that it was
not Kira's true intention that I stop.
I'm positive that the real Kira
would want L to die.
There's no way he'd make me stop."
-[Light] Ryuzaki.
-Yes, Light?
I think you're mistaken.
I would never do that if I were Kira.
Why not?
Well, if you're L and I'm Kira,
then I'd already know your personality
pretty well.
L would never agree to appear on TV,
no matter what threat he was facing.
And he wouldn't allow someone else to die
in his place.
The L I know would find some way
to escape the situation.
So, you figured it out.
Look, Light, you've got to stop that.
I don't like hearing you say,
"If I were Kira."
Even hypothetically.
Oh, I'm sorry, Dad.
I just wanted to let Ryuzaki know
exactly what I thought of his plan.
I posed that scenario because
I want to help solve this case.
It's the only chance I have
to clear my name.
Besides, the only reason
I feel comfortable
saying things like that
is because I'm not really Kira.
[L] That's a good point.
You're not Kira.
That is, it would be a problem
if you were Kira.
Because... [sighs]
I feel you're the first friend
that I have ever had.
[Ryuk gasps]
[Light] Uh...
Yeah, I know what you mean.
The two of us have a lot in common.
Thank you.
And I have missed having you around
at school.
We should play tennis again, soon.
Yes, we should.
A friend?
He's your friend?
That's a good thing, isn't it, Light?
That damn Ryuzaki,
he had no problem figuring out Kira
and the Second Kira had made contact
with each other.
-I've got to eliminate him right away.
-I see.
[Light] The way things are progressing,
I can't afford to be seen with Misa.
[Misa yells] Light!
-[Light grunts]
-I'm sorry,
but I just couldn't wait for two weeks
like you said.
Actually, I was just on my way to
your house when I spotted you. [giggles]
[groans]
[Light] This is the first time in my life
that I've been provoked to hit a woman.
I... I just wanted to see you so badly.
Well, you might as well come over.
Yay!
Another girlfriend?
Oh, great to see you Misa.
I saw you in a whole bunch of magazines.
-Please, come on in.
-[Misa giggles]
Sorry to drop by like this.
Could you make us some tea, Mom?
-[Light] Rem.
-Huh?
You are Misa's ally, aren't you?
Yes, I'd seen her many times
from the Shinigami realm, and then...
certain events made me develop feelings
for her.
Feelings? But you're a Shinigami?
[laughs]
You don't like what I said before,
about how I'd kill you
if you even attempted to kill Misa.
So if Misa is happy, does that mean
that you'll be happy as well?
I suppose you could say that.
I definitely don't want her to suffer.
[Light] As you know...
Misa loves me.
Oh, Light.
-Misa.
-Yes?
If I was happy,
would that make you happy, too?
-[Misa] Yes.
-[chuckles]
Then, could you ask Rem to kill L?
-Huh?
-Rem said
that your happiness was important.
But what do you think would happen
if L caught one of us?
It means our happiness would be ruined.
[laughs] It's true
that Shinigami are forbidden
to give out a person's name
to anyone.
But then again, there's no rule
that prevents Rem from killing anyone.
That's right.
And if you agree to kill L,
it would only make me love Misa
that much more.
Plus, I'd be grateful to you.
Most importantly, the two of us
would be happy together.
Rem.
I want Light to love me.
And I know we could be happy together.
It's all I ever wanted.
That's a shame.
[Rem] Fine.
As you wish, Light Yagami.
But I do not like you.
This will not kill me, even if it ends up
lengthening your life.
I will kill L for you.
It really makes no difference.
He is just another human to me.
Hurray!
Oh, Rem, thank you so much.
I knew I could count on you.
Huh...
L will die.
That's all it took?
TO BE CONTINUED
[theme music plays]