[theme music plays]
I feel you're the first friend
that I have ever had.
[both exclaiming]
-Misa.
-Yes?
Then, could you ask Rem
to kill L?
Huh?
Rem…
I want Light to love me.
And I know we could be happy together.
It's all I ever wanted.
That's fine.
I'll kill L for you.
[Light] L will die...
That's all it took.
WAGER
-[Rem] So, when should I kill him?
-[gasps]
If you take me to where he is,
I can kill him immediately.
The sooner, the better.
Maybe tomorrow.
Hmm. I should think this through
before we do anything.
I need tonight to decide
how we're going to kill L.
I'll give you my answer tomorrow.
[Rem] Very well.
[Light] Also, no matter what,
you can't kill him until I give the order.
No matter what. Understood?
[Rem] All right. I'll promise you that.
At least where L is concerned.
Misa, I need you to give me
your cellphone number.
About time! What took you so long?
Give me yours too, okay?
No, Misa, I'm afraid I can't do that.
Why not?
I'm your girlfriend!
I should have your number.
I already told you,
I'm under surveillance by the police.
Keep in mind, it's not difficult for them
to bug even cellphones these days.
Oh...
Okay then, what about this?
I'll just give you one of my phones.
I ended up with three of them.
'Cause I use them for different things.
Yeah, good idea.
If we use yours, I think we'll be safe.
That's great! I can hear your voice
every day, and text you too!
No, I'll keep this one turned off.
I'll be the only one making the calls,
and only when it's absolutely necessary.
What? No way.
Then when are you gonna call me?
-Probably tomorrow.
-Huh?
That will most likely be the day
we execute L,
but I'll call you either way.
What? Tomorrow?
It doesn't sound like a very romantic call
but I suppose we can always
talk about us afterwards.
Well, I think you should probably
go home now, Misa.
Huh? But why? It's only seven o'clock.
The time for lovers
is just beginning, you know?
We can go for a romantic dinner,
then maybe a moonlight stroll in the park,
and after that, the main event!
-Misa.
-Huh?
[gasps]
[Ryuk chuckling] Wow.
Listen.
You have to go home now.
Okay.
Also, when you're talking to Rem outside,
be careful that no one's around to listen.
Just whisper.
That's what I always do with Ryuk.
Okay.
Bye bye! Have a good night.
Bye bye, Misa! Come again real soon!
[Ryuk chuckles]
That kiss came out of nowhere.
[Light] Sure. It's very important
that Misa stays infatuated with me.
[Ryuk] Oh?
More importantly, I need to decide
if L should die tomorrow.
Since he hasn't gone public yet,
if Ryuga dies,
the other Task Force members
will be suspicious of me.
So I have to make sure I'm prepared.
[Ryuk] I see.
I thought perhaps you were hesitating
because he said he thinks of you
as a friend.
[chuckles] A friend?
I just gave him what he wanted.
From the start, I've said
if it's my friendship he wants,
I'd give it to him
as a way to win his trust.
Ryuga and Light Yagami
appear to be friends.
But L is Kira's enemy.
[Light] That's right.
Ryuga revealed that he is L.
Therefore, he must die.
If I have him die in an accident,
chances are that less people
will suspect I'm Kira.
And even if they do, there'd be no proof.
I can only speculate
what will happen after he dies.
Tomorrow will be L's,
or at least Ryuga and Ryuzaki's...
last day alive.
Hair.
Hmm...
[L sniffs] Snack crumbs.
[L] Hair.
-Mr. Yagami.
-Huh?
If I die within the next few days,
your son is Kira.
Oh, another hair.
[gasps]
What did you just say, Ryuzaki?
Exactly.
What are you talking about anyway?
If anything happens to me, I have asked
Watari to make himself available to you.
So, I'm counting on you, team.
Ryuzaki!
You said he was almost cleared,
and now this?
Honestly, how much do you suspect my son?
Hmm, the truth is, I don't even know
what to think anymore.
Huh?
I've never been in a situation like this.
If Kira and the Second Kira
are working together right now,
things are not looking good for me.
Given that,
I may not be thinking
as clearly as I normally do,
so I could be wrong.
[slurps loudly]
Maybe I still consider him a suspect
only because we don't have anyone else.
But still...
if I do happen to be killed soon,
please assume that your son is Kira.
[all grunting]
[L] I have no choice
but to make a sneak attack.
This is all a wager now.
[birds twittering]
[indistinct chatter]
[Light chuckles] I wouldn't say that.
I just know how to get by, that's all.
[gasps]
Hey, what's wrong?
Ah! Hey, Light!
How's it going?
[sighs]
Kiyomi, could we continue this later?
I need a moment alone with him.
Uh, okay.
I hope she's not upset.
Never mind that. Is it okay to be here?
Didn't you say you were afraid
to appear in public?
Yeah, I did. But then I realized
that as long as you're not Kira,
I should be safe.
The fact is, you're the only one
on the outside who knows me as L.
In the unlikely event
that I die in the next few days,
I've instructed your father
and everyone at headquarters,
to assume that you are Kira.
Damn him.
Besides, you told me yourself
that you missed having me around
at school.
So I figured, why not come back
for a little change of pace?
As long as it doesn't kill me,
college is a lot of fun.
[Light] I have to admit,
without you around,
intelligent conversation
is hard to come by.
[L chuckles] I see. Luckily,
Kiyomi's there to fill the void.
[Light] Well, something like that.
[Ryuk laughs]
[Light] Now I don't know.
Is it still okay to kill him today?
No. As soon as I make the decision
to kill him, he suddenly appears.
Almost as if to distract me from my goal.
I guess he's trying to guarantee
his safety.
And the way things are,
I'm playing right into his hands.
Hey, do you want to have some cake
with me in the cafeteria?
Sure. I have a break now anyway.
Um, that's perfect.
I'm kinda craving shortcake right now.
Well, let's hope they have it.
[Misa] Light! There you are!
I had a photo-shoot nearby,
so I thought I'd come by to see you.
[Light] Misa, you idiot!
Oh, this must be a friend of yours.
He looks so different. Unique.
Wait! I've won!
Misa will be able to see
Ryuga's real name!
Hi there. I'm Light's girlfriend,
Misa Amane.
Nice to meet you.
I'm Hideki Ryuga.
Huh? Hideki Ryuga?
Yeah, he has the exact same
first and last name
as the famous idol.
Pretty bizarre, huh?
[Misa] But it's different
than the name I'm seeing.
[Light] Ryuga,
deciding to come here today
was a mistake. Huh?
[laughing softly]
Why the hell is he laughing?
Could it mean he noticed something?
But it makes no sense.
If he somehow guessed
that she's the Second Kira,
there's no way he'd be laughing right now.
[chuckles] Light...
You're a lucky guy.
[Light gasps]
I have been a huge fan of yours
ever since the August issue of Eighteen.
What? Really? That's so sweet of you.
Hey! Oh my God,
isn't that girl Misa-Misa?
You're right! It's her!
[girl] She's so cute!
Wow, I should've guessed I'd be spotted
with all these kids around.
I'm, like, your biggest fan!
Keep up the good work.
Thank you! Couldn't do it without you.
What is this?
No way! Somebody just touched my butt!
Uh...
This is an outrage!
Taking advantage of this situation
is unforgivable.
I will find whoever
is responsible for this.
[Misa giggles]
Oh, Ryuga, you're so funny!
-I want to touch her too.
-Stupid!
I want to ask Misa what L's real name
is as soon as possible,
but all these people are in the way.
Misa!
It's time! Or were you planning
to be late again?
No. I'm sorry, Yoshi.
-Let's go!
-Oh, okay.
Perfect.
Now that Misa's away from the crowd,
I just have to give her a call
and ask for L's real name.
Bye, Light! I'll see you after work.
Miss you already. [giggles]
Now then, perhaps we should get going.
Yeah.
Actually, could you go on ahead?
I need to go use the restroom.
Oh, okay then. I'll see you there.
It's over.
It's been fun… L.
I'm grateful that I was the one
to discover your name
so I could kill you myself.
[Light] L, it's been fun.
I'm grateful that I was the one
to discover your name
so I could kill you myself.
[phone beeps]
[phone ringing]
[pop music ringtone playing]
[ ringtone continues playing]
Yes, hello?
What do you mean, "Hello"?
Oh, is that you, Light?
I guess someone must have
dropped this phone
in all of the commotion earlier on.
He took it. Bastard!
Uh, hello?
[Light] Yeah.
That's Misa's cellphone you have.
-I can give it back to her.
-I see. Sure, that makes sense.
[hangs up]
Ryuga...
He probably thinks he's pretty clever
right now.
But Misa has another phone
he doesn't know about.
I'll just call that one instead.
[phone ringing]
[L] Oh, this time
it's actually my cellphone.
[clears throat] Yes?
Yes, I see.
So, it's done then?
I understand.
I'm not exactly sure how you'll take this,
but regarding Misa Amane,
there's something you should know.
We've taken her into custody
under suspicion of being the Second Kira.
[Ryuk chuckles]
[Light] How long has he known about Misa?
I never thought
he'd find her this quickly.
We gathered physical evidence
from the envelopes that were sent
by the Second Kira.
In particular,
we recovered hairs and fibers
from the masking tape used to seal them.
They matched what we found in Misa's room.
There would be a public uproar
if it gets out that she's been apprehended
as the Second Kira.
So, officially, we've charged her manager
with drug possession
and she's a voluntary witness.
But I doubt any of this would get out.
[Light] I was careless.
The videos...
I should have destroyed all the evidence
before the police had a chance
to go through it.
In the end,
Ryuga knew that his best defense
was to stay close to me
rather than trying to hide.
He confronted things head on.
This wager was my...
[L] Was my…
Was my…
-No!
-[gasps]
Not yet.
The real battle is just beginning, L.
[sighs] Watari, has she said anything yet?
[Watari] No, she hasn't spoken a word.
Get me a visual of her, will you?
Are you sure?
Yes, and quickly.
[exclaiming]
[whimpering]
[Mogi] Ryuzaki!
What's the meaning of this?
[L] I've apprehended her on suspicion
of being the Second Kira.
I'm afraid this is necessary.
Chances are Amane is guilty.
There seems to be enough evidence
to convict her, but all the same...
Yes, there can be no mistake.
Now we need a confession out of her.
We need to know how she kills,
whether she knows Kira...
and, if so, who he really is.
Watari, take the necessary precautions,
but beyond that, you're free to do
whatever has to be done, okay?
Just make her speak.
[Watari] Very well.
-[L] Oh, and Mr. Yagami?
-Huh?
Light has now become our prime suspect
and I'm probably gonna bring him in
for interrogation as well.
Please, be prepared for that.
[grunts]
[Watari] Ryuzaki, Amane is talking.
Huh? Quickly, get me a visual and audio!
[panting and grunting]
[Aizawa] Finally,
after three days of this, huh?
[Misa whimpering]
[Misa] I can't take it anymore.
Kill me.
[all gasping]
Kill me. Please, just kill me!
I don't know, maybe this was all too much
for a young girl to take.
He's right. We've pushed her too far.
[L, distorted voice]
Misa Amane, can you hear me?
[Misa] I hear you.
Please, just kill me now.
Does this mean you admit
to being the Second Kira?
Is this the reason you wish to die?
[Misa] No! I don't know anything
about the Second Kira.
I really can't take this anymore!
I'd rather be dead.
Now, hurry up and kill me!
If you wanted to, you could kill me
right now, couldn't you?
Misa, do you mean...?
Yes, kill me.
Do you really mean that, Misa?
Yes, I do.
I can't take it anymore. Kill me.
If I do this, then Light Yagami dies too.
This is all his fault.
You can't. No, you can't.
Please, just kill me.
Why, Misa?
Why do you want to die for him?
[Misa] Fine!
If you won't kill me…
Stop her!
Watari, don't let her bite her tongue!
[exclaiming]
[muffled yelling]
[all grunting]
Is it possible that this behavior
could be attributed to Kira
controlling her actions before death?
[Ryuk] Oh.
What's the matter, Rem?
Light Yagami…
Misa has refused my offer
to help her escape.
No doubt because she knows
it would cause you trouble,
since the police would then have
proof of her powers.
When her suffering became more
than she could bear,
she started begging me to kill her.
All of this because she wants you
to love her.
I could not possibly
let it go on like that.
I couldn't bring myself to do it.
There was only one way
to save her from her suffering.
Forfeiting ownership of the Death Note.
Yes.
If Misa forfeits ownership
of the Death Note,
all her memories related to it
would disappear.
All the murders she committed with it.
The fact that you are Kira.
All those memories would be gone.
Your secret would be safe.
Also, Misa would no longer
be able to see Ryuk or me either.
SEVERAL HOURS EARLIER
Misa…
When this is done, you'll forget
everything about Shinigami
and the Death Note.
[Misa, muffled speech]
It's okay.
The human being who you love
is Light Yagami.
I promise those feelings will remain.
[muffled sigh]
So, Misa...
forfeit ownership of the Death Note
and leave everything to Light Yagami.
[muffled] Okay.
Huh?
Hmm...
And so, Misa is no longer
the owner of the Death Note.
You did the right thing, Rem.
I was beginning to think that was
the only way out of this situation.
If her memories of the Death Note
are gone,
then chances are they'll have
to release her eventually.
Light Yagami,
I proposed this to Misa
knowing it was exactly what you wanted
and that it would serve your purposes.
But I did so on one condition.
And that is, if you don't save Misa,
I will kill you.
[Ryuk chuckles]
I understand.
And I have a pretty good idea
of what L will do next.
I have a plan.
This is goodbye, Ryuk.
Huh?
TO BE CONTINUED
[theme music plays]