[theme music plays]
ALLY
[console beeps]
[retina scanner beeps]
-[buzzer]
-Hmm?
[Aizawa] Oh, okay! Maybe the belt…
[buzzer]
[Aizawa] Huh? What now?
Well, looks like this system
is gonna take some getting used to.
[Aizawa] Fine!
How's this? Huh?
[door opens]
Good morning!
[Matsuda] Huh?
What's wrong? Did you get hurt?
Oh, this? Kind of.
Uh… I had a little fight
with my wife, and…
It's just that my daughter
is still young,
and I'm hardly ever at home
as it is, so…
Oh, yes. It's probably best
if you sleep at home.
Well, you're gonna be missing out.
The rooms in this place are amazing.
If I were you, I'd just move
the whole family in here.
Yeah, yeah, yeah,
that's easy for you to say as a bachelor.
-Where are they?
-[Matsuda] Oh, they're on a date.
Last we checked all of them
were up in Misa-Misa's room.
[Yagami] Hmm.
[Aizawa] Surveillance cameras, huh?
Well, since we know Misa has
some connection to the Second Kira,
I guess it does make sense.
But for God's sake, Matsuda,
would you stop with this Misa-Misa crap?
[Matsuda] Oh… yeah. Sure.
Man!
This is gotta be
the lamest date I've ever been on.
No, no, no, please. Just pretend
I'm not even here, okay?
By the way, are you gonna
eat that piece of cake?
[Misa] Cake makes you fat.
I'm not gonna eat any.
Actually, I've found that you
don't gain any weight
as long as you burn calories
by using your brain.
[Misa] Hm! So now
you're calling me stupid?
Fine then. I'll give you the piece of cake
as long as you agree
to leave me and Light alone.
Even if I leave you two alone,
I'm still gonna be watching
on surveillance cameras.
-So, it wouldn't make any difference.
-You pervert!
Could you stop
with your creepy hobby?
You can call me whatever you like.
Last chance for cake.
Okay, then.
I'll just close the curtains
and turn off the lights.
[Ryuzaki] We have infrared cameras
in here as well.
-[Misa groans]
-What's wrong with you?
I thought moving here
was supposed to help us catch Kira,
but since we've been here
you don't seem all that motivated to me.
[Ryuzaki] Not motivated?
You're right.
Actually, I'm depressed.
Depressed? What for?
Well, hmm…
Truthfully, all this time,
I thought that you were Kira
and my entire case
hinged on that fact. [gulps]
I guess I just can't get past the fact
that my deduction was wrong.
Although, having said that,
I'm still suspicious of you.
That's why we're wearing these.
And we also know
Kira can control people's actions.
Which means it's highly likely
that Kira was controlling your actions
so that I would suspect you.
If I assume both you and Misa
were being controlled by him,
then everything we've observed so far
makes a lot more sense to me.
If that's what you think,
Misa and I were both Kira
during the time
we were being controlled, right?
[Ryuzaki] Yes,
I don't think I could’ve been
wrong about that.
The two of you are Kira.
[both] Hmm.
[Ryuzaki] If what I'm thinking is correct,
when your confinement began
you were Kira.
I don't believe it's coincidence
that as soon as you were in prison
all the killing stopped.
Until then, everything
pointed to you being Kira,
but after two weeks,
criminals actually began dying again.
KIRA RETURNS
Based on that evidence,
I can only conclude that…
Kira's power passes between people.
That's an interesting idea.
But if it's true,
it'll be nearly impossible for us
to catch Kira.
Yes. That's why I'm overwhelmed.
Even if we catch someone
under his control,
they'll likely lose their powers
and any memory of their crimes.
So, in the end,
pursuing them becomes futile.
But at this point we have no way
of knowing if that's the case.
Cheer up, would ya?
"Cheer up"?
No, I'm sorry, I can't.
It's probably better
if I just stop trying so hard.
By chasing Kira so desperately
we're just putting our lives at risk
for nothing.
Yes.
It's just a waste of time.
[sighs]
Ryuzaki…
Huh?
-[Ryuzaki grunts]
-[Misa screams]
-[Ryuzaki and Light grunting]
-[objects clatter]
[yelps]
[groans]
-[Misa moans]
-[Ryuzaki groans]
You know, that really hurt.
That's enough.
You don't feel like doing anything,
just because your genius deduction
was wrong and I'm not Kira?
[Ryuzaki grunts] Fine.
Perhaps I phrased it the wrong way.
I meant it would be pointless for us
to make a move,
so we shouldn't even bother.
If we don't chase Kira,
he will never be caught.
Is that what you want?
If you were just gonna give up,
then why did you involve
all those innocent people?
More importantly, what was the point
of putting Misa and me behind bars?
I understand.
But still, whatever the reason…
-[Ryuzaki grunts]
-[Misa screams]
…an eye for an eye, my friend.
[both scream]
-[Ryuzaki and Light grunting]
-Ooh!
[Ryuzaki grunts]
It's not my deduction that was wrong.
The fact is, I can say
that Light Yagami is Kira and
Misa Amane is the Second Kira,
but it won't be enough
to solve the case.
And that's why I'm a little depressed.
-Is that so unreasonable?
-Yes.
Yes, it is.
Besides, you should hear yourself.
It's as if you won't be satisfied
unless I'm Kira.
I… I won't be satisfied
unless you're Kira?
Well, there may be some truth to that.
In fact, now that you mention it,
you're right.
I think I wanted you to be Kira.
[grunts]
As I said before, an eye for an eye.
I'm a lot stronger than I look, you know.
[Ryuzaki grunts]
We've got to call the room and stop them!
-[phone ringing]
-[both] Huh?
-Yes?
-[Matsuda] Ryuzaki, I've got good news.
Misa-Misa is number one
in Eighteen Magazine's reader
popularity poll!
[Ryuzaki] Oh, I see.
[Matsuda] And get this!
She's gonna get a lead role
in Nishinaka's next movie!
What was that?
Matsuda's acting stupid again.
[line beeping]
[Light] Well, that is his specialty.
I can hear you, you know.
TWO MONTHS LATER
Ryuzaki.
I know you're not feeling up to it,
but come over here for a second.
Take a close look at this.
-It can't be coincidence.
-Huh?
[Light] All of them were prominent
Japanese businessmen.
CEOs whose companies are leaders
in their respective industries.
In just over a month
they all died of heart attacks.
As expected, there's been
a general downturn in the market.
With the exception of Yotsuba.
In other words,
their deaths have worked
in Yotsuba's favor.
Looking back,
there have been 13 similar deaths
in the past three months.
Your thoughts?
Based on this I can only conclude
that Kira is supporting Yotsuba.
Hm. It could be.
But if what you're saying is true,
we can assume that punishing criminals
is not this Kira's real intent.
[Light] Right
Punishing criminals
is a diversion for him.
It obscures the fact
that he is actually killing people
for the benefit of his company.
Hmm.
Are you…
feeling a bit more motivated now?
[man 1] It's funny.
This is starting to feel too easy.
Look at all we've done
and no one suspects a thing.
[man 2] Our stock continues to increase
but we've kept it below the radar.
[man 1] Indeed.
Everything appears to be proceeding
according to plan.
That's true. However, there is one thing
that has me concerned.
Those three we had killed last week.
Why did all of them die of heart attacks?
I thought we agreed
one would be accidental.
You're quite right. We did.
The problem was that we named
a specific location in Japan.
You see, he wasn't even here when he died.
I hear he and his mistress
were in Italy at the time.
Makes sense.
If our request
is physically impossible then…
Kira will kill that person
using his default method. A heart attack.
It's just like I was saying last week.
If you want it to look believable,
request accidental death or disease
and Kira will always find
the quickest way to make it happen.
Anyway, given Kira's history,
the police are probably
still focused on the dying criminals.
Quite frankly, if someone was able
to trace the deaths of these people
back to us,
then he would have to be a god.
Besides, we've taken precautions.
-Hm?
-Oh?
Hey, Chief! Oh, you too, Mogi!
I've got some great news.
This is amazing!
I'm not even sure how he figured it out,
but Light has a theory that Kira
is somehow involved
with the Yotsuba Group.
Can you believe it?
Yotsuba?
Uh… yes.
That's probably it.
-Good work.
-Huh?
We just spoke with the director
and it seems Kira has offered bribes
to a number of politicians.
[sighs] Kira made an offer…
As long as the NPA agrees
not to pursue him anymore,
he won't lay a hand on any politicians.
So, that's that.
The police caved into him.
[all gasp]
Mogi and I have already
made up our minds on this.
Aizawa, Matsuda…
if you wish to continue working this case,
you'll have to hand in
your letter of resignation to the NPA.
Just as Mogi and I are going to do.
[both gasp]
Like it or not, you cannot pursue Kira
as member of the police force anymore.
Wha… Hold-- Hold on a second, Chief.
They made it quite clear.
If you continue to work with L
you will be fired.
That's all there is to it.
So then, Chief, you're gonna…
In a few hours,
I'm no longer going to be your chief.
However, we all have our own lives.
So, think it over carefully.
That's true, Chief.
Especially, if you've got family
to support.
[breathes heavily]
[Ryuzaki] If you want my opinion,
you'd be better off as police officers.
[Yagami] Hmm?
[Ryuzaki] I was alone
when I started this case.
And although I'm grateful to all of you
for staying with me as long as you have,
I know that I can do this by myself.
I'll be sure to visit you
at the department
and bring you Kira's head as a reward
for all that you've sacrificed.
Ryuzaki!
As long as I'm alive,
you won't be working alone.
-You have my word on that!
-[chain rattles]
[Ryuzaki] Hm. That's right.
I'll have Light working with me
until I catch Kira,
so I won't be alone after all.
But as I said, I think the rest of you
should remain as police officers.
But when you first contacted us,
you said that you'd need the help
of the police in order to solve this case.
[Ryuzaki] That's because the police
as an organization,
were still hoping to arrest Kira.
They weren't bowing to him.
Besides, with all due respect,
there's a big difference
between the help of two or three civilians
and the police as an organization.
Mm. And as you said,
the police have made their position clear.
They don't wanna catch Kira,
so let's just leave it at that. [swallows]
[sighs]
Well, I suppose what you're saying
makes sense.
If we are not police officers anymore,
we won't be of much use to you.
However, we're all
personally involved in this.
All of us have risked our lives
to catch Kira.
Doesn't that give us the right to decide
whether we stay here
or return to the police force?
Hmm. Good point.
Then by all means, please,
make your decision.
But, Chief, wait. If you quit your job
with the police force,
you'll be unemployed.
Even if we do catch Kira,
what are you gonna do after that?
-[Matsuda] Oh…
-After that?
I hadn't really thought of it,
but I suppose after we catch Kira…
I'll have to dust off my resume.
Count me in!
I'm gonna quit the police
and chase Kira too, Chief!
And I still have my job
as Misa-Misa's manager!
Besides, if I stayed on
as a police officer,
I'd feel like a total loser.
[Yagami] Think before you open
your mouth, Matsuda.
Oh…
[Aizawa] Uh…
Uh…
Is there any way I could still keep my job
and help you in my spare time?
[sighs] There isn't.
If you remain a police officer,
then please, don't come back here.
But you know I won't leak any information.
I won't be sharing any of our information.
[gasps]
You are free to pursue Kira on your own,
if you want to.
But I don't think
it's fair to your families
to burden them by giving up
your livelihood just to continue this…
I can't see how that's a good idea.
It's as Ryuzaki says,
no one here is gonna blame you
for quitting.
Yeah. Right.
We all understand why you gotta do this.
But the Chief has a family, too.
Our situations are completely different.
[sighs] Damn it.
To leave now
after all we have been through…
I said I was prepared to die
if that's what it took to catch him
and I meant it.
What kind of friend would I be to Ukita
if I quit now?
I became a detective,
so I could catch the bad guys,
not run away!
[Watari] Ryuzaki.
Early on in the investigation,
you specifically told me
that if a task force member
were to lose their job,
under any circumstances,
I should make preparations to ensure
that their family's financial future
was secured.
If you recall, a trust was set aside
for that very purpose.
I'm a little curious as to why
you're withholding this information?
-[gasps]
-This is not the time or place, Watari.
[Watari] I'm sorry.
No way! So, all this time
we had nothing to worry about?
I can't believe you did that!
There you go, Aizawa.
Isn't that a great news?
[gasps] Oh?
Ryuzaki,
I assume that was some kind of test
to determine how committed I was
to this task force.
It-- It-- It's not like that, Aizawa.
Ryuzaki's just not the type
to say things directly.
You should know that by now.
Yeah, that's right.
-[Ryuzaki] No.
-[all] Huh?
[Ryuzaki] I was testing you.
I wanted to see
which one you would choose.
-Oh.
-Ryuzaki…
[breathes forcefully]
Fine then!
If I wasn't sure before, I am now!
But Aizawa!
Let's face it.
I wasn't able to decide right away,
like you guys.
I was leaning towards
going back to the police.
Come on, Aizawa. Don't be so stubborn.
[Aizawa] No! I quit!
Now, I know this for sure!
I've always hated Ryuzaki!
I hate him and his way of doing things!
[Ryuzaki] That's too bad,
because I like you, Aizawa.
[gasps]
[growls quietly]
I also hate the way
you've always gotta have the last word!
You insult me
and now you say something like that?
That's it! I am outta here!
Thank you for everything.
[door opens]
[door closes]
[Light] I just found another one.
A general manager of a bank,
Yotsuba's biggest competitor,
on September 7th, he slipped and fell
on the front steps of his house and died.
Instantly.
[Yagami] September 7th was a Friday,
wasn't it?
[Light and Ryuzaki] Hm?
After going over this again,
I noticed something.
All the deaths
which are beneficial to Yotsuba,
are concentrated around the weekends.
Huh? On the weekends?
With the first few victims
the time of death
appears to have been random,
More recently they all take place between
Friday night and Saturday afternoon.
I'm amazed
that you even noticed that, Chief.
Matsuda, I thought I told you
to stop calling me "Chief."
I'm sorry,
but you'll always be the Chief to me.
This is a really important clue, Dad.
Nice work.
Well, you know, I can't let myself
fall behind you and Ryuzaki.
After all, the last thing I want
is to be dead weight.
Oh. "Dead weight"?
[Ryuzaki] Is Kira someone from Yotsuba?
Or is Kira simply using Yotsuba?
I haven't figured that out yet,
but we will proceed under the assumption
that this is Kira's doing.
We will focus on Yotsuba.
[grunts] This is all
of the Yotsuba Group's employees.
Here.
Thank you very much.
[Light] That's 300,000 people.
How did he put this together so quickly?
That's amazing, Mogi.
[Ryuzaki] He's been incredibly efficient
from the start.
Ryuzaki!
Please, tell me, is there anything
I can do to help with the investigation?
Besides the manager thing.
[Ryuzaki] So, you really wanna be useful?
Yes!
[Ryuzaki] Then could you get me
another cup of coffee?
Huh?
[Ryuzaki] And for our guests
over there as well.
Huh?
Who are they?
Hold on a sec. Who let them in?
Those two are the newest members
of the task force.
The name's Aiber.
I'm a conman. How's it going?
I'm Wedy. And I'm a thief by trade.
Oh. A conman and a thief?
That's right. Aiber is a lifelong conman.
His unparalleled social skills
allow him to befriend
and gain the trust of any target.
We'll use him for infiltration.
As for Wedy,
she is a thief who specializes
in cracking high-end security systems.
As proof of that,
she was able to enter the building
without setting off a single alarm.
You expect us to work with criminals?
Yes, that is correct.
However, these two
have never once been caught.
So, it's unlikely
they'll be killed by Kira.
Think of them
as professionals of the underworld.
I understand.
To investigate Yotsuba,
we're gonna need the help
of people like this.
Let's all do our part
and make this happen, okay?
-Yeah!
-Yeah. Deal.
[girl laughs]
Oh? Daddy?
-Huh?
-[giggles] Daddy!
Oh, Yumi…
Eriko…
What are you doing here?
Shouldn't you be at work right now?
You need to tell me
if you're planning to be home for dinner.
I just went shopping
and I only bought for me and Yumi.
You can eat my dinner
and I'll have dessert instead!
Sorry.
It was sort of a last-minute decision,
but they just gave me some time off.
Huh? Is a "time off" a vacation, Daddy?
Yeah. That's right.
Yippee!
From now on,
I can have a break every single week.
Now I can go with you to the park.
[trembling]
Maybe we can go to the zoo together,
or the amusement park…
[Aizawa sobbing]
Ooh. What's wrong, Dad?
[Yumi] Mommy, why is Daddy crying?
[Aizawa sobbing]
TO BE CONTINUED