[theme music playing]
MAKESHIFT
[Ooi]
Well then, let's begin tonight's meeting.
[Light] There's supposed to be eight
of them, but only seven are present.
That must mean that...
[L] They probably killed one
of their members.
[Soichiro] Hmm...
[Ooi] In order to further the growth
of the Yotsuba Group
and best serve its financial interests,
who should we kill next?
[all gasp]
You see? It's just like I told you
last week!
[L] This is not good. At this rate...
[Ooi] But before we get to that,
there are several topics
that we need to discuss.
First, there is the issue
of Hatori's death.
[Namikawa] That was unavoidable.
To be honest, in a certain sense,
I'm relieved that Hatori's dead.
Kira has demonstrated that we must
be committed to these meetings.
We now know what will happen
if we try to leave.
[Ooi grunts softly]
I think we all understand what Hatori's
death means for the rest of us.
Let's not take it lightly.
Now, moving on. Our next topic
is Eraldo Coil's report…
[all gasp]
One of their members just died
and that's all they're going to say?
So did we really pay five million dollars
for this report?
I mean, come on. Look at this.
He hasn't found out anything important
about L like his name or his face.
Is this Coil guy seriously going
to be of any use to us?
Hold on a second.
There is something very interesting
in the last part of this report.
Coil's warning us that we can't afford
to take L's existence too lightly.
In particular, it says, "The concentration
of killings that are beneficial to Yotsuba
will likely be noticed by L
if they continue on Fridays
and Saturdays."
Sounds like this Eraldo Coil
has figured out what we've been up to.
I admit, it's quite impressive.
At any rate, I personally think
we should stop killing every weekend.
This is unbelievable. It's like they're
trying to confess to everything.
Hmm, as long as we have this video
as evidence,
we could probably arrest
all seven of them.
[L] This is not good.
Kira hasn't been flexible
up till now, has he?
It would be nice if he could spread out
his killings over the whole week.
The fact that Coil noticed
what we've been up to
makes it dangerous to continue killing
at our usual pace.
From now on,
we have to be even more careful
and make sure that nobody else happens
to notice a trend in these deaths.
Now, onto the main topic.
Who should we kill?
[Soichiro sighs]
I think we should focus on ELF Insurance.
If they expand into the Japanese market,
Yotsuba and many other companies
will lose valuable clients to them.
[Higuchi] Agreed.
Alright. Any objections to killing these
people from ELF with accidental deaths?
[all] No objections.
-Ah.
-Is this for real?
How can they do this so easily?
[Ooi] Another potential candidate
is Sentara Zenzai,
a member of the Kugisawa Group.
He's been protesting
Yotsuba's resort development plans.
Zenzai's known to have
high blood pressure,
so we can designate a time
for him to suffer a stroke,
resulting in natural death.
Any objections?
-[Yotsuba Group] No objections.
-[gasps]
Kira? Deaths by accident? By disease?
Designated times of death?
It's all just as we suspected.
We were right.
No. Unfortunately, we can only be
completely sure
after those people they've named are dead.
[both gasp]
[L] We will continue
to monitor these meetings
and take note of what they say,
how they act, and most importantly,
whether the people they choose
actually die.
If we can confirm the connection
between their plans and the deaths,
then we'll definitely be able
to catch Kira.
-[both] Ryuzaki!
-[L grunts]
What is it? There's no need
to yell in unison.
I can't carry on
knowing these people will die!
-That's just immoral!
-Right.
[L] Here it comes.
I know you're planning to catch Kira
by letting these guys
actually carry out these murders,
but... we can't let that happen!
That's right. It's obvious that these
seven men are behind the killings.
With Matsuda's testimony
and this footage we've recorded,
we have all the evidence.
[L] You're making this difficult.
If we were to take action now,
everything we've done would go to waste.
[Ooi] So, what do you say we take care
of the ELF in three weeks,
and as for Zenzai, we'll ask Kira
to kill him this weekend?
[all] No objections.
If that's what they're going to do,
then there's not much time left.
Light, we already know the phone numbers
of these board members, don't we?
Yeah.
I don't care who we call.
I need to reach one of these men
and have them stop these murders.
[L] Please, hold on.
That would cause suspicion.
It would mean the investigation
caught up to them
three days after they were contacted
by Aiber.
Also, it would make it far more unlikely
that we would be able to discover
who the real Kira might be.
We can't afford such a huge setback
seeing how far we've come.
[slurping]
In order to catch Kira…
we're going to need some solid proof.
Ryuzaki, if one of these seven men
is in fact Kira,
would it be safe to say that if I tried
calling one of them,
the odds of that person actually being
Kira is going to be one in seven?
I'm thinking there could be more
than one Kira among them.
A probability of two in seven at most.
If we're prepared to let them know
that the investigation
is catching up to them...
let's place our bets on these odds.
Ryuzaki, I'm going to pose as L.
And judging from their conversation
so far, the one least likely to be Kira
but with the most influence is...
-[L and Light] Namikawa.
-[Matsuda] Is Ooi!
[Matsuda groans]
[L] If you're going to make a call,
please use this phone.
It's set up, so it can't be traced
or tapped.
[Higuchi] You know, this would all go
a lot faster if we kill off the execs
of our rival companies
and be done with it.
[Mido] That would be going
a little too far.
CALL FROM ANONYMOUS
[Higuchi] Why? We could kill them
and split their holdings.
[Light's voice distorted]
Is this Reiji Namikawa,
head of the Yotsuba Group's
Marketing Department?
Hmm. Yes, and who is this?
[Light] Listen carefully,
but don't draw attention to yourself.
I am L.
[gasps]
[Light] I've planted cameras and wiretaps
around that meeting room.
Even as I speak, I'm recording footage
of your entire meeting.
The first thing you discussed
was Hatori's death.
Now you're debating who to kill next.
Am I correct?
[Namikawa] He's been watching everything!
If you are not Kira,
or if you are not someone
who can contact Kira directly,
let's make a deal.
[Namikawa] A deal?
[L] I need you to delay the deaths
of ELF's president
and Mr. Zenzai by one month.
I doubt it will be difficult for someone
of your standing to accomplish that.
[Namikawa] Yes, yes, I see.
Right. Go on.
[Light] If you complete your end
of the deal
and cooperate with our requests
from now on, then your crimes--
No, not just yours, but everyone's crimes
with the exception of Kira
will be parked, based on the premise
that Kira blackmailed you
into participating in these meetings.
I see. Okay.
[Namikawa] My only option is to join L.
No, I'll be dead if Kira manages
to find out.
What should I do?
If you tell the others about this call,
they will panic.
It would be no advantage to you.
Everyone would be arrested immediately.
But that's not my intention.
I'm planning to go one on one
against Kira.
Listen. If I win against Kira,
you'll be acquitted of all charges.
If Kira wins, then you'll be free
to carry on with your comfortable life.
Just play along with both parties.
Staying on the sidelines will be best.
You're not in a position to lose anything
regardless of who wins in the end.
You would only be at a loss if I decided
to arrest you right here and now.
[Namikawa] Damn it. He already knew
what answer I would've given.
[Light] That's all for now.
Right. I'll see you Monday, then.
What's going on, Namikawa?
Who was that?
One of my men screwed up again.
I'll have to fix it on Monday.
Anyway, sorry for the interruption.
Let's get back on topic.
We were discussing when we should kill
Zenzai and the men from ELF.
Here's what I'm thinking.
We'll give Coil one month
to reveal L's identity.
If he still hasn't uncovered
the information we need,
then we can go ahead
and kill the targets randomly.
Then, we'll give him another month
to investigate and repeat the process.
Once we get rid of L permanently,
we can go back to killing
two or three people a week.
In other words, our top priority
should be the elimination of L.
I see.
Once we kill L, there won't be anything
standing in our way.
But until then, we need to be careful.
Right. Sounds like a reasonable plan
to me.
We need to be extremely careful
if we don't wanna get caught.
[Ooi] Then we're in agreement.
We'll give Coil one month.
[Yotsuba Group] Agreed.
[Namikawa] L, this should satisfy you
for now.
[Ooi] We'll still be meeting
on a weekly basis. That is all.
[L] That went well.
[Light] Yeah.
You really are quite amazing, Light.
Not only did you manage
to delay the killings,
but you also set up Namikawa
as a potential mole for us.
Sounded exactly like the sort of thing
I would do.
And you thought of it quicker than I did.
At this rate…
if I end up dying somehow,
it's quite possible that you would be
capable of succeeding me.
What? Why are you being so morbid?
There isn't time for that. We only have
a month to figure out Kira's identity
and gather evidence against him
to prove it.
This is only the beginning.
[L] Yes…
But you were the one who first noticed
the connection between Yotsuba and Kira.
You actually might be more capable
than I am.
I honestly believe you could take this on.
[gasps]
[L] Tell me. If I should die…
would you take over from me as L?
Huh...
[L] If I should die,
would you take over for me as L?
If he is Kira and just playing innocent,
he's sure to say yes.
What are you talking about?
As long as we're joined by these,
we would die together anyway.
I see.
Ryuzaki, I'm sorry,
but I'm gonna have to tell everyone
-what you're really thinking right now.
-[Matsuda gasps]
[Light] He thinks that if I am Kira,
then there are two possibilities.
I'm either just pretending I'm not him
and putting on an act,
or that Kira's power has passed on
from me to someone else,
and I have no memory
that I was ever Kira in the first place.
He's trying to determine which,
if either, is the truth.
The first theory,
if I am putting on an act,
he will never remove these handcuffs.
No, even if it wasn't pretending
to be innocent,
I'm sure he still wouldn't take them off.
Ryuzaki still believes that I'm Kira.
Even if that power had been passed
to someone else,
he thinks that I would have planned
to have it return to me once I'm safe
from suspicion.
In other words,
I wasn't being controlled at all.
He thinks it was a plan,
to pass on the power and arrange for it
to come back to me once I'd been cleared.
[L] Impressive. You figured out exactly
what I'd been thinking all this time.
[Light] Ryuzaki's theory
is that once I steal L's title,
I will become Kira again.
[L] Correct.
[Light] Taking on the identity of L,
having the power to control the police
in every country
while being Kira in secret...
It's ideal.
And you're thinking I could do it.
No, that I would do it.
That's what you're saying, isn't it?
[L] Yes.
[Light breathes sharply]
But what about now?
I told you, I don't want your title.
That should prove, even to you,
that I'm not putting on an act,
shouldn't it?
[L] If this is all an act
and you are trying to steal my identity,
there's no chance you'd be foolish enough
to reveal your plan in front of everyone.
-Wouldn't you agree?
-[Light exhales]
[Light] Ryuzaki…
Huh?
Do you think that I'm actually capable
of becoming a murderer?
Kira?
Even after I helped you catch him?
Do I seem like that kind of person to you?
[L] Yes, you do. I've always thought so.
[both gasp]
[groans] Not again!
Okay, break it up! Once is enough!
It was a draw, so let's just leave it
as an even match, okay?
[sighs] Yeah, you're right.
Anyway, let's focus on catching
the Kira that's in front of us right now.
As long as I have the handcuffs on,
you shouldn't have any complaints.
I suppose so. We only have a month,
so there's no time to get distracted.
[Matsuda sighs in relief]
-Ryuzaki...
-Yes?
[Soichiro] We have plenty
of footage from this meeting.
Can't we use that as evidence
against those seven men
and prevent the murders
of other criminals?
[L] Here we go again.
-Unfortunately, no.
-But why?
At the moment, we're not certain
if Kira is among those seven men.
If all they have
is a tenuous connection with him,
then Kira will kill them
as soon as they're arrested.
We have to be absolutely sure
that Kira is among them,
so there's no point in detaining them now.
And even if it does turn out
to be one of them,
it will still be quite difficult
to determine who the culprit is.
Hmm, I believe it's still far too early
for us to make our move.
Hold on. At the same time, we can't say
that he's definitely not among the seven.
That means there's a chance
the killings will stop
if we take this opportunity
to arrest them.
I think Dad's right. There is a chance.
We have to act on it.
Excuse me, but I think from now on,
I should go after Kira by myself.
[Light] Huh?
You can use these headquarters,
as you wish.
I'll also be here,
but we will be working independently.
You can conduct your investigation
under your own direction.
Feel free to arrest those men if you like.
I will be carrying on
my own investigation.
We'll only get into arguments if we don't
split up and act separately at this point.
This is for the best.
[Soichiro] Are you saying
you're going to figure out
who Kira is by any means necessary?
[L] Yes. This case will never be solved
unless we capture Kira himself.
Don't get me wrong. I wouldn't say
that preventing deaths is pointless.
But if we don't uncover the entire truth,
once and for all,
Kira will only appear again and the number
of victims will continue to increase.
That's why I believe it's more important
to try and find out who Kira really is.
As I've been saying,
I'm opposed to arresting those seven men.
If you want to do so, then you will have
to take responsibility for it.
I will pursue Kira on my own.
We only have one month.
I wonder who will succeed.
[stammering] Ryuzaki. Where are you going?
[L] To Amane's room.
Sorry, I know you're on your father's side
in all this,
but I can't remove these handcuffs.
I'm afraid you're gonna have
to come along with me.
[Misa humming]
[door opening]
[gasps] Light! I didn't know we were
supposed to have a date!
Oh, right. I should have known.
-Misa Amane.
-[Light grunts]
Tell me, do you love Light
from the bottom of your heart?
Huh?
-Yeah! Of course I do.
-But you also worship Kira, don't you?
Well, yeah...
So, then. If you had to choose
between Light and Kira,
-who would you pick?
-What?
That's obvious.
Of course it's gonna be Light.
I'm really grateful to Kira and want
to meet him someday in person,
but that's not true love.
I definitely choose Light.
But your precious Light is planning
to catch Kira.
Isn't that right?
-Well yes, of course I am.
-[Misa yelps]
He says he wants to catch Kira.
Now what will you do?
Well, if that's what Light says,
then I'm gonna support him no matter what.
[L] I see.
So, if you were given the opportunity
to work with Light on this investigation,
-would you take the offer?
-What? Ryuzaki--
Yeah! Of course I would.
I'd do anything I could to help Light!
Wait. Hold on a second.
Where are you going with this?
[L] I'm planning to have Aiber
pose as Eraldo Coil again.
He'll tell the Yotsuba members
that while he was investigating L,
he discovered that Misa Amane
might know who he is.
He'll also tell them that L brought her
in for questioning
on the suspicion that she was
the second Kira.
[Misa] That part is true.
If the Yotsuba Group believes that Misa
could be their lead to finding L,
then they'll say
that they want to meet her
to discuss their advertising campaign.
They'll use that opportunity
to question her.
Thanks to Matsuda's screw up,
they may already be considering Misa
as their new spokesperson,
so this could work.
Yeah. Right.
-We can't do that.
-Why not?
This plan is too risky.
Who knows what could happen to you?
[gasps] Oh, wow. Does that mean
you're worried about me? Yay!
But don't worry.
I won't mind doing something like this
if it's for you, Light.
Listen, Misa. If they suspect
that you might know who L really is,
we don't know how far they'll be willing
to go to get that information.
No problemo. I promise I won't
say anything, even if they torture me.
I can attest to that.
But Kira can control his victim's actions
before their death.
There's a good chance
he might try to manipulate her
into revealing what she knows
and then kill her.
Also, if he does manage to kill L,
he won't have any use for Misa.
He'd kill her to keep her silent.
I don't like the sound of that.
-[L] Light.
-Hmm?
You forget that if we win against Kira,
Misa won't die.
Besides, as long as we're handcuffed
together, you and I share the same fate.
If I die, so will you.
[Misa whimpers]
[L] If that happens, Misa is the one
who would grieve most of all.
Either we lose and both die together,
or we successfully catch Kira.
Which is it?
We catch Kira! I would never dream
about living in a world without Light.
-Yes, that would be dark.
-Cut it out. This is just crazy.
We're running out of time
and I'm starting to get desperate.
As for Misa Amane, I've turned to her
because I know her bravery
and love for you is boundless.
Do you really mean it?
Oh, no. I think I've totally
misunderstood you all this time.
I even called you a pervert.
But you actually do understand
how I feel, don't you?
Yes. Misa is indisputably the most perfect
and worthy woman for Light.
Yay!
You're such a sweetie. Thank you, Ryuzaki.
I could actually fall for you.
[Misa] Let's not go that far.
But you could maybe be a friend of mine.
Would that be okay?
Yes. So now I've gained
yet another friend.
Yeah! Of course, any friend of Light's
is a friend of mine as well. [laughs]
-Let's all be friends together!
-[L] Yay, fun...
And of course, I would never think
of betraying any of my friends.
With our powers combined,
we'll arrest Kira!
-[L] Unfortunately...
-Huh?
Light's taking a different
investigative approach from us
and will be working with his father
and the others.
-[Light] Huh?
-[L] I'm afraid it'll just be you and I.
Huh? What's up with that?
Come on, L, now you're just playing dirty.
You're leaving me with no other choice
but to join your--
[L] No, that's quite all right.
[Misa] What are you talking about?
Of course he'll be joining us!
That's not it either.
I've been opposed to this investigation
since the beginning.
-It's too dangerous for her.
-Oh, Light…
You're so sweet.
Thank you for worrying about me.
But please let me do this.
I wanna be useful to you somehow.
If I can be useful,
then maybe you'll love me even more.
And besides, I would gladly die
if it were for you, Light.
[Soichiro] Figuring out the logistics
of arresting seven people
is going to be challenging.
I don't suppose you two have any ideas?
Mogi? Matsuda?
TO BE CONTINUED
[theme music playing]