[Kyosuke Higuchi] Then, once you're
fully convinced that I'm the real thing,
-you and I can get married.
-[gasping]
And so, based on what he said,
Higuchi is Kira.
GUIDANCE
[tense music playing]
[L] If the killing of criminals stops now,
then there's no doubt that Higuchi
is the one with Kira's powers.
However...
I knew that Amane would do
almost anything for Light Yagami, but…
but to think she would
actually go this far?
If criminals do stop dying after this
it will make it difficult to determine
a critical element:
How Kira conducts his murders.
I have to think of a plan.
Misa, how did you get Higuchi to confess?
Easy. That guy is totally in love with me.
All I had to do was tell him
I'd marry him if he was really Kira.
Plus, I managed to convince him
that I'm the second Kira.
[Misa Amane] If I didn't say this now,
I'd probably end up
contradicting my story later.
Misa, you idiot!
Didn't I tell you to deny all that?
[Misa]
But now we know Higuchi is Kira, right?
So what's the problem?
Can't we just catch him?
I suppose this is what you would call
a victory, right? Matsuda?
[Light chuckles]
But right now, we still don't know exactly
how he kills his victims, do we.
Yes, that's what I was thinking.
Before we move to arrest Higuchi,
I want to find out how he kills people.
If the criminals stop dying,
we'll be able to figure it out,
unless we come up with another idea.
Isn't that right?
Yes. At any rate,
even if we do arrest Higuchi,
we're not going to do it
until we're certain
that criminals have stopped dying.
Let me think about this for a moment.
-[L] Wedy.
-[Wedy] Yeah.
An update on the current situation,
please.
[Wedy]
Everything's going smoothly.
We should be able to track 70%
of their movements
using our cameras
inside the office building.
[L]
What about outside of the office?
That's not going to be possible
with just Watari and me.
What if you just focus solely on Higuchi?
Higuchi?
I've only been able to enter the houses
of five of the men, so far.
But Mido, Namikawa and Higuchi's
all have super high tech security systems.
Especially Higuchi.
He recently constructed a dampening room
that shuts out any electronic waves.
It took me two days
just to break into the place.
This guy sure does sound suspicious.
Hmm. All right. Then begin installing
microphones, trackers, and cameras.
But not in the house.
Instead just put them in every car.
[Wedy] What? After getting this far?
Do you know how difficult it is
to get break into someone's house?
Besides, do you have any idea
how many cars this guy has?
[L] He has six.
Fine then. I just have to install them
in all his cars, right?
Yes, thank you.
[Misa] Oh, if Higuchi had been bugged
earlier, I would have been in big trouble.
[L] Light, I'm sorry
to keep coming back to this topic...
I'll just get right to the point...
[Light] What is it?
Do you remember?
Killing anyone, I mean?
[Light] Huh?
[upset] Are you still going on about that?
Look, I'm not Kira. How many times do I--
I just want you to answer the question.
Well, do you remember?
No, I don't.
Misa, what about you?
I don't remember.
How could I, because I'm not Kira.
Look, Light. Please listen to
what I'm about to say.
I'd like you to thoroughly analyze
my current theory.
This could determine the way
in which we end up catching Kira.
[L] Light Yagami used to be Kira.
Kira's power has somehow
passed on to another person.
Light Yagami now has no memory
of ever being Kira.
I need your analysis,
based on these assumptions.
Do you think you can do that for me?
[Light] Yeah, I'll give it a try.
[L] Light Yagami used to be Kira.
Kira's power has somehow been passed on
to another person.
Was that because Light Yagami
wanted that to happen?
Or was there someone else
in control of Light,
lurking in the background,
who gave him the power?
Was it that person who passed
Light's powers to someone else?
Given your premise,
it would be my will.
[L] Yes, of course.
If there is a third party with the ability
to bestow or transfer Kira's power,
and they didn't want their method
to be discovered,
It makes no sense
that they would wait so long
to transfer it from you to the next Kira.
If we believe that this was the work
of some being, watching us from above,
then we'd have to accept
that they are impossible to catch.
Not to mention that I'd already be dead,
or at the very least I'm being made
to be a fool
by eternally dancing in the palm
of someone's hand.
It's highly unlikely
that such a being exists.
[L] Even if Light Yagami was Kira…
Kira's power can only be transferred by
the will of the person who possesses it.
Thank you, Light. I can now say
that I feel 99 percent better.
We'll create a situation where Higuchi
will not be able
to pass on his power to anyone else
We'll have him show us
how he kills.
So, what are you going to do?
[L] I'm going to trick Higuchi
using Sakura TV.
-Like a hidden camera show!
-[Misa] What?
[L] We'll use The Kira Special
that Demegawa airs every week.
We'll book a three hour time slot.
It'll be announced that Kira's identity
will be revealed
near the end of the special.
Would anyone actually buy that, though?
This is Sakura TV, after all.
[Matsuda] For all we know,
Higuchi might not even watch that program.
We'll get Namikawa to call him
and say
"This is bad. Turn on your TV."
That should be enough to get him watching.
[Light] Higuchi will buy it once he
realizes that the special guest on TV
is someone who knows his secret.
Oh, I get it.
So, we'll be using Aiber, then.
[Matsuda]
He'll reveal that he was a spy all along.
No, I'm afraid you're incorrect.
We will not be using Aiber.
[L] Whoever appears on the show...
has to be someone who Higuchi believes
he'll be able to kill.
[L] In other words, it has to be someone
whose name he can look up easily.
But we're never going to find
a person like that, are we?
[everyone] Hmm...
-You're the only one who can do it.
-Matsu!
Matsuda.
Higuchi probably thinks that
you were listening in on their meeting.
and overheard their plans
to kill people.
[Light] It would make sense that
Misa's manager, who he thought was dead,
-is the one revealing his secret.
-That's right.
We'll have Sakura TV use a voice filter
and frosted glass
to protect your identity.
Higuchi will probably realize from
the announcement and the silhouette
that it's the manager, Taro Matsui.
[L] And just to make sure,
we'll have the studio mess up
and accidentally reveal your face
from behind the frosted glass.
Wow! Sounds exciting.
[L] Until the show ends, the announcer
will keep saying they'll reveal
the full name of H,
who's acting as Kira.
Higuchi would feel cornered.
He'd have no choice but to find out
the manager's name as soon as possible.
We can anticipate what actions he'll take.
We'll witness his killing method.
After that, we arrest him.
There is one potential problem
with this plan.
If Higuchi can kill
by simply looking at someone's face,
just like the second Kira...
-Matsuda will die.
-[gasps]
But, considering the fact
that you're still alive,
and how he's pursuing Misa,
I doubt that's the case.
[L] At any rate,
we're only going to do this
once criminals stop dying.
We'll have to wait for two or three days
to see whether or not that happens.
[L] In the meantime,
Matsuda will have to decide
if he wants to go through
with this plan.
Hm.
[Matsuda] I don't need two or three days
to decide.
I want to do this.
[Reiji Namikawa] Well I'm here.
What's with this private meeting?
Namikawa, tell me,
who do you think is Kira?
[scoffs]
Why do you want to know what I think?
Besides, for all I know,
it could be you, Shimura.
Or maybe even Mido.
Shimura can't be Kira,
he was the one who came crying to me
about how he can't go along
with Kira's crimes anymore.
Really? But if Mido had turned out
to be Kira, you would have been killed.
No, you and Mido would have
been successful on your own.
There's no way either of you would need
to hold those stupid meetings,
let alone with seven others.
[Shimura] I can at least see that much.
We're all cooperating with these killings
because we're afraid
of Kira turning on us.
I mean it's only a matter of time
until the public finds out.
And this isn't going to stop
until that happens.
So, Shimura, let me ask you then.
Who do you think Kira might be?
Takahashi or Higuchi.
No, Takahashi is just a decoy.
Kira would make sure
there are people less clever than him.
Huh. Well then it looks like
we all know the truth already.
[Namikawa] It's Higuchi, isn't it.
Yes, he's the one who's most obsessed
with money and success.
He might always act like
he's not interested in those things,
but that just proves it all the more.
And he always insults everyone around him
and can't use his people well.
I believe that's why he was demoted
from being head of
the development department.
By the way, I meant to ask,
was I the only one you invited here?
[Shingo Mido] I also invited Ooi, but...
but he said, "You can hold your stupid,
private meetings by yourself."
-Go figure.
-[Namikawa] Ha!
Good old Ooi,
always the blunt one.
[Mido] We can also rule out Kida
as a possible suspect,
as he was the one who provided
the account for funds
in order to commission Coil.
Namikawa, during that first meeting
after Hatori died,
you got a call on your cell phone.
I was wondering who it was from.
Hm, you know, Shimura,
you're really are a sharp one.
Kira probably selected you
because he appreciates your caution.
[phone rings]
[Namikawa] Hm.
Namikawa speaking.
It's L.
-Before I go on, are you by yourself?
-No.
[Light] Then just act like
it's a normal call again.
I don't think there's any need for that.
One of the people here with me
was just expressing his suspicions
about your last phone call.
Who is that on the line? Namikawa?
-It's L.
-[gasping]
L, Mido and Shimura are here as well.
I'm reasonably certain
that neither of them are Kira.
In fact, they seem fed up with it
at this point.
I'll speak for them and say
they choose to stand back
and watch your face-off with Kira,
like I plan to.
Hm. That's fine.
Tonight, I'm going to catch Kira.
But I'll need a favor from you.
[Namikawa] Hm.
Then it's the end for Higuchi.
What? You know that it's him?
Ha! So even the great L
can be tricked.
Based on your reaction,
I'm now a hundred percent certain
that Higuchi is Kira.
Namikawa is pretty smart, huh?
But then I always thought he was,
from looking at his face.
I guess this proves it.
No, that was just because Light messed up.
I'm baiting Higuchi
with a staged TV special tonight,
Sakura TV.
[Light] A few minutes into the program,
I want you to contact Higuchi.
Tell him to tune in.
Do that for me
and I won't go after you
or any of the other five.
If the others, Kida, Takahashi,
and Ooi if they try to do anything,
make sure to stop them.
All right, I understand.
It seems it really was Higuchi.
He'll be captured tonight, apparently.
[laughing]
It's been about three days
since I stopped killing criminals.
That should be good enough,
shouldn't it?
Now, when I marry Misa Amane,
The Second Kira...
I'll have the Shinigami eyes.
With that power in my hands,
Yotsuba will be under my control.
[laughs maniacally]
[phone rings]
Higuchi, we've got a problem.
Turn on the television.
Check out Sakura TV.
[Higuchi] Hm?
KIRA'S IDENTITY
[MC] So, you're saying
one of those people is Kira, right?
[Matsuda, voice disguised] Yes. I've got
a lot of evidence to prove it, too.
What the hell is this?
Come on, it's probably a hoax.
This is Sakura TV.
[Namikawa] No, it's more than that.
At the beginning of the show
he said he overheard
a meeting,
between eight people.
[Higuchi] What?
Someone who knows about the meetings?
Who is it? Did someone betray us?
[Matsuda] One of them was killed by Kira
and now there are only seven left.
The man who died was Mr. H.
[Higuchi]
Mr. H? Hatori…
If he knows this much,
he could be one of the other six.
No, maybe it's Coil?
[Matsuda] Mr. H wanted to leave
the meetings
and was killed by Kira because of that.
[Higuchi] No, it can't be any
of the others,
there's no benefit for them
to do this.
But no one else knows about the meetings,
do they?
Damn it, who is it?
What?
Wait, could it be...
-[scraping sound]
-[Matsuda winces]
It's-- it’s him!
[clamoring]
It's Misa's manager.
Matsui, that's his name.
Why is he still alive?
[Namikawa] He explained earlier
that he thought he was going to be killed.
He pretended to fall out of
the apartment window
and escaped to a balcony
a few floors below.
[Higuchi] That can't be.
Just to be careful, I went home that night
and wrote his name in the notebook
like it was written on his business card.
TARO MATSUI
[Higuchi] Why is he still alive then?
Could he be a former entertainer
who became a manager
using his stage name?
Is that possible?
If that weren't bad enough,
he said that he continued
to investigate Yotsuba up until now
and he's figured out
which one of us is Kira.
I'm contacting everyone right now
to let them know.
All right. We'll talk later.
[MC] Sir, we are terribly sorry
for that accident. Are you all right?
We can stop if you want.
[Matsuda] No. I knew I was going to be
in danger going into this.
This is for the sake of justice.
So I'll see it through to the end
even if it means my death.
[man] Yeah, that's perfect.
Listen, just be sure to hold off on
the Kira announcement
until the last minute, all right?
[Higuchi]
I have to kill him.
Calm down. Misa knows his face,
so if she's the Second Kira,
she should know what his real name is.
[phone beeps]
[phone rings]
It's him.
-[busy signal]
-[Higuchi groans]
What the hell.
[Matsuda] To be honest,
I've been debating
for a long time whether or not
I should make this announcement.
But now that I'm here, I know I've done
the right thing in coming forward.
This is bad.
Who knows
when they'll make the announcement
[MC] ...Kira's identity will be
announced soon.
[phone rings]
[voice-over on TV]
Cosme Misa.
-A devilish charm, an angel's glitter…
-[Misa giggles on-screen]
Misa's new line of lipstick.
Just for you.
Mido, it's me.
Are you watching Sakura TV?
Why don't you call your father
at the House of Councilors.
Have him pulls some strings
at the Ministry of Internal Affairs
to stop this broadcast.
I'm watching but I don't think
we could stop it.
[Mido] No one believes this program
so we'd only make ourselves
look suspicious if we stop it.
[gasps]
Besides, there shouldn't be
anything to worry about.
That guy revealed his face earlier.
Everyone knows it's really Taro Matsui.
Namikawa has already gone ahead
and told to watch the show.
Since one of us seven has to be Kira,
that should mean
Taro Matsui will soon be dead.
-Right?
-[Higuchi] Of course.
I'm the only one who knows
or even suspects
that Taro Matsui
isn't his real name.
That means, if I say anything,
it will reveal the fact that I'm Kira.
-[MC] That's right...
-Yeah,
that's true. I'll talk to you later.
[MC] Stay tuned to Sakura TV
Damn it!
[dials number]
[computer beeps]
[Soichiro Yagami] Ryuzaki, Mogi is in
position in front of Yoshida Productions.
He's just received a call from Higuchi.
Yes, it's time for phase two.
Everything's as planned.
[Higuchi] Moji, where's Misa?
[Mogi] Oh, Mr. Higuchi,
a pleasure to hear from you.
I'm sorry but Misa Misa is taking
a much-needed vacation right now.
She should be back by, oh,
tomorrow morning though.
You can reach her then.
[Higuchi] I'm asking you
where she is now.
[Mogi] Well that's private information.
She's requested
that no one know where she is.
I'm very sorry. I'll have her contact you
tomorrow, first thing.
[Higuchi] Damn. I know his face.
I could kill him at any time,
if I only knew his name!
Do you know if Misa's former manager was
an entertainer at some point?
-Come again?
-[Higuchi] I'm talking about Taro Matsui.
[Mogi] Oh. I was only recently hired
[chuckles] so I don't know much about him.
If you need some information I can let you
talk to someone from the office
I just remembered, everyone's in Okinawa
at the moment.
You could try calling the president,
though.
This is going exactly as I planned.
It's almost scary.
You shouldn't be scared, Light.
You should be happy.
[Yagami]
I'm patching you into Higuchi's call
with the president of Yoshida Productions
[Higuchi] This is Higuchi from Yotsuba.
That manager's real name
isn't Taro Matsui...
He's not even pretending to hide
what he's asking about now, is he.
Stupid Higuchi.
If he's acting like that
it's proof he's beginning to panic.
Then what was his real name?
[President of YP] I think it was Yamada…
No, wait... Yamashita.
Yeah. And his first name was…
I'm sorry, I can't remember.
[yelling] Don't screw with me!
Why the hell can't you remember
the names of the people you hire?
[President of YP] All right, no need
for that kind of language.
I've got his personnel file
back at the office.
Then go back there and get it.
[President of YP] You've gotta be
kidding me. Give me a break.
We're on our first company vacation
in two years!
But if you want to know that badly,
I'll give you the pin code
for the office lock.
You can go in yourself
and look it up, how's that?
The personnel files are in the desk
at the back to the left.
You'll find them filed in
the bottom drawer.
They should all be sorted alphabetically.
But I'm pretty sure it was Yamashita.
[Higuchi] If they're going to announce
at the end of the program,
that means I have two hours.
[Misa] So, what's he going to do?
[engine revs]
[Wedy] I see Higuchi.
He's only carrying a single bag.
I'm in pursuit.
Everything is still going
according to plan.
Yes.
I'll kill him.
I'll kill him no matter what.
I've come this far,
I won't let them stop me.
I'm not giving up
until I have everything.
[laughs maniacally]
TO BE CONTINUED
[theme music plays]