KIRA'S IDENTITY
[MC] So you're saying
one of those people is Kira, right?
[Matsuda, voice disguised]
Yes.
I've got a lot of evidence
to prove it, too.
The man who died was Mr. H.
[L] If Higuchi can kill
by looking at someone's face
like the second Kira was able to,
-Matsuda will die.
-[Matsuda gasps]
SPECIAL REPORT ON KIRA
THE CONCLUSION
TODAY'S SHOW WILL REVEAL
THE TRUE IDENTITY OF KIRA
It's... It's him!
[screaming] Don't screw with me.
Why the hell can't you remember
the names of the people you hire.
That means I have two hours.
[engine revs]
[tires squeal]
[Wedy]
I see Higuchi.
He's only carrying a single bag.
I'm in pursuit.
[Kyosuke Higuchi] I'll kill him.
I'll kill him no matter what.
I'm not giving up until I have everything.
FRENZY
[voice-over] Cosme Misa.
A devilish charm.
An angel's glitter.
Misa's new line of lipstick
just for you.
Ryuzaki, the commercial's almost over.
Oh, is that so?
[Matsuda] Next thing you know,
I'm in a hotel room,
drinking with all eight of them.
[MC laughs]
Well, that's rather amusing.
[Matsuda] But if I give you
any more details,
I'm afraid the people who were there
that night
would realize
which one of them is Kira.
So I think I'd better leave it at that
for now.
[MC] Of course.
Please take your time to tell us
all the details of your ordeal
to find Kira.
[L] Light, please put Higuchi's car
on audio channel one.
and Sakura TV on channel two.
[Light Yagami] As expected,
Higuchi is watching every minute of this
from his car.
[MC] And so, according to you,
it was actually at that party
that you met Kira.
[Matsuda] Yes.
But of course at the time,
I had no way of knowing
he was actually Kira.
[MC] So, that means he saw your face.
This is incredible.
I think it's amazingly courageous of you
to step forward and appear
on this program.
-Are you sure you're okay with it?
-[Matsuda] Yes.
After I started investigating him,
I found out there are two things
Kira has to have
in order to kill someone.
There are rumors on TV and the internet
as to what those two things might be
but I know the truth.
[Higuchi]
A name and a face.
[Matsuda] But Kira only knows
one of those two things about me.
so that means I should be safe.
[Higuchi] So he's saying he feels
safe enough to step forward
just because I don't know
his real name.
Wait a minute, does that mean
there's nothing left that can connect me
to his name?
Maybe he's already destroyed his file
at Yoshida.
Am I'm wasting my time?
Rem, what do you think?
What do I think? About what, may I ask?
Rem, who's that?
There's no one else in that car, right?
It's impossible for someone to be hiding
without us knowing.
He isn't using his cell phone.
Could it be a hidden radio?
No. There's aren't any radios
or other devices.
Only the bugs, cameras, and tracking
beacons that Wedy placed.
I have no doubt that she did
a thorough job.
Do you think I'll get
to Yoshida Productions
only to find his file isn't there?
Is he talking to himself?
Why ask my opinion? I don't see how
I'm supposed to know something like that.
If this guy was smart,
he would destroy everything
that connects him with his real name
before he appeared on TV.
[Higuchi] And don't you think
it's a little too reckless
for Yoshida Productions to just let me
into their offices unsupervised?
Hm, maybe not. If there was a robbery
they'd figure out right away who did it,
since I know where the key is.
This isn't sounding very good.
He'll still go there,
don't you worry.
Even if he does have a file at Yoshida,
it could be just another alias.
Damn it. I wouldn't put it past this guy
to do something like that.
No wonder he's confident.
[Rem] It must be Light and Misa's plan
to have Higuchi go
to Yoshida Productions.
If that's the case...
That may be true,
but if he knows that you are Kira,
he's going to announce your name
in public.
That's an inescapable fact.
[MC]
All right, there's only one hour left
until the big announcement.
Your only option is to go.
If the name on his file is false
that will be unfortunate.
But if it isn't,
you can kill him discretely
with the notebook.
Yeah, I already know that much
myself.
But just to be on the safe side,
I should kill the people
I contacted at Yoshida Productions.
That includes the president, Misa,
and that manager of hers.
What? No way, he's going to kill me?
It's all right. Don't worry.
He's talking about doing that
after he's killed Matsuda.
There would be no point in killing
the rest of you
until he's gotten rid of
the main threat.
That's true, but still...
[Rem] Don't be reckless.
He's the only one you have to kill.
If the people you called
end up dying too,
the phone records will implicate you
in their deaths.
Oh yeah. Rem, I didn't think
you were so smart.
Then I'll make them all erase
their call histories before they die.
But the telephone company
will still have a record of the calls.
There's no way he can
just be talking to himself.
But, who's Rem? Who is he talking to?
If he's talking to someone right now,
it could be...
a Shinigami.
[Misa whimpers]
Perhaps.
[Rem] I should just go ahead and ask him.
How about giving up ownership
of the notebook and returning it to me?
No, I'd end up being ruined
if I did that.
Even if I forgot the notebook
this guy says he has concrete evidence
to back him up.
If he points out Yotsuba's recent growth
on the air
no one would ever doubt his claims.
They'd believe whatever he said.
That means whoever he says is Kira
will be marked as Kira.
Even if he didn't have proof
and I got rid of the evidence
by returning the notebook,
my life would be over.
I wouldn't get promoted, I wouldn't even
be able to stay with Yotsuba.
[MC] Of course, Sakura TV has
broadcast this show
under the premise that right now,
as we speak,
Kira is watching this program.
[Matsuda] In that case,
I'll take this chance to call out to him.
Kira, please turn yourself in.
[Higuchi] The guy is acting like
a complete idiot.
Still, he was smart enough to fake his own
death to avoid being killed.
-I have to kill him as soon as possible.
-[tires squeal]
-[engine shuts off]
-[car door opens, shuts]
He's arrived at Yoshida Productions.
The show is about to begin.
[footsteps approach]
[door unlocks]
To the left as I come in.
The desk at the very back.
The very bottom drawer.
MANAGER
TAICHIRO YAMASHITA
[L] Now, Kira, how do you kill?
Show me!
We're in position
and ready to take him down.
-We'll move on your command.
-[L] Right.
TAICHIRO YAMASHITA
[groans with pleasure]
He's not doing it. He just made
a note of his name before leaving.
So, he's not going to kill him here?
Ryuzaki, do you want us
to apprehend him?
Negative. We still don't know
how he kills.
Perhaps he's planning to do something
once he's back in the car.
[L] Let's see camera one again.
-[beeping]
-[clicking]
It's weird, you'd think he'd be desperate
to kill Matsuda this very second
but he's calm.
It is strange.
If all he needed was the name,
then he should have taken
the personnel file with him.
But he just put it back in its drawer
after taking the note.
[Higuchi]
Thirty-six, 37...
Thirty-eight, 39...
Forty seconds.
[Matsuda] Kira is a cold-blooded murderer.
I can't forgive him for what he's done.
[grunts]
Damn, he didn't die.
[Light] What's he talking about?
He said he didn't die.
[L] Did he already try and kill Matsuda?
Was writing his name down
all he had to do, or was it...
What do we do know?
Should we just continue watching
what he's doing?
What if he can cause a death
by just imagining it?
[L] I don't understand what's going on.
I still can't figure out how
he kills people.
But even if we restrain him now
and try to get him to confess...
[MC] Only fifty minutes to go
-until the big Kira announcement!
-Damn!
I don't have any time!
-[phone dialing]
-[Light] He's making a phone call.
It's probably Misa again.
-[phone rings]
-[Misa] Yeah!
Huh?
[groans]
[yells]
All right, calm down.
I already know his face.
If I go back to company HQ
there should be surveillance videos
from when he snuck in.
If I had the Shinigami eyes...
Half of my remaining lifespan, huh?
That's a lot. But if he makes
that announcement
my life is as good as over anyway.
Better to have a life
that's short and sweet.
Rem, let's make the deal.
[high pitched ringing]
The deal? Who is this Rem person
he keeps talking to?
Could it really be that Kira's power comes
from another world or some being?
I really don't want to think
that's the case.
Then what is this Rem?
A Shinigami?
Whatever it is, we need
to keep watching him.
We'll learn nothing if we take him now.
We may still be able to find out
how he kills.
[Higuchi] With these eyes
I'm invincible.
I have more than enough options now.
[engines rev]
[Soichiro Yagami] We're heading after him.
[siren wails]
[police] You in the red car,
pull over to the side of the road.
-[Higuchi grunts]
-[police] Now!
[Wedy] This is bad.
Higuchi's been pulled over by
a traffic cop.
[Wedy] I'm going to have to pass him
and leave the pursuit to Aiber's team.
You were speeding. License, please.
Yeah, no problem.
Switch all screens to Higuchi's car.
[Higuchi] Let's see.
Where did I put it.
[high pitched ringing]
[Higuchi] This will take care of him.
YUKITO SHIRABA, ACCIDENT
[engine revs]
[police] Hey!
Higuchi ditched the cop.
He's driving away.
[siren blares]
What a bastard!
This is traffic control squad.
[cries out]
[tires squeal]
That motorcycle cop just rear-ended
that truck. He's dead.
He's dead?
By accident?
This is very bad.
[L] All he did was put his hand
in his bag.
Could he have done something
in that moment?
More importantly,
how was he able to obtain
the name of the cop who stopped him?
Does he only need a face,
like the second Kira?
Rem. A deal.
[L] No, if he had the power to kill
by looking at someone's face,
he would have already killed
Matsuda by now.
What's going on?
Unless...
Everyone! It's too dangerous
to allow further action by Higuchi!
Let's bring him in.
[L] I believe he has the same powers
as the second Kira.
He is able to kill
just by looking at someone's face.
Please keep this in mind
when you move in to arrest him.
[cars approaching]
[chuckles]
[L] Watari, connect me
to the director of the NPA.
[Watari]
Yes.
[L] This is L. We are now aware of
Kira's true identity.
He's currently heading
from Hibiya to Shibuya
along Highway Route One,
in a red sports car.
Our group will be handling the arrest.
In the meantime,
please instruct all officers
to refrain from approaching his car.
All right, Dad. During the next commercial
take measure seven.
Understood.
Demegawa,
during the next commercial break,
swap Matsuda and the MC
with mannequins.
We'll make it seem as if the broadcast
is continuing as normal
using the voices we've already prepared.
We'll leave the cameras running
and everyone evacuate the building.
So then, Light.
What say we go join the fun as well.
Yeah.
[Misa] Huh?
I'm sorry to do this, Misa,
but I have to make sure
you're restrained for a while.
[yelling] What? But that's...
Stop joking around.
[helicopter propeller thrums]
[Light] I didn't realize you could pilot
a helicopter. That's incredible.
[L] Well, you can figure it out
with intuition.
[Light] Higuchi isn't going to Sakura TV.
He's headed the wrong way.
[L] Based on his route, I'd guess
he's coming to the Yotsuba main office.
[MC]
You've been outstandingly brave.
[Matsuda] No. I'm just doing
what anyone would do.
[Higuchi] If I go to the main office
and find the surveillance video
with him on it, I can kill him.
Come in, Wedy.
Have you removed absolutely everything
relating to Matsuda
at the Yotsuba headquarters?
[Wedy] Yeah.
Why, is he headed there now?
Isn't that convenient.
That should give me more than enough time
to go ahead and meet up with Mr. Yagami
to set up the ambush.
-[tires squeal]
-[car door opens, shuts]
[Higuchi] What the hell, I can't find him!
This is the right tape.
Someone must have erased it.
Did he come back
and erase them himself somehow?
Or has someone from the group betrayed me
and started working with him?
No, doing that would not
absolve them of their crimes.
Who cares. I'm out of time.
I've got to hurry!
[engine starts]
[MC] We're quickly approaching
the time for the announcement.
How are you feeling?
[Matsuda] I feel ready for this.
I really want you to do it now.
[MC] Yes, I understand. But let's cut to
a quick commercial break first.
[Higuchi] Damn it!
I have to go to Sakura TV
and kill him there.
[engine revs]
Dad, Higuchi has left Yoshiba.
He's on his way to Sakura TV.
He'll be there in less than 15 minutes.
Are you ready?
[Yagami] I don't need my son asking
if I'm ready.
Of course I am.
[MC] Is there anything more you'd like
to add before the announcement?
[Matsuda] I want everyone to think hard
about Kira after he's caught.
People have to realize
that Kira is...
You ready, Mr. Yagami?
It's almost time
I know.
-[Wedy] Here.
-Hm?
Aiber hates using guns.
Right now, I'm the only one armed.
I can't take this.
I'm no longer a police officer.
Japanese law forbids civilians
from having guns.
That means you shouldn't be
using one either.
I guess you're as stubborn as always, huh?
SAKURA TV
[groans]
I made it in time.
Huh?
Why isn't anybody here?
Is it just in case the announcement
is true and Kira decides to retaliate?
Hm. At least it makes my job easier.
[Mogi] We've arrived at Sakura TV.
We're moving into position.
-Let's go, Aiber.
-Okay, Mogi!
[MC] Right now we are being flooded
with phone calls and faxes
showing support for
your courage and strength
and demanding that Kira's identity
be revealed right away.
[Higuchi] Huh?
Even the studio is deserted.
Still, I've got to be careful of
where the cameras are.
Can't let myself be seen.
[MC] ...beyond our control,
we will now end this broadcast,
[Higuchi] What?
Dummies. This can't be!
-[Yagami] Higuchi, hold it right there.
-[gasping]
[Wedy] Don't move!
I'd give up
if I were you.
You... you must be making
some kind of mistake.
I'm only here to meet with Mr. Demegawa
and discuss something with him.
[Higuchi] They're wearing tinted helmets.
They must be taking precautions
against Kira.
In that case...
I'm with the Yotsuba Group,
from the Development Department.
Let me show you my business card.
[Higuchi yells]
[grunting]
[Aiber] No, Chief!
[Wedy] Aiber!
Damn it!
I didn't want to use one of these, but...
No!
L, Higuchi has a gun on him.
The chief has been shot.
Higuchi is escaping!
[Yagami] I'm all right. Sorry, Ryuzaki.
If we pursue him,
we can still catch him. Hurry!
This is bad. He's escaped from Sakura TV!
[engine revs]
[tires squeal]
This leaves us no choice.
We'll have to move in
and apprehend him.
Watari, are you ready?
-Yes.
-[L] Light...
I think you should hold on to this
for self-defense.
This is Kira we're after.
No thanks.
Firearms aren't allowed in Japan.
You know, I'm sure your father
would say the exact same thing.
[honking]
He's driving like a maniac.
-Don't lose sight of him.
-Yes.
-[grunts]
-[tires squeal]
[helicopter propeller thrums]
[Higuchi]
What the hell was all that about?
It had to be a trap.
[TV announcer]
We now end our current broadcast
and return you to regular programming.
The evening news is next.
[Higuchi] The program is over!
It didn't end just because I showed up.
What the hell is going on?
[cries out] What the...
[sirens wailing]
Just like I thought, it was a trap.
Police cars with tinted windows?
So all that stuff about
the police not going after Kira was a lie!
They were preparing for this.
[Watari]
What's happening?
I thought we told the police
not to get involved with the arrest.
[Light] The only one
who would do this is...
Yes, you must be right.
[grunts]
[tires squeal loudly]
[gasps]
Damn it! That way!
Stop right there!
[gasps]
[grunts]
Stay back!
Stay back or I'll shoot, I swear.
[cries out]
It's over.
Yes. It's over.
[grunting]
TO BE CONTINUED