[theme song playing]
[crunching]
Wow, it's been a long time.
Thank you for always taking
such good care of my father.
Gees, Sayu, you're all grown up.
This is Yagami.
[caller] Look, about trading the director
in exchange for the notebook...
-It's been canceled.
-[all] Huh?
The new deal is this:
The notebook for Sayu Yagami.
Come to L.A. by yourself in two days
and bring the notebook with you.
I'm pleased to meet you at last,
L Number Two.
[gasps]
I am at the center of the SPK.
You can address me as N.
N? Who is this guy?
Is he joking?
Like, this strange feeling, what is it?
IMPATIENCE
[Light] N?
Why do I feel like I'm talking to L?
[N] I told you that we wouldn't rely on L.
But that's a bit of an understatement.
The FBI and the CIA have explicitly asked
that I head up their investigation,
not you.
Having said that,
we are outraged by the recent murder
of the director of the NPA
and feel something must be done.
After revealing the information,
I believe there's a possibility
that solving this case
could lead to the arrest of Kira.
As such, I'm willing to lend you
my full support.
[Light] "Lead to the arrest of Kira"?
Who is he anyway?
This confidence.
[N] Is there a problem, L?
[Light] No.
It's just that following the death
of Takimura,
Deputy Director Yagami's daughter
was kidnapped
and we believe the same person
is behind it.
He's arranged for a trade in Los Angeles.
[N] A trade?
The girl in exchange for the notebook,
I assume?
Yes.
Understood.
I'll have a team on standby in L.A.
But for now, they'll be working
on a need-to-know basis.
My cell can monitor the city
via satellite.
Or...
On second thought, I'll let you have
full authority on this, L.
[N hangs up]
That's good.
It means we're taking the lead.
But what's all this about the Americans
not trusting L anymore?
I don't like the sound of that.
Near, is it really safe to leave this case
in the hands of a fake L?
He hasn't had any success
in catching Kira so far.
I'm aware of that.
That's why it's a good idea.
It means there'll be an opportunity
to take advantage of him.
Of course, saving people’s lives
is important,
but as the SPK,
our primary goal is very clear.
We'll work to get the notebook
and capture Kira once and for all.
-[Soichiro] Light…
-Hmm?
At this point, I don't care
if it costs me my life.
Please, just save Sayu.
Promise me.
Stop talking like that, Dad!
You might have made your peace
with the idea of dying,
but have you ever thought
about how painful it would be
for everyone else you leave behind?
I'd never be able to forgive you
if you ended up dying in front of Sayu.
Look, it's true that you might
lose contact with us.
But if that happens and you have to make
a split-second decision by yourself,
then I want you to do whatever's necessary
to make sure both you and Sayu
get out of this alive.
Promise me, Dad.
All right.
[Misa] What? No way!
You really want me
to go to Los Angeles with you?
Yeah, there's a chance I might need
to use your eyes this time,
so I want to have you close by.
Oh, Light! You're the best!
Oh my gosh,
I'd better start packing right away.
[chuckling]
[Misa giggles]
Let's see, which one should I bring?
I can't decide.
Light, which do you like? Hmm?
Huh...
[water pouring]
If things go badly,
I may have to kill Sayu.
[bird chirping]
[Light] Dad, I'll fly to L.A. ahead of you
and make preparations for the handover.
Ide and the others
should arrive shortly after,
but to be safe, we should all arrive
on separate flights.
Aizawa, I want you
to tail my father closely
and get on the same plane as him,
just in case something goes wrong.
[Aizawa] Got it.
I'm gonna get a haircut
so they won't recognize me.
[planes flying overhead]
[Light] Okay everyone,
I'm counting on you.
Mr. Yagami.
Who are you? One of the kidnappers?
You're going to board flight SE333.
I have your tickets with me.
It leaves from Gate 18.
Right, I understand.
Someone has intercepted him at Narita!
Should I arrest him?
[Light] Calm down, Mr. Aizawa.
Don't make any sudden moves.
I can understand your concern,
but arresting him now
will accomplish nothing.
Keep your distance
and don't lose sight of them.
[Aizawa] Oh, damn it...
They're boarding a different flight
than originally planned.
I'll tell them at the gate
that I'm a police officer and--
Get a hold of yourself!
You'll just blow your cover
and the operation would be ruined.
Can you find out
where the flight's headed?
Let's see... Huh?
This one's going to L.A. too.
Could they have somehow arranged
for another plane?
Oh, this is bad.
[plane engines roaring]
[air traffic control] Flight SE333?
Flight SE333, do you copy?
Do you copy?
You have strayed from your flight path.
[pilot] This is Flight SE333,
I read you loud and clear.
I assure you, everything's okay.
This is a detour.
[air traffic control] What is this?
You need to tell me
what's going on up there.
This is not a hijacking.
We're simply making a detour
and a quick stop to drop off a passenger.
[pilot] You can track us by radar.
However, if you attempt
to call the authorities
to interfere with our course,
I will not hesitate to crash the plane
and take all the passengers with me.
This is bad, Light… I mean, L.
The Deputy Director's flight
has just changed direction.
A passenger's going to be
dropped off somewhere.
It can only be him.
Damn it! What the hell is going on?
I already checked today's flight crew
and passenger lists ahead of time.
No one on board was suspicious.
The pilot's a veteran
of over fifteen years.
The co-pilot checks out clean too.
Then the kidnappers are powerful enough
to influence these people.
Uh, it looks like I have no choice.
[dialing]
Director, this is L. Get me N.
[Director] Right.
[Light] N, I'm sure you're aware
of our current situation.
I need you to do me a favor.
Can you notify the airlines,
police, and military on your end
not to take any action yet?
What's he thinking?
I never realized he was this unreliable.
All right, L, agreed.
We'll locate the landing site
and keep surveillance over the area
using our satellite video feed.
If there's anything else we can do,
don't hesitate to let us know.
I have a message for you.
Put this in your ear.
[Mello] Yagami, right now,
you're the only one who can hear my voice.
Listen very carefully.
I'm the one who kidnapped your daughter,
but don't get the wrong idea.
I have no interest
in your daughter's life,
one way or the other.
Or yours, for that matter.
There's only one thing I want
and you know what that is.
The notebook.
Now, all you have to do
is follow my instructions.
If you do that, no one has to die.
As for the trade,
I prepared things so that both of us
can walk away satisfied.
Play along and there'll be no problems.
[Soichiro] I'm going to give the notebook
to some criminal
in exchange for my daughter's life.
When the time comes,
what's the right thing to do?
As a police officer, as a human being,
and as a parent...
[plane engines roaring]
[tires screeching]
[plane engines shutting down]
[machines beeping]
L, we've been able to use
our satellite cameras
to pinpoint where the plane has landed.
I'll send you a direct video feed
of what we're currently seeing here.
Dad!
[chuckling]
So, what's gonna happen?
How will he make the exchange
in a place like that?
Hmm.
[mechanical whirring]
[Mello] You see the entrance,
don't you, Yagami?
Go inside.
They're underground?
Well, well, isn't that interesting?
[mechanical whirring]
Damn it. An underground facility?
The kidnapper must've predicted
that we'd be watching him by satellite.
That means there's no way
to keep an eye on Dad.
[clears throat]
[gasps]
[inaudible]
-[gun cocks]
-[Soichiro gasps]
[gunshots]
[man] The glass is bulletproof,
understand?
This place used to belong
to a crime syndicate.
They used to make trades just like this.
We've made a few modifications as well.
Slide the notebook through here.
Once that's done, I'll release the lock.
You'll both step back
and spin the glass door.
The notebook will end up on my side,
and the girl on yours.
However, if you don't agree to this trade,
I'll shoot your daughter
through this opening.
Hmm...
[N] L, do you have a plan?
You can't seriously think
that handing the notebook over
to someone you don't know
is a good idea, can you?
All right, Y462, proceed.
First, open the notebook
and insert it halfway into the slot
in the glass door on your left.
Damn it! Damn it!
It's setback after setback.
And I've only just arrived in the US,
so I'm not in any position
to start giving orders
to the American police.
[heavy breathing]
At this rate, the notebook's going be--
Light, is everything okay?
Is something wrong? You look kinda--
Misa, just shut up
and do what I told you, all right?
[Misa gasps]
[Light] Look, I need you to keep killing
Japanese criminals so just do that.
This guy is obviously investigating Kira
and he won't give up.
If the killings are delayed,
we're in trouble. Don't you understand?
Uh, okay. But who is this guy?
[Light] Just get on with it, all right!
Taking out your anger on her, huh?
Huh?
[ticking]
[gasps] I can still make it.
But at this rate, is my only option...
to kill Sayu?
[man] Now then, I'll test the notebook.
[Soichiro] Test it?
You're gonna kill someone?
No, I can't allow that.
We can't make the trade
without making sure it's the real thing.
Do you really want
to see your daughter die?
[Light] I can't do it.
No one but the police
knows about this case.
If Sayu dies,
I can't blame her death on Kira.
-Argh!
-[all gasp]
[groans]
What's wrong? You okay, Miller?
Look, that's what you get
when you steal from me
and sell goods behind my back.
He's a worthless idiot.
This is the first time he's been useful.
[man] Y462, the target is dead.
[laughing]
It seems the notebook
is genuine after all.
Now, let it go. We'll make the exchange
for your daughter.
[sighs]
[gasps]
Dad, Sayu...
Hey, they actually made it.
[Mason] The suspect is headed
for a helicopter.
Based on our intel, that's his only method
of transportation.
So this means we can be absolutely certain
that the notebook has been exchanged.
Hmm...
[Light] Be careful.
We still don't know what they're planning
to do beyond this point.
N, I need you to maintain surveillance
of that helicopter until it lands.
Don't lose sight of it, no matter what.
You seem to think
that's quite an easy task.
Nevertheless, we'll do what we can.
[N] I'm sorry.
I'm afraid we've been tricked.
-[Light] A missile?
-Wow!
[N] You won't be able that with radar.
Is the notebook on that thing?
[gasps]
[rocket blasting]
[Rester] The missile's been launched!
The missile or the helicopter? Which one?
[rotors whirring]
Boss, I'm sure you were watching.
I did everything you asked me to,
just like we planned.
Yeah, I saw that. Good job.
Then this is gonna wipe out
all those past screw-ups of mine, right?
Oh yeah, wiped out for sure.
Do it!
[bleeping]
Near, the helicopter...
I thought so.
In that case, it means the notebook
is definitely on the missile.
Damn! We can't track it.
We've lost the signal.
It could be anywhere now.
[machines bleeping]
[gasps]
[grunts in frustration]
[splashing]
It won't be difficult
to retrieve the missile
once it lands in a deserted area.
He would have already laid out
the flight plan accordingly.
He should be getting his hands
on the notebook any moment now.
And when he does, I have a good idea
of what he'll do next.
[dice rolling on the floor]
[groaning in pain]
[clattering]
[yelping and choking]
[gunshot]
[clattering]
[gasping]
[N] L.
[sighs]
Yes?
He got us.
-"Got" you?
-Yes.
The majority of the SPK's members
have just been killed by the notebook.
[gasps]
L, you were the one who handed over
the notebook without a fight.
You and your people were totally helpless.
N, are you saying
if you were in command,
you wouldn't have handed it over?
No, considering their preparations,
it would have been impossible
to avoid this.
There's really no point in us quarreling.
[N] I propose we work together
and share the information we know so far.
For starters, I should admit
that I have a very good idea
of who the culprit behind this might be.
[gasps]
[N] I suspect the person who arranged
the kidnapping and the trade
is someone who goes by the name "Mello."
[Light] Mello? Who is he?
[N] I don't have his photograph
and I don't know his real name.
All I know about him
is that four years ago,
he was living at an orphanage
located in Winchester, England,
known as Wammy's House.
Wammy's House?
That's the place Watari established.
[N] I believe Mello
is playing a game with me.
He wants to see which of us
will be the first to take down Kira.
The final challenge.
Armo Justin…
It's Armonia Justin.
Okay, um, I've got a little problem.
I went to the king to report
that I lost my notebook,
but after I described it to him,
the old man said
that Ryuk said it was his,
and that he had dropped it and took it.
[laughing]
What do you think I should do
to get it back?
Guess you have no choice
but to find Ryuk and ask him yourself.
Yeah, that's what I thought.
So, I guess I have
to go to the human world.
Yep, that's right.
Have fun.
Well, that sucks.
TO BE CONTINUED
[theme music playing]