[theme music plays]
I think we should do this every day.
The sun will do you good.
What in the world
am I supposed to do now?
[wind howling]
FATHER
[groans]
[Sidoh]
Hi, Ryuk.
Sidoh, what are you doing here?
Hey, quit following me.
I want my notebook.
Damn, guess I shouldn't be surprised.
Too bad.
Things got a little complicated recently.
I have no idea where it is.
Why am I not surprised?
Look, I told you,
stop following me.
Then give me back my notebook.
[exasperated]
I don't know where it is.
If you want it back, you're gonna have to
look for it yourself.
Moron.
[continues munching apple loudly]
[Shuichi Aizawa] Wammy's House
isn't exactly a normal orphanage.
It's like a school
for gifted children.
But here's the crazy part.
Its real purpose is to groom these kids
so that one of them can become the next L.
[Light Yagami] L's successor.
[Aizawa] Apparently the one most likely
to succeed L
is this kid named Near.
[Light] Near. Is that N?
Also, we founds some leads on Mello,
the one N mentioned.
He's smart too,
but he always came second to Near.
[Light] So Near was meant to be
L's successor. There's no mistake.
He has to be N.
He's the one commanding
the SPK.
As for Mello, he would have wanted
to become L's successor.
But he probably lost out to Near.
That gives him a motive
for wanting to get his hands on
the notebook first.
It all adds up perfectly.
This guy is definitely the same Mello
that N told us about.
[Aizawa]
These are sketches of both of them.
We couldn't find any photographs.
[Light] L's successors.
Looks like I'm still fighting L
after all this time.
But first thing's first.
I have to find out
where Mello and his mafia associates
are hiding themselves.
I already had Misa check
a list of known Mafia syndicates
using her Shinigami eyes.
[Misa Amane gasps] Look, I found him.
I can't see his lifespan.
He's number 105.
They have him listed as Jack Neylon.
But his real name is Kal Snydar.
He's got the notebook.
[Light] After that, it was the simple
matter of using the death note
to make Snydar send a letter to me with
the location of the gang's hideout.
It should be arriving soon.
[door creaks]
[gasps] Hi, Light.
Great news! The letter arrived.
[Light]
He's in LA.
I did it. I out-maneuvered
both Near and Mello.
Guess it's no surprise.
As long as I have the notebook
and Misa's eyes, I'm unstoppable.
So, Light. I guess this means
I was helpful to you again, doesn't it?
Yeah.
I love you, Misa.
[Misa sighs, giggles]
[Sidoh]
Los Angeles.
The next step is for me to figure out
just how much I can control people
with this thing.
[Sidoh] Oh, they're gonna have to
be able to see me
before I can even talk to them.
What a drag.
Looks like Snydar is
the owner right now.
Guess I'll have to make him
touch the notebook first.
Oh, well...
[gasps]
[Sidoh] Tag, you're it.
What the...
The notebook just flew.
[chuckles]
It's a notebook that kills people.
Hell,
nothing surprises me anymore.
[screaming]
[yelling]
Boss, who is this?
The guy in the freaky costume,
who the hell is he?
Who brought him here?
I came here on my own.
I'm actually a Shinigami.
[man] A Shinigami?
[laughs hysterically]
If you don't want everyone to think
you're crazy,
pass the notebook around
so they can see me, too.
-[groans]
-[notebook slides on floor]
He says you can see him
if you touch the notebook.
[groans]
Please, everyone, touch it.
I swear I'm not crazy.
Fine. Whatever.
Come on, guys.
Touch the notebook.
[indistinct yelling]
[bullet casings clink on floor]
Nice try.
You humans can't kill a Shinigami.
[gasping]
Jack's right.
That ain't no costume.
That's a real, live Shinigami.
So now what do we do?
[Light] Ryuk.
As of now, I'm going to forfeit ownership
of this notebook.
All I ask is that you agree to follow
whichever person I give it to.
[man] What?
You're giving up ownership again?
[Misa] But wait. Won't you lose
all your memories if you do that?
Misa, lend me your notebook.
I'll keep it on me like this.
That way, even if I forfeit ownership
of my notebook
I won't lose my memory.
I'll give you as many pages you need.
From this moment on,
you're going to be Kira.
Can you do that?
Of course. But I don't get
why you're doing this.
I'll explain everything to you right now.
I won't forgive any mistakes.
[loud munching]
-Chocolate is so good.
-Hey.
What about that stuff you told us?
Is it true?
"If the person using the note
fails to consecutively write
names of people to be killed
within 13 days of each other,
then the user will die.
If you make this note unusable
by tearing it up or burning it,
all the humans who have touched
the note till then will die."
Are you saying
those two rules were made up?
[clears throat]
Oh yeah, those rules are definitely fake.
My guess is some Shinigami wrote those
down as a joke
before giving the notebook
to a human. [munches]
[Mello] As for the 13-day rule, we can
test that out by using one of our people.
But the real question is,
was this the notebook
that was used by Kira?
And if so, was he aware
that these two rules were false?
If he did know, he could have used
these rules to his advantage.
In particular,
the 13-day rule would have allowed him
to prove his innocence
in only 13 days.
[keeps munching]
-[Mello] Sidoh, go keep watch outside.
-Huh?
It will be very convenient for us
that you can't be seen by humans.
Go outside and keep watch. Got it?
[Sidoh] What's with this guy?
He's human,
but he's scary.
[phone rings]
Yagami speaking.
This is Kira.
-[Touta Matsuda] What did he say?
-[Soichiro Yagami] Kira?
[Kira] I understand that the notebook
that was in your possession
has fallen into criminal hands.
[Yagami]
Can you prove that you are the real Kira?
[Kira] Prove it? Now that there are others
using the notebook,
there's no point in predicting killings
in order to identify myself.
They could just as easily kill
the same targets.
But don't worry,
I've already taken this into account.
I've sent you something that will
clearly prove to you that I am Kira.
It's my own notebook.
[Yagami] Wha... What do you mean?
[Kira]
The notebook I've sent you
gives me the power to know
a person's name by only seeing their face,
and you will be able to gain
that same power.
Do you understand?
[Misa] Please stay calm.
and listen carefully.
I've gathered information
from the FBI and other sources.
On November 10th, at exactly 11:59 p.m.
arrangements have been made
so that all known associates
-of the mafia will die.
-[gasping]
[Kira/Misa]
It's already written in my notebook.
so it's impossible for me to make
any changes
You will not be able
to prevent these deaths.
I already know their location.
I will hand over that information
along with the notebook,
so remember...
on November 10th, 11:59 p.m.,
that's when it all happens.
That moment is your best
and only chance to get the notebook back.
It's up to you.
[gasps softly]
[Light] What should we do?
If the Mafia members are going to die
on the day Kira specified,
it would be a chance to get
the notebook back.
I don't like the idea of following
Kira's plan, but it's our best option.
[Ryuk]
Exactly.
[Ryuk grunts]
But still,
knowing the time of death
for these guys
isn't going to be enough for us
to make our move.
[stammers] Ide, I think we both know
what needs to be done.
We get the Shinigami
to follow us in,
and then we do the deal for the eyes
and make sure they're all dead, right?
I will make the deal for the eyes.
[excitedly] No way, chief.
Let me be the one to do it.
I was responsible for handing over
the notebook in the first place.
Since that moment, I've been unable
to live with what I've done.
I've even thought of killing myself.
I'll use the notebook
to kill any criminals who try to stop us.
And after 13 days, I'll die as well.
[Light]
If Dad writes a name in the notebook,
then...
when the time comes...
NOVEMBER 10, 23:47
Report,
is everybody ready to move in?
[all] Roger.
All right. Deputy Director,
make the eye deal
with the Shinigami.
All right, Ryuk. I'm ready.
Sure thing, boss.
[loud rumbling]
[high pitched noise rings out]
Once you're finished,
I want you to look at the photographs
of the criminals I gave you.
Can you see their names and life spans?
[Yagami]
Yes, I can.
Their name should disappear soon.
That's your cue.
[clock ticking]
[screaming]
Everyone, move in!
[Mello] So, Kira's involved
after all.
I didn't think he'd go this far.
My plan was supposed to be perfect.
Damn. What the hell is Sidoh doing?
Relax, Sidoh.
Just shut up and watch, all right?
All you have to do is sit here
and do nothing.
If you can do that,
you'll get your notebook back.
Roy. Skyer.
The notebook is under Rod's body
Bring it to
the surveillance room upstairs.
[groaning]
[coughing]
[Aizawa yells] Don't move.
[Yagami] L, we've apprehended two
of the criminals .
We've also been able to secure
the notebook.
[Aizawa]
We'll being withdrawing now.
Not yet. Keep going.
-Huh?
-[man] What?
[Light] We still haven't found anyone
who resembles our picture of Mello.
That means he must be hiding
somewhere in the building.
We've come this far.
Let's finish this.
Do a thorough search.
[men scream]
-[Matsuda] What's was that?
-[Aizawa] An explosion?
[Mello] Don't move.
I've already blown up the two entrances
to this place.
This will be your only warning.
The next explosion will take out
the entire building
as well as all your men inside.
So you better do as I say.
[Light]
It's Mello.
-[Mello chuckles]
-[Yagami] Hm?
Yagami again, huh?
Maybe I should have killed you
when I had the chance.
History repeats itself.
But I never dreamed in a million years,
that I'd be bargaining for the notebook
with you again.
[high pitched noise rings out]
[Yagami]
M-I-H-A-E-L K-E-E-H-L.
Your real name is Mihael Keehl.
[Mello]
What the hell...? How did he...?
I did it.
It's over, Mello.
It's time to turn yourself in.
If you give up, I won't kill you.
You have my word on that.
[Light]
What are you doing? Don't be stupid!
Write his name down and kill him!
Now!
You know how this works.
I write your name and you will die.
Let go of that trigger
and put your hands in the air.
-[Mello] Yagami...
-Don't move!
I've written your first name
and it will only take me a second
to write your surname.
[Light grumbles]
You idiot! Just write it! Kill him!
I'm truly sorry.
For what it's worth, I give you my word
that I never wanted to kill you.
But tell me, Yagami.
You've never killed someone before,
have you?
[grunting]
Fire?
[bullet casings clink on floor]
[groaning]
[man]
What was that?
Jose! The notebook!
[Jose] Damn!
This guy.
He won't let go of the thing.
Son of a... [strains]
-[footsteps]
-Huh?
[gasping]
[Mello] Deputy Director!
[Aizawa]
It's all over, Mello.
Put your hands up and surrender.
[gasping]
[Aizawa] Matsuda, are you all right?
[Matsuda] No, I don't think so.
[Yagami] I'm sure you'll live.
[Aizawa] L, I don't see any sign of Mello.
[breathes uneasily]
[Light] Damn it. After all that,
he got away?
That's why you should have
just killed him.
[wind blowing]
[monitor beeps]
[Light] Come on, please, Dad.
You can't die on me like this.
Light...
Yeah, Dad?
I...
My goodness...
[whimpering]
You'll be fine. It's okay.
Light...
I still have them.
I still have the Shinigami eyes.
According to that Shinigami, Ryuk,
I can't see the lifespan of someone
who owns a notebook.
But I can see the numbers above your head.
Light...
You really aren't Kira.
I'm so glad.
My son...
Don't tell me
you're still worried about that, Chief.
Of course he's not Kira.
Come on, you shouldn't talk so much, Dad.
That's important, but I've got
bigger things to deal with right now.
I've got to get him
to write Mello's name in the notebook.
I'm so sorry, but...
In the end, I couldn't do it.
I couldn't bring myself to kill him.
[Light] I can't just come out and say,
"It's not too late."
No wait, maybe I can.
It all depends on how I do it.
No one will think it's weird
if I get upset and panic.
Come on, Dad, write his name!
You can't let him beat you like this.
Write his name, Dad.
With your last bit of strength!
Do you want to die in vain?
D-- Dad, no!
[Yagami, softly] Light...
[monitor beeping goes flat]
I'm sorry for your loss.
Dad!
Wake up!
[yelling] Come on, damn it!
Don't you die on me, you idiot!
Dad!
[sobs]
You're the Shinigami who came here
to take back this notebook, aren't you?
[Sidoh] Yes.
[Light] The notebook might be helpful
to the Kira investigation
but we really only need one of them.
I'll give this one back to you.
[Sidoh] Humans who use the notebook
are cursed with fear, pain and misery. Hm.
Of course,
Soichiro didn't use the notebook.
He got to die believing
his son wasn't Kira.
I guess that means...
he was happy.
TO BE CONTINUED