[theme music playing]
[classical music playing]
-Delete!
-[man screaming]
Delete!
[man groaning and choking in agony]
[narrator] The average Japanese adult
would say that Teru Mikami
was a child
with a strong sense of justice.
He was able to distinguish right
from wrong better than any of his peers.
And compared to
the average Japanese person,
Teru had been through
and seen far worse miseries...
and even witnessed death.
[classical music continues playing]
SELECTION
[alarm clock beeping]
[birds chirping outside]
[indistinct chatter]
[kids laughing]
[Teru] In this world,
there is only good and evil.
That was one of the first universal truths
I grasped
from observing the world around me
when I was a child.
Every human being, without exception,
ends up falling into one category
or the other.
Even in those innocent years
of elementary school,
one could not escape that fact.
CLASS REP. THIRD-YEAR GROUP A
TERU MIKAMI
As class president, I strived to achieve
great things for my fellow students.
But there were always enemies,
good against evil.
[clattering]
No, stop! Let go of me, please!
[kids laughing
[panting]
Evil has to be confronted.
[grunting]
-[pencil snaps]
-[boy] Get him!
There were times when it seemed
evil would triumph over good.
But no matter what happened to me,
I felt happy for one reason.
[sniffing] Thank you, Teru.
Hearing those words of gratitude
from the victims
made me want to save them again and again.
For that reason,
I never spared any effort.
And in the end,
I was able to stand up for
my sense of justice.
[kids laughing]
-Yeah! Do it!
-Does this bug you?
[kid laughing]
Huh?
[nervous laugh]
[Teru] But...
that was only true
in the world of children.
Middle school was another matter entirely.
The more I confronted evil,
the more enemies I had to face.
[crunching]
Victims would become participants,
and even the people watching
would be influenced by evil
and become enemies themselves.
But for justice to triumph,
it requires action.
So, I realized, to serve justice,
I had to delete evil.
The only person who understood my hopes
and remained my ally
was the woman who raised me on her own.
My mother.
No, rather, it used to be my mother.
Teru, not everything in the world
is going to work the way you want it to.
You have to stop doing this.
There's no reason for you
to suffer so much for your beliefs.
What do you think you're proving
getting hurt like this?
This is plain foolishness.
You have to realize that some things
will never change.
[Teru] My mother was wrong.
She didn't side with justice.
She was one of those
who deserved to be deleted.
[tires screeching]
[Teru] That was when the miracle happened.
[car crashing]
Four of the worst delinquents
from my school
lost control of their car
while they were joy-riding.
They died instantly.
One bystander was killed as well.
That bystander was my mother.
In one fell swoop,
all the people I resented
had been deleted.
At first, I was terrified.
I couldn't stop shivering.
But then, it hit me.
With these people out of the picture,
how many others would benefit as a result?
Clearly, their victims were relieved.
But, beyond that,
wouldn't everyone in my class
be happier now that they were gone?
And sure enough, I was right.
Our classroom
became a peaceful, joyful place.
There will always be consequences
for evil deeds.
That is the way the world is.
The way it should be.
Evil must be deleted.
[Teru] Now then, let's see.
Are there any more problems
with these records?
-[man] No, they're fine.
-[Teru] With every passing year,
my commitment to justice
only grew stronger.
I saw that there will always be those
who have no reason to exist.
Those whose very existence
is a threat to society.
And the closer they grew to adulthood,
the less likely it was
that they would ever reform.
They could only be deleted.
Mysteriously,
every time I judge someone as evil,
they would soon be taken care of.
Was it coincidence?
Was I special somehow?
In the end, it didn't matter.
Divine judgment
must be brought upon evil.
And if it isn't, then someone must
take it upon themselves to punish evil.
COURTHOUSE
That's why I became a prosecutor.
GUIDE TO JAPANESE SENTENCING
It is the role of the prosecutor
to see that evil is brought to justice.
It was an ideal job for me.
And then...
[gasps]
God came before me.
MASS MURDER OF VICIOUS CRIMINALS
Everything that had been happening
around me wasn't coincidence.
WHO IS THE CRIMINAL KILLER, KIRA?
It was divine justice.
God had been watching me.
[grunting]
God had seen
how I did not surrender to evil.
He reached out his hand
and punished the evil people for me.
Once I realized that,
I started to frequent places
where God was bound to be watching.
And then it happened.
[ominous music playing]
[screaming]
God recognized me, as I had always hoped.
Not only that, but He found me worthy
of sharing His power to eliminate evil.
With this, it doesn't matter
if I can't hear His voice.
I shall figure out what Kira wants
and carry out His will.
Delete.
Delete. Delete.
Delete. Delete. Delete.
Delete. Delete. Delete. Delete.
Delete.
[rapid typing]
[Light] Mikami made the choice
to kill Demegawa himself.
I never requested it.
An understandable move
but now there's no spokesperson.
Kira needs a voice.
At the moment,
I can't make any moves myself.
What will he do?
[Teru] Kira isn't saying anything.
He must be in a situation
where he can't move freely.
But this is an important time for him.
We need a spokesperson
to spread His word to the people.
Then, I will take the initiative.
-[door opening]
-[men] Hmm?
Extra, extra!
There's a new development
in the Kira case!
He's chosen a new spokesperson
to take Demegawa's place.
-Huh?
-Take a look!
[upbeat music playing]
Huh? That woman…
Kiyomi Takada!
[Kiyomi] Good evening.
This is Kiyomi Takada from News 6.
Starting today, it will be my duty
to spread the word of Kira,
accurately and quickly.
From now on, NHN will fairly...
[Matsuda] So he picked
NHN's star newscaster, huh?
Kira's got good taste.
Choosing Takki was a good idea.
[Kiyomi] ...will be passed onto him
through me.
[Mogi] There's no mistaking it.
That's the girl
that Light dated in university.
You've moved quickly, Mikami.
However, it won't take them long
to find the connection between us,
which could be a problem.
No, on second thought,
she's not a bad choice.
It's one I never would have considered,
since I already knew her.
This could actually make things easier.
I can definitely use her,
but I'll have to find a way
to contact her soon.
[Teru] Kiyomi Takada.
I had a chance to meet her
when I was on a debate program
she was hosting.
She was a shrewd and fair host
for the most part,
but her attitude changed suddenly
when Kira's name was mentioned.
She had a uniquely rigid sense of justice
that I could identify with.
She hates crimes and social evils
with a passion.
I talked with her privately
several times after that.
She clearly supports Kira,
but it's more than that.
She thinks like Kira.
That makes her the broadcaster most worthy
of being the new voice of Kira.
[tense music playing]
Kiyomi Takada.
It'd be too suspicious for Kira
to choose an ex-girlfriend
as his representative.
And there's been no sign of Light
sending her any messages.
Maybe I'm thinking about this too much.
Everyone, I just had an idea.
I was thinking we could make use
of Kiyomi Takada.
To be honest, I know her.
Back in university, she and I
were actually dating for a little while.
Oh?
[Aizawa] So, he admits it?
He has no intention
to hide the connection.
If she's acting as his spokesperson,
she must be receiving orders from him.
She's in contact with Kira somehow.
I think our best bet
is to use that connection
to find a way to Kira through her.
KIYOMI TAKADA CHOSEN AS
KIRA'S SPOKESPERSON
But Takki's probably doing it
because Kira's threatening her, right?
She might be too scared to help us out
with our investigation.
[Aizawa] That's a good point.
I'm not too worried about that.
I know her current cellphone number.
I'm pretty sure that I'll be able
to convince her once we get talking.
She'll meet with me, if I ask her to.
[laughs] Wow.
Listen to this guy! You're the man, Light.
Talking to her will be easy,
but the real challenge will be to get her
to help us find and arrest Kira.
We used to talk about a lot of
different topics while we were in college.
And one thing was clear.
-She worships Kira.
-Huh?
But we might be able
to use that to our advantage.
The police claim they support Kira,
but aren't doing anything
one way or the other.
So I'll reveal that I've joined the police
and ask her what we can do
to help Kira further.
To her, it will sound like a good idea.
We can convince her to assist us
as long as we pretend
it's for Kira's benefit.
Do you think that will go over well?
I'm not entirely sure,
but it's worth a try at least.
I agree. It would be foolish for us
to pass up a lead like this.
In that case, I'll call her tonight.
[men] Light!
If you don't mind, I'd like to listen in
on your conversation with Ms. Takada.
Of course. That's fine with me.
Actually, it's better if you do.
If she lets slip something about Kira,
it would be best if more than one of us
was listening.
Uh, yeah.
[tense music playing]
[phone ringing]
Yes, hello?
[Light] Kiyomi? This is Light Yagami.
[Kiyomi] Light?
[Kiyomi] Hi, it's been a while.
What's going on?
Kiyomi, I have something important
to tell you.
Could we meet somewhere?
I have a favor to ask you.
[Kiyomi] A favor?
Yeah.
I know my timing is pretty bad. I mean...
You're the woman the whole world
is watching right now,
so it might not be possible.
[sighs] Don't play innocent and humble
with me, Light.
You wouldn't have called if you didn't
think it was possible to see me.
-[Light] You're right.
-Huh?
Ever since we graduated,
I wanted to talk to you again,
but I never had the chance.
And now it looks like
our jobs have brought us together.
After so much time,
our paths are about to cross again.
Call me crazy
but I feel like this is fate.
What do you mean, "our jobs"?
[Light] I'm working with the police now.
That was part of what I wanted
to talk to you about... in person.
[Kiyomi] The police aren't doing anything
to defy Kira at this point.
All right, I may be able to help you,
depending on what you're asking for.
I appreciate it.
At the very least, I just want you
to hear what I have to say.
Anywhere. Just us two.
Well, okay then.
After tonight's broadcast has finished.
That sounds perfect.
I'll book a hotel room for us.
[Kiyomi] A hotel room? Are you sure?
The last I heard,
you were still living with Miss Amane.
Are things not going too well
on the home front?
[Light] Well, to be honest...
Misa's just not intelligent enough
to be my partner.
-[Misa] Mochi.
-Yes?
Your cooking is really good.
And I appreciate that you're doing
everything for me,
-but it's been five days now.
-Right...
Light doesn't know about you
hanging around all the time, does he?
I'm beginning to get a really bad feeling
about this whole thing.
-Uh huh...
-I mean,
I know that Light trusts me totally,
but don't you think most people
would start saying I'm cheating on him?
Oh, he'd be so jealous!
[Mello] Near and the others told me
that this woman's supposed to be
the Second Kira.
But could it really be
this unbelievably stupid girl?
[crunching]
It seems that Kira still hasn't tried
to contact me yet.
If he's in a situation where he's
unable to contact me even if he wants to,
then the next best thing would be
for him to contact Takada instead.
[clicking]
[Kiyomi] Good evening.
This is the nine o'clock news.
First, I have an announcement
that comes directly from Kira.
His words are to become
the new law of the world.
Kira will never forgive those people
whose existence is a threat to justice,
but he will also not forgive those
who live wastefully
and refuse to use their abilities
to contribute
to the betterment of society.
What?
So Kira's gonna kill lazy people now?
You're kidding me.
[Light] You're taking this too far,
Mikami.
It's too early to be making
those kinds of statements.
I've gotta get a hold of him soon.
Matsuda, how is it?
Good. Audio and video online.
No blind spots.
-Until next time.
-The nine o'clock news is just ending.
Everything's in order.
I'll head back to HQ.
Okay.
[footsteps leaving]
[door opening and closing]
[tense music playing]
[door creaking open]
[soft classical music playing]
I missed you.
[gasps]
[both exclaiming]
[Light] Oh. I'm sorry, it's just...
Anyway, please sit down.
To be honest,
it doesn't seem like that long
since we last saw each other.
[sighs]
[gasps]
What the hell is Light doing?
He's not saying anything.
If he just stays silent,
she'll get suspicious.
Come on, don't tell me
you've never been in love before, Ide.
-What?
-How's it going?
The mood's perfect.
That's not what I meant.
Uh...
[phone vibrating]
Please excuse me.
-[gasps] Kira…
-[gasps]
Is it Mikami?
She just said it's Kira!
Kira's contacting her directly?
You should answer it.
[Kiyomi] Um, right...
Hello? No, I'm with a friend right now.
Yes, we're alone.
If luck is on my side,
I can get on the phone myself.
Well, Mikami, can you make it happen?
[Kiyomi] He wanted to meet me
all of a sudden.
[Teru] Someone who requests
a private meeting
with Kira's spokesperson?
I'd like to speak with him, if I may.
[gasps]
He said that he wants to speak to you.
Perfect.
I was right to choose you, Mikami.
She's passed the phone to Light.
It could be dangerous
if he's the real thing.
Yes, hello?
[distorted voice] Who am I speaking to?
Five pages on November 26?
I don't get it. What do you mean?
You're God!
You're doing well, Mikami.
Let's just see how much
you can figure out.
[Teru] God, you're not free
to speak right now.
[Light] Yes.
You're being watched at the moment.
Yes. But how I can trust
you're the real Kira?
Is he asking me
to judge someone right now?
Turn to Sakura TV!
What's that? Sakura TV?
Quick! Let's check it out.
We'll invite Kira back to our program,
no matter what it might take.
[groans in pain]
-He died!
-[Ide] This is bad! He's the real thing.
-Mikami...
-[Teru] Yes?
...you're even better than I expected.
KIRA WANTS ROOM CHECKED FOR DEVICES.
I'M REMOVING THEM BEFORE HE SEES THEM.
[Matsuda] What? He's removing the bugs?
We don't have a choice.
[Kiyomi] I don't understand.
What's going on?
Now I can talk without any constraints.
What?
Listen, Kiyomi…
I am the real Kira.
[gasps]
That's right. I'm Kira.
That's what I wanted to tell you.
[Kiyomi] Light is… Kira?
Listen, I won't allow you
to ask Kiyomi who I am.
You don't need to know my identity.
Yes. I'll leave the rest to you, God.
[Light] Do you understand?
I am Kira.
The man who was on the phone
is one of my followers
who I've shared my power with.
[gasps] I can't believe it's you.
You were the only man
I ever really admired.
To be honest, the only man
I ever felt a connection with.
And now, to find out you're Kira...
It's incredible.
[Light] Please, join me, Kiyomi...
and you will be
the goddess of the new world.
Oh, Light...
[dramatic music playing]
-[phone ringing]
-[men exclaiming]
Light, are you okay?
Yeah. Kiyomi was able
to work things out with Kira.
I've decided that from now on,
I'm going to pretend to be dating her.
We might be able to find Kira that way.
[Teru] Delete, delete, delete,
delete, delete,
delete.
Delete!
TO BE CONTINUED
[ending theme song playing]