[theme music plays]
[intense music plays]
I'm going to announce
my engagement to Light
at the Pop Music Festival.
I used to really like Kira too,
but I know for sure
that Light is gonna catch him soon.
[bangs the table, glass clatters]
And as for you,
you'll probably be executed.
You're to send me a fan letter
that I'll be able to recognize as yours.
You will also enclose something else
in the envelope.
Five blank pages from the notebook.
Carry on with your judgements and killings
as usual
until I receive the letter and the pages.
[Mikami] And how about
after you receive them?
[Takada] Make a notebook that looks
as close to the original as possible
and act as if you're killing people
by using this decoy.
[man] Oh, come on now, lady.
I mean, wearing a short skirt like that
in the winter.
Please, someone.
[grunts]
Delete…
He's getting off the train.
[woman screaming]
[woman sobbing]
VIGILANCE
A man who was on the same train
as Mikami just collapsed.
He was harassing a young woman
and suddenly fell to the floor.
It all happened about half a minute
after he wrote something in the notebook.
That’s gotta be it.
Well, now we know for sure.
X-KIRA
MIKAMI
Yes. Our next order of business
is to get as close as possible to Mikami.
But before we rush in blindly,
there's something
we need to be careful of.
And that…
is the being known as the Shinigami.
The Shinigami will be loyal to Mikami
and will warn him if he discovers
we're following him.
But the Shinigami can only be seen
by those people
who have touched the notebook.
It's going to be pretty difficult
to be careful of something
we can't even see.
[Near] We're gonna try,
no matter how difficult.
Right. Understood, sir.
[static noise]
Light is having another one
of his meetings with Takada this evening.
Right after they started having
these encounters,
Takada got a phone call from Kira
and all the surveillance cameras
had to be removed.
The first thing that came to my mind
was that they'd be able
to communicate secretly
by writing messages.
-Everything checks out in here.
-Huh?
I've gone over the entire room
and there's nothing in it.
There's only the wiretap on me.
[Aizawa] Uh… right.
Then all that's left is the bathroom.
Why does Light care so much
about checking for cameras and wiretaps?
Never mind that.
Why is Kira allowing these meetings
in the first place?
Something just doesn't add up.
Hmm.
If they really are
writing notes to each other,
there's only one way to prove it.
Light, I thought you should know.
I had a private chat
with Miss Misa Amane yesterday.
[Light] About what?
Whoa. Oh, boy! Light's in trouble now!
Matsuda, is there some reason
you're so happy about this?
She told me that she's planning
to announce her engagement to you
during her appearance
at the Pop Music Festival.
WHAT IS MISA TO YOU?
Oh, he is busted. Light's in the doghouse!
Shut up, Matsuda!
No. She thinks we're together
because I haven't been able
to break it to her yet.
But she means nothing to me.
Misa, you idiot.
Why pull a stunt like that?
No, Takada. You're just as bad.
Why are women like this? [grunts]
Nothing, you say?
Why should I believe you?
[gasps]
[Light's voice] She was
in charge of killing before T.
Somehow, she gained
the same power as I had
and found out that I was Kira.
In the end, I had no choice
but to take her as my partner.
It's the only reason I would ever choose
such an impulsive girl.
[Takada] So, Misa was doing
Kira's killings.
But right now,
I'm the one doing it for him.
Light had no choice with Misa.
But he chose me specially to help him.
Believe me, she's nothing.
You're the only one for me.
"You're the only one for me?"
Is that supposed to be serious?
I expected better from you, Light.
[Matsuda] She does have a point.
-That's a pretty cheesy line for Light.
-[Light] Sorry. That's just how I feel.
[Ide] Do you think he will pick
Amane or Takada?
[Takada] I wonder
how many women you've said that to?
-[Matsuda] He could keep two-timing them.
-[Light] You think I'm that kind of guy?
-[Ide] You don't see a problem with that?
-[growls]
-[Matsuda] Hey, I'm not the one--
-Will you two shut up?
You're going to have to
prove yourself from now on, Light.
But I will trust you.
Of course, if I find out
that you're lying, you'll pay dearly.
In fact, I'll tell Kira about it.
Hmm.
Kira, huh?
You know, I understand that the world
really needs Kira right now,
but I just can't help but wonder,
will the day ever come
when you and I can be together?
I can't help but hate Kira
for choosing you as his spokesperson
because it keeps us apart.
I don't mind if he kills criminals,
but we've done nothing wrong.
We have the right
to lead happy lives, don't we?
"Yes, I want
to be happy together with you."
"But that could only happen
if Kira wasn't around."
You're right.
If only Kira wasn't around.
"Kira
should be arrested."
It's true.
If you and I are ever going
to have a chance
of being happy together,
Kira needs to be caught.
Wait a minute, Kiyomi.
Do you seriously mean that?
[Takada] Yes.
[Light] All right.
But if I'm going to arrest him,
I'll need your help.
You'll be putting yourself in danger.
[Light] After all,
I'll be defying the police,
and you'll be going against Kira
and the entire world as well.
Are you sure
that's okay?
That's a long pause.
[Takada] All right.
"If cooperating with you
means that we can be together,
then I'm prepared
to make that sacrifice, Light."
What a turnaround!
Just like you'd expect from our guy!
He was able to move the conversation
from cheating on Misa-Misa
to getting Takki to help him!
Mikami is talking to himself!
What's going on?
[Gevanni] He's too far away from me
to pick up his voice.
But I recorded video of his lips moving.
I'm sending you the footage
I was able to get.
It's of Mikami during his lunchbreak.
This is it right here.
He's saying something.
[Rester] Show it to us one more time
in slow motion.
"Is that you, Shinigami?"
is what he said.
[Gevanni] He seems to have reacted
to the scrap of paper at his feet.
[Rester] He just gave a small sigh.
[Gevanni] At this point
he talks to himself a little more.
I'm gonna zoom in on his lips.
[Rester] That Shinigami.
Ever
since
he…
handed me the notebook…
he hasn't reappeared.
"That Shinigami. Ever since
he handed me the notebook,
he hasn't reappeared."
[Near] Mikami was given the notebook
by one of the Shinigami.
But it seems that
Shinigami hasn't been following him.
Hmm.
So, that's how it is.
I guess that's all for today.
See you next time.
Of course.
[Matsuda] [grunting] It's finally over.
Man, things got pretty intense today,
don't you think?
It's tough to do this for hours on end.
Yeah, you really look
like you're suffering.
[Aizawa] All right. I'm gonna
wrap things up at the hotel.
Okay. Thanks for all your hard work.
You know, I feel kind of bad
that Aizawa is stuck
with booking the hotel
and checking out every time.
[gasps]
It's gone.
The mark I left is gone!
[gasps]
I left four marks.
Two of them are gone.
The room's been left just as it was.
Housekeeping hasn't come in yet.
Then how and why would anyone
switch these two notepads for new ones?
That settles it.
They're writing notes!
-[phone ringing]
-Huh?
Yes?
What's that?
You want to meet
and talk with Near in person?
Mr. Aizawa, it's been a while.
And it's a pleasure to meet you.
That's very nice of you,
but kinda hard to accept
while I'm blindfolded.
He doesn't have
any weapons or cameras on him.
In that case,
you're free to take off your blindfold.
Hmm. [gasps]
Near,
I believe what you said earlier.
L has been meeting Takada
almost every single night.
-[Near] I know.
-Wha…?
Well, then what about this?
They are passing notes to each other.
I confirmed it.
[Near] Mr. Aizawa,
please don't take any unnecessary actions
on your own.
"Unnecessary actions?"
[Near] Yes. This is not the point
where we bring up evidence against Kira
and openly confront him.
I must corner him in a dead end
with a plan that
would guarantee his defeat.
This is what it will take
to stop him for good.
Mr. Aizawa,
I'm going to be blunt with you.
You and the rest of the task force
are already out of the picture.
[gasps]
[Near] However, if you still want
to help capture Kira, you can.
All I want you to do
is keep an eye on him
as you've been doing.
That's it? Keep an eye on him?
Yes.
Of course,
there certainly is a purpose
in watching over L.
In fact, I've already
taken it into account
as a part of my plan.
That's why I'm hoping
you can help me in that respect.
I want you to watch him.
In order to win against Kira.
And after that,
I want you to be a witness
to the end of Kira.
[gasps]
NHN HALL
[Takada] This has been a year
of breakthroughs for me,
and I'm sure for many others as well.
And what better way to bring this year
to an exciting close
than with the East West
Pop Music Festival.
I'm your host for this evening,
Kiyomi Takada.
We hope you all enjoy the show.
[Matsuda] All right.
The Pop Music Festival is about to begin!
[Ide] Matsuda, shouldn't you be
checking over
the reports on Kira's killings?
Yeah, in a minute.
But after Misa-Misa performs.
She's the opening act this year.
We gotta cheer her on. Yeah!
[whimpers]
[Misa] C-- Can we help you?
-[door opens]
-Huh?
Pardon me. We're from the SPK.
We'll need you to come with us.
[Misa whimpers]
Before we continue,
I'm afraid I must apologize
on behalf of the staff of NHN.
It's very unfortunate,
but it seems that this year's opening act
Miss Misa Amane
has not entered the concert hall yet.
-Huh?
[Takada] Of course…
-many unexpected things can…
-[Aizawa] What's going on?
-Mogi didn't tell us anything about this.
-It's always full of surprises.
[Misa] Take me back to NHN right now!
What is this?!
Are you trying to ruin my reputation?
Misa-Misa, you've got to try
and stay calm.
Mochi, why should I?
[Mogi] We need to do this
in order to catch Kira.
[Misa] But that has nothing to do with me!
You should know that I was going
to take you at gunpoint
as a last resort.
But you didn't resist.
That was a great help.
Thank you, Mr. Mogi.
[Misa] Huh?
[Mogi] I probably would have resisted
if I hadn't listened
to what Aizawa told me. But…
after hearing about the notepads,
there’s no doubt in my mind.
Hmm… What's going on?
[Light] Near.
[Near] Yes, what is it, L?
[Light] We have a problem.
Mogi and Misa Amane have gone missing.
[Near] I'm already aware of that.
I was the one who took them into custody.
Uh! He what?
For what reason?
Oh, just in case.
[Light] Near,
kidnapping is a blatant criminal act.
You have to stop this now.
[Near] Actually, Mr. Mogi and Amane
both came here willingly.
You can even ask them yourself.
I'll put them on the line now.
Here they are.
-Mogi, Misa, this is L speaking.
-[Misa] Huh?
[Misa] Light!
[Light] I'm told
that Near is detaining you.
He said that you both agreed to it.
Is that true?
It is.
[Aizawa] Mogi…
Actually, I was against the whole thing.
But Mochi said it would be best
if I just went along quietly.
He told me we would have both
been killed if I didn't.
[Light] All right.
It's fine as long as you both
consented to this.
So, now I've removed Misa Amane,
the one who might be the Second Kira,
from the equation.
Light Yagami,
I'm sure the significance of this move
isn't lost on you.
[man] No way! You're planning to end this
without Misa-Misa performing?!
God, what a rip-off!
[Gevanni] It looks like Lidner
and the others were successful.
-[woman] Yeah!
-[man] We want our money back!
[Gevanni] It's past nine.
All right, it's my turn.
[grunts]
Hmm.
Mikami leaves work
at almost the same time every day
with only slight variations.
He leads a completely scheduled life
for the most part.
So, he always goes
to that particular gym
every Monday and Thursday
at around nine o'clock.
Is that correct?
Yes. He's kept that routine
for the past four years,
ever since he joined.
He didn't even skip New Year's Day.
I became a member
and made a few inquiries
to confirm it myself.
Good. So, then can we assume
that he'll be there
on Monday the 31st as well?
[Gevanni] Yes. If he's the type of man
who would go on holidays,
then he'll certainly
go on New Year’s Eve.
[Near] Gevanni.
Would it be possible for you
to touch the notebook
on the 31st at the gym?
[gasps]
Yes.
I've already done a thorough check
of the hotel security.
The locker room is definitely free
of any kind of surveillance.
[Near] Then I'll leave it to you.
Sir, if there is a Shinigami with him,
there's a distinct possibility
that I will die, isn't there?
[Near] Yes.
Part of the reason you're doing this
is to test that theory.
Even if you don't see any Shinigami
after first touching the notebook,
I want you to continue
watching Mikami for a while longer
before we conclude whether or not
he has one following him.
I can have Rester do it
if you're too scared.
No. I understand.
I'll do it.
Hmm.
[heart beating loudly]
[Gevanni]
If there's a Shinigami around--
No, if there was one, I'd be dead.
It's too late to turn back now.
I have to touch it.
[heartbeat getting louder]
[gasping]
[sighs]
Sir, I've succeeded
in touching the notebook.
I can't confirm the existence
of any Shinigami
at this time.
[Near] Commander Rester,
please connect me with Mr. Mogi
for a moment.
[Misa] Huh?
Mr. Mogi.
According to your investigation
on the rules of the notebook,
how long can a person
be controlled before their death?
Based on the data
we got from Yotsuba's experiments,
it's 23 days.
[Near] Are you sure?
Yes.
I'd say that the killings done by Yotsuba
were more than enough to prove it.
[Near] Thank you for your assistance.
We have to consider the possibility
that Gevanni is already being controlled.
In that case, they could be making him
say that there is no Shinigami.
That means I need to confront L
in exactly 24 days…
if Gevanni is still alive until then.
[Rester grunts]
JANUARY 3
[Light] Kiyomi, I saw you had some trouble
at the Pop Music Festival.
Yes. I never imagined
that Miss Amane would go missing.
[Light's voice]
"Give T an order to contact you
and let you know as soon
as he's confirmed everything."
"Once you hear from him,
I want you to send me a text message
or call me with the following message,
'I want to see you as soon as possible'".
JANUARY 6
[Rester] Photographs?
[Near] Yes.
I want to see exactly
what he wrote in the notebook.
I want to see the pattern
in how Mikami writes,
if there are any habits,
and what kind of notebook it is.
I wanna see it all.
Everything in detail,
with my own eyes.
[camera shutter clicking]
[mysterious music plays]
[grunts]
[Rester] What do you think, Near?
[Near] Perfect.
Gevanni has done an excellent job.
The handwriting matches that
of the records Mikami keeps as prosecutor.
There's absolutely no doubt.
This is his handwriting.
[Rester] I agree.
With this, we can do it.
TO BE CONTINUED
[theme music plays]