Equator Sauna
Beware of Borrowed Plumes
I think the first guy to freestyle was KIN.
What? From Mellow Yellow?
Shiho, 18 years old, Tokyo
Hey.
Ah, yes?
What's that taxi driver's name?
Huh? You mean Odokawa?
Odokawa...
That's his name.
You know the missing high
school girl case in Nerima?
Yes.
Rumor has it she got into Odokawa's taxi.
What?
But we haven't heard anything
about the case since then, right?
You're right.
The investigation request was withdrawn.
Huh? So they found her, then?
No. Apparently they received
a message from her secondhand.
That's great. She's all right, then.
That said, I'm allegedly the reason
she ran away from home.
What? What did you do?
Could you investigate her whereabouts?
What? You want me to do it?
It's Don-chan's daughter.
Whose daughter? I don't know
what you expect me to do.
Later.
Huh?
Uh, yeah. Talk to you later.
Huh? He was on the phone?!
Odokawa-kun, let's go for a drive.
Sure thing. You'll pay your fare, won't you?
Maybe, if you give me
some useful information.
What information?
More importantly, that toy
is awfully distracting.
Is it a toy, or is it real?
Hey.
Boss, what is it?
What's that taxi driver's name?
You mean Odokawa?
Odokawa...
What about him?
You know the missing high
school girl case in Nerima?
Yes.
Rumor has it she got into Odokawa's taxi.
Boss, about that...
But we haven't heard anything
about the case since then, right?
You're right.
The investigation request was withdrawn.
I heard about that from the older Daimon.
He said they heard from the missing girl.
No. Apparently they received
a message from her secondhand.
I see...
That said, I'm allegedly the reason
she ran away from home.
What do you mean?
Could you investigate her whereabouts?
Why do you care about a high
school girl from Nerima, boss?
It's Don-chan's daughter.
What?!
Later.
Bye.
Odokawa-kun, apparently you picked up
the missing high school girl from Nerima.
Apparently. I handed over my dash
cam data to Big Daimon a while ago.
Yeah, I know. I have your data.
Sounds like you guys are involved, then.
I have a request.
I need you to keep your mouth shut.
Also, I want your help with something.
Big Daimon already told me
to keep my mouth shut.
He said a wanted criminal armed with
a gun would kill me if I told the police.
In fact, there's a wanted criminal armed
with a gun trying to kill me right now—
Not just the police. Don't tell anybody.
Tell 'em you lost your dash cam data.
Don't tell anybody? Like who?
Everybody.
So, what do you want help with?
If anyone shows up looking
for your dash cam data,
I want you to let me know.
And if I refuse?
I'll kill you.
Why are you so desperate
to find this girl, Dobu?
That ain't any of your damn business.
I can't help you if I don't
know what's going on.
Besides, without some information,
I won't know what I'm not
supposed to tell whom.
Fine.
First, my boss is looking for the missing
high school girl from Nerima.
Why?
Because she's the daughter of a classmate.
What about the police?
Officially, the police suspect me.
Suspect you? Aren't you
besties with the police?
Hey, you insult me. Just with Big Daimon.
Really? Not Little Daimon?
Little Daimon's an idiot.
So, you're not actually involved?
Nope. Swear to God, I'm not involved.
If anything, I was framed.
Why do you have my dash cam data, then?
Don't interrogate me like
you're the police, Odokawa.
Can't help you if I can't trust you.
Honestly, I thought you were connected
to the Nerima missing persons case.
Apparently you've been talking
to someone in your apartment.
At first, I thought I'd get my hands
on your dash cam data
so I could blackmail you with it.
So you don't suspect me anymore, then.
Nah, I still think you might've done it.
The investigation request's
been withdrawn, though.
Withdrawn? Then her family must
be satisfied with the situation.
They got word that she ran away
because of the relationship
between my boss and her dad,
so they withdrew the request.
They haven't accepted the situation.
Do you have any idea who might be involved?
There's only one guy who
could've put her up to this.
A guy named Yano.
Yano?
My junior.
If he's your junior, go talk to him yourself.
My job is collecting payments for my boss.
There's not much point in
telling you about it, so I won't,
but it's about obligation or principle.
But Yano only thinks about
collecting more money than me.
He doesn't work for obligation or principle.
In other words, Yano doesn't like me.
You're saying there's no point
in asking Yano directly.
Bingo.
So if someone comes to take
your dash cam data,
in all likelihood it'll be Yano
or one of his henchmen.
That's why I want your help.
Why don't you tell all this to your boss?
I couldn't. I didn't tell him
that I have the dash cam data.
Why?
Because Yano is always telling everyone
that I only do petty jobs.
It's reached the boss's ears, too.
In other words, he's a show-off.
Yeah. I think Yano knew what he was doing.
I get the picture.
You don't want me to tell anyone
that you have my dash cam data
because you don't want
your boss to find out.
And if anyone comes looking for it,
you want me to let you know.
That's right. You're quick
on the uptake, Odokawa.
If Yano is involved
in the missing persons case,
then I can find evidence of that
and use it to bring him down.
No, thanks.
What?!
You're still a criminal.
I'm not interested
in helping someone like that.
Even if I threaten to kill you?
You can't kill anyone.
You may be a small-time gangster,
but you've got your pride.
You asshole!
You, in the taxi. Pull over.
Get us out of here, or I'll shoot.
If you shoot me, you'll just get arrested.
Don't say anything stupid.
Damn it.
Which one is it? The older
or younger brother?
Is something the matter?
Can't you tell? I'm being
robbed. He's got a gun.
Be quiet. You'll bother the neighbors.
He's got a gun. Search him.
Something's wrong with this driver.
It certainly seems that way.
How much is he paying you?
In any case, could you turn off
your emergency light? It's confusing.
This is Shinjuku 4 to Central.
Shinjuku 336 10-22...
Hey, Bro. What was that about?
Ah, Little Bro. It was nothing.
His taxi broke down.
Really, Bro? I heard something about a gun.
Listen, Little Bro. Think about it.
Can you believe anything a taxi driver says?
You're right. Damn those taxi drivers!
Head to Shinjuku.
You turned on your taxi's
emergency light and kept me talking,
found a cop car, and provoked me
so I'd turn my gun on you.
You wanted the cops to see.
That was quite the risk you took.
What if I'd actually shot you?
Whatever. I wouldn't mind dying.
You're not afraid to die?
Someone who's not afraid to die doesn't
need your weird sense of justice.
I am afraid. Unbelievably so.
But I'd rather die than get involved
in what sounds like a pain in the ass.
I get it, Odokawa-kun.
I understand that threatening you
won't get you to do what I want.
What motivates you? You don't
seem very interested in money.
I know, I'll hurt your friends.
Who should I hurt?
What's your friend's name? Kakihana?
Kakihana, huh?
He's probably better off dead, too.
You're so cold, Odokawa-kun.
You seemed a little shaken, though.
You're actually bluffing, aren't you?
Who should I choose?
Taeko.
Shirakawa...
So, that's your weakness.
Why Shirakawa-san?
Sounds like we have a deal, then.
Thanks for your help.
New message
Miho Shirakawa
I'll wait at the park across
from the clinic.
"I'll wait at the park across
from the clinic."
Super Rare Dodo
You came.
Do you have some business with me?
Is wanting to see you not
a good enough reason?
You know those fast-forwarded videos of
landscapes filmed on a fixed-point camera?
Watching those makes me feel so anxious.
The sun sets in the blink of an eye.
The stars move, and clouds drift by.
It forces us to confront the fact
that time marches on,
regardless of what we have to say about it.
It kind of sounds like you're
being snide about my tardiness.
I don't believe there's such
a thing as wasted time.
But they say "time is money," you know?
Why not take things slowly, then?
Try saying that again, but meaner this time.
Why not enjoy a bit of sherry
and a fudge brownie
while strolling along the West Coast?
Your snide remark has
a rather American quality to it.
You don't want to be friends with me.
Why not?
Because I've got some
yakuza-type guys after me.
They know who my friends are.
It's kind of dangerous.
I'll be fine. Despite how I look...
I used to practice capoeira.
That was surprising. I thought
a Bollywood movie was about to start.
What's capoeira?
A Brazilian martial art.
Why?
At first, I was trying to lose weight.
Then I got interested in seeing how much
I could improve my queixada form.
Oh, a queixada is a kick to the chin. It's—
That's not what I meant.
Your makeshift capoeira won't
be enough to beat these guys.
That's obnoxious. How do you know
my martial arts skills are makeshift?
If it was to lose weight, then it can't
be effective in a real fight.
So it's makeshift.
It wouldn't upset you if someone
called you a makeshift taxi driver?
Obviously I'd be upset. It's my job.
I'm not calling you a makeshift nurse.
By the way, what does "makeshift" mean?
You got upset when you
didn't know what it meant?
I understood more or less from the nuance.
Use a synonym that's easier to understand.
It means "temporary substitute."
Who's a temporary substitute nurse?!
I didn't say that,
and I'm astonished that you got
upset for the same reason twice.
Please, no more queixada!
Anyway, it's dangerous for us
to be meeting like this.
For you, that is.
It doesn't matter. I'm an adult.
I can protect myself.
What's your goal?
For what?
What do you gain from meeting
with me, Shirakawa-san?
Am I bothering you?
Would it bother you to occasionally
meet and chat like this
or exchange messages?
I find being around you
relaxing, Odokawa-san.
I'm working the day
shift today. I should go.
I'll drive you there.
Oh, right. After all, you are a taxi driver.
I won't run the meter.
It's the "What's for Lunch?!" Segment!
What's for Lunch?!
Asking People Around
Kichijoji to Lunch!
Let's get started. In this segment,
we talk to people around town
and eat lunch with them.
It's already our fourth episode, and
we've received absolutely no response.
Is everything okay?
I'm actually kinda worried.
Well, we're shooting all four at once.
Oh, right. No wonder I'm not hungry.
Explain where we are right now.
Hey, Odokawa.
Here we go. Hey, what's for lunch?
What happened with Shirakawa-san after that?
You're unusually annoying today.
Has your affection for her grown?
It's the size of Jupiter now.
That's quite the growth.
Love is both a painful and beautiful thing.
Are you in love?
I was pretty popular
in high school, remember?
Yeah, you played baseball.
But once you're an adult,
people have pretty high standards
regarding your appearance
or work performance.
As I've gotten older,
I'd started to give up on it.
My spring's finally on the horizon, though.
Really? That's great.
I've mentioned this before,
but in the marriage marketplace,
there's no demand for guys
with specs like ours.
That's exactly it.
Why is a 28-year-old nurse interested in me?
It's that special feeling
that outshines your specs.
I compared my feelings to Jupiter before,
but I don't really understand
attraction or romance myself.
I always thought they were concepts
that had nothing to do with me.
In any case, I'm not confident.
Before you know it, you're in love.
That's just how it is.
Don't lecture me on love. It's aggravating.
You wanna see the girl I'm talking to?
Shiho, 18 years old, Tokyo
She's just a little girl.
She's still only 18.
So far we've only exchanged messages,
but we get along great.
We're supposed to meet up soon,
but she's busy with work.
Did you meet her on a matchmaking site?
That's right.
I know what you're trying to say.
You think she doesn't exist, don't you?
Well, read it and weep.
Kakihana-san!!
Good luck at work
Ma'am, another helping.
It's not that I doubt her
existence. It's just...
Are you sure you're not being tricked?
Are you jealous?
Kakihana, I'm not saying
this out of jealousy.
Think about it. You said so yourself.
There's no demand for us
in the marriage marketplace.
I'm telling you, it's the feeling—
You've never even met her.
How can there be any feeling?
I told you, we've been exchanging messages!
Take a look at all of these!
Let me see your profile.
Give me that...
No way. Why, you...
Stop that!
Give me your phone...
Hey.
Ouch...
Eiji Kakihana
41 Years Old, Tokyo
Profile
Born: Tokyo
Education: College Graduate
Annual Income: 20,000,000
These specs you lied about way
outshine any kind of feeling.
I know.
But still, I wanna dream.
I can dream, right?
"Good evening.
Good evening.
I finished work, and I'm in Arakawa.
Could I see you now?
Shiho
I finished work, and I'm in Arakawa.
Could I see you now?"
What should I do? What should I do?
I'm on my way!
Goriki's missing?
I can't get in touch with him.
What should I do, Odokawa-san?
Shiho-chan?
Kakihana-san, I've been wanting to see you.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
I was glued to my monitor at work.
I rushed here in a taxi, but had
trouble finding this place.
You're even more wonderful
than I thought. I'm relieved.
You're all wet. Poor thing.
Shall we get some tea someplace?
Y-Y-Yeah. I know a place
that serves good Darjeeling,
but I don't really know this area.
There's a Doutor nearby. Let's go there.
Huh? Okay.
Thanks.
Next Time: Tanaka's Revolution
"Our story begins four years ago."
"He was working for a game company—"
Don't read that.
What is this?
It's an interview conducted by a writer.
This doesn't belong at
an auspicious event like this.
Anyway, I'm surprised you came,
Mr. Successful Comedian.
Are you being mean on purpose?
I've got nothing in my schedule right now.