Summer already, huh?
Senpai!
It's that sweaty time of year again!
You're too hyper, that's all.
Hey, hey, Senpai?
What?
Can I come over to your place today?
Today? Again?
I'm just really worried you'll build
more of Uzaki Hills without me!
I so won't.
Creepy old tower.
Looks like an evil emperor's hangout.
An evil emperor's hangout? No way!
That's my dream house,
stuffed full of my perfect ideals!
You'd set up a lava trap at your own house?!
Oh, that?
That is so you can always come by and visit!
What, you want to trap me?
Trap you? Why, I never! How rude!
With the lava! What else could I mean?
"Uzaki-chan Wants to Hang Out!"
"Episode 5: I Want to Meddle
in My Friend's Business!"
What are you doing out there, kitty?
I'll rescue you.
Stay right there and be a good kitty.
Almost there...
It's all right.
Hey!
No!
A dream? I was... dreaming?
Well, yeah.
Must've nodded off, then woke up in a panic.
That hasn't happened in a while.
If anyone saw that...
It had to be her--and only
at the worst possible times!
Turn around! We're in the middle of class!
Hey, hey, Senpai, Senpai, Senpai!
Were you dreaming of falling from a high place?
You totally jolted awake!
Don't be nodding off, now!
To think I was a witness to the big moment!
God, you bug me!
Be quiet. Class has started!
Whoopsie!
Are you familiar with dream interpretation?
It holds that the content of
one's dreams reveal one's mental state.
Dreams of falling from a height, for example,
indicate deep-seated feelings of anxiety,
while vague unease about
one's career or personal prospects...
Oh, you're anxious, Senpai?
Don't worry--you can tell me anything.
Shut up.
Dreaming of falling when one is in
high spirits or getting carried away
can also be interpreted as a warning
to put one's feet on the ground,
Getting carried away there, Senpai?
Shut up, I said!
a subconscious dissatisfaction
with the action or attitude responsible.
Quit getting so excited!
Get those feet on the ground!
Look who's talking!
Talk about a timely lecture! Too funny!
Really laid bare your deepest psyche, huh?
Can it. Besides, I'm not a kid--
I don't believe in that stuff.
Maybe it was a little juvenile...
Well, I'm more of a believer.
Psychological tests, blood-type fortunes...
Superstition, all of it.
That's not what psychology is about.
Sure, you say that, but are you
sure you're not just acting tough?
Yeah, right.
But psychologically speaking--
Uh-oh... I'm--
Watch out! What are you doing, idiot?
Nice catch, Senpai. That was scary!
That's what happens when
you're focused on riling someone up
instead of watching your step.
Be careful, dummy!
Which reminds me...
Of what?
People who trip down stairs
can develop climacophobia,
the fear of descending stairs.
Uh, what? Where'd this
come from all of a sudden?
It's a psychological aftershock.
Huh?
It's also known as "the stair yips."
You're navigating stairs as usual, until one day
you just can't go down them smoothly,
or you tumble down them--
until at last, you're scared
of the very stairs themselves.
Stop that!
That's terrifying!
Aw!
C'mon, why not?
Ah!
'Cause I have plans with that guy.
Maybe next time, okay?
Aw!
You showed up at the perfect time, Sak.
Those girls are relentless!
What gives, Itsuhito? You running away?
"Itsuhito Sakaki, 21 - College Junior"
It's honestly not much fun going drinking
with that bunch. We just don't click.
Huh.
So many people drink way too much.
I prefer a more stylish approach
to enjoying alcohol.
In the end, sober me is left
to clean up the mess.
Yeah, I'm not into that, either.
There goes Sakaki. Aren't we going after him?
Hmm... But that other guy's a little scary.
I get that.
It's the eyes.
Yeah--the eyes.
Those two are together a lot. Are they friends?
Hey, it feels like I barely saw
you around at all last month.
Yeah, I popped over to Okinawa.
Okinawa?! It's not even summer break!
I just had this sudden urge
to see that gorgeous ocean.
He's living free and easy.
What about you, Sak?
Anything happen while I was gone?
Nope.
Well...
It's just... hmm... What even was that?
My days were... hard to describe.
What the hell?
Life was ordinary enough, generally speaking.
I went to classes,
worked my job, played games and stuff...
Kept pretty busy.
Enough! Will you go hog wild just once?!
I've been hanging out with you
for three years. Your life is dull!
It's depressing just hearing about it!
Only four years of college,
and you're wasting it! Enjoy it!
Get a girlfriend!
You always say that.
This is no time to be drinking!
What the--? You gave it to me!
Shut up! Jerks like you
who waste their youth are insufferable!
Hey, Senpai!
There you are!
Huh?
Might this person be...
Wait--could he be--your... friend?
Yeah, that's right.
What?!
So you... you really did have a friend.
You did talk him up sometimes...
...but I thought he was imaginary.
You saw me eating with him in the dining hall!
I thought maybe you were
pretending he was your friend.
I'm so happy... Oh, I really am so glad...
Wait--you were seriously worried about me?!
Quit looking at me like that!
Oh, right. You're that girl
who's with Sak now and then.
I'm a junior, like him. Name's Sakaki--pleasure.
Hana Uzaki, sophomore!
Senpai is a hardcore gloomlord,
but I hope you'll get along well together.
Who even are you to me?
Don't you worry, Senpai--
I'll still keep hanging out with you.
So where are we going to go after class today?
Why are you saying that like
my schedule's already booked?
I said I was going
to hang out at your place today.
You want to come over again today? Seriously?
I mean, if you're always hanging out
with your one male friend, people'll talk.
They'll make fanart outta you!
Who exactly are you worried about?
Do you even know what that means?
And don't assume, amid all this nonsense,
that I only have one male friend.
Now, now--you don't have to show off.
I'm not!
So that's how it is.
No, really--it's fine!
Whoops! Well, I've got another class.
Get to it.
She's a nice girl.
Sometimes.
Oh, Sak...
It's not like that.
Don't worry; I get it. Just leave it to me.
Huh?
You've found love at long last!
You don't get it at all!
Don't be bashful!
I'm your wingman--I've got your back!
Ugh! Another giant pain in the ass!
What sort of situation are you after?
Romantic? Erotic?
"Summer Romance Watermelon"
"Icy Cold" "Icy Cold" "Icy Cold"
Oh, this is going to be one fun summer!
Yes!
Ah, dammit.
Hey, you two.
Oh, hi.
Hey.
So how long have you known each other?
She was my junior in high school.
We were in the same club.
Huh. A pretty long time, then.
You could say that.
Uh-huh.
And how far have you gone?
Any fooling around?
Look here, you...
This guy looks good,
but he's really just the worst, huh.
So, is that a no?
It's a no!
It's not something you talk about--and
we wouldn't tell you even if we did!
Not even a little?
No!
Not at all?
Not at all!
Huh?
Eh?
Oh, uh... never mind.
Huh? Eh? N-Now hang on a sec--
I seriously don't remember anything!
N-No, it's fine. I mean, it's just between us.
If you don't know,
then it doesn't count. It's okay.
It is not okay! Tell me! What did I do? Where? When?
I knew it!
Ugh! Shut up! This is sexual harassment!
Now you're mad at me, and I don't even know why!
Sakaki, too, going all in
on the sexual harassment!
Just drop it.
S-Sexual... harassment?
Sorry.
Senpai's a good guy.
From where I stand, he's the
safest creature in the whole world.
When you put it like that...
it's actually pretty awful.
Again, sorry. I'd just never heard
any romantic tales about Sak before.
Seeing Mr. Serious here with
a girl piqued my interest, that's all.
We can't really help that.
He's a gloomy klutz of a sleepyhead
villain loner, so I keep him company.
Who are you calling a gloomy klutz
of a sleepyhead villain loner?!
I like to spend my time quietly, by myself!
You two get along amazingly well!
And it's not just me. I bet everyone thinks so!
You know: "Oh, those two must be dating."
Haven't you heard that tons of times?
But we're not.
Okay, you're not--for now. I get that much.
But you're gonna have to eventually.
Uzaki.
Let's grab some ice cream
from the convenience store. My treat.
Really? Hooray!
Did they just run away?
Still, that's not the reaction I was expecting.
I pictured something a little more innocent.
But it's not that he simply dislikes her...
There must be a reason.
Hmm?
Got a sec?
And who are you?
Ami Asai, senior. Friend of those two.
I'm Sakaki--same year as Sakurai.
Nice to meet you.
Sakaki.
What was that?
What was it? Just a friendly chat, that's all.
Were you listening in?
You should have joined us!
You've gone too far.
Teasing those two is one thing,
but do you have to be so blunt about it?
Just putting out some feelers.
I got shut out, though.
I want to watch over those two--and
I won't let anyone get in my way.
Doing things your way may very well
end up nipping their love in the bud.
You must watch them from a distance,
with no unnecessary prying!
I see...
So you're rooting for them, too, huh?
And you really care.
You've changed my mind.
After all, we both want them to be together.
How about we team up, then?
I'd do anything for those two!
Wrong!
What?!
I don't need anyone's help! Quit your meddling!
And what part of me wanting to observe
from out here do you not understand?!
You're pretty crass yourself!
I won't let you meddle
indiscriminately in their business!
Jeez, what a pain!
You both are.
Want to share, Senpai? C'mon.
You don't want any?
Don't be shy. After all, you bought 'em.
C'mon.
That refreshing green-blue
packaging... choco-mint, huh?
Is choco-mint any good?
Choco-mint is delicious!
Choco-mint...
But choco-mint--isn't that toothpaste?
Huh?
What did you just say?
Eh?
Look me in the eye and say that again.
Wait... what?
It's just... I was wondering
if choco-mint was really any good,
since that's what toothpaste tastes like.
There it is! You idiot!
That is always what people
who don't eat choco-mint say
when they're mocking choco-mint!
I'm not mocking anything.
You are! It started when
you compared it to toothpaste!
Even though it's your garbage palate's
fault you can't eat choco-mint,
you cowards are always
so quick to blame the mint!
"Coward"
Then these jerks always go to
"No way can that be good"
and "Why don't you just eat toothpaste, then?"
Morons!
Toothpaste isn't something you eat!
Can you even imagine it, Senpai?
How humiliating it is to be mocked
by idiots who don't know the difference
between toothpaste and food?!
Uh... yeah.
But what I really can't stand
is the sheer arrogance of people
who think it's okay to persecute
what they don't understand!
That's right! We choco-mintians
have been exposed for so long!
"Choco-mintians"?
Exposed to the unknowing abuse
that stems from a lack of understanding!
Isn't that just toothpaste?
When choco-mint, as ice cream,
made its way to Japan from distant continents,
sales were poor due to its
intense coloration and unique flavor.
And yet!
We choco-mintians, amidst bias and prejudice,
slowly grew in number with many years of effort.
Now it's praised as
invigorating, Instagrammable--
with more cafés serving choco-mint sweets
and more varieties of choco-mint goods
on food-store shelves every year!
Nevertheless!
The palate-poor anti-choco-mint
brigade chooses ignorance!
Rise, O choco-mintians!
Turn your sadness into anger
and make your stand!
You hate it, don't you, Senpai?
It sucks when people mock your favorite game
when they've never played it
and know nothing about it!
Well, yeah, it does.
Besides, it's all out of order!
Mint doesn't taste like toothpaste--
toothpaste tastes like mint!
Idiot!
She... She is seriously pissed.
Never mind those palate-poor losers!
I'm grateful for choco-mint!
Thank you, choco-mint!
One bite and the sharp,
refreshing mint flavor fills your mouth,
the gentle notes of sweet chocolate
slowly fading away.
That soothing feeling makes you
want to take another bite right away.
No matter what anyone says...
...choco-mint is delicious.
What the hell?
Thank you very much.
Brava. I guess you've been
holding onto some things, too.
Oh, yeah.
You can hate whatever you want,
but don't diss what someone else likes.
Mind your own beeswax!
Though you did mock my solo movies.
But man, I never dreamed that you
would be one of those lower lifeforms.
Over one lousy ice cream? That's a little much.
It's not that I hate it...
I couldn't handle mint as a kid.
Ever since, anything with that cooling
sensation--gum, cough drops--forget it.
I even use a non-mint toothpaste.
That cooling sensation is the best part!
With the sweet chocolate chaser?
That's the real charm of choco-mint!
But since I can't do mint,
I've never tried choco-mint.
What?!
Why, you... Mock choco-mint untasted, will you?!
All right! I'm sorry, I'm sorry!
I see. So it all stems from childhood trauma.
But that means you should be fine now, right?
They do say your sense of
taste changes as you grow up.
Maybe, but still...
Wanna try one, just to see?
Why the hesitation?
You'll be fine--it's not an intense mint.
What, are you scared?
Huh?
C'mon, you can do it.
Conquer your pickiness. Mint's not scary.
Your eyes sure are!
Look, just eat it already. C'mon!
All right, fine. Here goes...
Great! Say "ah"!
Now that I think about it, isn't this...
An indirect--?!
Wait--now it's rubbing off on me!
But if I don't eat this now,
it'll turn into this big thing again.
Couldn't she be a little more mindful?!
Ugh!
Well?
It... it's actually, uh... tasty, I... I'd say.
That's a pretty vague answer.
But you managed to eat it!
Last one's mine!
Oh, I-I'm sorry.
For... For what?
N-Nothing...
Don't realize it now!
But it'll take a thousand years
for them to get together on their own!
Then I'll live a thousand years!
"Episode 6: Summer! The Beach!
I Want to Test My Courage!"
I will get you two together, Sak!