Look, Senpai--the ocean!
I mean, obviously.
Right?
Ocean! Ocean! Ocean!
It's so hot...
"Beach Barn"
"Watermelon Piñatas 2,000 Yen"
Niiice.
The beach in summer makes everyone open up.
What are these four doing there?
It all began one afternoon a week earlier,
right here in this café.
All right, folks: here comes
Uzaki-chan Wants to Hang Out!
Ready? Go!
"Uzaki-chan Wants to Hang Out!"
"Episode 6: Summer! The Beach!
I Want to Test My Courage!"
And so,
this is our new part-timer: Hana Uzaki.
Glad to be part of the team!
What's the big idea?
You were so gung-ho on me quitting
so I could get some peace!
Aw, don't be a hater. We'll have fun!
Although I'm here in part because
I wanted to see that hater face of yours.
Damn you!
With summer break around the corner and all,
I wanted a little more spending money.
I asked the owner and got his immediate okay!
I thought it'd be fun,
so I figured I'd hire her.
That's your reason?!
Now, Sakurai, you may not like Hana,
but she is the one who
came to me looking for a job.
Wouldn't it be wrong for you to try to stop her?
B-But...
Well, just show her the ropes for now.
One learns by teaching, you know.
All right.
You sure about this, Senpai?
Think you can teach me?
Listen, you...
When a customer comes in,
show them to their seat.
Regulars often head to their
favorite spot before you take them there.
I'm a practice customer.
Here: ice water and a hand towel.
This is the first thing
we bring to each new customer.
Wait till you see they're seated,
then bring these out.
Please let me know when you're ready to order.
Careful not to make a menu-reading
customer feel rushed or pressured.
Then you take their order.
That's how it usually goes. Next we'll--
Ooh! Senpai!
Huh? What is it?
Where are all the jokes?
There aren't any! What exactly did you expect?!
This act is going on forever!
You gotta toss in a little joke or three.
What act?! We're not putting on a skit here!
So serious!
Of course! You're getting
paid for this--take it seriously!
So serious!
Hey, it's your café, Mr. Employer!
We've been showing her how
it's done since before you arrived.
This right here was all about winding you up!
What the hell?!
Thank you very much!
Hey, are you going anywhere over summer break?
Hmm? Nowhere in particular.
I've been looking forward
to this game that's coming out--
I plan to hole up at home as much as possible.
What?!
You do that all year long!
You're gonna waste your
precious summer break on games?!
Oh, man... this is shaping up
to be the best summer ever!
Th-This athletic shut-in is just hopeless.
I've got to do something!
Then let's go to the beach! Or a pool!
Eh?
Then it's settled! A done deal!
You haven't done any swimming since
you graduated high school, have you?
Now that you mention it... no.
Huh!
Heard you were working together
and came by to see for myself.
Huh?
Oh!
Now this looks like a fun conversation!
It's so hot...
Hey, Ami!
Over here!
Hey, Hana!
Here, here! Over this way!
What a terrible sight.
Those things are weapons.
We rented an umbrella and
set out a beach blanket! C'mon!
Thanks!
I wish the bossman could have come, too.
Not after he threw out his back.
Ow, ow, ow, ow, ow...
Oh, Sakaki? He came a little earlier,
said he was gonna check out our lodging.
Right.
I'll handle transportation and lodging.
Huh? You sure, Itsuhito?
Hooray! Let's all go together!
Beach! Beach! Beach!
Hey! Where do you get off--
I know how you feel, but... it's them.
Can you in good conscience send them off?
Just the two of them--no regrets?
So now it's up to me to watch over those two.
Oh? Where's Sakurai? Wasn't he with you?
Senpai? He's...
...there!
That's far! How did he wind up out there?!
"Kids, don't try this at home!"
He got so hyped up gazing at the water,
then went running into it full tilt
like he just couldn't take it anymore!
That jerk will stop at nothing
to get his alone time.
I've never swum in the ocean before--
the waves make it
a little different than a pool.
And fun!
Hardcore much?!
Listen, Sakurai, you don't need goggles
at the beach--let alone a swim cap!
You're not a lifeguard!
Oh, really?
See? It's like I told you.
The whole swim-club look turns
people off, so let's skip it today.
Look, we're here to have fun!
This is leisure time!
Forget all about swim club for now!
She's super ticked off.
And why'd you leave Hana behind
and go swimming alone?
Huh?
See, if you're all alone, so is Hana.
What if someone hits on her?
Huh?
Can you be responsible if something happens?
The guy she came with has to look out for her!
Got it? Say something!
Y-Yessir...
You can start with swimsuit compliments.
I doubt it'll come easy to you,
but that's what you get for going solo.
Uh... okay.
Let's see...
You look really good in that swimsuit.
Just wonderful.
The sky blue suits your personal image,
and, uh...
Not mine!
Wow, what a shock. Looking at me
so seriously from so close up...
Doofus.
Hey, Uzaki...
What's up, Senpai? The dolphin's almost ready.
Oh, dear! Did he say something?
Huh? Oh, nothing! Nothing at all!
Covering up her embarrassment, huh?
Will that do?
Good job. Well done.
I remain somewhat suspicious.
Hey! Enjoying yourselves? I brought a snack!
Oh, thanks.
Ooh, a watermelon!
But we'll use this.
A bat?
That's right--it's time for...
...a seaside standby: the watermelon piñata!
Why me?
You've never done it before!
We're making memories, Sak!
Okay, blindfold's on.
If you insist. Come at me--from any direction!
It's actually more fun to be on the guiding end.
Or the mis guiding end.
First let's blindside him
and drop-kick him into the ocean!
You go there first?
What kind of games do you play, anyway?
Okay, Uzaki, you get right on Sak there.
Roger that!
Hang on--can I get a video
of this with my phone?
Hey! You realize I can
hear everything you're saying!
Go on then, Sak!
Ooh, Senpai, you're practically a sitting duck.
I'll get you for this.
Okay, here goes...
Right!
Over a short distance: up, down, left, right, B!
That's how you start? Are you nuts?
Down, up, down, B, down-right,
up-left, B, up, up-left, A!
Why the hell are you feeding me
inputs for fighting-game moves?!
Seriously, quit screwing around!
Right, right, up, down, left, B!
Left, down, right, up, A, B!
Wow, is she in her element.
Nothing left for us to do.
That doesn't make any sense!
Now that's what I call a gift.
Dammit...
Start by walking forward, Sakurai.
"True"
A little to the right--to the right!
Senpai, Senpai! Up, X, down, B, L, Y, R, A!
"Not an option"
Shut up, Uzaki!
Uh-oh--
Ow, ow, ow, ow, ow...
Huh?
What's this? A jellyfish?
Now, come on--that's just way too convenient!
Hey, tell me where to go! Where's that melon?
Aren't you grabbing it right now?
Huh?
Could you please move first?
Are we there yet?
Relax. The place is just up ahead.
What are you so pouty about?
Nothing. I'm not pouty.
Oh?
It was bound to happen.
Ugh, forget it! Where's that damn watermelon?
Huh? Oh, so that was the watermelon.
He is such a doofus.
Here we are.
When you said you'd handle the lodging...
Is this your summer home?
Come on in. Pick whichever room you like!
I didn't know you were rich, Sakaki.
I knew you had a summer home,
but this is the first I've seen it.
I invited you last year--you just didn't come!
And my parents are the rich ones, not me.
Whoa! Check it out, Senpai!
A rich person's light switch!
Wow! It really is!
Whoa! The intercom has a camera!
Seriously?!
Whoa! It's one of those click-pull things!
Awesome!
What's your standard for "rich," anyway?
Take anything you want from the fridge.
I stocked it up for today.
Wow...
Look, Senpai: meat!
You do like meat, don't you?
Well, of course I do! After all, it is meat!
Mmm, delish! Cookouts are the best!
What are we going to do after this?
I brought a game!
So did I.
Then it's a showdown!
Hey, you two, you can do that any old time!
It's summer break!
Sleeping away from home! And nighttime!
That calls for a certain... activity.
To the back hills!
Well, we did what you said
and followed you here...
Is there something up there?
It's awfully dark.
Are we going to build a campfire?
Sure, it's a little clichéd,
but it's just not summer without...
...a test of courage! Let's do it!
I'm out.
There's this bluff up ahead, see?
I don't want to hear it! I'm out!
What gives, Sak? Not into this kind of thing?
I don't play horror games
or watch horror flicks.
And do you know why?
Because they're scary!
You struck a pose to say that?
He's desperately trying to avoid danger.
Okay! I'm sorry!
I seriously didn't know it was
a problem for you. I apologize.
Still... while it's great to be honest and all,
maybe it wasn't such a hot idea
to announce your own weakness.
Huh...
So scary stuff is too much for you, eh, Senpai?
Why, I had no idea. Huh!
Knock that off, Uzaki. It was all my fault.
Isn't it too early to raise the white flag?
He really can't deal with scary stuff, can he?
Yoink!
Ah!
Woohoo! Got your phone!
Time to air all your dirty laundry
for everyone to see!
No! Give that back! I mean it!
You'll have to catch me first!
Damn you!
Ooh, you're fast, Senpai!
Quit going further in!
Wait up! Hey!
Was this the plan?
I figured we'd all go in together.
Plus, I was picturing it the other way around.
Oh, Senpai, I'm so scared!
Good girl.
Ah, well. Shall we go after them?
The other day...
Huh?
You told me not to meddle, to watch over them.
That's right.
So I thought I'd just create
the right conditions instead.
Conditions for them to turn
into something interesting.
I knew it. I figured that's what happened.
But when every move those
two make is so unexpected...
It doesn't go so well.
But... why?
Huh?
Why would you go to such lengths?
Why? Hmm...
Sak's a great guy,
but he's so damn serious,
and awkward, and bad at making friends,
and a loner...
And while I know it's none of my business,
I wish his college life could be more fun.
Otherwise, it's kind of
a waste, don't you think?
That and... other reasons.
Other reasons, huh?
Oh, there they are.
Huh?
I'm really sorry, Senpai. Please forgive me!
I got carried away.
Sakaki and Ami are here, see? We'll all head back
and have some ice cream, okay?
I can't move another step.
His voice is so weak!
All right, I'm calling it off. Let's go back.
We can go back and play games, Senpai.
Play games...
So weak!
Yesss! Look at that, Senpai! New high score!
You said you were going to play games!
Sakaki and Ami fell asleep, too...
Well, we did have a really active day today.
Everyone's just tuckered out.
Still, seeing his sleeping face
like this gets me all restless!
It's your fault for letting down your guard!
S-S-Senpai! What are you doing?!
He's asleep?
So he's a hugger, huh? Didn't see that coming.
Phew, what a fright.
Wh-Whoa, Senpai!
You're not secretly awake, are you?!
He's out cold.
I guess he wouldn't do this if he were awake.
After all, I am the one who teased
the scaredy cat and tired him out.
Maybe it's okay for a little while, anyway.
Just for today... Just for today...
Huh!
So I fell asleep in the
living room after all that, eh?
But man, it feels like
I had a great night's sleep!
You might want to invest
in one of those body pillows.
Huh? Why's that?
Oh, no reason!
I get the feeling we missed on
something extremely important.
Next time I'll get those two together for sure!
And I bet Kakyoin's soul
that you'll fail yet again!
"Episode 7: I Want to Hang Out
at a Cat Café and a Pub!"