Let's get going!
"Tottori Sand Dunes Conan Airport"
Where to first?
Well, let's see.
We're in Tottori, so...
No Starbucks, just Sandbox!
Crab rich, cash poor!
Welcome to Tottori Prefecture!
What's with that guy, Senpai?
Don't you know, dummy? Why, he's...
No 7-Elevens? Still heaven!
He's a big shot.
We should probably hit the sand dunes first.
Says here we can paraglide--or go sandboarding!
You like the more active stuff, huh?
Oh, yeah.
All solo activities, I notice.
You're going full loner here in Tottori, too!
And you still don't know when to zip it.
So how are we gonna get there?
We'll take a bus or something.
Yoohoo!
Yo!
Itsuhito!
Ami!
"Uzaki-chan Wants to Hang Out!"
"Episode 10: I Want to Hang Out in Tottori!"
So you're both here, too!
Dad gave me a summer break. And then...
I was thinking of taking
a trip when she ran into me
and suggested meeting up with you two here.
Huh! I feel bad, you guys renting a car and all.
Nah, it's totally fine.
You're so thoughtful, Sakaki!
Your personality's a little iffy,
but you sure are thoughtful!
That personality, though...
Please, enough with the compliments!
Those weren't compliments.
It's definitely more convenient
to travel by car. See?
It's a lot broader than I imagined.
Right? A rental car is a must
if you want real freedom.
Spoken like a seasoned traveler.
You know me!
So went our story.
But our trip here serves another purpose.
That's right: Hana and Sakurai,
vacationing alone together...
I view their relationship as hands-off,
and even I couldn't stay away!
We've been watching over them thus far.
We have a duty to see
this trip through to its end!
And we get front-row seats! What a treat!
Not to mention a trip to Tottori.
Pure happenstance, but amusing nonetheless.
These two still don't know the real Tottori!
Hey, a 7-Eleven!
Hey, yeah! So they do have them.
"Tottori Sand Dunes National Park"
When you see them in person,
they really are spectacular.
Aren't they? What a sight!
The Tottori Sand Dunes
measure 2.4 km north to south
and 16 km east to west.
They're the largest
accessible sand dunes in Japan.
The dune in front there is called
the Horse's Back; it's about 50 meters high.
It's quite popular:
you can see the entirety of the dunes
and take in views of
the Japan Sea from its peak.
Wow, nice!
All right, Senpai! Race you to the ocean!
You're on!
If I win, you owe me a nashi pear ice cream!
And if I win, you owe me
a sand-dune coffee ice cream!
Okay, here goes.
Get set...
Go!
The sand's really grabbing my feet.
This is tough!
Hey, hey!
Wha--
Hey! What is that?
A sandboard, just like you were
talking about! I reserved one!
That's not fair!
Ha! A contest begins well before it starts!
Catch you on the flip side!
Dammit!
You'll never catch up to me, Sen... pai?
Hold it right there!
I win.
A competition...
against this... beautiful backdrop...
Have you no soul?
I admire your nerve, whining
about losing under the circumstances.
Still...
It really is beautiful.
Makes our race seem like small potatoes.
So I don't owe you?
No--you do.
Excuse me!
Could you please take our picture?
Oh, sure.
Thank you!
Tottori!
Thank you very much!
Oh, Atsy-pie, you look so cool in that shot!
And you are just too cute, Miho-Miho!
Sh-Shall we?
I can't walk...
Oh, all right.
I still have some strength left.
It's so round!
This is Japan's oldest circular school building,
originally a primary school.
Now dilapidated, it was due to be torn down,
but the many citizens who wanted it
to remain spurred officials into action,
and the building was reborn as a museum!
Now it has various local specialties on display.
Regional specialties, eh?
Like nashi pears?
Can't forget Matsuba snow crabs...
Figurines!
And Nendoroids, too!
Tottori is the Manga Prefecture,
the birthplace of many manga artists--
and home to a figurine factory as well!
In other words, manga and figurines
are indeed local Tottori specialties!
I'm starting to get that feeling, yes.
Really packs an irresistible punch.
Oh, these are adorable!
Senpai, buy these for me as a souvenir!
Four of them?
They look like four sisters--and
I want the full set!
Oh! Different versions! Double or nothing!
Double--nothing!
Tottori!
A rabbit!
And that "Mistress Himiko!" person.
Ōkuninushi-no-Mikoto.
Also known as Ōnamuji-no-Kami.
Ōkuninushi-no-Mikoto,
famously of "The White Hare of Inaba,"
in enshrined here at Hakuto Shrine.
Because the deity healed a hare
whose fur had been torn off by a shark,
the shrine is revered for its benefits
to those with skin diseases and injuries.
Senpai, look! Rabbit cakes!
Wow, those look tasty!
Er, Uzaki? Who's this?
The shop clerk.
Would you mind paying, please?
Much obliged, Senpai!
Now it's my treat?!
Soft and chewy and oh so delish!
Good for you.
Oh, don't be so angry. Here!
There's enough for you, too.
All right. Here goes.
Ack! He's gonna gobble me up!
Ugh! Curse you humans!
Nooo!
Will you shut up? I can't eat like this!
You're not gonna eat that?
Well! Don't mind if I do!
Half! In one bite!
Mmm-mmm-mmm! One more bite!
As if!
You're wide open!
Inattention is the greatest foe.
Look here...
Isn't it just so delicious?
Mmm, it sure is!
Okay: say "ah"!
Aw, you ate half of it!
You have to notice these things
before you go off on a roll!
Right...
Quit looking at my mouth!
Is this it?
Yes. Any minute now and they
should tweak to the truth about Tottori.
May our travels end without a hitch.
May Senpai's loner ways be healed.
I'm not a loner!
Hey, they have fortunes, Senpai!
Let's see who wins!
It's not a competition.
But sure.
"Number 11" "Middling Luck"
Ha! "Middling Luck"--this has to be a winner!
"Number 18" "Great Luck"
Nice try! Mine is "Great Luck"--"Great Luck"!
Looks like I win!
How's it feel to be all smug about
middling luck and then lose, huh? Huh?
I have no words.
Now then! What's it say?
"Hobbies: A gamer is best.
Personality: Preferably a loner.
Age: One year older.
Direction: Right in front of"...
Huh?
What kind of fortunes are these?!
Don't tell me... is this shrine...
"Hakuto Shrine couples." "Search."
Hmph. It seems you've finally arrived.
You've reached the truth of Hakuto Shrine--
indeed, that of Tottori itself.
You knew?
We didn't do all that touring for nothing.
That myth has linked Hakuto Jinja
to healing skin conditions and injuries.
But that is just a cover!
That same hare arranged a match between
Ōkuninushi-no-Mikoto and Yagamihime.
And based on this, Japan's first love story,
Hakuto is a matchmaking
shrine--rivaling the shrine at Izumo!
And Tottori is home to two more sites,
both veritable meccas for lovers
on a par with Hakuto Shrine here.
Do you see what I'm saying?
No way...
That's right: to say that
"Tottori tourists" equals "couples in love"
is no exaggeration!
"It's an exaggeration"
That's where you two,
a man and a woman, came to visit.
And this is how everyone else saw you!
"I'm not too heavy, am I, darling?"
"You're lighter than
a Tottori dune beetle, my honey!"
"Mementos of my Tottori trip with you, darling!"
"I'll take everything on the shelf!"
"Oh, darling, rabbit cakes
taste best ears first."
"I'm a tail-first kind of guy, my honey!"
You have got to be kidding me!
But people totally did think you were a couple.
Ha ha! Sak and Hana, sittin' in a tree!
Damn you...
K-I-S-S-I-N-G!
What are you talking about?
Me and Senpai, all lovey-dovey? Yeah, right!
Oh, come off it already!
Why does everything have
to be about love with you, anyway?
Is that all there is?
Are you some kind of love fiend?
You really are hopeless.
At 1,700 meters tall, Daisen is the
highest mountain in the Chugoku region.
It's a destination for all seasons with
autumn color and snowy winter landscapes.
And it's another spot for lovers.
Not that again...
That has nothing to do with us!
C'mon, Senpai. Here's the lift.
A couple's seat! Isn't that wonderful?
They must be really in love!
Sak and Hana, sittin' in a tree!
Please, go ahead.
Oh! You must play for the other team!
Oho!
What "other team"?!
You're dragging me into this?
I just want to enjoy my Tottori trip!
It really isn't like that with--
Uzaki!
Eeyeah?!
We came here to hang out in Tottori--that's all.
To visit the dunes, eat nashi and Matsuba crabs,
and have fun with all
the Conan and Kitaro stuff!
Right?
Uh... yeah.
All right! So let's forget
the others and enjoy ourselves!
Senpai...
We'll show them!
Right on!
Dammit, Tottori, read the room!
Tottori!
"Towels used with permission
for filming purposes"
With 850 years of history,
Misasa is a world-class radium hot spring
and home to many types of hot-spring treatments.
It's said that any malady will be cured
after your third morning at this hot spring,
hence the name: written with
the characters "three" and "morning."
See you later.
Yep.
Phew, I'm beat.
We did a ton of running around today.
Are you sure about this? After finally
getting to share a room with Sakurai?
Just kidding.
What are you doing? That was your chance!
I told you, it's not like that.
Hey.
It will be.
Itsuhito...
Look, you're wrong, okay?
Senpai! Let's go to the steam bath--
Don't you dare!
At Misasa Hot Spring, the waters are
for soaking, drinking, and breathing in.
Inhaling the mist at this steam bath
will cure what ails you from the inside out.
I bet it'll heal your mean face
if you inhale enough of it.
Really? I better get breathing, then.
Hey. Rude.
Pretty half-hearted comeback there, Sakurai.
It's so hot, that's all he can manage.
Wow, you're sweating buckets.
It's never-ending.
Can I have your towel, Senpai?
Just how sweaty are you?
It's pouring out of me. Your towel...
Senpai, you're all damp and sticky!
That's your fault! Get off me!
That tickles!
Sorry--you're going to have to deal with it!
Yow! Not there!
Please! Save that for
the privacy of your room!
Eh?
Ah, this feels great!
Especially after sweating so much.
I was soaking wet!
Senpai wouldn't give me his towel.
He is so inconsiderate!
Who are you calling inconsiderate?
Are you eavesdropping on us? Pervert!
Oh, shut up.
All that sweating must have
flushed the badness out of you.
Now go live an orderly life.
"Badness"? What "badness"?
You're the villain-faced loner introvert!
If only you'd sweated
out your annoyingness, too.
And at a hot spring, no less.
What an unsexy conversation.
All right--fine!
Let's see which one of us is worse!
Oh, you are on!
Gotcha.
They're just not going in...
All right: I've got the hang of it.
I can win this.
You can put those
extra balls in this box, Senpai.
Hey, thanks.
Sure thing.
Now then...
Hey!
Tch.
Hurry up, Senpai!
Wait up, will you?
Make it snappy or you're gonna lose!
This is tyranny!
So nothing changed, after all that.
That's all right.
They're tasty enough just as they are.
Are they, though?
A frog! What's this for?
What, indeed?
"Matchmaking: The Kajika Frog"
"Rub this beloved matchmaking kajika frog
to make your dream match come true."
A matchmaking kajika frog?
"Rub to make your dream match come true."
I guess they are pretty tasty.
Right?
Thanks for the feast.
"Mizuki Shigeru Road"
We have to finish with this place!
Check out all these yōkai, Senpai!
There are some I know and some I've never seen.
There are 177 bronze statues of yōkai
over 800 meters of this street,
which leads to Sakaiminato Station.
177 of them? Amazing!
What's this, Senpai?
A dragon?
Let's see... Nope! It's a shiro-uneri!
Shiro... uneri?
Okay, next! What's this?
A crayfish?
Bzzt! An amikiri!
These are tough. What's the next one?
Right here!
A yeti!
Keukegen! What's this "yeti" stuff?
That's not even Japanese--whoa!
Dammit. You try this next one. Here.
Wait: this is--aw!
Rokuro-Kubi! It's Rokuro-Kubi!
I knew that one!
Okay, moving on!
"Mizuki Shigeru Museum"
Yep, this is the place.
The Mizuki Shigeru Museum is a must-see.
"Mizuki Shigeru Road"
"Episode 11: Does Sakurai
Want to Hang Out, Too?"