Environmental concerns and the
increasing scarcity of fossil fuels
have led to the cessation in the manufacture
of cars with internal combustion engines.
As a result, high-powered sports cars
have become an endangered species.
Almost as a requiem to mourn their
imminent passing, a new motorsport series
has arisen here in Japan.
With a global audience
of 30 million subscribers,
it has achieved explosive popularity.
The only regulation is
uniform grip-to-weight ratio,
resulting in some no-holds-barred,
white-knuckle racing.
Its name: MFG.
MF Ghost
The Challenger
from England
It's the MFG season opener,
and we're here at Odawara Pikes Peak
for the start of the
second day of qualifying.
Ten seconds to go.
Nine. Eight. Seven.
Six. Five. Four.
Three. Two. One.
Come on, Aiba. You've got this!
He's really going for it!
MFG, huh?
Just once, I wish I could go
see them race in person.
Not happening. They don't let
spectators line the route,
and there's still volcanic gas
in the air from that eruption.
My friends in England
were all obsessed with it, too.
Makes sense it's popular here,
as it started in Japan.
I honestly can't make head or tail of
these addresses. Talk about a bad start.
Hey, Wakana.
The English guy is showing up today, right?
Technically, he's half-English, half-Japanese.
You shouldn't get your hopes up, anyway.
I don't really get cool vibes from England.
Aw, you're no fun at all.
You'd better introduce me if he's hot!
Get real, Wakana.
It's because you go after anyone hot
that you always end up with lame guys.
I can't even imagine love at first sight.
Excuse me. I'm Aiba Shun.
I came in ninth last year, and, um,
from the moment I first saw you...
A-Anyway, I'm serious!
Sorry.
That was fast!
I don't know how you expect me to react
when you don't know anything about me.
W-Wait, just one thing!
On the MFG Angels' profile page,
you're the only one listed
without any info, right?
Could you at least tell me your name?
MFGA Seven.
You can call me Number Seven, if you wish.
Looks are basically the same as clothes.
They don't reflect who you really are.
I wanna fall in love with
a guy who I think is super hot,
even if 99% of girls don't
agree with me that he is.
I'm home.
You're late, Ren.
Come in here and let me introduce you.
Pretty sure I said I was gonna be late today
because of work. I told Mom, at least.
This is Kanata-kun. Mr. Kanata Rivington.
He just got in this afternoon.
This will be his first time living overseas,
so I'm sure he'll have questions,
and I'd appreciate you helping
him as much as you can, Ren.
It's a pleasure to meet you, Ren-san.
You can call me Kanata.
I-I...
Uh, I have math homework, so...
Well, she's at an awkward age.
I have to say, I'm impressed by
how fluent your Japanese is.
My mum taught me when I was still young.
I see.
It's a real shame what
happened to Katherine.
You remind me a lot of her
when she was younger.
Crap.
I feel like I just got shocked
with a million volts.
Why's my heart still pounding?
I'm not supposed to judge
people by appearances.
So... what is this feeling?
Odakyu Katase-Enoshima Station
Morning, Ren!
Wakana.
So how'd it go?
How'd what go?
Isn't it obvious?
Your houseguest from England.
I... don't really know.
What the heck? You could
at least show me a picture.
I didn't take one.
He's sticking around for a while,
so just come by and see him.
That's so hot! Shacking up
with some half-English guy...
What's he in Japan for, anyway?
Just vacation stuff?
I dunno. Come to think of it,
I didn't really ask about anything.
Ogata Automotive Ltd.
Is this it?
Qualifying Run
Excuse me.
Right on time!
Uh... Are you Kanata Rivington?
And you're Ogata-san, yes?
It's a pleasure. I'm Kanata.
Oh, you actually speak
Japanese? That's a relief.
Ogata Automotive
I hear you went to a
famous English racing school?
I thought Saionji-san was joking
when he brought it up.
So I'm sure you're aware,
but MFG has a bit of a weird rule
about standardized grip-to-weight ratio.
The strongest cars tend to be
European models with lots of horsepower
and good balance, without a lot of modding.
As a result, people complain about the rule,
calling it the "rich man's regulation."
Which is why I'm not able to
provide you with a competitive vehicle,
looking at the big picture
of MFG performance.
I've heard.
But I'll be happy just
getting to experience MFG.
Okay! In that case,
I'll support you in any way I can.
Care to take a look at the car?
Wow.
Good.
It's so cool.
You don't have to flatter me.
It's just an old-fashioned three-pedaler.
Can you work with it?
No problem.
Back at the academy, H-pattern shifters
with three pedals was the standard.
I've already taken care of your entry.
You're running on the seventh
and final day of qualifying.
1st Odahara Pikes Peak Official Qualifying Run
Qualifying Run
Huh?
What a coincidence.
Sure seems like it.
Are you on your way home
from school, Ren-san?
You can drop the "san."
For one thing, I'm younger
than you. Just "Ren" is fine.
Where are you coming back from, Kanata?
I went over to Tokyo to visit
the British embassy in Yotsuya.
I also bought a new cell phone.
Really? In that case, let's swap contact info.
Not, like, in that way...
But it means, if you need help at all,
you can get in touch with me right away.
Good idea. Hang on a minute.
You had work yesterday,
right, Ren? What about today?
My job's a little, uh, irregular.
It's maybe two or three days a week,
then there's a big gap until the next time.
I see.
I actually wanted to ask
you something, Kanata.
Could we take a picture together?
A picture?
When I told my friend about you,
she wanted to see what you look like.
Is it okay?
Here I go. Smile!
That turned out great! Wanna see?
Photos aren't my thing.
What made you want to leave home
and come to Japan, Kanata?
I don't mind making an
exception and telling you, Ren.
I came to Japan for two reasons.
Well, really, it's only one.
What's that?
To find my missing father.
Your dad?
MF Ghost
MF Ghost.
Morning, Ren!
Good morning, Wakana.
Show me the thing! C'mon, c'mon!
I saw that coming.
Here.
Oh my god! Can you believe it?!
I guess Kanata really is hot?
What's this?
A picture from 20 years ago.
And the only one I have of my father.
I love that photo because of how
happy my mother looks in it.
It was taken in a town called Kamakura.
I decided that, if I ever made it to Japan,
I'd find the location in that photo.
Kamakura's pretty close by. I know it.
Do you mind if I help you find it, Kanata?
It's just a really romantic idea, that's all.
I want to help you find this place.
What's wrong, Kanata?
Why are you so kind to me, Ren?
I don't really know how
to express my gratitude.
You and your father have
just been so wonderful.
I can't thank you enough.
Japanese people are amazing.
It's not happening, Aiba-san.
Aw, come on. Don't be such a stickler.
All I'm asking for is
Number Seven's name and age.
Profile
Name: ? Birthday: ? Birthplace: ?
You've posted all kinds of stuff
about the other Angels.
That kind of personal information
is confidential. No exceptions.
Then, could you at least tell me
which race she's working next?
Hm, let's see...
Katagiri Kanata-san.
If you'll just sign here.
Right.
Never seen him before. Is he a rookie?
Hey, man.
You entering MFG?
That's right. Who are you?
I'm Aiba Shun. I'm ranked
a dizzyingly high ninth.
Oh, I know you! Aiba in the Nissan GT-R!
This is great! It's truly an honor!
People love your GT-R back in England.
England?
Yes! I arrived from there two days ago.
I'm Kanata Rivi—Wait, no.
My name is Katagiri Kanata.
I'm running on the last day of qualifying.
You sure you're gonna be okay?
This is MFG we're talking about.
Well, I guess it's fine.
I bet we met for a reason.
I don't mind taking you
under my wing for a bit.
Listen up, Kanata.
From now on, you call me "Senpai."
We're big sticklers for the beauty of
tradition around here. You follow?
Yes, sir, Aiba-senpai!
Aw, man. I love how earnest this dude is.
Odawara
Office
Did you eat yet? I'll treat you to a
great Japanese lunch. Follow me.
Sir!
He's steadily moving up the times
through Sector 3 of the course!
There's only one car
between him and top spot!
Michael Beckenbauer's
showing no sign of weakness!
Am I imagining it or is that
Porsche smaller than a regular one?
Curry
Beef
Bowl
Beef Bowl + Curry
Open
It's a Cayman. They're about
a size smaller than the 911.
You seriously didn't know that?
Beckenbauer's straight out of
Porsche's motorsports program.
He's some kinda super-elite racer.
He would probably have been a
Le Mans driver in the good old days.
Qualifying Run / 1st Position
Oh, great. He's made it to
the top of the leaderboard.
How the hell is he managing these times
with the kind of power a Cayman has?
Here you are.
Go ahead and eat up.
Beef bowls are a delicacy.
Thank you for the food.
How old are you anyway, Kanata?
I'm 19.
Damn, that's young.
Five years younger than me.
Wait, you don't know how to use chopsticks?
Hey, miss. Could you bring this guy a spoon?
Ogata Automotive Ltd.
Are you around, Ogata-san?
Oh, hey, Kanata.
What's up?
I wanted to see if there was
anything I could help you with.
Yeah, sure. I was looking
to take a break, anyway.
Koala's
March
It's good.
They don't have snacks anywhere
near as good as this in England.
Japan is unbelievable.
Between this and beef bowls,
it's like everything you guys eat is amazing.
You're exaggerating.
I'll admit the snacks here are good, though.
To tell you the truth, Kanata,
one of my cars has raced in MFG before.
It hasn't been refitted since,
so it should easily pass the inspection,
and there's no real need
to make big changes.
Who was the driver?
You, Ogata-san? Wow!
I guess. Call it a youthful misadventure.
I used to race back then, and was
pretty confident about my skills...
But I didn't amount to much.
The downhill stretch in
Sector 3 scared me so bad,
by the time I crossed the finish line,
I was heartbroken and exhausted.
What it boils down to is I'm better suited
to tinkering with cars than driving them.
Ogata Automotive
Can't deny how much I love these
old gasoline models, though.
I don't think this is it.
The buildings in the background
seem totally different.
I'm pretty sure it was taken on the
grounds of a shrine or a temple...
And wouldn't you know it? Kamakura's
absolutely crawling with spots like that.
We'll have to use process of
elimination to work through them.
Let's stay strong!
It really does feel strange, being here.
So much so, it's hard for me
to put it into Japanese.
What do you mean?
My mother met my father here
when she was still just a teenager.
They fell in love,
lived together, then I was born.
Being here in Kamakura is unbelievable.
Like something out of a dream.
It feels like I've come to
the hometown of my heart.
I've wanted to visit
ever since I was small.
Kanata...
Hey, Kanata, let's make an offering.
He's so earnest.
It's adorable.
Asakura Komachi Road
What did you wish for, Ren?
I'm not saying.
If you tell someone else,
the gods might not hear you.
Crap, it's already late!
Remember, Mom, I've got work today!
I know.
Don't trip in your rush.
Be careful.
I'm off!
Ren's got work today?
And I have an event of my own.
Hello. This is Joyu
with the Tokyo Main Office.
The Executive Organizer
made a direct request.
There's a name on the entry list
he was hoping to meet.
Kanata Rivington, 19 years old.
He's a British citizen.
Not there? That's odd.
Did the kid Ryosuke mentioned not show up?
Hello there to the 30 million
MFG fans across the globe!
I'm MFG's walking encyclopedia, Tanaka Yoji,
and I'll be providing live commentary today.
It's finally the seventh
and last day of qualifying,
and this round has been typified by a lot
of shakeups at the top of the timesheets.
Thanks to aggressive moves
by the Porsche camp,
the Italian big hitters, Ferrari
and Lamborghini, have struggled.
The hope of home nation manufacturers,
Aiba Shun and his GT-R, is currently in fifth.
Odawara's own "Kamikaze
Outlaw" is making waves.
Only 15 of the 302 entrants
will make it into the race proper,
earning them the title
of the "Godly Fifteen."
The "Godly Fifteen"?
Well, we gotta worry about
qualifying before anything else.
The new set of tires I put on
should last for three races.
Ogata-san, I apologize if the tires
are worn out after this race.
It's better if I warn you in advance.
And there's the board. We have 10 seconds
left before the first racer takes off.
It's being held up by Number Seven,
a new addition to the Angels this year.
I'm personally a big fan.
Look at those curves!
It's enough to take your breath away!
Shut the hell up, Tanaka.
Where do you get off,
creeping on my Number Seven?
And there's the start!
Just the sight of her makes my heart hurt.
Number Seven, my darling...
Oh, Aiba-senpai!
Oh, hey, if it isn't Shun! It's been a while.
Is that you, Ogata?
What're you doing here?
Didn't you already set a time?
Well, I, uh...
I'm here to root for Kanata,
of course. I'm kinda worried.
How do you even know Kanata?
Aiba-senpai bought me a beef bowl.
I ran into him at the office.
Wow, that's a hell of a coincidence.
Talk about a small world.
Anyway, the chitchat will have to wait.
We've only got 10 minutes until the off.
Let's hurry, Kanata.
You need any help? Which car is it?
The one I used to race in.
There it is.
Number 86.
Good.
Got a few crucial pieces of info
for you to remember, Kanata.
The most important thing about
qualifying is to finish the lap.
Don't go damaging the car.
A lap around Odawara Pikes Peak is 40 km.
That makes it the longest MFG course.
I've been doing this for a while, and even
I don't have the whole thing memorized.
You scope it out at all
on the official website?
I've got the course
layout memorized, Senpai.
No way. How many hundreds
of times did that take?
I think... only three?
This is no time for jokes, Kanata.
Listen up. This thing
doesn't have a ton of power,
so you'll wanna go uphill at around 70%.
It's hell going downhill.
For Sector 3 in particular, you'll wanna
pull back to around 50-60% there.
I think you'll understand what
I'm saying once you've finished.
Okay, get to it.
Car 86, please proceed
to the inspection table.
Next up is a rookie
making his first appearance.
Car 86, driven by a
challenger from England.
Katagiri Kanata, 19 years old.
Kanata?
Are you kidding me? Is that really him?
What are you doing here, Kanata?
Six. Five. Four.
Is it me or did she just look
really surprised for a second?
Three. Two. One.
Kanata...
Next time, Turn 02:
The Shocking New MFG Generation.