Sales Department
Niijima Keisuke
As you can see, using our service gives you
access to multiple payment options
The Convenience of Payment Services
that you will find very convenient.
Thank you.
Hmm.
You make some very compelling points,
but is it really that important for us
to hurry and adopt this system now?
Uh, well, you have a point.
Hey, Niijima!
But the future of our product
is looking very bright!
Sure, but still...
Excuse me.
May I say something, Chief?
S-Sure.
I definitely sense potential from this.
Transactions overseas are
increasingly turning cashless,
so I do believe we should
start looking into this now.
What would you say to us
using it for a trial period?
HINA Group Holdings Ltd.
Store Management Division
Koga Takae
It may feel somewhat unfamiliar at first,
but I am certain you will adjust to it quickly.
If you ever encounter any problems,
we will happily come to your assistance.
Thank you very much.
Good work today.
I'm glad there was so much interest.
Yes. And I appreciate you taking time
out of your busy schedule, Koga-san.
Thank you very much.
Now that sounds like a hungry tummy!
E-Excuse me. I was so nervous this morning,
I didn't eat anything before work.
Do you want to get some food
before our next stop?
No, I'm sure I'll be fine.
Or, if you don't mind...
Follow me.
Wow!
Is this really okay?
If you don't mind my home cooking, sure.
I have a company dinner afterward,
so I won't get a chance to eat it anyway.
Then thank you very much. I will.
This is great! It's totally delicious!
It's so good!
I'm so happy! I'm in paradise!
H-Huh?
It's nothing. It's just that I've never seen
anyone eat a bento with such gusto.
To: Koga Takae
Sub: I hope you are well
Hello. This is Niijima from
Houbun Payment Service.
I wanted to thank you for
accompanying me to the
stores and even sharing
your lunch with me.
If you don't mind, I
would love to return
the favor over a meal
sometime. Would you...
"...over a meal sometime..."
No, no, no, no, no!
I should just say thank you.
If you don't mind, I
would love to return
the favor over a meal
sometime. Would you
be interested in joining
me? I look forward to
your response.
I sent it.
Whoa!
A response already?
It's a miracle!
Inbox
From: Koga Takae
Sub: Re: I hope you are well
Dear Niijima-sama,
Thank you for the message,
and thank you very much for
your assistance the other
day. I was relieved that you
enjoyed my bento so much
and kept it from going to
waste, so I really don't expect
anything in return, but I was
nonetheless delighted to
receive your invitation. I would
love to join you for a meal.
Look who's walking, look who's walking!
I think you're supposed to say that
once she's up on two feet.
Is that right?
But Mai is so good at crawling already,
I just can't help it.
You hear that? Good for you, Mai.
Good morning.
Good morning, Dad.
You sure are up early.
A delicious smell woke me up.
Same for me!
Well, that's what I was going for.
I overslept!
Don't forget your lunch!
Thanks. See you later!
Be careful, okay?
I know already!
Oh, dear.
Oh. I've got to go, too.
All right. Here's your bento.
Thanks as always.
No problem.
You don't need to do the cooking
every morning, you know.
I know you're busy at work.
It's fine.
You act responsible, but you tend to
space out sometimes, and that worries me.
Being able to hand you a bento made with love
gives me one less thing to worry about.
Does it? Then I guess
I can keep counting on you.
Of course you can.
And I'll keep on making your lunches for you.
Hello. This is Niijima.
It's been ten years now.
Hey.
Okue-san.
A little something from my trip.
Share them with your daughter.
Thank you very much.
You free after work? It's been a while.
Ah, no.
I'm sorry.
There's no reason to apologize.
Why is the sales division
chief inviting him out?
Niijima-san used to be in sales, too.
He was?
I'll catch you next time, then.
Ever since that day ten years ago,
it's like time has stopped for me.
I'm home.
Welcome back.
Ready for dinner?
Mm-hmm.
Mom!
Takae, hey...
Why?!
Yes?
I'm home.
Huh?
Um... Young lady, I think you
might be at the wrong house—
I'm not wrong! This is my house!
I'm Niijima Takae! I'm your wife!
I'm Mai's mother!
TsumaSho
Episode One
A Family Again
Um...
The platform at Kita-Asaka Station.
That's where you proposed to me.
Our wedding anniversary is December 10th.
Mai's first boyfriend was her
classmate Yoshida-kun.
The last family vacation we took
was to the Noto Peninsula.
You lost your phone and even
managed to get lost yourself,
and then Mai and I really chewed you out.
Do I need to keep going?
Uh, no. But how...
How am I supposed to know?
I guess it's what people call "reincarnation."
I died in the accident ten years ago, right?
And the new me is ten
years old, so it lines up.
I only started to remember my
previous life recently, though.
I happened to be walking past here,
and all of a sudden, pow! It all came back.
This is still unbelievable.
Huh? What else can I say?
No, it's unbelievable, but your
tone of voice, your personality...
You are absolutely my Takae!
Takae!
Well, now that I got you to believe me...
What's all this tasteless junk
you got for dinner?!
You'd better not tell me you've been eating
convenience store food ever since I died!
I thought we decided that no matter what
happened, we'd eat balanced meals for dinner!
Even if it's something simple! I told you
how important that is for a family, didn't I?
And you, Mai!
Are you working now?
Um, just some remote work from home...
Huh?! You can't waste your twenties
shut in the house all the time!
You gotta go out and hunt! Hunt!
"Hunt"?
When I was your age, I was dying to
fool around and hop from man to man
like there was no tomorrow!
Of course, I didn't because
I met your father, but...
Mai, you're lucky enough to be blessed
with your mother's good looks,
so please don't let your youth go to waste.
Okay.
All right, then. Back to
my current home for now.
But we're going to do something
about that diet of yours.
On Mondays, Wednesdays,
and Thursdays, I'll make bentos.
Thanks. I'd appreciate that.
And I know how this looks,
but I'm honestly very happy that
I get to see you two grow older.
I'll come back soon.
It really... is Mom.
Takae!
Now, stop that.
You could get reported for this.
I missed you so much, Takae!
You were everything to me!
Being with you was my
entire reason for living!
Well, that's not very encouraging.
You never know where life will take you.
Even if you try to run a three-legged race,
sometimes the strap connecting you breaks.
But that's marriage, isn't it?
If you were to just hit rock bottom on your own, that'd be one thing,
but what about Mai?
Can you please not let your own
negligence ruin Mai's life, too?
You're absolutely right. I apologize.
I'm just so truly grateful that you came back.
Well, actions speak louder than words.
I really had hoped you would
both move past my death.
So if you are truly grateful,
change your attitude and show me that you
know you have a future worth living for!
After all, I didn't choose to come back.
This is just some random miracle.
And I'm the daughter of
a different family now.
So try to do your best, Keisuke, Mai.
Dad...
Takae!
You are absolutely right!
I promise I'll show you!
I'll do my best, too, Mom!
Keep your voices down!
See you later, Mom!
Thank you, Takae!
Enough already! Bye!
Hoya-kun, have you finished
inspecting the new cards yet?
Ah, my apologies. I'm not done yet.
Oh, I'm not trying to rush you.
But my work is nearly done,
so I'll help you out.
Thank you very much!
Oh, but first I'm off to eat lunch.
See you afterward.
I'm still not used to Niijima-san
chatting with me like this,
but he sure is a fast worker.
It sounds like he used to be very productive.
And here I thought I'd never get
to eat another one of her lunches.
Here's your bento.
It sure was hard to make in such a short body.
Eat it and build up some energy.
It's good! It's too good!
What a lovely-looking bento.
Moriya-kun...
May I sit with you?
Be my guest.
Niijima-san, did something
good happen to you recently?
Oh, I'm sorry! I didn't mean to surprise you!
I'm all right.
You just seem to have changed.
Maybe I have. How do I explain this...
I had something precious
that I thought I'd lost forever,
but then something appeared
and filled that hole in my life.
And all of a sudden, I started to look
forward to living each day again.
That sounds wonderful.
Would you mind if I asked what happened?
I can't talk about it now.
Huh?
It's just such a fortuitous miracle that
I feel like if I tell anyone about it,
it'll go "poof" and disappear
as if it never happened.
All right, then. I won't ask.
Sorry, Moriya-kun.
It's fine. But I'm still glad.
I don't think I've ever seen you smile
before now, so it's a real relief.
That's very kind of you, Moriya-kun.
Oh, well, it's not as if I'm
watching everyone like that.
Huh?
Huh? Oh, listen to me, blabbing on.
I just never get the chance to eat with
anyone anymore, so I'm really enjoying this.
Let's eat.
Yeah.
Moriya-kun, do you make your own bentos?
Yes, but I don't know anyone else who does.
I think it's great that you're so responsible.
Thank you for the compliment,
but I really don't deserve it.
No, I honestly do think it's impressive.
Getting up early, even when tired,
and working with such small hands...
What's wrong?
Oh, nothing. I just have a lot of respect
for people willing to do all that cooking.
That's about the nicest thing you could say
to someone who makes their own lunches.
Oh, I don't know.
Niijima-san, would you mind
if we became bento buddies?
Huh? Bento buddies?
Talking to you has gotten me all fired
up to make more bento lunches!
I would love to eat together again.
If that's all right with you, I'd be happy to.
I'll be eating here every Monday,
Wednesday, and Thursday.
Thank you very much!
Hmm... I'm not used to not having
physical buttons on these things.
Are you sure you don't want
one with cell service?
It would be a huge problem if I got caught
with a phone registered in your name.
As long as I have Wi-Fi, I should be fine.
That's my Takae! You're so responsible!
Only because you're so bad at risk management.
Ugh. My hands are so small,
my fingers don't even reach.
Huh? What in the world did I just press?
Hey! Who said you could take my picture?!
Well, I thought I'd make it my new wallpaper.
Do you hear yourself?
What are you going to tell people
at the office if they see that?
That it's a picture of my wife, of course!
Are you stupid?
You'll get reported to the police!
Delete that, now!
I'm not deleting anything!
You need to think about the risks!
It'll be fine!
Oh, you're here, Mom?
Welcome back, Mai!
Keisuke told me the whole story.
So you're looking for a new job?
Yeah. I just started, though.
Hey, turn around and show
me what you've got there.
What? It's just a plain old suit.
Aww, you look lovely.
Next, put your hand on your hip.
This is embarrassing!
Okay! Today, let's go all-out
and make katsudon!
The pork cutlets will be
the ready-made type, though.
All right, I'll make a salad.
Takae! I thought you weren't coming today.
My schedule opened up.
And I really wanted to use up
the leftovers from last night.
That's what you're saying, but I know
you really just wanted to see me.
What are you talking about? Don't be a creep!
Great. You've got your lunch now,
so get a move on.
All right. Thanks!
I'm going to lunch.
Niijima-san?
Moriya-kun?
Um, I actually made two bentos today.
If you don't mind,
would you like to eat them together?
Huh? You went to the trouble
of making me one, too?
I live alone, and I ended up with
too much for just one person.
This is one of the days
you don't bring lunch, right?
Oh, I'm sorry. I don't mean to be pushy.
No, actually, thank you. Since you did
all that work, I think I'd love one.
He sure is late. Overtime, maybe?
If I'm not home soon, I'll get in trouble.
I should start heading toward the station.
Why, you...
I give! I give! I give!
Huh? Oh, Takae?
Why are you eating here of all places?
Weren't you able to eat at lunch?
Oh, well... I have a younger coworker
who made an extra bento for me today.
I thought it would be good chance
to socialize, so I ate that one instead.
Is that coworker a woman, by any chance?
Yeah.
How old?
Uh, late twenties, I'd guess.
And single?
I'm pretty sure she's unmarried.
Are you telling me that you...
Ugh. It doesn't matter.
If that happens, you don't need
to force yourself to eat mine.
What kind of adult eats bentos alone
in a park at this time of day, anyway?
Don't you have any shame?
Indeed, this is embarrassing.
But I'd rather do this than waste the bento
you put all that work into making for me.
The only thing I really hate is not being able
to say my wife made it for me with love!
My beloved wife made this! For me!
Would you quit calling me your wife in public?
People will think you're a pervert!
Why can't you figure that out?
Because you already
disappeared from my life once.
Ten years ago, I learned a very painful lesson.
That even when you think
you'll be with someone forever,
they can still disappear from
your life at any moment.
I don't want to have any more regrets.
I want to treasure the time we have together
and not spoil it with lies and deception!
Every minute. Each and every second!
Fine. All right.
That is just like you, I suppose.
You sure do love me, don't you?
What, you never even noticed?
No, I knew.
I've always known.