Wow! When you're the size of a child,
the scale sure is impressive!
What a unique experience.
It's also unique to be able to go
to the aquarium with your wife,
who's now an elementary schooler!
Unique... More like miraculous.
I'm so glad we can go out
and do things together again.
Me, too. We haven't gone anywhere
together in ten years. Let's enjoy it!
This really does feel like a dream.
I'm never this relaxed on my days off.
I wish there was some way we
could all be this happy forever.
Hey, why are you crying right now?
This is so embarrassing.
Wipe your tears.
O-Okay.
By the way, Mai, I hear you're having
some trouble with the job hunt.
Yeah.
I got a job right after I graduated
from vocational school,
but I quit before even three months had passed.
I couldn't fit in with the people there.
I think that was probably the reason.
Oh, don't sweat it.
It just means it wasn't the right job for you.
Just like freshwater fish
have freshwater tanks,
and saltwater fish have saltwater tanks,
everybody has a work environment
that fits them best.
It isn't just a question of ability.
Don't worry! Just start again fresh
and take your time looking, okay?
That's just like you, Mom.
That's right, Mai.
Your mother is the sun
at the center of our family.
If we ever run into trouble, let's just have
another day out to take our minds off things.
Yeah.
Having regained the memories
from my past life, I started going out
and spending time talking with Keisuke
and Mai like we used to.
Today sure was fun.
But no matter how much fun we have,
we always return to different homes.
It was, but you got a little too carried away!
TsumaSho
Episode Two
Right Now
Here.
Thanks as always.
It's fine.
Say, about the bentos...
Oh, sure! You need money, right?
Huh?
I realized I haven't been
paying you for supplies at all.
I'm sorry for eating up all
that food from your home!
From now on, use this.
That's too much.
If a grade schooler goes around carrying
that much cash, people are going to notice!
A thousand yen should take care of it.
Really? Well, if you run out, just let me know.
Your bentos always put a spring in my step!
Please keep on making them for me!
Sure.
Moriya-kun, I took my family to
the aquarium over the weekend.
I got you something as thanks for the bento.
Really? Thank you so much!
Sunfish Manju
Do you like sweets?
Yes, I love them!
By "family," do you mean you took
your daughter's family, as well?
Huh? Oh, no.
My daughter is still single.
She's looking for a new job right now.
We just went out for a change of scenery.
Oh, that makes sense.
It sounds like you all get along well.
Well, I suppose so.
She did get herself reincarnated
just to come see us again!
I wonder if Takae is eating lunch right now.
Oh, she must be eating a school lunch.
I wonder if she can get along with a bunch
of actual elementary school students.
She's almost forty, after all.
Okay, okay! Stop fighting!
Um, Marika-chan...
Oh, yeah? You're friends with Himari,
so you're gonna take her side now?
It's none of your business, Shiraishi-san!
It is, though. We're classmates, aren't we?
In a situation like this, it's best
if you have someone to arbitrate.
Like in a court of law, you know?
Huh?
I've heard both sides,
so let's lay out the issues.
What triggered it was a statement you
made about Miyuki's bedroom, correct?
Y-Yeah. Mayumi-chan asked me about
her room, and I said it was dirty.
See? She's saying mean things about me!
N-No, I'm not trying to be mean!
I just said what I thought.
Then why did you say it was dirty?!
It's all her fault.
Even the boys heard about it.
And they made fun of me!
Well, maybe you shouldn't
have run your mouth like that.
Himari, you need to apologize for that.
I-I'm sorry.
See? Himari regrets what she did.
I don't care! I'll never, ever forgive her!
That's enough from you.
If you get so upset over
little things all the time,
you're never going to make it as an adult!
Listen. In order to deal with other people
who live in your apartment building,
or the other mothers you
see at the park every day,
you've got to start developing the social
skills to be considerate of others now,
or you'll end up as a lonely
and isolated adult!
Con sitter... it?
What are you going to do if you destroy
your relationships with your neighbors?
You'll stop getting the neighborhood
bulletin brought to your house!
Wait! I don't get a word you just said!
Talking to you makes me feel
like I'm turning into an old lady!
Boys don't like naggy girls, anyway.
You're never gonna get a husband!
Uh-huh!
Really?
Takeru-kun!
It's totally okay with me.
Hey, Shiraishi!
Takeru?
You always walk home alone these days.
Let's walk together sometimes, okay?
You don't need to watch out for me.
Oh, don't say that.
We've been friends since kindergarten.
Hey, you've kinda changed, haven't you?
Huh?
You're a lot cheerier now. You could
never help settle fights and stuff before.
Um... I think I've always been this way.
Have you?
Well, I guess if you gotta live
with a mom like yours,
you need to learn to
speak up for yourself, huh?
I was just a little worried about you.
After your last name changed last year,
you seemed super unhappy.
I'm glad you've cheered up, though!
Yeah. Thanks for worrying about me.
My current parents
apparently divorced last year.
Shiraishi
But I don't remember much about that time.
It might be a countereffect of regaining
the memories of my past life.
At any rate, at home,
it's just my mother and me now.
There you are. You told me you
were going to stay home today.
My plans were canceled, so I came home.
And it's already evening.
So where were you?
I-I'm sorry.
Answer the question.
I went to the aquarium with some friends.
Huh? How did you pay for that?
Change from my dinner allowance.
I've been saving it up for a while.
Now, you listen here!
I gave you that money to use for food!
Who said you could spend it on something else?
And all this sneaking around makes me sick!
Today, you said you'd stay home but
lied and went out somewhere instead?
Don't you dare lie to your mother!
Huh?
Give me the rest.
You have some money left, right?
Even if it's just a few yen, hand it over! Now!
This is it?
Yes.
I don't trust you.
M-Mom?
You must have more hidden in your room.
Mom!
Oh, no! The smartphone!
I really don't have any more!
Mom!
Move it!
You're just like the others. All you do is lie!
Yes.
Oh. Yeah, but you could have called me.
Huh? Work? Why didn't you just tell me?
Yeah, of course I'm mad. I told you
how much I hate that sort of thing.
Well, now that I know why, I'll let it slide.
But you'd better make it up to me.
Sure. See you.
Next time you lie to me,
you'd better be prepared.
You won't get off this easy again.
Maybe I never should have gotten
involved with the Niijimas after all.
Mai, do you have any ideas for where
we should go during summer vacation?
I'd love to take a trip somewhere,
but I know that would be tough for Mom.
Yeah, I wonder. I bet it would be okay
if we got her parents' permission, though!
No, no, no! What parent would let their
child go on a vacation with strangers?
Hmm...
Well, maybe just a day trip, then.
Let's see what your mother's plans are.
Today
Do you have a day you can leave open
this summer for a short trip somewhere?
Next time you lie to me,
you'd better be prepared.
You won't get off this easy again.
Keisuke
Do you have a day you can leave open
this summer for a short trip somewhere?
No. I can't meet for a while.
Next weekend?
I'm definitely free!
Anywhere I want? How about Atami?
No way! Is that really okay?
You'd better not stand me up this time!
If you do, I'll knock your lights out!
Oh, I got a response from your mother!
She says she's free on July 28th!
Huh? But that day is...
Yes! Let's start planning our trip!
First an amusement park, then a movie,
then grape picking followed by peach picking,
then a hot spring, then a fireworks show,
and then squeeze in some karaoke!
There's no way we can do
all that in one day, Dad!
I just wanted to peek into their lives
and see how they were doing,
but when I saw how Keisuke had never gotten
over my death, I ended up getting involved.
Maybe I never should have done that.
Any way you look at it, the world
sees me as that woman's child.
Right now, she is my family.
But still,
If she found out about my
relationship with these two,
Mai
It says they have guinea pigs to pet!
That sounds nice
This summer, do you have a day you can
leave open for a short trip somewhere?
I'm free on July 28
Keisuke
Then how about the sunflower fields or something?
There's a petting zoo nearby, too.
it would be a disaster.
Huh? No, no, that's what I'm saying!
Are you being serious?
I expect it would cause her
a tremendous amount of grief.
I can't let that happen.
Next time I see them, I'll tell them
that we can't meet again.
Excuse me! Would you mind
taking a picture for us?
Oh, I'd be happy to.
All right. Here we go.
What a great picture.
Yeah!
Sure is. Would you send it to me later?
Yeah, of course!
An obstacle course that even adults can try?
Maybe I'll go give it a shot.
Oh, forget it. You're just going to get hurt.
I'll be fine! I've still got it in me.
Who's gonna get to the top first? Let's race!
And there he goes.
What a pain in the neck.
Sh-She's fast!
You rescued me.
Don't be so foolish! Get a hold of yourself!
Okay, then let's hit the reset button
and head to the petting zoo!
Hey!
It sure is hot.
Mom, is something wrong?
Hmm? What's that?
Are you tired?
I'm fine.
When do I tell them?
I'm still good to go!
I know that they'll...
Wha—
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey!
Well, what a special treat!
I'm carrying my wife on my shoulders!
You're supposed to do this with children!
Carry Mai instead!
No way! That would look even worse, Mom!
Here we go!
Hey, wait!
That was a blast!
I had fun, but it was so hot!
Should we order delivery for dinner?
That sounds great. I vote for sushi!
What do you think, Takae?
Is there anything you want to eat?
Sorry.
I'm actually not very hungry.
Oh, you aren't?
Then I don't need dinner, either.
We've got drinks in the fridge.
I'll go get them.
The Niijimas have been so welcoming...
I really let them spoil me.
It was so fun seeing them.
They made me so happy.
To tell the truth, I...
No, I need to tell them. Soon.
Um, I need to tell you two some—
Huh?
W-Wait. What happened? A power outage?
Mom, happy birthday!
Huh?
To the old you, that is.
That's right... now that you mention it.
I'm surprised you remember.
How could we forget?
We're family, aren't we?
Okay, please hurry up and
blow out the candle, Takae-chan.
Takae-chan
Hey, don't start treating me like a kid now!
Yay!
Happy birthday, Mom!
Congratulations, Takae.
Dad, turn the lights back on.
Sure.
Ah, wait!
I need to go to the bathroom before I eat.
I'll get the lights.
Ah... Okay.
I wonder if that cheered her up.
She was acting a little strange today.
I'm sure she's dealing with a lot
of things that we aren't aware of.
Of course she is. Her situation is
complicated enough to begin with.
You're right. I wonder if we
can do anything to help.
We'll try our best to have fun together.
Just like we used to.
She was always really strong. She never
shared her troubles with other people.
But at the same time,
she also has a lonely side.
So we've got to do what we can to support her.
You're right. We're family, after all!
This is good!
Oh, right. Didn't you have something
you wanted to say, Mom?
Thank you.
Thank you for playing with me today.
And celebrating with me.
We should be thanking you, Mom.
For coming back... Thank you so much!
I mean, there's no way we would have been
able to celebrate with you like this otherwise.
Mai...
Takae?!
Oh, boy. I was holding it in, but then
you had to go and start crying, Mai.
You don't need to hold it in.
Cry as much as you want.
It's nothing to be ashamed of.
I don't understand why I was
reincarnated or what it means.
But I do want to live with these two.
They're both like the sun to me.
I don't care if this isn't the proper choice.
I'm allowed to be a little selfish!
Takae!
Because right now,
I'm an elementary schooler!